<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>The Coin Republic</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/</link>
	<description>By the Coins, From the Coins, For the Coins</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/thecoinrepublic-logo_4dfefd11e401f10473b04f3db4d145f2-75x75.png</url>
	<title>The Coin Republic</title>
	<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor: The Visionary Behind the Bitcoin Movement</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/michael-saylor-the-visionary-behind-the-bitcoin-movement/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/michael-saylor-the-visionary-behind-the-bitcoin-movement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nancy J. Allen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Michael Saylor" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>Let&#8217;s delve into Michael Saylor&#8217;s journey, the man behind MicroStrategy and the biggest Bitcoin bull known for his BTC buying spree</strong></em></p>



<p>Michael Saylor the name resonates with innovation, determination, and a futuristic thinking approach toward the world of finance. As the Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy, an organization he founded in 1989, Saylor has been at the leading edge of the commercial enterprise intelligence enterprise. However, it&#8217;s far his advocacy for Bitcoin and his strategic investments that have made him a central attraction in the crypto space.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Early Beginnings Michael Saylor and Microstrategy</strong></h2>



<p>Saylor&#8217;s journey started with a dual diploma from &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Michael Saylor" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Michael-slayor-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>Let&#8217;s delve into Michael Saylor&#8217;s journey, the man behind MicroStrategy and the biggest Bitcoin bull known for his BTC buying spree</strong></em></p>



<p>Michael Saylor the name resonates with innovation, determination, and a futuristic thinking approach toward the world of finance. As the Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy, an organization he founded in 1989, Saylor has been at the leading edge of the commercial enterprise intelligence enterprise. However, it&#8217;s far his advocacy for Bitcoin and his strategic investments that have made him a central attraction in the crypto space.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Early Beginnings Michael Saylor and Microstrategy</strong></h2>



<p>Saylor&#8217;s journey started with a dual diploma from MIT in Aerospace Engineering and History of Science, a mixture that mirrors his deep expertise of generation and its context within human progress.</p>



<p>His entrepreneurial spirit led him to establish <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/12/microstrategy-buys-12000-bitcoins-bitcoin-will-eat-gold-saylor/">MicroStrategy</a>, which quickly became a frontrunner in offering enterprise intelligence solutions. The organization&#8217;s fulfillment is a testament to Saylor&#8217;s management imagination and prescience, as it keeps innovating and making its attain within the virtual age.<br><br>Saylor&#8217;s interest in Bitcoin flashed a vast change in MicroStrategy&#8217;s investing approach. In 2020, he began directing the employer&#8217;s reserves into Bitcoin, spotting the cryptocurrency&#8217;s capability as a store of cost and hedge in opposition to inflation. </p>



<p>This move became no longer without a chance, but Saylor&#8217;s conviction in digital foreign money proved to outstanding move. MicroStrategy&#8217;s Bitcoin holdings have grown extensively, making it one of the biggest corporate holders of the cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Did Michael Saylor Grow in Wealth?</strong></h2>



<p>Saylor&#8217;s reputation is anchored in his founding of MicroStrategy, a leading business intelligence enterprise, and Alarm.com. His innovative contributions have earned him over 48 patents, and he is also the author of &#8220;The Mobile Wave.&#8221; He has made a bold prediction about Bitcoin&#8217;s possibility to surpass gold in the future.</p>



<p>Saylor&#8217;s wealth is intricately linked to MicroStrategy&#8217;s fortunes. When the company went public in 1998, he held a significant number of shares valued at over $14 million. Although his net worth soared during the dotcom boom, it suffered a decline post-bubble burst.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, his strategic investment in Bitcoin, with personal holdings exceeding 121,044 BTC, has significantly boosted his financial standing.</p>



<p>In addition to his strategic investments, Saylor&#8217;s role as CEO and later as Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy has been rewarded with a substantial salary and bonuses, reflecting his unwavering commitment and leadership within the company.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Saylor&#8217;s Influence and Thought Leadership</strong></h2>



<p>Beyond his organization&#8217;s investments, Saylor has emerged as an outspoken proposal for the Bitcoin Standard. He believes that BTC represents the virtual transformation of capital and has the capacity to serve as a foundational element for a new economic model. His instructional platform, Saylor Academy, offers unfastened sources to those looking to apprehend Bitcoin and its implications for the destiny of money.</p>



<p>Saylor&#8217;s effect extends past his business choices. He is a prolific speaker and idea leader, sharing his insights on diverse media platforms. His interviews and discussions regularly highlight the bullish elements riding <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2023/01/15/bitcoin-adoption-will-increase-thanks-to-podcasting-2-0/">Bitcoin adoption</a> and the transformative nature of the cryptocurrency enterprise. Saylor&#8217;s perspectives are knowledgeable by using his deep expertise in generation and economics, making him a respected voice within the debate over digital currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>MicroStrategy Bitcoin Holdings</strong></h2>



<p>In a personal capacity, Saylor invested in 17,732 Bitcoins in October 2020, spending $175 million at an average price of $9,882 per Bitcoin.&nbsp; As of March 11, 2024, MicroStrategy has amassed a substantial Bitcoin portfolio of 205,000 units. The company&#8217;s average expenditure per Bitcoin stands at $33,706.00, culminating in a total investment of USD 6.91 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Michael Saylor&#8217;s net worth in 2024</strong></h2>



<p>As of the latest available data, Saylor&#8217;s net worth is evaluated to be around $5.1 billion. This estimation comes after a significant increase due to a three-day pop in crypto and MicroStrategy&#8217;s stock. It&#8217;s important to note that net worth estimations can fluctuate based on various factors, including stock prices and market conditions. For the most current figures, it&#8217;s always best to refer to the latest reports from reliable financial news sources.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Future of Money and Technology&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Looking in advance, Saylor sees a vivid future for Bitcoin and blockchain technology. He envisions an international wherein virtual belongings play a vital position in worldwide finance, supplying balance, scalability, and protection. His perspectives on the integration of AI and ETFs into the Bitcoin ecosystem recommend a decade-long &#8220;gold rush&#8221; for the cryptocurrency, powered with the aid of institutional hobby and technological improvements.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h3>



<p>Michael Saylor&#8217;s journey from a tech entrepreneur to a leading Bitcoin endorse is a tale of adaptability, foresight, and unwavering belief in the transformative power of generation. His contributions to the cryptocurrency area have not only shaped MicroStrategy&#8217;s trajectory but have additionally stimulated the wider communication approximately the future of money. As the sector continues to grapple with monetary uncertainty, Saylor&#8217;s imagination and prescience for a Bitcoin-centric financial machine gives a hopeful and compelling narrative for what lies beforehand.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>FAQs</strong></h4>



<p><br><strong>Who is Michael Saylor?</strong></p>



<p>Michael Saylor, recognized for his role as the Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy, has an estimated net worth of $1.5 billion according to Forbes. Despite a temporary setback due to the cryptocurrency downturn in 2023, Saylor&#8217;s wealth rebounded with the rise in Bitcoin&#8217;s value, which also bolstered his company&#8217;s stock value.</p>



<p><strong>What is Michael Saylor&#8217;s Net Worth?</strong></p>



<p>As per the data, Google Michael Saylor&#8217;s Net Worth is 510 crores USD.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/michael-saylor-the-visionary-behind-the-bitcoin-movement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NVIDIA’s GTC: Render Founder, J. Urbach To Speak in The Event</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/nvidias-gtc-render-founder-j-urbach-to-speak-in-the-event/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/nvidias-gtc-render-founder-j-urbach-to-speak-in-the-event/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Adarsh ​​Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NVIDIA's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RNDR token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="NVIDIA" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>In the coming 3 days, Urbach&#8217;s presentation at Nvidia’s GTC conference is expected to outline the future roadmap of Render Network.</strong></em></p>



<p>Jules Urbach, the founder of Render Network, is scheduled to speak at the upcoming Nvidia GTC 2024 conference in four days. This appearance may increase the prospects of the RNDR token&#8217;s price.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Nvidia’s GTC Event&#160;</strong></h2>



<p>Nvidia&#8217;s GTC scheduled for March 18th, is the most important event of the year for those interested in AI and GPU computing. Generative AI technologies made significant progress last year, and decentralized AI networks have emerged as a result.</p>



<p>Since the last &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="NVIDIA" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Render-Founder-To-Speak-At-NVIDIAs-GTC-In-4-Days-RNDR-Surge-Ahead-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>In the coming 3 days, Urbach&#8217;s presentation at Nvidia’s GTC conference is expected to outline the future roadmap of Render Network.</strong></em></p>



<p>Jules Urbach, the founder of Render Network, is scheduled to speak at the upcoming Nvidia GTC 2024 conference in four days. This appearance may increase the prospects of the RNDR token&#8217;s price.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Nvidia’s GTC Event&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Nvidia&#8217;s GTC scheduled for March 18th, is the most important event of the year for those interested in AI and GPU computing. Generative AI technologies made significant progress last year, and decentralized AI networks have emerged as a result.</p>



<p>Since the last GTC, Nvidia has introduced many groundbreaking AI advancements. One of them includes the HGX H200 GPU line, and new open-access Large Language Models (LLMs). In addition to this, Tensor Core AI acceleration in the popular RTX line of GPUs.</p>



<p>This year&#8217;s conference will focus on the Blackwell HPC chip architecture. This is expected to succeed the Hopper H200 GPU accelerators and explore the intersection of immersive media and spatial computing. In addition to this, the conference will emphasize the integration of the Open 3D standard OpenUSD with generative AI.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Render’s Jules Urbach Return</strong></h2>



<p>Jules Urbach is making his first live presentation since the COVID-19 pandemic, as he returns to the GTC stage. He has been a regular fixture at the prestigious event since 2010, and is the only crypto founder to have been invited to speak. Urbach&#8217;s knowledge of GPU technologies has been instrumental, and his insights have been foundational.</p>



<p>This presentation will offer an updated vision for the future of generative AI, spatial media, and decentralized GPU computing technologies. In addition to this, the discussion will focus on the convergence of decentralized computing, and generative AI.</p>



<p>In addition to this, it will also focus on holographic technology, as demonstrated in The Archive—an immersive spatial experience produced on the Render Network for Apple Vision Pro.</p>



<p>The crypto community can expect Urbach to share Render Network&#8217;s milestones, including technological advancements and significant projects completed using the platform. Moreover, these accomplishments demonstrate the network&#8217;s capacity for professional-grade rendering tasks.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Additionally, Urbach&#8217;s presentation may outline the future roadmap of <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2023/09/09/recent-updates-by-render-network-pushing-rndr-price-skyhigh/">Render Network</a>, including upcoming features, technological enhancements, and expansion plans that promise to revolutionize the rendering landscape.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Render Team Shares Their Views</strong></h3>



<p>The team of Render Network has announced that they plan to surpass the iconic 2013 keynote presentation by Nvidia Founder and CEO Jensen Huang in their upcoming presentation this year. In the aforementioned keynote, Jules had revealed the initial cloud GPU rendering pipeline.</p>



<p>Urbach also stated how he thinks it will be one of his most relevant GTC talks. He added that it is a reflection of the next paradigm shift they are entering for distributed GPU systems. In addition, to this Urbach also remembers the first such event back in 2013 when he took the stage with Jensen to announce Render’s centralized precursor (ORC) and then launched with AWS.</p>



<p>Potential partnerships with Nvidia and other industry giants could be an explosive topic of discussion, given Nvidia&#8217;s leadership in GPU technology and AI. Such collaborations could further enhance Render Network&#8217;s capabilities and, importantly, boost the RNDR price massively.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Effect On RNDR</strong></h3>



<p>Ahead of the event, crypto experts anticipate increased attention on AI crypto tokens, particularly RNDR. This is likely to be accompanied by a &#8220;buy the rumor of an extended partnership&#8221; sentiment that will drive up prices.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Nvidia&#8217;s GTC on March 18th is a crucial event for AI and GPU computing enthusiasts. Nvidia has introduced many groundbreaking advancements since the last GTC. Render Network team is excited about this year&#8217;s presentation, which promises to build on an iconic 2013 keynote presentation with Nvidia Founder and CEO Jensen Huang.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any people named in this article are for informational purposes only. They do not establish financial, investment, or other advice. Investing in or trading in stocks, cryptos, or other related indexes comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/nvidias-gtc-render-founder-j-urbach-to-speak-in-the-event/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Saitama Inu Price Surge Soon Or Keep Hovering In Range?</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/can-saitama-inu-price-surge-soon-or-keep-hovering-in-range/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/can-saitama-inu-price-surge-soon-or-keep-hovering-in-range/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brandi Veil]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saitama]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saitama Inu Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Saitama Inu Price" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>Saitama Inu (SAITAMA) price has begun to rally from this pivotal support level, suggesting a possible shift in market sentiment.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>SAITAMA price is demonstrating bullishness with strong momentum as it stays above the 20 and 50-Day EMAs.</a>
    </li>
</ul>



<p>Saitama Inu is built on BSC (Binance Smart Chain). This is crypto&#8217;s as one of the interactive digital currencies, that are steered by the community and are designed to build a fun and fascinating experience for its crypto investors and other meme enthusiasts alike.</p>



<p>The Saitama Inu token has recently shown signs of a potential reversal in its price trajectory. After &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Saitama Inu Price" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/saitama-inu-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>Saitama Inu (SAITAMA) price has begun to rally from this pivotal support level, suggesting a possible shift in market sentiment.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>SAITAMA price is demonstrating bullishness with strong momentum as it stays above the 20 and 50-Day EMAs.</a>
    </li>
</ul>



<p>Saitama Inu is built on BSC (Binance Smart Chain). This is crypto&#8217;s as one of the interactive digital currencies, that are steered by the community and are designed to build a fun and fascinating experience for its crypto investors and other meme enthusiasts alike.</p>



<p>The Saitama Inu token has recently shown signs of a potential reversal in its price trajectory. After a significant decline, where the price formed a pattern of lower lows and highs, it found support at the $0.00004900 level without breaking through the key demand zone.</p>



<p>Despite a historically bearish trend, <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/01/16/saitama-crypto-aka-saitachain-crypto-in-depth-info-and-analysis/">Saitama crypto</a> price has begun to rally from this pivotal support level, suggesting a possible shift in market sentiment.</p>



<p>Saitama Inu price is demonstrating bullishness and upward momentum as it keeps above major trend 20 and 50-Day EMAs, subject to the buyers&#8217; surge the price could thrust upward strongly from the dynamic supports of these major EMAs as well.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Saitama Inu Price Analysis Over Daily Chart</strong></h2>



<p>SAITAMA’s technical indicators are exhibiting bullishness. The asset is showing that bulls are gaining control gradually and can continue to rise in the forthcoming sessions. Likewise, the Saitama Inu crypto asset is displaying strong buying characteristics, as sellers are getting weaker over time over the daily chart and bulls can make the price jump higher and extend its gains.</p>



<p>The recent Saitama Inu price chart of the past week has shown good performance which indicates a possible healthy sign of the beginning of a consistent upward trend.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Over the past week, Saitama Inu has shown promising performance, hinting at the start of a sustained upward movement. With a recent 2.40% rise in the last 24 hours, the token is currently trading at $0.00007800.</p>



<p>Therefore, if the demand surges abruptly, the Saitama Inu asset price could bounce back from the current level. Then the next goal for the price could be to reach $0.00010650.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="980" height="513" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Saitama-Inu-Price.webp" alt="Saitama Inu Price" class="wp-image-197122" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Saitama-Inu-Price.webp 980w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Saitama-Inu-Price-300x157.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Saitama-Inu-Price-768x402.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Saitama-Inu-Price-750x393.webp 750w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Source: SAITAMA/USD: POLONIEX 1D. TradingView</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Conversely, if the token cannot maintain its footing above the $0.00004900 support level, there&#8217;s a risk of further decline.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Saitama Inu price highlights the bullish sentiments and perspectives regarding the crypto asset in the daily time frame. The SAITAMA price action highlights a bullish view at the time of publishing, as it recently attempted to surge from a pivotal level.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Moreover, the technical parameters of SAITAMA’s price suggest the continuation of the uptrend over the daily time frame chart.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Technical Levels</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Support Level</strong>: $0.00004900</p>



<p><strong>Resistance Level</strong>: $0.00010650</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>In this article, the views, and opinions stated by the author, or any people named are for informational purposes only, and they don’t establish the investment, financial, or any other advice. Trading or investing in cryptocurrency assets comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/can-saitama-inu-price-surge-soon-or-keep-hovering-in-range/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could Electroneum Price (ETN) Reach Higher Price Levels?</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/could-electroneum-price-etn-reach-higher-price-levels/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/could-electroneum-price-etn-reach-higher-price-levels/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amanda Shinoy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electroneum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electroneum price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETN]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Electroneum Price" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>The volatility has not advanced that much, illustrating stability in the price.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>The activity of whales in the ETN crypto along with the price movement is on the rise.</a>
    </li>
</ul>



<p>Electroneum (ETN) has introduced a novel algorithm known as Proof-of-Responsibility (PoR) to enhance the security, accountability, and environmental friendliness of its blockchain.</p>



<p>If an attack is detected in its platform, the system is designed to promptly isolate without delay and deactivate the offending validator. Furthermore, the PoR model establishes a controlled network where validators are selected for their commitment to the project&#8217;s long-term goals.</p>



<p>Currently, the network is maintained &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Electroneum Price" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Electroneum-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>The volatility has not advanced that much, illustrating stability in the price.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>The activity of whales in the ETN crypto along with the price movement is on the rise.</a>
    </li>
</ul>



<p>Electroneum (ETN) has introduced a novel algorithm known as Proof-of-Responsibility (PoR) to enhance the security, accountability, and environmental friendliness of its blockchain.</p>



<p>If an attack is detected in its platform, the system is designed to promptly isolate without delay and deactivate the offending validator. Furthermore, the PoR model establishes a controlled network where validators are selected for their commitment to the project&#8217;s long-term goals.</p>



<p>Currently, the network is maintained by 12 non-profit organizations, which contribute to charitable causes using the rewards earned from validating transactions. This system not only secures the network but also aligns it with philanthropic activities, reflecting Electroneum&#8217;s dedication to social responsibility.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Price vs Volatily chart Of Electroneum Crypto</strong></h2>



<p>This chart exhibits the contrast between the volatility with the price movement in the Electroneum crypto. On examination, it shows that the ETN crypto has witnessed wonderful growth in recent sessions. However, the volatility has not advanced that much, illustrating stability in the price. </p>



<p>Moreover, the ETN crypto seems comfortable at higher price levels, suggesting that the sellers are sitting in the rear, and the bulls may assist the Electroneum crypto price to rise further.</p>



<iframe loading="lazy" title="Santiment Chart: Price (ETN), Price Volatility 1w (ETN)" width="1170" height="425" src="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=electroneum&#038;pt=ETN&#038;df=2023-12-25T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&#038;dt=2024-03-15T18%3A29%3A59.189Z&#038;emcg=1&#038;emhwm=1&#038;wm=price_usd%3Bprice_volatility_1w&#038;wax=0%3B1&#038;wc=%232e934a%3B%23FF5B5B&#038;ws=%7B%22node%22%3A%22area%22%2C%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D%3B" scrolling="no"></iframe>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Price vs Volume Analysis Of Electroneum Price</strong></h2>



<p>Per the Santiment chart, in January and February 2024 entirely, both the asset volume and price were relatively low, indicating a lack of interest and activity. The volume mostly remained under $1 Million, and the price hovered around $0.002800 in that period.</p>



<p>However, in the last week of February, volume and price continued to rise abruptly, indicating increased demand and excitement about ETN crypto price. The trading volume exceeded $1 Million and the price rose drastically from $0.002800 to $0.006650.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The price vs volume chart describes an increase in volume along with the <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/01/07/electroneum-price/">Electroneum price</a> rise in a couple of previous daily sessions, but the volume plunged some points and caused the price to get chills, suggesting the continuation of the ongoing trend after a possible pullback. </p>



<iframe loading="lazy" title="Santiment Chart: Price (ETN), Volume (ETN)" width="1170" height="425" src="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=electroneum&#038;pt=ETN&#038;df=2023-12-25T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&#038;dt=2024-03-15T18%3A29%3A59.189Z&#038;emcg=1&#038;emhwm=1&#038;wm=price_usd%3Bvolume_usd&#038;wax=0%3B1&#038;wc=%2326C953%3B%23D2D6E7&#038;ws=%3B" scrolling="no"></iframe>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Market Cap, Social Volume, And Whales Activity On Electroneum chart</strong></h2>



<p>The higher market capitalization often provides better liquidity as it assists in better investing and buying or selling ETN assets more quickly and easily.</p>



<p>Likewise, a high market cap with high trading volume might indicate vast liquidity, making it much easier to buy or sell Electroneum without affecting the price</p>



<p>In the same way, The social volume seems to be rising in the recent sessions, this indicates a continuation of the ongoing short-term trend in Electroneum. The rise in the social volume also indicates the rising awareness of ETN crypto among users.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Followed by, the activity of whales in the ETN crypto over a period of time along with the price movement in the same duration, over the Santiment chart. The analysis displays that the whales have been continuously increasing their portfolio in Electroneum. </p>



<iframe loading="lazy" title="Santiment Chart: Percent of Stablecoin Total Supply held by Whales with more than 5 million USD, Marketcap (ETN), Social Volume (ETN)" width="1170" height="425" src="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=electroneum&#038;pt=ETN&#038;df=2023-12-25T00%3A00%3A00.000Z&#038;dt=2024-03-15T18%3A29%3A59.189Z&#038;emcg=1&#038;emhwm=1&#038;wm=percent_of_whale_stablecoin_total_supply%3Bmarketcap_usd%3Bsocial_volume_total&#038;wax=0%3B1%3B2&#038;wc=%23FF5B5B%3B%23FFCB47%3B%2368DBF4&#038;ws=%3B%3B%7B%22interval%22%3A%221d%22%7D" scrolling="no"></iframe>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Price Structure Of Electroneum Price Highlights</strong></h2>



<p>It highlights that the price was in a decent uptrend, but got a pause at a higher level and attempted to make a possible pullback before resuming the major bullish trend.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Therefore, if the demand increases, the ETN asset price could bounce back from the current level. The next goal for the price is to reach $0.00800 and the primary resistance would be $0.00700.</p>



<p>However, if the crypto price fails to stay above the $0.00500 level, it could decline further.</p>



<!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN -->

<script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script>

<script type="text/javascript">

var tradingview_embed_options = {};

tradingview_embed_options.width = '980';

tradingview_embed_options.height = '425';

tradingview_embed_options.chart = 'GziqmONw';

new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);

</script>

<p><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/chart/ETNUSDT/GziqmONw-ENT-BULLISH/"></a> <a href="https://in.tradingview.com/u/Sam_TCR/"></a> <a href="https://in.tradingview.com/"></a></p>

<!-- TradingView Chart END -->



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>The Electroneum price has demonstrated significant growth with stable volatility, suggesting a strong bullish sentiment.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Recent trading sessions have seen a rise in volume accompanying the price increase, although a slight drop in volume suggests a temporary consolidation before the trend continues upward.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Whale activity analysis indicates ongoing investment in ETN, with a potential pullback at higher price levels before resuming the upward trend.</p>



<p>Therefore, if market demand persists, ETN&#8217;s price could recover, aiming for a target of $0.00800 with resistance at $0.00700. Conversely, a failure to maintain support above $0.00500 could lead to further declines.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Technical Levels</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Support Levels</strong>: $0.00500</p>



<p><strong>Resistance Levels</strong>: $0.00700</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>In this article, the views, and opinions stated by the author, or any people named are for informational purposes only, and they don’t establish the investment, financial, or any other advice. Trading or investing in cryptocurrency assets comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/could-electroneum-price-etn-reach-higher-price-levels/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Renq Finance Price: Is RENQ Price About To Get Wings Soon?</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/renq-finance-price-is-renq-price-about-to-get-wings-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/renq-finance-price-is-renq-price-about-to-get-wings-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RenQ Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Renq Finance Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="renq finance price" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>The recent Renq Finance chart shows good performance last week.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>The Renq Finance asset is indicating bullishness and upward momentum as it keeps above major trend 20 and 50-Day EMAs.</a>
    </li>
 
</ul>



<p>RenQ Finance (RENQ) is a community-led establishment that was formed to provide a one-stop resolution for all classes of traders under one platform in the DeFi world.</p>



<p>RenQ provides advantages over conventional financial products by wiping the need for a systematized central clearing house, furnishing global and equal access, and permitting users permanent command over their funds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Renq Finance Price (RENQ Crypto) Technical Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>The price action earlier &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="renq finance price" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/renq-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>The recent Renq Finance chart shows good performance last week.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>The Renq Finance asset is indicating bullishness and upward momentum as it keeps above major trend 20 and 50-Day EMAs.</a>
    </li>
 
</ul>



<p>RenQ Finance (RENQ) is a community-led establishment that was formed to provide a one-stop resolution for all classes of traders under one platform in the DeFi world.</p>



<p>RenQ provides advantages over conventional financial products by wiping the need for a systematized central clearing house, furnishing global and equal access, and permitting users permanent command over their funds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Renq Finance Price (RENQ Crypto) Technical Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>The price action earlier depicted a terrific downfall in <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/02/07/renq-finance-price-forecast-will-renq-break-above-key-emas/">RENQ Finance price</a> by creating lower lows and highs on the daily chart. It dipped like a falling knife shattering all nearby support but failed to pierce through the major demand zone area and formed a support at $0.005000.</p>



<p>On the overall chart, it has shown bad performance in the past month, and three months by 7.18%, and 14.29% respectively, highlighting a consistent downward trend.</p>



<p>However, the Renq Finance price has indicated a sign of a major turnaround as the price rose from a critical key level of around $0.005000 on the chart.</p>



<p>Its price action appears like the RENQ crypto is ripe for an upcoming splendid surge, as it harnesses energy to pierce the above resistance level and climb strongly to new altitudes from the current demand zone. In the same way, the Renq Finance price is demonstrating bullishness and upward momentum as it stays above the 20 and 50-Day EMAs, subject to the buyers&#8217; surge, the price could thrust upward strongly from the dynamic supports of these major EMAs as well.</p>



<p>Similarly, the RENQ asset&#8217;s technical indicator is exhibiting bullish performance as MACD shows a bullish cross with a growing graph of the histogram. The Renq Finance asset is showing that bulls are gaining control gradually. Likewise, the Renq Finance crypto asset is displaying strong buying characteristics, as sellers are getting weaker over time over the daily chart and bulls can make the price jump higher and extend its gains.</p>



<p>Last week the crypto climbed 23.70%, which is an indicator of the beginning of a consistent upward trend. RENQ declined 1.55% in the last 24 hours and was trading at $0.0067 at press time.</p>



<p>Therefore, if the demand surges abruptly, the Renq Finance asset price could bounce back from the current level. Then the next goal for the price could be to reach $0.01000 and in between resistance could be $0.008950.</p>



<p>Another possibility would be that if the RENQ crypto price fails to stay above the $0.005000 level, it could decline further.</p>



<!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN -->

<script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script>

<script type="text/javascript">

var tradingview_embed_options = {};

tradingview_embed_options.width = '980';

tradingview_embed_options.height = '425';

tradingview_embed_options.chart = '3AFUqH1H';

new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);

</script>

<p><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/chart/RENQUSDT/3AFUqH1H-the-Renq-Finance-crypto-asset-is-displaying-strong-buying/"></a> <a href="https://in.tradingview.com/u/Sam_TCR/"></a> <a href="https://in.tradingview.com/"></a></p>

<!-- TradingView Chart END -->



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>The Renq Finance crypto has indicated a sign of a major turnaround as the price rose from a critical key level. Moreover, the Renq Finance asset is highlighting bullishness with strong momentum as it stays above the 20 and 50-Day EMAs.</p>



<p>RENQ is displaying strong buying characteristics as sellers are getting weaker over time over the daily chart and bulls could take the price higher, extending gains.</p>



<p>Therefore, if the demand surges abruptly, the RENQ price could bounce back from the current level. Then, the next goal for the price could be to reach $0.01000 with resistance from $0.008950.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Technical Levels</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Support Levels</strong>: $0.005000</p>



<p><strong>Resistance Levels</strong>: $0.008950</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>In this article, the views, and opinions stated by the author, or any people named are for informational purposes only, and they don’t establish the investment, financial, or any other advice. Trading or investing in cryptocurrency assets comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/renq-finance-price-is-renq-price-about-to-get-wings-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Comprehensive Guide To Koinly; Overview, Features &#038; Use Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/a-comprehensive-guide-to-koinly-overview-features-use-cases/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/a-comprehensive-guide-to-koinly-overview-features-use-cases/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Anderrson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koinly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koinly Features]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Koinly" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>Koinly, is one of the most popular and user-friendly softwares allowing users to track transactions across hundreds of exchanges and digital wallets.</strong></em></p>



<p>Acceptance of cryptocurrency in different forms in different regions raised the need for a cryptocurrency tax calculator. Koinly, a crypto tax software thus introduced to the crypto universe to make crypto transactions and related activities effortless.&#160;</p>



<p>Let’s uncover the facts and features linked to the respective crypto tax software.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Koinly?</strong></h2>



<p>Koinly was founded by Crispian Robinson, Maria Bilo, and Robin Singh in 2018 and is legally known as Koinly Pte Ltd. It is a platform that &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Koinly" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-Comprehensive-Guide-To-Koinly-Overview-Features-Use-Cases-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>Koinly, is one of the most popular and user-friendly softwares allowing users to track transactions across hundreds of exchanges and digital wallets.</strong></em></p>



<p>Acceptance of cryptocurrency in different forms in different regions raised the need for a cryptocurrency tax calculator. Koinly, a crypto tax software thus introduced to the crypto universe to make crypto transactions and related activities effortless.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Let’s uncover the facts and features linked to the respective crypto tax software.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Koinly?</strong></h2>



<p>Koinly was founded by Crispian Robinson, Maria Bilo, and Robin Singh in 2018 and is legally known as Koinly Pte Ltd. It is a platform that generates tax reports for crypto trading and similar activities automatically.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/K0STbXmbXWUzaWKfbAMZYkAzruj0at7f2-9hPCBx8EdEb0vAAuKssZsCjgbk4iCe7UD6FW8Fv7vJQ5QngCSg-JXamyRWEyY_y6pAhodNvesKIwEdbJALZqKwbOfjioX1OdAPeVTMg8B6J1EhdjuDrD8" alt="Koinly"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><strong>Source:</strong> Koinly</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>In blending with all the key blockchains and exchanges including Binance, Coinbase, Bittrex, etc., the platform mitigated crypto tax reporting to a few minutes of work. It is emerging as one of the most popular cryptocurrency tax software solutions and is mainly developed to help crypto users calculate and report related taxes.</p>



<p>Easy import of trades, preview of capital gains, and download of tax documents enhanced the value of the platform among investors. It is one of the best software that solves all crypto tax-related issues effortlessly.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Koinly Features&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>The cryptocurrency tax calculator and portfolio tracker hold a wide variety of features that make it an unbreakable part of the crypto universe.</p>



<ul>
<li>Individuals can track real-time crypto transactions as well as gains or losses.</li>



<li>The platform supports around 400 crypto exchanges, 20,000 crypto assets, 170+ blockchains, and wallets.</li>



<li>It supports a wide range of accounting methods including FIFO, LIFO, Highest Cost, Average Cost Basis, and more.</li>



<li>Integration with key tax software such as TurboTax and TaxAct is a significant feature.</li>



<li>User-friendly interface and tax reports for over 100 nations including the UK, US, Canada, and Australia.</li>



<li>Portfolio tracking, integration, data import, transaction monitoring, and crypto tax reports are major benefits of the software.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How the software resolved the crypto taxes problem</strong></h3>



<p>Since the day cryptocurrency was launched, <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/10/an-ultimate-guide-on-doge-killer-leash-cryptocurrency/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Cryptocurrency </a>transactions become taxable in most of the developed and developing nations. Moreover, there are no appropriate rules and regulations to govern all the transactions as a digital asset is classified differently in different nations. </p>



<p>In some regions, crypto is classified as a property, whereas in some regions it is considered as maliciousness or intangible property. To resolve this issue and update with the latest crypto tax rules, Koinly was introduced.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It helps in simplifying the crypto tax accountabilities through automated determination of tax implications and each transaction. It also helps in avoiding human errors and saves time in generating ready-to-sign tax reports.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How does the platform work?</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Registration: </strong>The very first step is registration in which the user can sign up for the platform using a Google account and additional details including country, desired plan, and base currency. The platform uses universal accountancy methods including First In First Out (FIFO), Last In First Out (LIFO), Highest Cost First Out (HIFO), and Average Cost Basis (ACB).</p>



<p><strong>Data Importation: </strong>Once registered over the platform, the next step is to link the crypto wallet, crypto exchange, and blockchains manually or automatically by entering API keys which are encrypted for security.</p>



<p><strong>Review and verification:</strong> after accomplishing the data importation the next step is review and verification. The step helps in ensuring that all the data has been imported accurately. Confirm the accuracy of the imported data. The platform doubles as a portfolio tracker, reviewing transactions, and establishing cost bases, market values, and profit calculations.</p>



<p><strong>Tax report generation: </strong>Once data is verified, detailed tax documents are ready for export. These reports are compatible with tax software like TurboTax and can be sent to accountants. The platform&#8217;s premium services include the creation of IRS-compliant documents such as Form 8949 and Schedule D.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pros and cons of the crypto tax software</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Advantages: </strong>Localized tax reports in around 20 countries and generic tax reports acceptability in approximately 100 countries is one of the main benefits of the respective platform. Another main benefit is the availability of the tool for free of cost and an easy user interface.</p>



<p>It supports around 20,000 crypto assets, 100+ wallets, 170+ blockchains, and 400+ exchanges which enhances its accessibility for investors. The platform detects duplicate transactions that should be excluded from tax reporting.</p>



<p><strong>Disadvantages: </strong>The platform is not 100% automated and a few of the transactions require manual input. A few of the users face errors when importing transaction history. Additionally, for RSI-compliant tax forms, the user needs to purchase the paid version which can be expensive for high-volume traders.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Some Alternatives of Koinly</strong></h3>



<p>Although Koinly is one of the best platforms when it comes to crypto tax reports there are a few challenges. Here are a few of the alternatives users can explore:</p>



<p><strong>CoinLedger:</strong> It is another crypto tax software that aims to simplify the procedure of tracking transactions and tax reporting for digital assets. It supports over 400+ exchanges, and 10K+ transaction limits. IRS Form 8949 and International tax reports are supported by CoinLedger.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>CoinTracking: </strong>Another tool widely used for crypto tax reporting is CoinTracking which is the first and leading digital asset portfolio tracker and crypto tax calculator. It offers unlimited transaction limits, supports 70+ crypto exchanges, and works with IRS Form 8949 and International tax reports.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h3>



<p>Koinly, the crypto tax software makes it easy for investors to keep track of the activities and crypto transactions. The software is compatible with a wide variety of cryptocurrencies, exchanges, and blockchains which enhances its acceptability and accessibility. IRS Form 8949, Schedule D, and International tax reports are the main tax reports supported by the respective software.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>FAQs</strong></h3>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is the software free to use?&nbsp;</strong></h4>



<p>The software offers a free version as well as a paid version. The free version holds limited features whereas the paid version offers a wide range of offerings.&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why use crypto tax software?</strong></h4>



<p>Operating with crypto taxes is complex due to the nature of actions that can have different tax implications and reporting needs. Crypto tax software thus helps in ensuring the accuracy and compliance related to the crypto transactions and actions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/a-comprehensive-guide-to-koinly-overview-features-use-cases/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto ETFs: CoinBase Slams Senators Creating Hurdles for SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/crypto-etfs-coinbase-slams-senators-creating-hurdles-for-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/crypto-etfs-coinbase-slams-senators-creating-hurdles-for-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steefan George]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CoinBase slams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="CoinBase" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>Coinbase did not hold back about a letter that contained information which was pushing the SEC to hold any more crypto ETFs.</strong></em></p>



<p>According to Paul Grewal, the chief legal officer of Coinbase the direct evidence shows that Ether&#8217;s futures and spot markets are as correlated as Bitcoin. This letter suggests that the recent letter by the US senators urging the SEC to regulate Bitcoin ETFs. In addition, rejecting any further crypto ETF applications is misguided.</p>



<p>In response to a letter from two US senators urging the SEC to regulate Bitcoin ETFs even more and reject any further crypto ETF applications, &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="CoinBase" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Coinbase-fires-back-at-senators-asking-SEC-to-halt-crypto-ETF-approvals-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>Coinbase did not hold back about a letter that contained information which was pushing the SEC to hold any more crypto ETFs.</strong></em></p>



<p>According to Paul Grewal, the chief legal officer of Coinbase the direct evidence shows that Ether&#8217;s futures and spot markets are as correlated as Bitcoin. This letter suggests that the recent letter by the US senators urging the SEC to regulate Bitcoin ETFs. In addition, rejecting any further crypto ETF applications is misguided.</p>



<p>In response to a letter from two US senators urging the SEC to regulate Bitcoin ETFs even more and reject any further crypto ETF applications, Coinbase chief legal officer Paul Grewal criticized the senator&#8217;s claims.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Was in This Letter?</strong></h2>



<p>The letter, dated March 11, claimed that approving further crypto ETFs beyond Bitcoin would expose investors to &#8220;enormous risks&#8221;. Grewal said that the senators&#8217; letter contained several falsehoods, and he argued that the evidence pointed in the opposite direction.</p>



<p>He explained that the market for many cryptocurrencies smaller than Bitcoin, notably Ether, demonstrated quality metrics that exceeded even the largest traded equities.</p>



<p>Grewal added that the spot market for Ether is deep and liquid, with only two S&amp;P 500 stocks having higher notional dollar trading volume. Additionally, there was direct evidence that Ether&#8217;s futures and spot markets were just as correlated as Bitcoin&#8217;s.</p>



<p>The letter from the senators, Jack Reed and Laphonza Butler, claimed that approving any further <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/11/04/crypto-winter-provoked-these-australian-crypto-etfs-delisting/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto ETFs</a> by the Securities and Exchange Commission would see investors exposed to thinly traded markets rife with fraud and manipulation. </p>



<p>However, there are currently eight proposed spot Ether ETF applications awaiting approval by the SEC, and there have been hopes that other altcoins could eventually walk the same path.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Senators Urged the SEC to Hold the Approval&nbsp;</strong></h3>



<p>The SEC has been urged by the senators to avoid setting a precedent for further approvals of spot Bitcoin ETFs, citing concerns about the market&#8217;s recent weakness.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Moreover, they argued that while Bitcoin&#8217;s market has undergone serious scrutiny, it is more reliable and established than the market for smaller cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>The SEC is under pressure to scrutinize Bitcoin ETF brokers and advisors. The success of spot Bitcoin ETFs is increasing political pressure on Gensler, making an Ether ETF approval in May less likely. Moreover, Both Butler and Reed have sponsored legislation to crackdown on cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In addition to this, Coinbase and Grayscale met with SEC officials on March 9 to discuss a rule change for the launch of spot Ether ETFs. The SEC may reject pending ETH ETFs based on &#8220;correlation.&#8221; Some believe the SEC&#8217;s pushback on Ether ETFs is political, not intended to &#8220;protect investors.&#8221;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Coinbase has criticized a letter from Senators that claimed approving further crypto ETFs beyond Bitcoin would expose investors to ‘enormous risks’. Crypto industry pundit, Balchunas, said that the letter was evidence of mounting political pressure on Gensler, which makes an Ether ETF approval in May seem less likely.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any people named in this article are for informational purposes only. They do not establish financial, investment, or other advice. Investing in or trading in stocks, cryptos, or other related indexes comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/crypto-etfs-coinbase-slams-senators-creating-hurdles-for-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts Claim Outflow in Spot ETFs Dragged Bitcoin Below $70k!</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/analysts-claim-outflow-in-spot-etfs-dragged-bitcoin-below-70k/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/analysts-claim-outflow-in-spot-etfs-dragged-bitcoin-below-70k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ritika Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197093</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong><em>Over the past few years, cryptocurrencies&#8217; popularity has suddenly surged globally. Bitcoin is the only crypto dominating over 50% of the market. A major difference is seen post spot ETFs approval.</em></strong></em></p>



<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the market pioneer, has most recently traded at its all-time high. However, the spike game was over in a few hours. When writing, it was trading at $67,983, with an intraday decline of 7.41%.&#160;</p>



<p>BTC&#8217;s highest trading price is $73,750, achieved on March 14, 2024. The price at press time was 8.33% lesser.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/04/30/ripples-xrp-is-categorized-as-just-a-impostor-cryptocurrency-by-coinmarketcap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinMarketCap</a>, there are 42.09 Million addresses that hold $0- $1k Bitcoins. &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-running-down-the-slope-with-a-crown-on-its-head-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong><em>Over the past few years, cryptocurrencies&#8217; popularity has suddenly surged globally. Bitcoin is the only crypto dominating over 50% of the market. A major difference is seen post spot ETFs approval.</em></strong></em></p>



<p>Bitcoin (BTC), the market pioneer, has most recently traded at its all-time high. However, the spike game was over in a few hours. When writing, it was trading at $67,983, with an intraday decline of 7.41%.&nbsp;</p>



<p>BTC&#8217;s highest trading price is $73,750, achieved on March 14, 2024. The price at press time was 8.33% lesser.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/04/30/ripples-xrp-is-categorized-as-just-a-impostor-cryptocurrency-by-coinmarketcap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinMarketCap</a>, there are 42.09 Million addresses that hold $0- $1k Bitcoins. However, the number of wallets that hold $100k BTC is 683.61k.</p>



<p>Compared to other years in 2024, a significant boost has been observed in the total number of Bitcoin holders. As of March 12, 2024, there were 452.61k whales holdings, 1.70 Million Investors, and 17.51 Million retail.&nbsp;</p>



<p>There has been a neck-to-neck competition between Binance and Coinbase for Bitcoin trading volume for the past few years. Binance is the highest Bitcoin trading volume contributor in spots, and Bitunix leads the perpetual trading of BTC.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In the past few years, a primary pump in the market capitalization of Bitcoin has been seen; when writing, it was $1.33 Trillion. Between March 13 and 14, the market cap of the most prominent crypto firm reached $1.44 Trillion.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Reason Behind Downfall!</strong></h2>



<p>Despite an inflow of funds in the Bitcoin ecosystem from spot ETF, a significant outflow of funds has been observed in the past few days.&nbsp;</p>



<p>BitMEX Research observed that the Grayscale spot ETF has suffered a severe outflow for the past few months. However, a record outflow of funds was seen on March 11, 2024, when Bitcoin peaked.</p>



<p>In the early days of approval, the spot ETF gathered significant attention, and billions of dollars were injected into the BTC ecosystem. Moreover, thousands of news addresses have started holding Bitcoin since January 2024.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Quarterly Bitcoin Hashrate Report</strong></h2>



<p>The Bitcoin hash rate has surged significantly in the past three months and reached 780.17 EH/s on March 07, 2024. The record was one of the highest hashrate in one quarter.&nbsp;</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/0zB09hnH1YV10L6Lj5WEj65Sx8mKyItdmEGPSOoC9ZBSvjmF2c_JIMywYKNFszQOWwIPW0ExXLI0gBWuLYKxdek4WdzusoPrkX-PWnRNNlqZi5CG3CqLDj7opvjUo_WUeRqTVPVdJ3tkfBea9MLLnzA" alt=" Bitcoin "/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Source: Blockchain</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>As per the whitepaper, Bitcoin&#8217;s hashrate is the calculated value that specifies an estimate of how much hashrate is being generated by Bitcoin miners trying to solve the pending Bitcoin block or any other block.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In simple words, Bitcoin hashrate calculates the difficulty of solving an individual block. On February 26, a significant spike in the hash rate was seen when it suddenly reached above 700 EH/s from 631.2389 EH/s a day earlier.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The hashrate is measured in units Hash (H/s), KiloHash (kH/s), MegaHash(MH/s), GigaHash (GH/s), TeraHash (TH/s), PetaHash (PH/s), ExaHash (EH/s), ZettaHash (ZH/s) and YottaHash (YH/s) is the highest measurement unit.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The bitcoin hashrate was 544.97 EH/s as of writing.&nbsp;</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h5>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any other person named in this article are for informational purposes only and do not constitute financial, investment, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/analysts-claim-outflow-in-spot-etfs-dragged-bitcoin-below-70k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berachain Secures $69 M in Funding; EigenLayer Raises Highest YTD</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/berachain-secures-69-m-in-funding-eigenlayer-raises-highest-ytd/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/berachain-secures-69-m-in-funding-eigenlayer-raises-highest-ytd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anurag S]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Berachain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EigenLayer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197092</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Berachain" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong><em>Berachain has emerged as a leading DeFi company in the past few quarters. Blockchain technology&#8217;s rapid evolution and advancement have lured global investors into supporting blockchain-backed companies. </em></strong></em></p>



<p>Berachain, a DeFi-focused, EVM-compatible Layer 1 built on the Cosmos SDK and proof of liquidity consensus, raised $69 Million in funding. The funding round was co–led by Brevan Howard Digital and Framework Ventures.</p>



<p>A Bloomberg report states that the project is raising money by offering digital tokens, which will be valued at $1.5 Billion. In the past few years, a significant shift of interest has been seen in funding crypto.</p>



<p>The report further &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Berachain" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Cryptos-Berachain-Becomes-Unicorn-in-69-Million-Funding-Round-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong><em>Berachain has emerged as a leading DeFi company in the past few quarters. Blockchain technology&#8217;s rapid evolution and advancement have lured global investors into supporting blockchain-backed companies. </em></strong></em></p>



<p>Berachain, a DeFi-focused, EVM-compatible Layer 1 built on the Cosmos SDK and proof of liquidity consensus, raised $69 Million in funding. The funding round was co–led by Brevan Howard Digital and Framework Ventures.</p>



<p>A Bloomberg report states that the project is raising money by offering digital tokens, which will be valued at $1.5 Billion. In the past few years, a significant shift of interest has been seen in funding crypto.</p>



<p>The report further states that Berachain is the only company that secured unicorn states during the ongoing bull run. Other than co-led in funding, OKX ventures, Robot Ventures, Shima Capital, Hack VC, Tribe Capital, and Polychain, among others.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Other Major Funding Since January 2024</strong></h2>



<p>Since January 1, 2024, EigenLayer and Hashkey Group have only raised $100 Million. Optimism has secured $89 Million in funding, and Zama gathered $73 Million in a Series-A round.</p>



<p>Over this period, most projects that have received funding are based on the Ethereum blockchain. Portal, a DeFi project, has raised $34 Million in its seed funding round, followed by Ether(dot)Fi $27 Million.</p>



<p>The first quarter of 2024 is on the brink of being completed, and to date, over 351 founding rounds have occurred, and several companies collectively secured $2,005,891,315.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Investors Ranking Per Funding Rounds</strong></h3>



<p>OKX Ventures has invested in more than 32 companies in the past 180 days, and HashKey Capital has injected funds in 26 rounds. Big Brain Holdings and Foresight Ventures have participated in 22 funding rounds.&nbsp;</p>



<p>HashKey Capital has topped the list in making investments in the past 365 days as it is invested in 51 firms. Coinbase Ventures did not lock any major funding deals in YTD, but it has invested in 366 companies since its foundation.&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Market Price Update&nbsp;</strong></h4>



<p>The fear and greed index of <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2023/03/13/stepn-gmt-and-digitoads-toads-predicted-to-reach-coinmarketcap-top-20-by-2025/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinMarketCap</a> shows extreme greed, with 87 points, which might lead to bearishness in the market. The market capitalization of cryptocurrencies slips 6.47% over the past 24 hours. </p>



<p>Bitcoin, the market leader, marked a new all-time high at $73,750; the price failed to sustain higher for a longer time. As of writing, BTC was trading at $67,804, with an intraday decline of 6.83%.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to several market analysts, the significant increase in the trading price in the past few days is due to the massive outflow from the Bitcoin ecosystem.</p>



<p>Similarly, the second most talked about cryptocurrency in the market has declined approximately 6.30% over the past 24 hours. Bitcoin SV tops the intraday loser list as its price slips 20.49%, Bonk (BONK) lost 16.26%, Injective (INJ) 16.26%, Mantle (MNT) 15.13% and Shiba Inu (SHIB) 13.36%.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Conflux (CFX) grew 8.02% in the past 24 hours, which makes it the leader of the past 24 hours gainers list, followed by Fetch.ai (FET) at 5.20%, Sei (SEI) at 3.27%, 0x Protocol (ZRX) at 3.17% and UNUS SED LEO (LEO) 1.59% including others.&nbsp;</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h5>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any other person named in this article are for informational purposes only and do not constitute financial, investment, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/berachain-secures-69-m-in-funding-eigenlayer-raises-highest-ytd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is This the Next Big Cryptocurrency Player? Traders Flock to Up and Coming Project</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-up-and-coming-project/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-up-and-coming-project/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Chess]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave cryptocurrency.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=197083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p>Investing in new cryptocurrencies is the most widespread strategy for entering crypto markets. Beginners constantly look for low-cap platforms to invest in, hoping to acquire large amounts of tokens at a low price. This strategy has significant benefits and is less risky, but it&#8217;s not entirely proven in any way, as many emerging cryptos often fail before the gains even begin.&#160;</p>



<p>However, if a new platform gets enough backing from investors in the earliest stages and offers excellent utility, it can result in high short and long-term gains. That brings us to Green Bitcoin, an engaging new platform with a &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto-and-‘TradFi-a-friendship-of-convenience-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p>Investing in new cryptocurrencies is the most widespread strategy for entering crypto markets. Beginners constantly look for low-cap platforms to invest in, hoping to acquire large amounts of tokens at a low price. This strategy has significant benefits and is less risky, but it&#8217;s not entirely proven in any way, as many emerging cryptos often fail before the gains even begin.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, if a new platform gets enough backing from investors in the earliest stages and offers excellent utility, it can result in high short and long-term gains. That brings us to Green Bitcoin, an engaging new platform with a hugely successful presale event.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://coinrepublic.care/b_btcmtx_43675?referrer=is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-exciting-up-and-coming-project" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>>>>Buy The Best Coin Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Green Bitcoin &#8211; Predict-to-Earn Staking Platform Showing Massive Potential</strong></h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="461" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-1024x461.png" alt="" class="wp-image-197087" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-1024x461.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-300x135.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-768x346.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-1536x692.png 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-750x338.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307-1140x514.png 1140w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-307.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure></div>


<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/04/09/green-bitcoin-mining-operations-are-not-too-far/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Green Bitcoin </a>is an upcoming cryptocurrency that has excited thousands of investors. It entered presale recently and is already showing clear signs of explosive growth. It&#8217;s primarily a staking platform with a unique Predict-to-Earn reward system that allows users to earn native $GBTC tokens by predicting future Bitcoin prices.</p>



<p>Its release will coincide with the next Bitcoin halving event, giving users another option to get higher returns during the upcoming bull run. Green Bitcoin is a gamified green staking platform with high sustainability, and it will be the next big crypto to explode in the upcoming period. It&#8217;s built on the Ethereum blockchain, so it&#8217;s compatible with all ETH-based crypto wallets.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Earn $GBTC Tokens Using Your Gut Feeling</strong></h3>



<p>The unique Predict-to-Earn reward system allows users to earn $GBTC tokens using their gut feeling regarding future Bitcoin prices. It&#8217;s an excellent choice for beginners and experienced traders, as it offers a simple platform for earning tokens with or without trading experience.</p>



<p>Once you buy $GBTC tokens during the ongoing presale, you can stake them to earn up to 118% returns before the first listing. After the platform goes live, you can earn even more tokens using various price prediction strategies and approaches. However, before you can place any predictions, you must stake a number of your $GBTC. Then, you have to wait until the staking period is over, and if your predictions are correct, you earn higher $GBTC returns.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://bs_795168e1.coinrepublic.care?referrer=is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-exciting-up-and-coming-project" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>>>>Buy Green Bitcoin Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Green Bitcoin Token Presale</strong></h3>



<p>The platform entered presale a few weeks ago and has already raised over $4.3 million, showing clear signs of growing demand and a positive market sentiment. The platform has a total of 21 million tokens, but only 50% is available during the event.&nbsp;</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-1024x576.png" alt="" class="wp-image-197086" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-300x169.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-768x432.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-1536x864.png 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-750x422.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306-1140x641.png 1140w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-306.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure></div>


<p>It&#8217;s just a few weeks of going live, and considering that the presale hard cap is set to $7 million, you only have a few more days to get into the action early. Moreover, if you buy $GBTC tokens during the presale, you can stake them for up to 118% rewards before the first listings. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Details to Look For When Investing In New Cryptocurrencies</strong></h2>



<p>Understanding how to recognize new<a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/02/28/5-top-cryptocurrencies-under-1-cent-to-grab-for-549-profits/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> cryptocurrencies </a>that have the potential to result in higher returns is essential for your success as a digital asset trader. Crypto markets are generally highly volatile and unpredictable, so you should take everything with a grain of salt. That said, there are a few details or signs you should look for when trying to identify cryptos that are the most likely to explode after release.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>1. Demand and Supply</strong></h3>



<p>The first rule of cryptocurrencies is demand and supply. The price of all cryptocurrencies is determined by two primary factors: availability and popularity. Bitcoin is an excellent example. When its demand spiked in 2017, Bitcoin went from $1 to $20,000 in less than 12 months. The same applies to any other cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Limited supply combined with increased demand is what drives prices higher over time. If the two factors work together, the asset&#8217;s price can explode, resulting in exponential growth and high returns. Things work the other way around, so token prices will likely decrease significantly if the supply and demand are too high.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://coinrepublic.care/b_btcmtx_43675?referrer=is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-exciting-up-and-coming-project" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>>>>Buy The Best Coin Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>2. Technological Factors</strong></h3>



<p>Many cryptos gain value after providing more details on project development, including future roadmaps, updates, and partnerships with other projects. A significant increase in funding, an appearance on Tier 1 exchange listings, etc., can trigger explosive growth. Such information often sparks investor confidence, resulting in high gains in a short period.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>3. Market Sentiment</strong></h3>



<p>Sometimes, the buzz surrounding a cryptocurrency can also result in high gains. For example, when Elon Musk Tweeted about Dogecoin in 2019, the token exploded almost immediately, resulting in a massive bull run. However, sometimes influencers use their social presence to manipulate market sentiment, resulting in artificial price increases that usually don&#8217;t last very long.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>4. Regulatory Changes</strong></h3>



<p>Cryptocurrency markets are still largely unregulated, so new regulations and policies imposed by governments can also affect <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2023/01/25/link-whales-tired-of-lifting-token-prices-new-disclosures-might-help/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">token prices</a>. Rising interest rates and deteriorating macroeconomic parameters almost always negatively affect crypto prices. However, as the FED reduces interest rates, more investors are willing to invest in digital assets, resulting in steady price increases across the entire crypto market.&nbsp;</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://coinrepublic.care/b_btcmtx_43675?referrer=is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-exciting-up-and-coming-project" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt;Buy The Best Coin Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Wrapping Up</strong></h4>



<p>Green Bitcoin is getting more support by the day and is quickly rising above many other platforms going live in the next few months. It&#8217;s one of the most anticipated cryptos in 2024, and the next platform will likely explode in the next few months. The demand for $GBTC tokens is growing exponentially, and it will go live right around the next crypto bull run following the upcoming Bitcoin halving event.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Visit the official Green Bitcoin site and stake your $GBTC tokens for 118% rewards. Jump on the Green Bitcoin train early to get the highest returns in the next few months.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Disclaimer: Any information written in this press release or sponsored post does not constitute investment advice. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not, and will not endorse any information on any company or individual on this page. Readers are encouraged to do their research and take any actions based on their findings and not from any content written in this press release or sponsored post. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not and will not be responsible for any damage or loss caused directly or indirectly by the use of any content, product, or service mentioned in this press release or sponsored post.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/15/is-this-the-next-big-cryptocurrency-player-traders-flock-to-up-and-coming-project/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
