<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>BeInCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://beincrypto.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://beincrypto.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:45:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/cropped-bic_favic-32x32.png</url>
	<title>BeInCrypto</title>
	<link>https://beincrypto.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ondo (ONDO) Price Soars 100% in a Week: More Upside Expected?</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/ondo-price-soars-correction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiago Amaral]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In just 7 days, ONDO's price leapt from $0.40 to $0.90, while its holder count doubled in a month. A high MVRV Z Score of 3.63 signals possible overvaluation, but bullish EMAs indicate there's room for even higher price records.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ondo-price-soars-correction/">Ondo (ONDO) Price Soars 100% in a Week: More Upside Expected?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>In the past week, the ONDO price witnessed a significant jump from $0.40 to $0.90, a movement that doubled its holder base in merely a month. </strong></p>



<p>This dramatic increase has pushed its Market Value to Realized Value (MVRV) Z Score of 3.63, suggesting a cautionary signal regarding the coin&#8217;s potential overvaluation. Despite these concerns, the Exponential Moving Average (EMA) lines for Ondo Finance (ONDO) project a highly bullish outlook. The technical analysis indicates there&#8217;s room for the cryptocurrency to establish new all-time highs. However, some corrections may take place before that. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ondo-finance-number-of-holders-soars">Ondo Finance Number Of Holders Soars</h2>



<p>During the initial months of 2024, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ondo-finance-tokenized-securities-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ONDO</a> experienced a steady increase in its investor base, with an average daily addition of 100 to 300 new holders. This steady progression was evident as the holder count reached 4,872 on February 26. Yet, the growth trajectory took a dramatic turn over the last week of March, witnessing a sharp rise. By March 25, ONDO holders had surged past the 10,000 mark, marking a significant milestone.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" width="850" height="288" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png" alt="ONDO Total Amount Of Holders." class="wp-image-489556" style="aspect-ratio:2.951388888888889;width:1024px;height:auto" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-360x122.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-768x260.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-1536x520.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-2048x693.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.23-25-Mar-2024-150x51.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">ONDO Total Amount Of Holders. Source: <a href="https://app.santiment.net/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>.</figcaption></figure>



<p>This remarkable increase in holders represents more than a doubling of the investor community within just one month. This upsurge aligns closely with ONDO price appreciation, which saw a notable escalation from $0.40 on March 19 to an impressive $0.95 by March 25 &#8211; translating to a 137.5% increase in just six days. </p>



<p>Should this <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/best-penny-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">growth momentum be sustained</a>, it could very well cement the faith of new investors in ONDO&#8217;s potential, potentially ushering in even higher price peaks shortly. Such rapid expansion reflects investor confidence and could also act as a catalyst for further elevating the ONDO price.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/top-defi-protocols/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Top 11 DeFi Protocols To Keep an Eye on in 2024</a></strong></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ondo-mvrv-ratio-z-score-also-increases">ONDO MVRV Ratio (Z Score) Also Increases</h2>



<p>The ONDO MVRV Ratio (Z Score) has caught attention, rising sharply from 1.39 to 3.57. This rise occurred between March 19 and March 25. The MVRV Z Score gauges an asset&#8217;s fair value, comparing the market to realized value. It reflects the current price against the average investor&#8217;s paid price. The Z Score shows deviations from the asset&#8217;s typical MVRV. It helps pinpoint times when an asset is unusually high or low valued.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="850" height="288" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png" alt="ONDO MVRV Z Score." class="wp-image-489555" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-360x122.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-768x260.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-1536x520.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-2048x693.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ondo-ONDO-07.34.37-25-Mar-2024-150x51.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">ONDO MVRV Z Score. Source: <a href="https://app.santiment.net/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>.</figcaption></figure>



<p>When the MVRV Z Score escalates sharply, as observed with ONDO, it signals that the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/crypto-leverage-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">price is potentially overextended</a> compared to its realized value, suggesting that the asset might be overvalued. Such a condition often precedes a market correction, where the price adjusts downward as the market seeks to reconcile the asset&#8217;s speculative market price with its underlying economic value. </p>



<p>In ONDO&#8217;s case, the rapid ascent to a 3.57 Z Score could be interpreted as a strong correction signal. Historically, high MVRV Z Scores have been associated with market tops and subsequent price declines as investors begin to take profits, leading to increased supply and pressure on the price to normalize. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ondo-price-prediction-what-s-next">ONDO Price Prediction: What&#8217;s Next?</h2>



<p>ONDO&#8217;s 4-hour price chart currently shows a bullish trend, despite the recent price surge. Short-term EMA lines recently crossed above long-term lines. <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/moving-averages-explained/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exponential Moving Averages (EMAs)</a> are indicators used in technical analysis that give more weight to recent price data, making them more responsive to new market information compared to Simple Moving Averages (SMAs). </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="850" height="386" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-850x386.png" alt="ONDO 4-Hour Price Chart." class="wp-image-489554" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-850x386.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-360x163.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-768x349.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-1536x697.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-2048x930.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ONDOUSD_2024-03-25_07-34-45-150x68.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">ONDO 4-Hour Price Chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/V4vUSDS5/?symbol=COINBASE%3ADOGEUSD" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a>. </figcaption></figure>



<p>Typically, traders interpret short-term EMA lines crossing above long-term EMA lines as a &#8216;golden cross,&#8217; a bullish signal indicating an upward price trend. This crossover suggests that recent price action is bullish compared to past trends, potentially attracting more buyers into the market.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/liquidity-pools-explained/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DeFi Liquidity Pools: How They Work and What You Need To Know</a></strong></p>



<p>Although EMA lines are currently extremely bullish for ONDO, its MVRV Z Score and this recent price surge could set the stage for a strong correction soon. ONDO could correct to $0.84 before trying new surges. However, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/best-crypto-apps-for-beginners/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">if the uptrend continues</a>, it could reach new all-time highs, surpassing its previous $0.95 record and potentially reaching $1. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ondo-price-soars-correction/">Ondo (ONDO) Price Soars 100% in a Week: More Upside Expected?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/bic_Altcoin_Season-covers_bull.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/bic_Altcoin_Season-covers_bull.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover B2Trader, a Brand-New Brokerage Platform from B2Broker</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/discover-b2trader-a-brand-new-brokerage-platform-from-b2broker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry is expanding remarkably, with Bitcoin hitting all-time highs and cryptocurrencies&#8217; total market capitalisation exceeding $2.37T. Moreover, the MiCA law will go into effect on June 30, 2024, and be followed by another wave on December 30, 2024, with the aim of encouraging a wider usage of cryptocurrencies via increased confidence and transparency. &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/discover-b2trader-a-brand-new-brokerage-platform-from-b2broker/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/discover-b2trader-a-brand-new-brokerage-platform-from-b2broker/">Discover B2Trader, a Brand-New Brokerage Platform from B2Broker</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The cryptocurrency industry is expanding remarkably, with Bitcoin hitting all-time highs and cryptocurrencies&#8217; total market capitalisation exceeding $2.37T. Moreover, the MiCA law will go into effect on June 30, 2024, and be followed by another wave on December 30, 2024, with the aim of encouraging a wider usage of cryptocurrencies via increased confidence and transparency.</strong></p>



<p>With over 20,000 coins and tokens and approximately 300 million users, cryptocurrency is beginning to appear as a better trading option than the FX market, which has 128 currency pairs and 50 million users. With the aid of blockchain protocols and L2 solutions, it is able to bring about cutting-edge business models in payments, fintech, finance, and other industries, which is driving its growth.</p>



<p>In order to meet the growing demand for cryptocurrency trading, brokerages are always searching for new avenues to enter the market. In response, B2Broker has announced the launch of the <a href="https://b2broker.com/bbp/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">B2Trader Brokerage Platform (BBP)</a>, a crypto spot broker service designed to help businesses take advantage of this growing industry and start making money faster!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-which-sectors-will-be-enhanced-by-b2trader-nbsp"><strong>Which Sectors Will be Enhanced by B2Trader?&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>B2Trader is a powerful tool for tracking market movements and breaking into the fastest-growing industry for brokers dealing in cryptocurrency (CFDs and derivatives), over-the-counter (OTC) products, FOREX, multi-asset and multi-market products, market makers, liquidity providers, payment systems, and even banks. Here’s how each business can use this system:&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-forex-brokers"><strong>FOREX Brokers</strong></h3>



<p>Any FX broker can massively benefit from B2Trader integration. In addition to the standard CFD trading platforms (MT4, MT5, cTrader), you can use B2Trader to offer spot trading exclusively for cryptocurrencies, attract a new clientele interested in ownership rather than CFDs or margin trading, and generate revenue through markups, commissions, and effective risk management.</p>



<p>Moreover, BBP gives authorised FX brokers the choice to split up their trading of digital assets over several licences, promoting strategic diversification and maintaining a competitive advantage in the current market.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-brokerages"><strong>Crypto Brokerages</strong></h3>



<p>Crypto brokers who specialise in cryptocurrency CFDs and employ cryptocurrency as collateral and provide both FX and crypto CFDs&nbsp; can use B2Trader to improve their present cryptocurrency spot trading solutions.</p>



<p>Given the competitive environment around acquiring and retaining customers, the absence of crypto spot trading options might lead to customers seeking services from other providers. Brokerages integrating B2Trader will have a strategic advantage as it will allow them to offer much-needed crypto spot trading and react swiftly to market changes.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-market-makers"><strong>Market Makers</strong></h3>



<p>With B2Trader, market makers may leverage several exchanges, efficiently aggregate liquidity, achieve favourable spreads, maximise pricing, and enable smart routing across multiple venues.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-liquidity-providers"><strong>Liquidity Providers</strong></h3>



<p>If LPs include spot crypto options in their asset offerings, they can attract more brokers, hedge funds, and experienced traders. B2Trader makes this task easier and gives them the resources they need to grow their revenue and market share.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-emis-payment-systems-and-banks"><strong>EMIs, Payment Systems, and Banks</strong></h3>



<p>Through its ability to provide diversified asset management, monitoring, and liquidity pool development, B2Trader offers banks, PSPs, and EMIs a competitive edge. These companies can utilise this solution to facilitate fast swaps and provide crypto services to their existing portfolio of offerings.&nbsp;</p>



<p>BBP provides these companies with several opportunities to embrace crypto and its alluring trends as the starting point in this growing field. B2Trader&#8217;s comprehensive API and complete set of required components and modules allow it to integrate seamlessly into any business model.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-unmatched-speed-and-efficiency"><strong>Unmatched Speed and Efficiency</strong></h2>



<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="602" height="337" src="https://lh7-eu.googleusercontent.com/M_YIBVMMU-AvhIqTuQbyC2xTYNU-oLm9UkHjBEmrmLguwf7WtmKIn6KBv6W9Amkse42__QcCK8PgVCQ-AtnJ0ZOMErkYgX7nKlCvddYQ52DTqcAbwzfNKKSQPVBtoPTuby7Hv8w7V81OTcYyH1hrArE"></p>



<p>B2Trader is designed for enterprise-sized brokers to service today&#8217;s financial markets. Even in its most basic setup, it can process up to 3000 trading instruments and handle up to 3000 inquiries per second. It offers real-time market data updates every 100 ms and extremely quick order execution starting at 1 ms. Increasing the power of computers and the cloud will improve these statistics even further.</p>



<p><em>&#8220;Today, B2Broker is a leading name in the FinTech industry. We began operating in the FOREX industry in 2014 and have been developing solutions for the crypto industry since 2017. B2Broker has earned multiple awards and recognitions, and our years of experience have allowed us to understand what the market needs exactly.</em></p>



<p><em>That&#8217;s why we created B2Trader. It&#8217;s our answer to the changing trends in finance. We have poured 18 months of hard work and $5 million into B2Trader. BBP is built by our dedicated in-house team of 40 engineers, each contributing to a solution that truly meets the demands of today&#8217;s brokers. In the next 12 months, we are planning to double the team and enhance our offerings even further!&#8221;</em></p>



<p><em>— Arthur Azizov, CEO and Founder of B2Broker</em></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-powered-by-latest-technologies"><strong>Powered by Latest Technologies</strong></h3>



<p>BBP prioritises security, scalability, and reliability while utilising the most recent technologies and systems. Because of AWS&#8217;s dependable infrastructure and little hardware risk, B2Trader is hosted on this excellent server ecosystem. It uses MongoDB and Amazon Redshift for data management, while the renowned TradingView is integrated for market research.</p>



<p>Scalable deployments are supported by Docker and Kubernetes, while CloudFlare provides DDoS protection. The reliability and effectiveness of B2Trader are enhanced by the FIX protocol. The following is a list of all the protocols and technologies:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-eu.googleusercontent.com/56mAbxy4g21Mg5RPHoo1VJDm9SY-pe4-rJOPUis5RJI1Z71VXEUf8c0GMKVmh5lJp8Co3nD-vlrbLkhKsS2hd37Z-WYDnj6woCJwfWNM9Xu99YUhOEmT-8-_63ygCKbvTISxV9RClsTUwQpz_kvD8x8" alt=""/></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-expansive-integration-options"><strong>Expansive Integration Options</strong></h3>



<p>As <a href="https://b2broker.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">B2Broker’s</a> latest and most advanced product, B2Trader offers a wide range of integration choices. The vast array of products that B2Broker provides includes a trading platform, OMS, pre-trade and post-trade control, liquidity management system, Trading User Interface, <a href="https://b2binpay.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">CRM, back office</a>, <a href="https://b2binpay.com/">blockchain wallets for processing</a> and collecting coins and tokens, blockchain management system for automated payouts and settlements, mobile applications, technical documentation, REST and FIX API protocols, sophisticated White Label options, and much more.</p>



<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="602" height="337" src="https://lh7-eu.googleusercontent.com/CzFe6LpeusE4-FHPN8RN62JBX0ZuzbMw7R5LptXbO7N20m9bD1wz5VdpRjYfc1TNnTQy12NyUCvaqaqfbHghKIGECg6GXBzxC2dzRKda0LAT_uBrmv03RLeEZoIgbR9r7g2c8lCZKZvVKfTbmaZGZp0"><br>Lastly, B2Trader&#8217;s connection with <a href="https://b2broker.com/products/marksman/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Marksman</a>, a cryptocurrency liquidity distribution engine, streamlines administration and ensures market updates with the latest data.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrency brokers may easily connect to the top exchanges by inputting their API credentials into Marksman after opening an account. Brokers can use B2Trader to create customised liquidity pools from several exchanges, assign specific execution and routing rules, and provide failover protocols for the pairings and liquidity pools.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-let-b2trader-open-the-gate-to-the-crypto-landscape"><strong>Let B2Trader Open the Gate to the Crypto Landscape</strong></h2>



<p>B2Trader Brokerage Platform is readily available as a turnkey solution or for integration with any CRM via REST API. The platform’s sophisticated configuration and effective infrastructure enable the new cryptocurrency spot trading solution to be launched in only one week.</p>



<p>The unparalleled speed of completion enables businesses to join the cryptocurrency market seamlessly and generate revenue immediately. If you aim to adopt cryptocurrency in the most straightforward manner possible, you can test this inventive new platform out for yourself by trying out B2Trader&#8217;s free demo!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/discover-b2trader-a-brand-new-brokerage-platform-from-b2broker/">Discover B2Trader, a Brand-New Brokerage Platform from B2Broker</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-200.png" medium="image" width="1486" height="834" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-200.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Finance Minister Says Crypto Should Not Be Prohibited</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/russian-finance-minister-crypto-not-prohibited/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489577</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Russia's Finance Minister opposes banning cryptocurrencies, aiming for regulation to facilitate domestic and international settlements, and considers the role of mining in financial transactions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/russian-finance-minister-crypto-not-prohibited/">Russian Finance Minister Says Crypto Should Not Be Prohibited</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Russia&#8217;s Finance Minister Anton Siluanov voiced a strong stance against the outright prohibition of crypto. </strong></p>



<p>Highlighting the ongoing dialogue between the Ministry of Finance and the Bank of Russia, Siluanov revealed plans to delve into the practicalities of employing cryptocurrencies for domestic and international settlements.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-russia-finance-minister-why-crypto-ban-is-a-bad-idea">Russia Finance Minister: Why Crypto Ban is a Bad Idea</h2>



<p>Siluanov&#8217;s remarks reflect a pragmatic approach toward the cryptocurrency market, emphasizing the necessity of regulation over restriction. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;I am sure that the Central Bank and we will come to an agreement. This issue has been discussed for several years. We cannot prohibit the circulation of cryptocurrencies. Therefore, we need to regulate this channel. I am sure that we will find a solution,&#8221; Siluanov <a href="https://www.rbc.ru/crypto/news/65fd7cc69a7947fb94c51d1c" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">stated</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>The discourse around cryptocurrency mining and its potential application in settling transactions has gained traction. Both governmental bodies expressed a preliminary inclination toward leveraging cryptocurrencies for external payments. This nuanced position reflects a broader consideration of the role of cryptocurrencies within Russia&#8217;s financial system, balancing between innovation and fiscal oversight.</p>



<p>Indeed, the dialogue is expected to shed light on permissible <a href="https://beincrypto.com/central-bank-russia-crypto-allegations/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">activities within the cryptocurrency domain</a>. Especially, on international financial interactions.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“We need to talk about what can and cannot be done with cryptocurrency. We have now agreed with the Central Bank to discuss the issue of mining &#8211; whether the results of this process can be used for settlements within the country and in international settlements,” Siluanov added.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/crypto-regulation/">Crypto Regulation: What Are the Benefits and Drawbacks?</a></strong></p>



<p>The backdrop to these discussions includes supportive <a href="https://beincrypto.com/russia-alfa-bank-digital-financial-asset-dfa/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">remarks from Elvira Nabiullina</a>, Head of the Bank of Russia. She previously endorsed the experimental use of cryptocurrency and mining in cross-border settlements. Siluanov&#8217;s affirmation of regulatory intentions further cements the government&#8217;s commitment to fostering a controlled yet vibrant cryptocurrency sector.</p>



<p>The economic implications of such regulatory advancements are substantial. With miners poised to generate liquidity for foreign trade settlements upwards of $2.59 billion, there is a vast potential for enhanced tax revenues from industrial mining. Indeed, Sergei Bezdelov, Director of the Industrial Mining Association, <a href="https://vk.com/video-25232578_456317691" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> the fiscal benefits of a regulated crypto framework.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/russian-finance-minister-crypto-not-prohibited/">Russian Finance Minister Says Crypto Should Not Be Prohibited</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BIC_Putin_russia-covers.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BIC_Putin_russia-covers.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bull Run Heats Up: BlueZilla Unleashes BlastFi IDO on March 26th</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/bull-run-heats-up-bluezilla-unleashes-blastfi-ido-on-march-26th/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlueZilla, the leading incubator, is making triumphant waves again. Renowned for pioneering project launches with titans like BSCPad, AIPad, and GameZone, BlueZilla continues its legacy of success, boasting a track record of incubating and launching 35% of the top IDOs in 2021. Zaibot’s recent launch showed incredible success, trending at 28x and capturing global attention &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bull-run-heats-up-bluezilla-unleashes-blastfi-ido-on-march-26th/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bull-run-heats-up-bluezilla-unleashes-blastfi-ido-on-march-26th/">Bull Run Heats Up: BlueZilla Unleashes BlastFi IDO on March 26th</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong><a href="https://bluezilla.vc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BlueZilla</a>, the leading incubator, is making triumphant waves again. Renowned for pioneering project launches with titans like <a href="https://bscpad.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BSCPad</a>, <a href="https://www.aipad.tech/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">AIPad</a>, and <a href="https://gamezone.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">GameZone</a>, BlueZilla continues its legacy of success, boasting a track record of <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinMarketCap/status/1468281278525063171?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">incubating and launching 35% of the top IDOs in 2021</a>.</strong></p>



<p>Zaibot’s recent launch showed incredible success, trending at 28x and <a href="https://twitter.com/ZAIBOTIO/status/1766468739380228533?s=20">capturing global attention on Twitter</a>. Now, a new milestone awaits with the BlastFi IDO scheduled for Tuesday, 26th March.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Brace yourself for the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BlastFi?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BlastFi</a> IDO, launching on Tuesday, March 26th!<br><br>Article: <a href="https://t.co/Gz8UWoMAjK">https://t.co/Gz8UWoMAjK</a><br><br><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3ae.png" alt="🎮" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Dive into the world of BlastFi: a cutting-edge DeFi platform designed to captivate the community with gamified leaderboards, weekly quests, and enticing bonuses. <a href="https://t.co/NPTWIK9Eex">pic.twitter.com/NPTWIK9Eex</a></p>&mdash; BlastFi (@Blast_Fi) <a href="https://twitter.com/Blast_Fi/status/1771869575237566549?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>After the recent news of Blast reaching a TVL of $2.4b in under 4 days, the ecosystem is primed for another significant surge with the introduction of <a href="https://www.blastfi.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BlastFi</a>. Positioned to be the leading incubator and launch platform, BlastFi prioritizes a gamified user experience and integrated DeFi infrastructure, all within the Blast network. Investors will gain unprecedented access to promising projects within the Blast ecosystem, supported by features like a gamified leaderboard, weekly quests, multichain accessibility, NFT integration, and more.</p>



<p>It is common knowledge that success hinges on the strength of your network and infrastructure! Backed and incubated by BlueZilla—a leader in project launches—BlastFi is primed for greatness. With a track record of over 100 successful projects, exceeding $500 billion in trading volume, and $80+ million raised, BlueZilla brings unparalleled expertise and resources to the table. With this solid backing and extensive network, BlastFi is poised to capitalize on BlueZilla&#8217;s wealth of experience and industry advantage.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-makes-blastfi-stand-out"><strong>What Makes BlastFi Stand Out?</strong></h2>



<p>In addition to its incubation and project launch prowess, BlastFi sets itself apart by seamlessly blending gamification with DeFi, all while prioritizing user engagement and community building. Here are some key highlights of its features:</p>



<ul>
<li>Multichain Accessibility between Blast, BNB, and Ethereum to provide maximum access across chains to the next 100x projects. BlastFi plans to add more networks in the future.</li>
</ul>



<ul>
<li>An integrated NFT wallet, NFT viewer and leaderboard, showing users scores from staking/locking, and a bonus score from events.</li>
</ul>



<ul>
<li>Low Volatility Native Yield Staking, where staked ETH gets converted into a score which is then matched in $BLASTFI tokens. In addition, a 2x score multiplier is applied, thus doubling the staking impact. All the rewards earned from this staking method go into buying back and burning $BLASTFI tokens strategically. This helps increase the token&#8217;s value by making it scarce and supports the platform&#8217;s goal of building a strong and lasting ecosystem.</li>
</ul>



<ul>
<li>A weekly bonus program, which adds an extra layer of engagement to the ecosystem. Active users will be incentivized to promote the growth of the community through inviting new users.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-leveraging-partnerships"><strong>Leveraging Partnerships</strong></h2>



<p>Recently announced on Twitter, BlastFi has made a significant partnership with EasyX, a heavyweight in leverage trading within the Blast ecosystem. EasyX provides 100x Power, gasless trading, and a seamless KYC-free experience, all wrapped in a user-friendly UI.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Look who we&#39;ve partnered with <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br><br>EasyX &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/Blast_Fi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Blast_Fi</a><br><br>BlastFi is igniting the revolution on <a href="https://twitter.com/Blast_L2?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Blast_L2</a> by offering staking, a dynamic leaderboard, NFT viewer, bridge and a launchpad for IDOs.<br><br>Working together is going to be EASY! <a href="https://t.co/95ly13B6Ai">https://t.co/95ly13B6Ai</a></p>&mdash; Easy X (@EasyXdefi) <a href="https://twitter.com/EasyXdefi/status/1768298505494200463?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 14, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>This strategic alliance brings sophisticated leverage trading tools to BlastFi, one of the most anticipated projects on Blast, providing its users with even more resources to capitalize on in&nbsp; the bull run.</p>



<p>Additionally, BlastFi has integrated with Galxe for maximum community engagement, allowing users to complete quests and earn points redeemable for $BLASTFI tokens. Within just a few days of launch, BlastFi has already seen an incredible response with over 34,000 registrations and counting.</p>



<p>Furthermore, BlastFi&#8217;s partnership with Thruster ensures its community can leverage the L2 Blast liquidity provision and swaps, adding further value to the platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-participate-in-the-blastfi-ido"><strong>How to Participate in the BlastFi IDO</strong></h2>



<p>BlastFi’s IDO will be held on Tuesday, 26 March 2024 on <a href="https://twitter.com/BSCPad" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BSCPad</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/AIPADTECH" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">AIPad</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/Blast_Fi" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BlastFi</a> itself in two stages: public IDO on BSCPad, AiPad and BlastFI and a private round accessible only to <a href="https://twitter.com/gamezone_app" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">GameZone</a> (Celestial Tier) and <a href="https://twitter.com/ethpadofficial" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ETHPad</a> (Diamond Tier). For full participation details click <a href="https://medium.com/@bscpad/blastfi-incubation-ido-details-bscpad-aipad-and-blastfi-3ba9392b0695" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">here</a>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Thanks to BlastFi&#8217;s partnership with Galxe, user activity on the Galxe platform directly influences their standing on BlastFi&#8217;s leaderboard and terminal bonus system. Join the <a href="https://galxe.com/dAjsAzAJu73vCXq44Q2hqE/campaign/GCcQNt443T" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Galxe campaign</a> now to start earning points and boost your leaderboard score!&nbsp;</p>



<p>Stay updated on all of BlueZilla’s launches by clicking <a href="https://t.me/BluezillaIDO/690" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">here</a>, and don&#8217;t forget to follow #BlastFi’s social media channels to stay informed about important announcements.</p>



<p><a href="https://www.blastfi.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Website</a> | <a href="https://t.me/Blast_Fi" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Telegram Ann</a> | <a href="https://t.me/Blastfichat" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Telegram Chat</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/Blast_Fi" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Twitter</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bull-run-heats-up-bluezilla-unleashes-blastfi-ido-on-march-26th/">Bull Run Heats Up: BlueZilla Unleashes BlastFi IDO on March 26th</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Снимок-экрана-2024-03-25-в-14.43.21.png" medium="image" width="1182" height="704" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Снимок-экрана-2024-03-25-в-14.43.21.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Will End Support for USDC on This Blockchain Next Week</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/binance-end-support-usdc-next-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ryan James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489367</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance will stop USDC transactions on Tron's network from April 5, 2024, following Circle's decision to cease USDC support on Tron.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/binance-end-support-usdc-next-week/">Binance Will End Support for USDC on This Blockchain Next Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong> Binance plans to halt USDC transactions via the Tron (TRC20) network starting from April 5, 2024, at 02:00 UTC.</strong></p>



<p>This move is in response to Circle&#8217;s cessation of USDC on the same network. Circle recently announced it would be discontinuing support for USDC on the Tron Blockchain.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-binance-stops-usdc-trc20-deposits-and-withdrawals">Binance Stops USDC TRC20 Deposits and Withdrawals</h2>



<p>Accordingly, Binance advises that post the deadline, <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-cease-support-for-deposits-and-withdrawals-of-usdc-via-the-tron-network-trc20-33df0ff0e2e94259950b5c4b1f4952f7" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">USDC deposits through TRC20 won&#8217;t be processed</a>. Yet, this change won&#8217;t impede USDC trading on Binance, which remains operational. Moreover, the exchange assures that USDC dealings on other networks are not impacted, promising uninterrupted service across diverse blockchains.</p>



<p>Furthermore, Binance stated the stablecoin will still be available for deposits and withdrawals on other blockchains: </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Deposits and withdrawals of USDC via other supported networks will not be impacted.&#8221; The announcement stated.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>This strategic update reflects a larger industry-wide recalibration as major cryptocurrency firms reassess their operational frameworks to better align with evolving regulatory landscapes and market demands. Circle&#8217;s decision to <a href="https://www.circle.com/blog/circle-is-discontinuing-support-for-usdc-on-the-tron-blockchain" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">phase out USDC support on the TRON network</a> demonstrates a careful approach aimed at upholding the integrity and utility of the USDC token on more universally accepted networks.</p>



<p><strong>Read More:<a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/best-stablecoins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> A Guide to the Best Stablecoins in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>For retail users and non-Circle clients with USDC on the TRON network, the best step is to move their holdings to a suitable exchange. This ensures a seamless shift to a blockchain that supports USDC. It allows users to handle their assets well during this change.</p>



<p>In essence, Circle&#8217;s strategic adjustment, together with Binance&#8217;s agreement, signifies the dynamic evolution of the crypto sector. As entities like Circle and Coinbase <a href="https://beincrypto.com/stablecoin-firm-cease-tron-blockchain-support-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">aim for public trading status in the US</a>, their operational choices reflect a strong <a href="https://beincrypto.com/why-crypto-firms-demand-clear-regulations/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">commitment to regulatory compliance</a> and market steadiness. Binance&#8217;s response to these developments highlights its commitment to offering a reliable and robust trading platform for its worldwide clientele.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/binance-end-support-usdc-next-week/">Binance Will End Support for USDC on This Blockchain Next Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_USDC_2-covers_neutral.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_USDC_2-covers_neutral.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Confirms First Downtrend In Seven Months &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-confirms-downtrend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaryamann Shrivastava]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX) Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price is struggling to recover with the bearish market cues getting stronger for the asset. Will TRX continue to decline or make a recovery soon?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-confirms-downtrend/">Tron (TRX) Price Confirms First Downtrend In Seven Months &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The Tron (TRX) price took a downturn towards the end of February, just as most of the crypto market began trending upwards, with many even marking new all-time highs.</strong></p>



<p>This bearishness will likely continue going forward as trend indicators signal a drawdown for the altcoin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tron-price-downtrend-begins">Tron Price Downtrend Begins</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-analysis-bearish/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tron price was noting a potential rise</a> over the past week, which failed to trigger a recovery for the asset. The ongoing decline has considerably impacted the overall growth of the crypto asset and the network. </p>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-founder-justin-sun-bitcoin-holdings/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The project is losing traction</a> among users, which can be observed by the fall in the number of users on the network. Weekly average users have taken a hit in the past two weeks, falling by 10% from 5.79 million to 5.25 million.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="354" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-850x354.png" alt="Tron Weekly Users. " class="wp-image-489507" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-850x354.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-360x150.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-768x320.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-1536x639.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-150x62.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514.png 1756w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Tron Weekly Users. Source: <a href="https://dune.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Dune</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Additionally, a chunk of the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/stablecoin-firm-cease-tron-blockchain-support-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">TRX supply is awaiting a profit trigger</a>, which, by its looks, will not take place anytime soon. About 1.36 billion TRX bought within the $0.1165 to $0.1205 range is hanging in uncertainty and might fall back into the loss-bearing territory.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/buy-tron/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Buy TRON (TRX) and Everything You Need To Know</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="273" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-850x273.png" alt="Tron GIOM. " class="wp-image-489508" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-850x273.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-360x116.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-768x246.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-1536x493.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-150x48.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199.png 1580w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Tron GIOM. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/">Into</a><a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TheBlock</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>This is because all signals point towards potential decline, which would turn the aforementioned price range into a resistance zone.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-trx-price-prediction-one-downtrend-ends-another-begins">TRX Price Prediction: One Downtrend Ends, Another Begins</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/stablecoin-firm-cease-tron-blockchain-support-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tron&#8217;s price is trading at $0.1174</a> at the time of writing after failing to breach the barrier marked at $0.1219. The decline, while seemingly halted, is potentially set to continue going forward. This is because the crypto asset that has been trading below the Ichimoku Cloud is now noting a confirmed downtrend.</p>



<p>The Ichimoku Cloud is a technical analysis tool that indicates support, resistance, trend direction, and momentum. Generally, when the price is below the cloud, bearish outcomes are possible; however, as the cloud turns bearish, the asset is expected to trade further lower.</p>



<p>Such is the case with <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/tronlink-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tron price as well since the Ichimoku Cloud</a> turned red over the last 48 hours. This is a signal confirming a downtrend for TRX, making this the first such instance in seven months since August 2023.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="373" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-850x373.png" alt="TRX/USDT 12-hour chart. " class="wp-image-489506" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-850x373.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-360x158.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-768x337.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-1536x675.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-150x66.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg.png 1755w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">TRX/USDT 12-hour chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Thus, Tron&#8217;s price could note a further decline, potentially sending it to test the support level of $0.1123.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/trx-wallet/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">7 Best Tron Wallets for Storing TRX Tokens</a></strong></p>



<p>On the other hand, Ichimoku Cloud is known to be a leading indicator, and given the recent attempt at recovery, TRX might stabilize for a while. If so, Tron&#8217;s price could observe consolidation and continue moving sideways, potentially breaching $0.1219, invalidating the bearish thesis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-confirms-downtrend/">Tron (TRX) Price Confirms First Downtrend In Seven Months &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bic_TRON_neutral_3.png" medium="image" width="5120" height="2880" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bic_TRON_neutral_3.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>X (Twitter) AI Grok Hints at Dogecoin Payments</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-ai-grok-dogecoin-doge-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ali M.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AI Grok's conflicting responses on Dogecoin payments on X (Twitter) spotlight the potential for future cryptocurrency integration and the dynamic role of digital currencies in social media.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-ai-grok-dogecoin-doge-payments/">X (Twitter) AI Grok Hints at Dogecoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>X&#8217;s (formerly Twitter) AI, Grok, has opened up new possibilities for cryptocurrency enthusiasts. With a nod towards enhancing user financial interactions, Grok suggested that users can engage in Dogecoin (DOGE) transactions directly through the platform. </strong></p>



<p>This notion hints at X&#8217;s leap into the cryptocurrency market, placing Dogecoin alongside traditional payment methods.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-grok-suggests-dogecoin-payments-on-x-twitter">Grok Suggests Dogecoin Payments on X (Twitter)</h2>



<p>When <a href="https://x.com/kingthies/status/1772104656518566196?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">asked</a>, &#8220;Can I send or receive DOGE on X?,&#8221; the mobile version of Grok said the process is remarkably straightforward for those looking to engage in DOGE transactions. </p>



<p>According to X&#8217;s generative AI, users wishing to send <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/buy-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dogecoin</a> must first ensure their X wallet is funded with DOGE. By selecting the &#8220;Send&#8221; option within the app, users can then enter the recipient&#8217;s X username or their unique Dogecoin wallet address, specify the amount, and finalize the transaction. </p>



<p>Receiving DOGE follows a similar user-friendly procedure. Grok suggested that by accessing the &#8220;Receive&#8221; function, users are presented with their exclusive Dogecoin wallet address, which can be shared with potential senders or linked to their X username, facilitating the receipt of funds.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">FULFILL THE PROPHECY <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE</a> <a href="https://t.co/J3fweq2hKH">pic.twitter.com/J3fweq2hKH</a></p>&mdash; Crypto Thies (@kingthies) <a href="https://twitter.com/kingthies/status/1772104656518566196?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>However, the desktop version of Grok painted a different picture, stating that <a href="https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-dogecoin-doge/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">X currently does not support direct Dogecoin</a> transactions. It hinted at possible future integration, advising users to keep an eye on updates from X and Elon Musk.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“At the moment, there is no direct support for sending or receiving Dogecoin (DOGE) on the X platform. However, recent developments and rumors suggest that crypto assets like DOGE could be integrated into the platform&#8217;s payment offerings in the future. It&#8217;s essential to stay updated with the latest news and announcements from X and Elon Musk to be informed about any changes or updates regarding Dogecoin integration,” the desktop version of Grok stated.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>This discrepancy raises questions about the platform&#8217;s direction concerning cryptocurrency integration and its support for Dogecoin. </p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/doge-dogecoin-price-prediction-2019-2020-5-years-updated-04-28-19-doge-usd-reaches-resistance/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Prediction 2024 / 2025 / 2030</a></strong></p>



<p>This news could signal a significant shift for DOGE holders in how they use and accept the altcoin for payments. Indeed, such an integration could solidify Dogecoin&#8217;s position within the crypto market as more than a meme coin. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-ai-grok-dogecoin-doge-payments/">X (Twitter) AI Grok Hints at Dogecoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Up.png" medium="image" width="2560" height="1440" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Up.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Country Plans to Shift its Focus Away From Bitcoin Mining</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/country-plans-shift-away-bitcoin-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ryan James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Iceland considers pivoting from its thriving Bitcoin mining sector to prioritize food security and sustainable energy. Prime Minister Katrín Jakobsdóttir expresses concerns over energy consumption's impact, prompting reevaluation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/country-plans-shift-away-bitcoin-mining/">This Country Plans to Shift its Focus Away From Bitcoin Mining</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>In a significant shift that may redefine its economic landscape, Iceland is contemplating a move away from its burgeoning Bitcoin mining sector. The country will address more pressing concerns related to food security and energy sustainability. </strong></p>



<p>Prime Minister Katrín Jakobsdóttir voiced her apprehensions about the nation&#8217;s energy consumption patterns. Especially in light of the increasing demands from the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6432a24b-b7c4-4c2f-85a8-79108dbe0644" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">cryptocurrency mining industry</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-mining-threatens-iceland-s-sustainability-pm-warns">Bitcoin Mining Threatens Iceland&#8217;s Sustainability, PM Warns</h2>



<p>Iceland, nestled atop the Mid-Atlantic ridge, is a haven for Bitcoin miners, thanks to its abundant renewable energy resources. The country&#8217;s vast reserves of hydro and geothermal energy have made it an attractive destination for data centers dedicated to the energy-intensive process of Bitcoin mining. </p>



<p>However, this has led to an unprecedented surge in energy consumption. Currently, the country consumes about 120 MW of power, making it the most <a href="https://beincrypto.com/iceland-leads-the-world-in-bitcoin-mining-but-not-everyone-is-thrilled/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin-mining-dense region globally</a>.</p>



<p>The Prime Minister expressed concerns over the sustainability of this energy consumption, especially considering the adverse impacts on other vital sectors like agriculture. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Data centers in Iceland use a significant share of our green energy,&#8221; Jakobsdóttir remarked, </p>
</blockquote>



<p>This revelation comes at a time when the global balance of Bitcoin mining is experiencing a shift. <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bitcoin-mining-invests-texas-facility-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">New players are continuously entering the mining scene</a>. Thanks to its cheap electricity and entrepreneurial spirit, Iceland, once a pioneer in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/iceland-largest-bitcoin-hash-rate-producer-capita/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">industrial-scale Bitcoin mining</a>, is now reevaluating its stance in light of broader economic and environmental considerations.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/bitcoin-mining-from-home/">Bitcoin Mining From Home: Is It Possible in 2024?</a></strong></p>



<p>The island&#8217;s alarming reliance on imports for basic food staples underscores the decision. With only 1% of grains and 43% of vegetables produced domestically. Jakobsdóttir&#8217;s proposed pivot towards bolstering food production signifies a strategic redirection of Iceland&#8217;s renewable energy resources to support more sustainable and essential sectors. This will ensure energy security for households and industries beyond crypto mining.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-mining-industry-prepares-for-post-halving-shake-up">Crypto Mining Industry Prepares for Post-Halving Shake-Up</h2>



<p>This strategic shift is reflective of a broader trend within the crypto-mining industry. Which is bracing for significant changes after the anticipated <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bitcoin-mining-stock-soars-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin halving event in April</a>. Industry experts, including Marathon Digital Holdings CEO Fred Thiel, have warned of the impending <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2024/03/22/large-scale-bitcoin-miners-are-competing-head-on-with-ai-companies-for-power-marathon-digital-ceo.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">financial pressures on smaller miners</a>. Which could lead to a consolidation in favor of larger players with more robust financial backing.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“Post halving I think you’ll see the smaller miners come under financial stress, which will enable the bigger miners to consolidate the industry,” Thiel stated.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>In navigating a crucial change, Iceland views its shift as more than just a way to secure energy and food. It&#8217;s also a sign of its dedication to sustainable growth. </p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/how-much-electricity-bitcoin-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How Much Electricity Does Bitcoin Mining Use?</a></strong></p>



<p>Hence, Iceland is redirecting its renewable energy from crypto mining to vital fields such as agriculture. This move showcases Iceland&#8217;s ability to merge tech progress with eco-friendly practices and economic stability.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/country-plans-shift-away-bitcoin-mining/">This Country Plans to Shift its Focus Away From Bitcoin Mining</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ecoway-crypto-green-mining.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ecoway-crypto-green-mining.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BloFin Announces Platinum Sponsor of TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BloFin, a top global crypto derivative exchange, is thrilled to reveal its platinum sponsorship for the highly anticipated TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024, a premier crypto event. This sponsorship marks a significant milestone for BloFin, following its successful participation as a Gold Sponsor at TOKEN2049, the premier blockchain event in Singapore in 2023. It is dedicated to &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/">BloFin Announces Platinum Sponsor of TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong><a href="https://blofin.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BloFin</a>, a top global crypto derivative exchange, is thrilled to reveal its platinum sponsorship for the highly anticipated TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024, a premier crypto event. </strong></p>



<p>This sponsorship marks a significant milestone for BloFin, following its successful participation as a Gold Sponsor at TOKEN2049, the premier blockchain event in Singapore in 2023. It is dedicated to furthering the blockchain industry&#8217;s growth and development by partnering once again with TOKEN2049. As a Platinum Sponsor, BloFin aims to showcase its commitment to innovation, technology, and community engagement within the blockchain ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>



<p>TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024 promises to be a gathering of industry leaders, innovators, and enthusiasts from around the world, and BloFin&#8217;s sponsorship underscores its position as a key player in shaping the future of blockchain technology and digital asset trading.</p>



<p>Moreover, given Dubai&#8217;s status as a global hub for crypto innovation and the pivotal role of TOKEN2049 in the UAE, BloFin&#8217;s exclusive<a href="https://lu.ma/BloFinWhalesNightDubai" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> WhalesNight AfterParty</a> is poised to make waves. Scheduled to be held at the scenic Sobe Dubai Rooftop Sundowner, the event will commence at 19:30 (UTC+4) on April 18, 2024. </p>



<p>The BloFin WhalesNight AfterParty will bring together industry leaders, BloFin Whales (influencers), and BloFin VIPs from around the world. Attendees can look forward to engaging discussions, exciting news, and valuable networking opportunities in a vibrant and dynamic atmosphere. It will serve as a platform for participants to connect, share insights, and explore new opportunities in the ever-evolving cryptocurrency landscape. </p>



<p>With Dubai being a hub for innovation and technological advancement, this event is poised to make a significant impact on the future of blockchain technology and digital assets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/NfVei8AiU5macxITjam6_3ErHv6soiofADoNuNjeqgU57_J9-ladjnLc5rm8UFSE8ddJewqIT0KTrlXSVWFpXJJxYw7tnZLtvjnK1Vg7g8sZyT80JIvfEbdVkC_MlunZvQ-WFC2R8Q_3-FOKSRg6Kjk" alt=""/></figure>



<p>With years of experience in the blockchain industry, Matt Hu, the CEO of Blofin, is anticipating this opportunity and recognizes the significance of attending TOKEN 2049 in Dubai as a platinum sponsor for his product:&nbsp;</p>



<p>&#8220;Bitcoin is being heralded as the modern-day gold, while Dubai is on the rise as the world&#8217;s new financial epicenter. Dubai Token2049 presents an unparalleled platform for dialogue, not just for us, but for global users as well. As one of the most rapidly expanding exchanges, BloFin is excited to showcase our breakthroughs in product innovation, cutting-edge technology, and unparalleled security measures. We&#8217;re not stopping there; BloFin is committed to ongoing investment in our product suite, technological advancements, security protocols, and operational efficiencies to ensure our users receive nothing but the most exceptional and dependable services. Join us at Dubai Token2049 to witness the future of finance, today.&#8221;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Attendees at TOKEN2049 in Dubai will have the opportunity to delve into the diverse features of the Blofin ecosystem, spanning futures trading, copy trading, and more. Through interactions with experts, Web3 builders, thought leaders, and enthusiasts at TOKEN2049, BloFin aims to forge a robust foundation for the advancement and maturation of the blockchain ecosystem.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-about-blofin"><strong>About BloFin</strong></h2>



<p>BloFin is a secure and cryptocurrency centralized exchange (CEX) that offers the best services for perpetual &amp; futures trading with an extensive selection of over 300 USDT-M perpetual contracts. Aside from derivatives trading products, BloFin now provides more high-quality services including spot trading, copy trading, earning, API, and more. The team prioritizes user trust and platform transparency above all else. </p>



<p>BloFin is committed to prioritizing user fund security by partnering with Fireblocks to safeguard users&#8217; assets and providing insurance coverage for potential crypto-related incidents and we continue to shape the future of crypto trading. As BloFin continues to expand its global presence and influence, partnerships with leading industry events like TOKEN2049 serve as a testament to its commitment to excellence and leadership in the cryptocurrency and blockchain sectors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/">BloFin Announces Platinum Sponsor of TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/photo_2024-03-22-14.33.22.jpeg" medium="image" width="1280" height="640" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/photo_2024-03-22-14.33.22.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real-World Assets Exchange DigiFT Debuts US Treasury Bill Tokens</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/real-world-assets-rwa-treasury-bill-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ali M.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Real-World Assets (RWA) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiFT's new U.S. Treasury Bill tokens revolutionize blockchain investment, providing direct beneficial ownership and legal transparency. This marks a first in blockchain-based real-world asset exchanges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/real-world-assets-rwa-treasury-bill-tokens/">Real-World Assets Exchange DigiFT Debuts US Treasury Bill Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>DigiFT recently unveiled its latest offering in the form of US Treasury Bill depository receipt tokens. This innovation introduces direct beneficial ownership in US Treasury Bills to the blockchain. </strong></p>



<p>The significance of this launch lies in its approach to solving a longstanding issue within Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization—the challenge of legally and accurately representing ownership and interest.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-us-treasury-bill-tokens-now-on-real-world-assets-exchange">US Treasury Bill Tokens Now on Real-World Assets Exchange</h2>



<p>The concept of depositary receipts has a rich history in facilitating international investment, dating back to their inception in the 1920s. Traditionally, these instruments enabled investors to access foreign markets with relative ease. Adapting this established structure, DigiFT aims to address the legal representation of token holders&#8217; interests in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/real-world-asset-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Real-World Assets</a>.</p>



<p>Currently, the market is saturated with wrapped tokens, which often come entangled in legal frameworks that obscure direct ownership. This can pose significant hurdles for investors seeking to navigate the implications of their investments. By contrast, DigiFT’s <a href="https://www.digift.sg/announcements/first-rwa-depository-receipt-tokens.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">deployment</a> of depository receipt tokens offers a clear, legally coherent framework. </p>



<p>This model simplifies investment comprehension and ensures investors have a direct claim on the returns of the underlying assets.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/tokenization-rwas/">What is The Impact of Real World Asset (RWA) Tokenization?</a></strong></p>



<p>Henry Zhang, Founder and CEO of DigiFT, highlighted the importance of the DR structure. It helps address market needs, particularly in terms of direct ownership and return on investment. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“DigiFT&#8217;s innovative DR structure addresses a pain point in the current RWA market, empowering investors with direct ownership of underlying assets and returns. Looking ahead, DigiFT remains committed to expanding the universe of traditional financial assets in the Web3 space through the DR model, offering better investor protection and transparency,” Zhang said. </p>
</blockquote>



<p>As the first licensed Real-World Assets exchange, DigiFT merges deep financial insights with advanced technological capabilities. The newly launched US Treasury Tokens (DRUST) are emblematic of this fusion, providing a regulated, blockchain-based option for managing treasury and cash flows. Highly liquid US Treasury Bills directly back these tokens, which appeal to a broad spectrum of institutional investors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/real-world-assets-rwa-treasury-bill-tokens/">Real-World Assets Exchange DigiFT Debuts US Treasury Bill Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/BIC_Tokenization_token_2-covers.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/BIC_Tokenization_token_2-covers.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finticipate &#8211; Third Annual SEE Fintech Forum is back, promising insights into future fintech trends</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=485874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Finticipate thrilled to announce the upcoming third annual Finticipate &#8211; SEE Fintech Forum, scheduled for May 31st, 2024, at the Mona Plaza Hotel in Belgrade, and via online platform. This event promises to be a highlight on the calendars of industry leaders and enthusiasts alike. Building on the success of previous editions, Finticipate Vol3 – &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/">Finticipate &#8211; Third Annual SEE Fintech Forum is back, promising insights into future fintech trends</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Finticipate thrilled to announce the upcoming third annual Finticipate &#8211; SEE Fintech Forum, scheduled for May 31<sup>st</sup>, 2024, at the Mona Plaza Hotel in Belgrade, and via online platform. This event promises to be a highlight on the calendars of industry leaders and enthusiasts alike.</strong></p>



<p>Building on the success of previous editions, Finticipate Vol3 – SEE Fintech Forum is poised to bring together prominent figures from the regional and European fintech and finance communities. Attendees can anticipate the presence of regulatory authorities, traditional banks, innovative neobanks, crypto exchanges, web 3 service providers, burgeoning startups, fintech payment platforms, international fintech associations, established financial institutions, BNPL (Buy Now, Pay Later) services, and more.</p>



<p>This year, Finticipate aims to delve deep into the emerging trends that will shape the future of the fintech landscape. From disruptive technologies to regulatory shifts, the forum will offer invaluable insights and perspectives on the evolving industry dynamics.</p>



<p>&#8220;We are excited to once again convene thought leaders and industry pioneers at SEE Fintech Forum,&#8221; said Jasna Nedic, Program director at Finticipate. &#8220;As the fintech ecosystem continues to evolve, this event serves as a vital platform for collaboration, knowledge-sharing, and networking.&#8221;</p>



<p><strong>Rare Bird discount</strong> is still on, priced at <strong>€370 + VAT</strong> per person until <strong>April 30th</strong>. For companies registering 3 or more attendees, the fee is reduced to €320 + VAT per person. <strong>Standard registration costs €450 + VAT</strong>, whereas <strong>online registration</strong> is available for <strong>€130 + VAT</strong>. Seating is limited, so ensure you register on time to secure your spot!</p>



<p>Registration for the forum is now open via the official <a href="https://finticipate.com/registration/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">website</a>, or interested individuals can reach out via <a href="office@finticipate.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">email</a>. Limited slots are available, so early registration is encouraged.</p>



<p>Join Finticipate on May 31st as we embark on an immersive fintech journey, exploring diverse viewpoints on the most pressing topics shaping the industry&#8217;s future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-about-finticipate">About Finticipate</h2>



<p>Finticipate is a leading platform provided by New Angles Consulting dedicated to exploring the latest trends, innovations, and disruptions in the fintech and finance sectors. Through forum and online content, Finticipate fosters collaboration and knowledge-sharing among industry stakeholders, driving forward the evolution of financial technology worldwide. Visit <a href="https://finticipate.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">website</a> to learn more.<br><br><a href="https://finticipate.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Website</a> | <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/finticipate-see-fintech-forum/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">LinkedIn</a> | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/new_angles_consulting/?hl=sr" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Instagram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/">Finticipate &#8211; Third Annual SEE Fintech Forum is back, promising insights into future fintech trends</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Banner_1200x627.png" medium="image" width="1200" height="627" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Banner_1200x627.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>High-Risk Appetite Evident as PUNDU Meme Coin Raises $100 Million</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/solana-meme-coin-nears-100-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana-based PUNDU meme coin presale achieved exceptional success, raising nearly $100 million in record time.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/solana-meme-coin-nears-100-million/">High-Risk Appetite Evident as PUNDU Meme Coin Raises $100 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>DAO Maker has achieved a remarkable feat, securing nearly $100 million in a presale for the PUNDU meme coin.</strong></p>



<p>The significant investment contributed within 36 hours reflects a pronounced appetite for high-risk ventures in the crypto market. However, the overwhelming response resulted in an oversubscription, necessitating refunds for contributors who sent funds post-target attainment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-solana-meme-coins-in-high-demand">Solana Meme Coins in High Demand</h2>



<p>DAO Maker unveiled an impressive $97.6 million raised across Binance Smart Chain and <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana</a>, drawing support from over 20,000 users. PUNDU, introduced by the launchpad just days ago, swiftly captured investor interest, with contributions exchanging SOL and USDT for PUNDU allocations.</p>



<p>This success marks a milestone, establishing PUNDU&#8217;s presale as the largest for a meme coin. Most deposits originated from Binance Smart Chain, amassing $60 million. However, the Solana presale address also saw substantial activity. It received 212,404 SOL, equivalent to $37.6 million, surpassing the 33,333 SOL hard cap, highlighting the fervent <a href="https://beincrypto.com/crypto-traders-solana-base-meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">interest in meme coins within the Solana ecosystem.</a></p>



<p>While PUNDU awaits its launch date, the meme coin pledges a fair rollout, earmarking 40% of tokens for the presale, another 40% for liquidity pools, and distributing the remaining 10% equally between marketing efforts and long-term exchange listings.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/solana-platforms-buy/">6 Best Platforms To Buy Solana (SOL) in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>According to crypto investigator ZachXBT, Solana presales have raised more than 796,000 SOL, equivalent to around $149.20 million. Such mania urged Solana Labs Co-Founder Anatoly Yakovenko to <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">advise</a> investors to &#8220;stop&#8221; sending SOL presales.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;To me, it&#8217;s just a bizarre thing, I think, of people being terminally online and kind of having nothing better to do,&#8221; Yakovenko <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/podcasts/the-protocol/solana-its-meme-coin-craze-growth-and-vision-with-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Stop doing this. <a href="https://t.co/wY7E38MqYh">https://t.co/wY7E38MqYh</a></p>&mdash; toly <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@aeyakovenko) <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko/status/1770086226919575677?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 19, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Moreover, the frenzy surrounding meme coins led to the emergence of racist tokens. These <a href="https://beincrypto.com/racist-memecoins-condemnation/">meme coins, with offensive names, symbols, and imagery</a>, include racial slurs, anti-Semitic references, and Nazi imagery.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/solana-meme-coin-nears-100-million/">High-Risk Appetite Evident as PUNDU Meme Coin Raises $100 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BIC_Memecoins_rocket_shib_positive.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BIC_Memecoins_rocket_shib_positive.png"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
