<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bitcoinist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:04:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/cropped-cropped-cropped-Icon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">225283986</site>	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Buying Spree: Robert Kiyosaki Set To Buy 10 More BTC Before April&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/kiyosaki-set-to-buy-10-more-bitcoin-before-april/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godspower Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andy Schectman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[michael saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silver]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Acclaimed Author and Bitcoin bull Robert Kiyosaki has once again displayed his confidence in BTC, revealing his intentions of increasing his holdings as he predicts significant gains for the largest cryptocurrency asset. Robert Kiyosaki Targets Bitcoin At $100,000 Robert Kiyosaki reiterated his positive view on Bitcoin in a recent X post where he spelled out [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed Author and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-says-bitcoin-headed-to-1-5-m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a> bull Robert Kiyosaki has once again displayed his confidence in BTC, revealing his intentions of increasing his holdings as he predicts significant gains for the largest cryptocurrency asset.</p>
<h2>Robert Kiyosaki Targets Bitcoin At $100,000</h2>
<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/robert-kiyosaki-avocates-bitcoin-investment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Robert Kiyosaki</a> reiterated his positive view on Bitcoin in a recent X <a href="https://x.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1772115533502259692?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> where he spelled out his thoughts on the digital asset and disclosed his ambitions to purchase an additional 10 BTC before the month of April. The author cites the upcoming Bitcoin Halving event as the true motivation behind his plans to acquire 10 more BTC.</p>
<p>It is noteworthy that the highly anticipated <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-halving-could-bring-uncertainty-to-mining-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin halving</a> is anticipated to take place in less than 30 days from now. The event is believed to have the potential to be the next big trigger for the entire crypto market.</p>

<p>He further provided an accumulation strategy for investors who are concerned about affordability, suggesting, &#8220;If a buyer is unable to afford a whole BTC, they could want to think about purchasing 1/10 of the coin through Satoshi&#8217;s or the new ETFs.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>I am buying 10 more Bitcoin before April. Why?  The “Having.” If you can not afford a whole Bitcoin, you may want to consider buying 1/10 of a coin, via the new ETFs or Satoshi’s.</p></blockquote>
<p>According to Robert Kiyosaki, if the aforementioned strategy plays out very well, an investor could own an entire BTC by the end of the year. Kiyosaki is very bullish about the leading crypto asset as he expects BTC to hit the $100,000 threshold by September this year.</p>
<p>He also advocates acquiring Silver coins, especially the United States silver eagles, if an investor is not interested in BTC. His friend Andy Schectman claims that the silver supply, which was formerly plentiful, is almost depleted. The reasons behind this is that China&#8217;s real estate market is toast, and smart money is aware that the US is the world&#8217;s biggest debtor nation. </p>
<p>Additionally, since 1990, Japan has been undergoing a depression; Germany is also experiencing one; mom-and-pop consumers are surviving solely on credit cards; banks are having troubles; and global conflict looms. </p>
<p>As a result, Kiyosaki is urging investors to consider investing in silver in order not to be poor given the current <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/robert-kiyosaki-safeguard-your-wealth-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">economic uncertainty</a> around the world today.</p>
<h2>Investing In Fiat Currencies Is Not A Smart Idea</h2>
<p>Fiat currencies, sometimes considered fake money, are dangerous to save with, according to Kiyosaki and his associates Andy Schectman and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/good-things-on-the-way-for-bitcoin-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Michael Saylor</a>. This simply suggested that investing in fiat currencies is not a smart move, and those engaging in the act are bound to end up poor in the future.</p>

<p>Thus, they advise everyone to invest in either silver, gold, or Bitcoin, citing that silver is the most affordable among these assets, and nearly everyone in the world can afford one silver coin or BTC Satoshi. &#8220;Coin prices for Bitcoin, Gold, and Silver are approximately $70,000, $2,500, and $35.00, respectively,&#8221; Kiyosaki added.</p>
<img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/bQtrJeLS/" alt="Bitcoin" width="2273" height="1351" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/iStock-1252711675.jpg?fit=640%2C330" width="640" height="330" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289365</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Battle Of Titans: Bitcoin Leads S&#038;P 500, Michael Saylor Asserts Amid Disagreement</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-leads-sp-500-michael-saylor-asserts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[michael saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Schiff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The allure of Bitcoin continues to spark debate, with proponents touting its skyrocketing value and critics warning of a potential bubble. This weekend, a prominent crypto advocate and CEO, Michael Saylor, reignited the discussion by showcasing Bitcoin&#8217;s impressive gains compared to traditional assets. Related Reading: SEC Chair Gary Gensler Says Crypto Industry Needs ‘Disinfectant’ – [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:304">The allure of Bitcoin continues to spark debate, with proponents touting its skyrocketing value and critics warning of a potential bubble. This weekend, a prominent crypto advocate and CEO, Michael Saylor, reignited the discussion by showcasing Bitcoin&#8217;s impressive gains compared to traditional assets.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:326"><strong>Bitcoin Debate: Saylor Vs. Schiff</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:326">Saylor, the chairman of MicroStrategy, a business intelligence firm, shared a chart highlighting the leading crypto&#8217;s over 430% growth against a backdrop of more modest gains from established investment options like the S&amp;P 500 (56%) and gold (7%). This, according to Saylor, underscores Bitcoin&#8217;s position as a dominant investment force.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> is Winning. <a href="https://t.co/3ESQRHKEDa" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/3ESQRHKEDa</a></p>
<p>— Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1771638958906110426?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:440">However, not everyone is convinced. Renowned economist Peter Schiff, a vocal critic of cryptocurrencies, remains unconvinced. He expressed concern over Saylor&#8217;s aggressive investment strategy, particularly MicroStrategy&#8217;s recent acquisition of over 9,000 BTCs. Schiff emphasizes the inherent volatility of digital currencies, highlighting the potential for significant losses, especially considering MicroStrategy&#8217;s leveraged purchases.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">MicroStrategy has acquired an additional 9,245 BTC for ~$623.0M using proceeds from convertible notes &amp; excess cash for ~$67,382 per <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#bitcoin</a>. As of 3/18/24, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MSTR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$MSTR</a> hodls 214,246 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$BTC</a> acquired for ~$7.53B at average price of $35,160 per bitcoin. <a href="https://t.co/oeYJGgiuy0" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/oeYJGgiuy0</a></p>
<p>— Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1770061111146033385?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 19, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:461"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-289357" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_8a90a8.png?resize=403%2C224" alt="" width="403" height="224" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:461">Saylor, however, remains <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/michael-saylor-to-buy-bitcoin-forever-details/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">unfazed by the recent price dip</a> (nearly 12%) following Bitcoin&#8217;s record high. He views volatility as a natural market phenomenon, even coining the phrase &#8220;volatility is vitality&#8221; to emphasize its role in a healthy market. This confidence extends to MicroStrategy&#8217;s investment strategy. The company has significantly increased its holdings, now totaling over 214,000 BTC, showcasing their long-term faith in the digital currency.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:355">The contrasting views of Saylor and Schiff represent the ongoing debate surrounding Bitcoin. Proponents like Saylor point to its historical growth trajectory and its potential to disrupt traditional financial systems. They believe the digital asset&#8217;s limited supply (21 million coins will ever be mined) makes it a valuable hedge against inflation, similar to gold.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:355"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/vWYGx9uW/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="13:1-13:404"><strong>Risks And Regulations</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:404">However, skeptics like Schiff highlight the risks associated with <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTC price fluctuations.</a> Unlike established assets with underlying fundamentals like company performance or resource scarcity, Bitcoin&#8217;s value relies heavily on speculation and market sentiment. A sudden shift in investor confidence could trigger a dramatic price drop, leading to significant losses for investors like MicroStrategy.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:291">Further complicating the picture is the evolving regulatory landscape surrounding cryptocurrencies. Governments worldwide are still grappling with how to regulate this new asset class. Stringent regulations could stifle innovation and adoption, potentially hindering Bitcoin&#8217;s future growth.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:306"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1fb6c5.jpg?fit=640%2C360" width="640" height="360" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289324</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Tomorrow (March 26) Will Be Pivotal For Ripple And XRP</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/march-26-pivotal-for-ripple-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289305</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the XRP lawsuit, the next crucial phase is set to commence for Ripple Labs against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) tomorrow. Defense lawyer James K. Filan has recently casted the spotlight on March 26. The SEC has already submitted its opening remedies-related brief along with supporting documentation, albeit under seal, to the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the XRP lawsuit, the next crucial phase is set to commence for Ripple Labs against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) tomorrow. Defense lawyer James K. Filan has recently casted the spotlight on March 26.</p>
<p>The SEC has already submitted its opening remedies-related brief along with supporting documentation, albeit under seal, to the court. This step is a significant progression in the protracted legal dispute that has spanned several years. Filan&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/FilanLaw/status/1771316749641687403" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statement</a> via X emphasizes the forthcoming public disclosure of these documents, slated for no later than March 26, 2024.</p>

<p>&#8220;The SEC has filed, under seal, its opening remedies-related brief and supporting documents. These documents are not public yet. Public, redacted versions will be filed no later than Tuesday, March 26, 2024,&#8221; Filan communicated, highlighting the importance of this date in the context of the Ripple vs. SEC case.</p>
<h2>Ripple Vs. SEC: What To Expect</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s crucial to understand the nature and significance of an &#8220;opening remedies-related brief.&#8221; This document represents a foundational element in the litigation process. Essentially, the opening remedies-related brief is the initial submission by a party—in this instance, the SEC—outlining the specific legal and financial remedies it seeks from the court against the opposing party, Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>The amount of remedies that the SEC is demanding is eagerly awaited. In particular, it will be interesting to see how much the SEC demands for the institutional XRP sales after the start of the legal dispute.</p>
<p>As Bitcoinist <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-victory-ripple-disclosure-financial-statements/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a>, US District Judge Analisa Torres has ordered Ripple to provide its financial statements from 2022-2023 and contracts about <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-settlement-rumors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">“Institutional Sales” of XRP</a> in February, which the SEC argues are essential for determining an appropriate remedy.</p>

<p>Despite Ripple&#8217;s assertion that details regarding its financial health are both irrelevant to the case and highly confidential, the court has found such information potentially significant to the remedy stage of the proceedings. In its motion, the SEC contended that access to the company&#8217;s financial data is crucial for establishing the scale and nature of penalties and remedies that should be applied.</p>
<p>Just a few days ago, Ripple Labs and the SEC <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-agreement-schedule/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">presented</a> a detailed schedule for the remedies phase to the Southern District Court of New York. This agenda outlines the procedures for sealing and redacting court documents pertinent to the remedies phase of the lawsuit—a critical aspect of the proceedings that will determine the legal and financial repercussions for Ripple Labs</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>March 22, 2024:</strong> The SEC filed its remedies brief under seal.</li>
<li><strong>March 25, 2024:</strong> A meeting between the SEC and Ripple to discuss and finalize the necessary redactions is happening today.</li>
<li><strong>March 26, 2024:</strong> The SEC&#8217;s deadline to file a public, redacted version of its opening brief.</li>
<li><strong>April 22, 2024:</strong> Ripple&#8217;s deadline to file its opposition brief.</li>
<li><strong>April 23-24, 2024:</strong> A planned meeting to finalize redactions for Ripple&#8217;s documents. If necessary Ripple will file a public, redacted version of its opposition brief.</li>
<li><strong>May 8, 2024:</strong> The SEC&#8217;s deadline for the public submission of its reply brief.</li>
</ul>
<p>The provided timeline offers clarity on the immediate procedural steps. Despite this clarity, there remains a level of uncertainty regarding the ultimate resolution of the case. Speculation about potential delays persists, particularly concerning whether the SEC may request an extension.</p>
<p>At press time, XRP traded at $0.63218.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-289307" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472" alt="XRP price" width="1024" height="472" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=3628 3628w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=1536 1536w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=2048 2048w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=1140 1140w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XRPUSD_2024-03-25_07-55-22.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/08.2023.SEC_Ripple.1000px.v2.jpg?fit=640%2C415" width="640" height="415" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289305</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu’s Shibarium Hits New Record Amid Chaotic Market Movements</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-hits-new-record-amid-chaotic-market-movements/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 18:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shibarium, Shiba Inu’s layer-2 solution, recently reached an all-time high total value locked (TVL) of over $3.67 million. As if the current bullish sentiment around the Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem isn&#8217;t enough, its layer-2 solution has now reached a milestone that could lead to a further price surge.  Related Reading: SEC Chair Gary Gensler Says Crypto [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shibarium, Shiba Inu’s layer-2 solution, recently reached an all-time high total value locked (TVL) of over $3.67 million. As if the current bullish sentiment around the Shiba Inu&#8217;s ecosystem isn&#8217;t enough, its layer-2 solution has now reached a milestone that could lead to a further price surge. </p>

<p>According to data from <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Shibarium" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DeFiLlama</a>, the total value locked on Shibarium jumped from $1.43 million on March 22 to $3.38 million on March 23, sparking optimism about SHIB’s price.</p>
<h2><b>Shibarium TVL Surges To New Milestone</b></h2>
<p>Shibarium’s total value locked hitting a new high shows the network effect in action. Interestingly, data shows Shibarium&#8217;s TVL has spent most of the year below $1 million before crossing over in late February. However, the TVL stands at $3.67 at the time of writing, revealing a positive change in the ecosystem. </p>
<p>The recent surge in TVL can be particularly attributed to the launch of the DAMN token on WoofSwap, which is a decentralized exchange built on the Shibarium. DAMN quickly gained attention as one of the hottest cryptocurrencies after its launch on March 18. </p>
<p>According to data from <a href="https://www.shibariumscan.io/stats" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shibariumscan</a>, this frenzy led to a surge in the number of daily active users to 2,482 on the day of its launch. Similarly, WoofSwap&#8217;s TVL has grown by 8,988% in the past seven days. </p>
<p>Another catalyst for the surge in TVL was the launch of KNINE tokens, a liquid staking solution on the Shibarium blockchain.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/IdmMEKDj/" width="2475" height="1163" /></p>

<h2><b>What’s Next For Shiba Inu?</b></h2>
<p>Naturally, Shibarium’s recent milestones have sparked <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-soars-10-in-reaction-to-explosive-2367-shib-burn-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">optimism about SHIB’s price</a> as the cryptocurrency is well known to react to updates about the layer-2 network. This growth shows that Shibarium is attracting more users, which could boost SHIB’s price. </p>
<p>Shibarium&#8217;s new milestone saw SHIB rallying 8.8% to $0.00002828 in less than 24 hours. This price rally highlights the close correlation between the growth of Shibarium and the SHIB price.</p>
<p>SHIB is trading at $0.00002806 at the time of writing. The cryptocurrency is in fact, still riding on the back of a 193% gain in the past 30 days <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-short-term-holders/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">despite being 37% down</a> from its $0.00004456 earlier in the month. </p>

<p>On-chain metrics and investor sentiment point to a continued price surge in the near future. On-chain analytics platform Santiment recently pointed out that Bitcoin, along with SHIB and other meme coins, remained the focus of traders throughout the weekend. SHIB, which naturally has a <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">strong price correlation</a> with Bitcoin, could <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-market-cap-price-surgeretesting-2021-highs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reignite a surge in tandem</a>.</p>
<p>According to Lucie, Shiba Inu&#8217;s marketing lead, the price of SHIB could <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-rise-250-pre-bitcoin-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">surge by 250%</a> before the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-halving-could-bring-uncertainty-to-mining-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">next Bitcoin halving</a> which is slated to occur in April.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_957668.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289288</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investment Genius Cathie Wood Says Bitcoin Is Headed To $1.5 Million &#8211; Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-says-bitcoin-headed-to-1-5-m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARK Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289225</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ark Invest CEO Cathie Wood has reiterated her bullish stance on Bitcoin. The investment mogul, who recently disclosed she allocated 25% of her wealth into Bitcoin, has now predicted the cryptocurrency is on a highway to new highs.  Related Reading: Crypto In The Spotlight: Estonia Greenlights Regulation Bill Particularly, Wood called Bitcoin a “financial super [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ark Invest CEO Cathie Wood has reiterated her <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/cathie-wood-bitcoin-gold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish stance</a> on Bitcoin. The investment mogul, who recently disclosed she <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-placed-25-wealth-bitcoin-bold-unveiled/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">allocated 25% of her wealth</a> into Bitcoin, has now predicted the cryptocurrency is on a highway to new highs. </p>

<p>Particularly, Wood called Bitcoin a “financial super highway,” amidst discussions of its importance in emerging markets. As a result, she reiterated that the price of Bitcoin could end up as high as $3.8 million.</p>
<h2><b>Cathie Wood Reiterates Bullish Stance On Bitcoin</b></h2>
<p>Wood made her <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-bitcoin-is-king-of-security/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">very bullish prediction</a> at a Friday Bitcoin Investor Day conference in New York. Interestingly, this recent prediction surpasses another one made in January where she predicted that the digital asset <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-sees-bitcoin-at-1-5m-by-2030/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">could potentially hit $1.5 million</a> by 2030. This means Bitcoin could increase by another $2.3 million after reaching her existing target. </p>
<p>Wood credits this price growth to a major shift in the global market dynamics as Bitcoin continues to receive adoption, especially in developing countries. She made a case of Nigeria, whose struggle with unprecedented inflation in recent times has pushed its citizens to run to cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin to hedge against inflation. </p>
<p>“There are signals that not all is well in the world,” she said.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Wood revealed that Ark Invest, her investment company, has now <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/ark-invest-pivots-to-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">diverted most of its attention</a> into emerging markets such as this. She also noted that Bitcoin could continue on a price surge as institution interest continues to rise and institutions start to allocate a little more than 5% of their portfolio to the cryptocurrencies. </p>
<p>At the same time, Wood believes the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s recent greenlight for institutional investment in Bitcoin is a huge driving force for its growth to $3.8 million.</p>
<p>“We think Bitcoin has miles to go,” Wood said.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Ju7s87Iy/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><b>What’s Next For Bitcoin?</b></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $64,256, up by 25% in the past 30 days. Most of Bitcoin&#8217;s price growth in the past few months has been centered around the launch of Spot Bitcoin ETFs in the US. Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest was one of the Bitcoin ETF issuers approved by the SEC and has done relatively well since then. These ETFs have now received a total net flow of $11.269 billion since their launch.</p>

<p>Bitcoin, however, is <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-long-term-holders-price-top-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">currently struggling</a> with its price surge. The crypto is now down 12% from an all-time high of $73,780 which it <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">attained earlier in the month</a>. At the same time, Spot Bitcoin ETFs witnessed <a href="https://x.com/BitMEXResearch/status/1771465855680823612?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">consecutive days of outflows</a> last week amidst the price struggle. On the other hand, Bitcoin continues to <a href="https://x.com/santimentfeed/status/1771358045098086909?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">attract bullish sentiment</a> from investors and the cryptocurrency could resume its price surge very soon. </p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_585683.jpg?fit=640%2C391" width="640" height="391" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289225</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Bytes To Bites: Iceland Prioritizes Food Over Crypto Mining</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/iceland-prioritizes-food-over-crypto-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agriculture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[green energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iceland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Iceland, the volcanic island nation famed for its stunning landscapes and clean energy production, is embarking on a new chapter. In a move that highlights a growing global trend, The country is shifting its focus from supporting the cryptocurrency mining industry towards bolstering domestic food production. Iceland Pivots: From Crypto To Crops This strategic decision, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:475">Iceland, the volcanic island nation famed for its stunning landscapes and clean energy production, is embarking on a new chapter. In a move that highlights a growing global trend, The country is<a href="https://bitperfect.pe/en/iceland-pm-sways-energy-use-away-from-crypto-mining-to-agriculture/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> shifting its focus</a> from supporting the cryptocurrency mining industry towards bolstering domestic food production.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="3:1-3:475"><strong>Iceland Pivots: From Crypto To Crops</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:475">This strategic decision, driven by a desire for increased food security and a more balanced energy grid, positions Iceland for a greener and more self-sufficient future.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:414">Prime Minister Katrín Jakobsdóttir spearheaded this shift, citing the need to prioritize sectors with a more direct impact on national well-being. While crypto mining has played a role in our renewable energy sector, stated Jakobsdóttir, they recognize the importance of a balanced and sustainable approach. By prioritizing food production, the government ensures its constituents have access to a secure and reliable food supply.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:414"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-289266" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_335c72.png?resize=523%2C290" alt="" width="523" height="290" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>


<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:393">Iceland&#8217;s abundance of geothermal and hydroelectric power plants has made it a global leader in renewable energy production per capita. This same clean energy has also fueled the rise of <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6432a24b-b7c4-4c2f-85a8-79108dbe0644" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">crypto mining operations</a> within the country. However, concerns surrounding the environmental impact of crypto mining, coupled with a desire for greater food independence, have prompted this strategic pivot.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:473">The move towards domestic food production presents a multitude of benefits for the country. Increased agricultural output will not only bolster food security but also create new jobs and stimulate the local economy.</p>












<h2><strong>Renewable Energy And Agriculture</strong></h2>
<p>Furthermore, this shift creates an opportunity to expand the reach of Iceland&#8217;s robust renewable energy grid. By supplying clean energy to a wider range of agricultural operations, the country can ensure a more sustainable and efficient food production system.</p>












<p>According to Jakobsdóttir, the energy demands of the country&#8217;s 375,000 citizens should take precedence over data centres and instead use precious renewable electricity for homes and other sectors.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:473"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3XxLQse5/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

























<p>“Bitcoin is an issue worldwide . . . but data centers in Iceland use a significant share of our green energy,” the prime minister said. A new proposal to boost wind power would put more premium on clean industries to achieve carbon neutrality, she added.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:372">The transition to a larger-scale food production industry, however, is not without its challenges. Iceland&#8217;s harsh climate and limited arable land necessitate innovative solutions.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:372">Experts believe that advancements in controlled-environment agriculture (CEA) technologies, such as hydroponics and vertical farming, will play a crucial role in overcoming these limitations.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:378">The impact of this decision on existing crypto mining operations in Iceland remains to be seen. While some operations may choose to relocate, others might adapt by utilizing more energy-efficient mining practices. Regardless, Iceland&#8217;s strategic shift signifies a growing global conversation about the responsible use of resources and the importance of long-term sustainability.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:364">By prioritizing food security and a robust domestic agricultural sector, Iceland is charting a course for a greener and more self-sufficient future. This decision serves as a model for other nations grappling with similar challenges, demonstrating the potential of clean energy to not only power a digital future but also cultivate a more sustainable food system.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:364"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_6926ee.jpg?fit=640%2C360" width="640" height="360" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289221</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin ETF Buzz In UK: Kraken Executive Pushes For Market Access</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-buzz-in-uk-kraken-executive-pushes-for-market-access/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The simmering debate over Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the UK has reignited, with industry leaders calling for wider access for investors. This comes on the heels of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving Bitcoin ETFs in January, sparking a surge in investment and renewed calls for a similar move by the UK&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:374">The simmering debate over Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the UK has reignited, with industry leaders calling for wider access for investors. This comes on the heels of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving Bitcoin ETFs in January, sparking a surge in investment and renewed calls for a similar move by the UK&#8217;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:335"><strong>UK&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF Advocacy</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:335">Bivu Das, Managing Director of Kraken UK, believes Bitcoin ETFs offer a &#8220;basic fundamental&#8221; for establishing the UK as a true crypto hub. These instruments allow investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements without directly owning the cryptocurrency itself, potentially offering a more regulated and accessible entry point.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ICYMI: Kraken UK Managing Director Bivu Das says he&#8217;d &#8220;absolutely&#8221; like to see a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> ETF in the UK, providing regulated access to crypto exposure currently lacking and boost UK&#8217;s crypto hub ambitions, and legitimize bitcoin for institutions.</p>
<p>— AP Crypto (@AP_Crypto_) <a href="https://twitter.com/AP_Crypto_/status/1771514821940547931?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:306">However, the FCA remains cautious. In 2021, they banned the retail sale of crypto-derivative products, including exchange-traded products (ETPs) backed by cryptocurrencies. This stance, some argue, puts the UK at a disadvantage compared to the US, where retail investors can readily invest in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-alert-analyst-issues-major-warning/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin ETFs.</a></p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:271">Das contends that the regulatory landscape has evolved since the 2021 ban. He believes ETFs could even alleviate some regulatory concerns, as investors wouldn&#8217;t directly hold the underlying Bitcoin. This could potentially pave the way for a more open approach from the FCA.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:271"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WjE9FkAe/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:271">There are signs the FCA might be inching towards a more accommodating stance. They recently approved the launch of crypto ETNs, but only for institutional investors. This move, while limited, could be seen as a cautious step towards wider crypto investment opportunities.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:288">While the regulatory body remains cautious, warning of potential risks for retail investors in the volatile crypto market, the FCA&#8217;s recent actions suggest a willingness to explore the space further.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="15:1-15:269"><strong>Expanding UK&#8217;s Investment Options</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:269">Coinbase UK CEO, Daniel Seifert, echoes Das&#8217; sentiment. He believes &#8220;consumers have more options&#8221; with a wider range of investment products like ETFs. This push for increased investor choice aligns with a broader trend towards democratizing access to financial markets.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:367">However, the FCA faces a delicate balancing act. While fostering innovation in the crypto sector is crucial for maintaining the UK&#8217;s financial competitiveness, protecting retail investors from potential harm remains a top priority. The high volatility of the crypto market raises concerns about the suitability of such complex instruments for inexperienced investors.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:369">The recent influx of billions into US<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Bitcoin</a> ETFs highlights the growing investor appetite for these products. This surge in demand could put further pressure on the FCA to revisit its stance. The potential benefits of increased investment and a more robust crypto ecosystem could outweigh the perceived risks, eventually leading to a more open regulatory environment.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:527">The future of Bitcoin ETFs in the UK remains uncertain. The FCA is likely to take a measured approach, carefully evaluating the potential benefits and risks before making any significant changes. However, the growing global acceptance of Bitcoin ETFs, coupled with increasing investor demand, suggests that a more open approach from the FCA might be inevitable.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:527"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_a28a48.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289193</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Bitcoin Miners Move Old Equipment Overseas &#8211; Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/us-bitcoin-miners-move-old-equipment-overseas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bloomberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethiopia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin halving, one of the most anticipated crypto events in 2024, is less than a month away, and miners seem to be in full preparation for its aftermath. The April event is expected to slash mining rewards on the Bitcoin network in half, making the validation of transactions less lucrative. As of now, miners [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin halving, one of the most anticipated crypto events in 2024, is less than a month away, and miners seem to be in full preparation for its aftermath. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-halving-could-bring-uncertainty-to-mining-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">April event is expected to slash mining rewards on the Bitcoin network in half</a>, making the validation of transactions less lucrative.</p>
<p>As of now, miners receive 6.25 BTC for each validated block added to the network. However, the halving will split their revenue to 3.125 BTC for each block. Interestingly, many miners in the United States seem to be making adjustments, including upgrading to more efficient mining computers, to ensure they remain profitable.</p>
<h2>Why Bitcoin Mining Machines Are Being Moved Out Of The US</h2>
<p>According to crypto-mining services and logistics provider Luxor Technology, about 600,000 S19 series mining rigs, which account for a large proportion of machines currently in use in the United States, are being moved out of the country. The mining computers are being transferred (or sold) primarily to countries in Africa and South America, a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-23/bitcoin-halving-spurs-exodus-of-old-us-mining-computers-abroad" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bloomberg report</a> revealed.</p>

<p>The S19 series are older models of Bitcoin mining machines, and they might not be cost-efficient to run in countries like the US, where energy costs are relatively high. <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-halving-havoc-only-a-few-miners-may-survive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">This explains why the miners in the country</a> are ditching the older computers for more efficient ones.</p>
<p>The report quoted another major player in the Bitcoin mining industry, saying that while the S19 series and similar models might not be cost-effective to operate in the United States, they “can still generate decent profits and get an extended life if hosted” in certain regions in Africa.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, some miners opt to sell their hardware, with buyers of the old machines operating in parts of the world with cheap power. Many of these buyers are from Paraguay, Uruguay, Tanzania, and, most notably, Ethiopia.</p>
<p>According to Luxor, the upcoming halving event has been influencing the behavior of buyers towards the purchase of old mining machines. “Some buyers are waiting until after the event to purchase older computers, assuming their prices will drop even more,” the company revealed.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">With the Bitcoin halving approaching, Luxor estimates that around 600,000 S19 bitcoin rigs, the majority of machines currently in use, are moving primarily out of the U.S. to places like Africa and South America, where energy is cheaper. The S19 can cost up to $11,500 per unit to…</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1771719313260712434?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Ethiopia: The Next Crypto Mining Hub?</h2>
<p>Ethiopia, a country located in the Horn of Africa, is forging a strong reputation for itself in the crypto and Bitcoin mining niche. As inferred earlier, a significant proportion of the old US machines are being transferred to the East African nation.</p>

<p>Ethiopia’s cheap electricity has been pinpointed as the major factor driving this development. The Bloomberg report revealed that electricity is about 3 cents per kWh in Ethiopia, while it ranges between <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ex-white-house-official-says-bitcoin-could-reach-170000-post-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">3 to 6 cents in the US</a>.</p>
<p>Earlier in February, Bloomberg disclosed that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-migration-chinese-miners-flock-to-ethiopia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Chinese crypto mining companies are increasing their investment in Ethiopia</a>. While China’s strict stance against cryptocurrency is believed to have played a role, Ethiopia’s cheap power seems to have played a bigger part in the firms’ move.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rBHhUwUm/" alt="Bitcoin" width="2174" height="1434" /></p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Mining.jpg?fit=640%2C420" width="640" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289178</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
