<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bitcoinist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 14:44:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/cropped-cropped-cropped-Icon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">225283986</site>	<item>
		<title>XRP Advocate Goes Big: $500,000 Pledged For Senate Campaign Vs. US Senator</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-advocate-goes-big-500000-pledged-for-senate-campaign-vs-us-senator/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 20:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Campaign]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a bold move, prominent lawyer and XRP proponent John Deaton has made a substantial $500,000 donation to his Senate campaign against incumbent US senator for Massachusetts, Elizabeth Warren. Deaton is presenting a Republican challenge to senator Warren, giving the prominent progressive her first serious, albeit still remote, opponent and setting up an election-season dispute [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a bold move, prominent lawyer and XRP proponent John Deaton has made a substantial $500,000 donation to his Senate campaign against incumbent US senator for Massachusetts, Elizabeth Warren.</p>
<p>Deaton is presenting a Republican challenge to senator Warren, giving the prominent progressive her first serious, albeit still remote, opponent and setting up an election-season dispute over cryptocurrencies.</p>

<h2><strong>Deaton&#8217;s Campaign Gains Momentum With Crypto Community Support</strong></h2>
<p>Deaton&#8217;s announcement has ignited a surge of support from the crypto community, with many prominent figures expressing their endorsement and willingness to contribute to his campaign.</p>
<p>Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson was among the first to step forward, donating the maximum allowable amount of $3,300. <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/elizabeth-warren-rallies-donors-marine-veteran-crypto-attorney-john-deaton-announces-senate-challenge" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Deaton&#8217;s campaign</a> has also embraced crypto donations, allowing supporters to contribute using various cryptocurrencies.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I put in $500K of my own money because I know I can win. Please help me get to $1 million by March 31. Donate traditionally or through Crypto because freedom is on the line. <a href="https://t.co/qgDX3PTWJQ" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/qgDX3PTWJQ</a></p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1768759999533334680?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 15, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2><strong>Deaton Confident In Victory, Cites Warren&#8217;s Vulnerabilities</strong></h2>
<p>Despite Warren&#8217;s long-standing presence in Massachusetts politics, Deaton exudes confidence in his ability to secure victory in the upcoming election.</p>
<p>He highlights several factors that indicate Warren&#8217;s vulnerability, including her low favorability ratings and the fact that a significant portion of eligible voters in Massachusetts are neither Democrats nor Republicans.</p>
<p>Deaton believes these factors, coupled with his strong support from the crypto community, give him a fighting chance to unseat the incumbent senator.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uB97CnpQ/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<strong>XRP Community Speculates On Deaton&#8217;s Potential Impact On Crypto Regulation</strong>
<p>While Deaton&#8217;s campaign primarily focuses on challenging Warren&#8217;s anti-crypto stance, the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">XRP</a> community is abuzz with speculation about the potential implications of his victory for the ongoing Ripple lawsuit.</p>
<p>Deaton&#8217;s extensive legal experience and vocal support for the crypto industry have led many to believe that his election could positively influence the outcome of the case.</p>
<p>However, it remains uncertain whether Deaton&#8217;s involvement in the Senate race will directly impact the Ripple lawsuit.</p>

<strong>Deaton&#8217;s Fundraising Efforts And Campaign Strategy</strong>
<p>To bolster his campaign&#8217;s financial resources, Deaton has set an ambitious goal of raising $1 million by March 31st. He has turned to his substantial social media following, primarily crypto enthusiasts, to contribute to the cause.</p>
<p>Deaton&#8217;s campaign strategy emphasizes the importance of freedom and the need for nonpartisan leadership in Washington that represents the interests of ordinary citizens.</p>
<p>He believes that his outsider status and willingness to challenge the status quo resonate with voters disillusioned with traditional politics.</p>
<strong>Media Attention And Recognition Of Deaton&#8217;s Challenge</strong>
<p>Deaton&#8217;s candidacy has garnered significant media attention, with outlets such as Fox Business recognizing him as a major challenger who poses a genuine threat to Warren&#8217;s re-election bid.</p>
<p>His campaign has successfully captured the public&#8217;s imagination, and his message of freedom and crypto advocacy has struck a chord with many voters.</p>
<p>As the race heats up, it remains to be seen whether Deaton&#8217;s grassroots campaign can overcome the challenges posed by Warren&#8217;s incumbency and political establishment support.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_5308c9.jpg?fit=504%2C420" width="504" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287549</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Whale Dumps Substantial Holdings On The Market &#8211; Here’s How Much</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287553</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Dogecoin (DOGE) whale recently offloaded significant portions of their DOGE holdings in an act of profit-taking. This action has negatively affected the meme coin’s price, which has been on a downward trend since then.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Partner Token Makes Waves On Leading US TV Station Dogecoin Whale Offloads 86 Million DOGE On-chain [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-tesla-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> whale recently offloaded significant portions of their <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whales-buy-up-doge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">DOGE holdings</a> in an act of profit-taking. This action has negatively affected the meme coin’s price, which has been on a downward trend since then. </p>

<h2><b>Dogecoin Whale Offloads 86 Million DOGE</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/dogecoin/b4feb230f7cf8d9e73562e41f7b8f1ec2c55df578f496b0babb706ce5114f667" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">On-chain data</a> shows that the crypto trader deposited 86 million DOGE into the crypto exchange Robinhood in an effort to profit from the meme coin’s recent price surge. The whale, however, looks to be bullish on the meme coin in the long term, as they have since repurchased a significant amount of DOGE and still hold a substantial amount of it. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, due to the size of such a sale, the price of Dogecoin has since dipped and is currently on a downward trend. Before now, Dogecoin and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coins-myro-wif/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">other meme coins</a> had led other altcoins, making significant gains in these past few weeks. As such, it is understandable that the Dogecoin whale in question seized the opportunity to take some profits.</p>
<p>This week has been one of profit-taking from the meme coin ecosystem. Bitcoinist <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-pepe-whales-sold/#:~:text=Whales%20Cash%20Out%20Big%20Time%20From%20Shiba%20Inu%20And%20PEPE&amp;text=Since%20then%2C%20on%2Dchain%20data,realized%20gain%20of%20%2448.105%20million." target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported</a> on Shiba Inu (SHIB) and PEPE whales that earned a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-realized-cap-sets-all-time-high-price-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">realized gain</a> of $48.105 million and $3.364 million from offloading their meme coin holdings. </p>
<p>This wave of profit-taking has partly contributed to the significant drop in the prices of the foremost meme coins, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-shiba-inu-drop-15/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">DOGE and SHIB</a>, with both crypto tokens down over 6% and 18% in the last seven days. </p>
<p>However, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coins-myro-wif/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana-based meme coins</a> have upheld the broader meme coin ecosystem, with these crypto tokens pulling astonishing numbers for crypto investors. Book of Meme (BOME) stands out, seeing the growth that it has recorded since launching just this week. It rose to a $1 billion market cap and has been listed on major crypto exchanges. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/xXpPvLxW/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><b>More Profit Taking From Meme Coin Traders</b></h2>
<p>On-chain analysis platform <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-pepe-whales-sold/#:~:text=Whales%20Cash%20Out%20Big%20Time%20From%20Shiba%20Inu%20And%20PEPE&amp;text=Since%20then%2C%20on%2Dchain%20data,realized%20gain%20of%20%2448.105%20million." target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Spot On Chain</a> revealed in an X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://x.com/spotonchain/status/1768821834412138522?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> a crypto trader who recently made millions of dollars from their <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-surge-0-000052/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB investment</a>. This trader had purchased 1.741 trillion SHIB (<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-0-0001-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">average price</a> of $0.000009272) for $16.146 million and sold all of them for $39.668 million (average price of $0.00002278), realizing a gain of $23.5 million. </p>

<p>This same trader is also said to have just realized $46.53 million in profits from FLOKI and BIGTIME. Meanwhile, Spot On Chain noted that smart traders, including MakerDAO founder Rune Christensen, have taken profits from SHIB in the past week, which has caused it to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-99-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">dip significantly</a>.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pixabay, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_100f74.webp?fit=640%2C405" width="640" height="405" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287553</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vanguard CEO Doubles Down On Anti-Bitcoin ETF Stance &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/vanguard-ceo-double-down-on-anti-bitcoin-etf-stance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vanguard]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287482</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Vanguard Chief Executive Officer Tim Buckley has once again reiterated the investment giant’s stance against the adoption of spot Bitcoin ETF. In a video release also featuring the company’s Chief Investment Officer Greg Davis, Buckley highlighted reasons backing Vanguard’s decision to be a non-partaker in the bubbling Bitcoin ETF market. Related Reading: US Political Candidates [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vanguard Chief Executive Officer Tim Buckley has once again reiterated the investment giant’s stance against the adoption of spot Bitcoin ETF. <a href="https://investor.vanguard.com/investor-resources-education/news/vanguards-perspective-on-bitcoin-etfs#modal-transcript" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">In a video release</a> also featuring the company’s Chief Investment Officer Greg Davis, Buckley highlighted reasons backing Vanguard’s decision to be a non-partaker in the bubbling Bitcoin ETF market.</p>

<h2>Bitcoin Too Volatile, Not Worthy Of Long-Term Investment: Vanguard Boss</h2>
<p>According to Buckley, Vanguard has been receiving numerous inquiries on the potential of the company finally offering a spot Bitcoin ETF. This development is quite unsurprising following the company’s prominent anti-crypto stance, which draws much attention due to its status as the second-largest asset manager in the world. </p>
<p>Following the historic approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs on January 10 by the US Securities and Exchange (SEC), Vanguard, alongside fellow investment firm Merrill Lynch were two major financial players to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/merrill-lynch-vanguard-says-no-to-spot-bitcoin-etfs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">deny access to these novel investment funds</a> inviting much criticism from their customers and industry figures such as <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/cathie-wood-vanguards-stance-terrible/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ark Invest’s CEO Cathie Wood. </a></p>
<p>Explaining Vanguard’s stance against offering Bitcoin ETFs, Buckley stated that the cryptocurrency operated as a speculative asset unsuitable for long-term investment and not in tandem with the company’s investment model. In buttressing this point, the Vanguard boss made reference to Bitcoin’s decline following a crash in the stock markets. </p>
<p>Buckley said: </p>
<blockquote><p>
Something like bitcoin is just too volatile and it&#8217;s not a store of value. It hasn&#8217;t been and it&#8217;s very volatile. When stocks got hammered in the recent crisis, bitcoin went right with them. And so it is speculative. Really tough to think about how it belongs in a long-term portfolio.</p></blockquote>
<p>
The Vanguard CEO also stated that they preferred to invest in assets with tangible “underlying cash flow” similar to stocks or bonds, a criteria they believe Bitcoin does not currently meet. In all, Buckley restated the investment company’s decision to abstain from spot Bitcoin ETF barring a change in the cryptocurrency’s asset class.
</p>

<h2>Bitcoin ETF Demand Surges On </h2>
<p>Amidst Vanguard’s conservative stance, some other asset managers have embraced spot Bitcoin ETFs, recognizing as they look to offer diverse investments catering to all their client’s unique needs. Most recently, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/4-bitcoin-etfs-get-nod-190-billion-wealth-manager/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">San Diego based financial firm Cetera</a> announced the adoption of four BTC ETFs as part of investment options.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Patient Capital, a $1.8 Billion asset manager<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/patient-capital-looks-to-invest-in-bitcoin-etfs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">, has petitioned</a> the SEC for approval to convert up to 15% of its holdings to Bitcoin ETFs. These developments are highly exciting for the crypto community as the launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs was expected to drive up institutional demand for the crypto’s largest asset. </p>
<p>So far, the spot Bitcoin ETFs have put on a stunning performance gaining a <a href="https://x.com/BitMEXResearch/status/1768556378858103064?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">total net flow of $11.95 billion</a> over the last two months of trading. Meanwhile, Bitcoin is currently trading at $69,260.35 as the crypto market leader attempts a market rebound following a price correction in the last two days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/anFazlXC/" alt="Vanguard" width="1479" height="893" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/what-is-an-etf.jpg?fit=560%2C420" width="560" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287482</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin: A &#8216;Decades-Long&#8217; Investment, CEO Says, Despite Recent Downturn</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-a-decades-long-investment-ceo-says-despite-recent-downturn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287525</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amidst the recent turbulence in the cryptocurrency markets, Bitcoin has once again proven its resilience, with industry experts advocating for a steadfast approach to weathering the storm. Related Reading: XRP Scores Regulatory Win: European Governance Institute Endorses Non-Security Status Bitcoin&#8217;s Rocky Ride Over the past 24 hours, Bitcoin has experienced a notable correction, shedding over [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amidst the recent turbulence in the cryptocurrency markets, Bitcoin has once again proven its resilience, with industry experts advocating for a steadfast approach to weathering the storm.</p>

<h2><strong>Bitcoin&#8217;s Rocky Ride</strong></h2>
<p>Over the past 24 hours,<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Bitcoin</a> has experienced a notable correction, shedding over 9% of its value, a significant downturn from its recent peak of $73,600. This correction has sent shockwaves throughout the broader crypto market, causing major altcoins to similarly plummet in value.</p>

<h2><strong>Navigating Market Volatility</strong></h2>
<p>In the face of this volatility, analysts like Kris Marszalek, CEO of Crypto.com, have stepped forward to provide guidance to investors.</p>
<p>Marszalek emphasizes the importance of adopting a long-term perspective when it comes to holding Bitcoin, advising against succumbing to panic amidst short-term fluctuations.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">&#8220;I think you would see a steady ramp-up, and that&#8217;s what we want. As the size of the market and the increasing liquidity happens, you will see lots of sudden moves,&#8221; said <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptocom?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@cryptocom</a> CEO <a href="https://twitter.com/kris?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">@kris</a> on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#BTC</a>. &#8220;This is an asset that you want to hold for decades, not for days or weeks.&#8221; <a href="https://t.co/GlMiDBEYKa" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/GlMiDBEYKa</a></p>
<p>— Squawk Box (@SquawkCNBC) <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1768604975737835605?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 15, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<strong>Understanding The Forces At Play</strong>
<p>Examining the reasons behind<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/24/03/37740013/bitcoin-bloodbath-digital-gold-loses-its-luster-but-are-investors-shaken-or-shopping" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Bitcoin&#8217;s recent rollercoaster ride,</a> Marszalek sheds light on the role of Bitcoin ETFs in propelling the cryptocurrency to new heights. These inflows have presented a supply-side challenge, contributing to the recent surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>However, he also points to the Options Market as a significant factor influencing the recent downturn, highlighting the complexities at play in the cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wqR5hgtW/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<strong>The Enduring Value Of Bitcoin</strong>
<p>During a recent appearance on CNBC’s Squawk Box, Marszalek shared his insights on Bitcoin&#8217;s enduring value amidst market volatility. He emphasized that Bitcoin is not a short-term investment but rather an asset to be held for decades, likening it to a digital gold standard.</p>
<p>This steadfast belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s enduring value echoes sentiments shared by many within the cryptocurrency community.</p>
<strong>Looking Ahead</strong>
<p>As Bitcoin continues to navigate the choppy waters of market volatility, analysts anticipate a gradual uptrend in its price trajectory.</p>
<p>Marszalek predicts that as the market matures and liquidity increases, sudden and drastic price movements will become less frequent, providing a more stable investment environment for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>While the recent correction in Bitcoin&#8217;s price may have rattled some investors, industry experts like Marszalek advocate for maintaining a steady hand and focusing on the long-term potential of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin continues to assert its position as a digital store of value, navigating market volatility with patience and foresight remains paramount for investors looking to capitalize on the opportunities presented by the burgeoning cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pixabay, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_27a281.webp?fit=640%2C366" width="640" height="366" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287525</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Unveils Bullish Prediction For Ethereum And XRP</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-analyst-bullish-on-ethereum-and-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A popular crypto analyst, identified as CrediBull Crypto on X (formerly Twitter) has unveiled bullish projections for both Ethereum and XRP. Doubling down on his previous XRP price prediction, the analyst has further affirmed that the cryptocurrency is poised to outperform Bitcoin and Ethereum in the upcoming 2024 bull run.  Related Reading: Shiba Inu Partner [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A popular crypto analyst, identified as CrediBull Crypto on X (formerly Twitter) has unveiled bullish projections for both <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/eth-price-prediction-2024-assessing-ethereums-potential-price-gain-in-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum</a> and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-prediction-rally-0-85/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP</a>. Doubling down on his previous XRP price prediction, the analyst has further affirmed that the cryptocurrency is poised to outperform Bitcoin and Ethereum in the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bull-run-2024-inevitable/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">upcoming 2024 bull run. </a></p>

<h2><b>Ethereum Set To Hit New All-Time Highs </b></h2>
<p>In a recent X post, CrediBull Crypto <a href="https://x.com/crediblecrypto/status/1766368033835044991?s=46" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">disclosed</a> insights on the next cryptocurrency to break out after Bitcoin. With BTC hitting its previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-skyrockets-past-71000-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">all-time highs above $71,000</a>, the analyst has suggested that Ethereum, the second largest cryptocurrency, is next in line to witness a significant rally. </p>
<p>According to the analyst, many crypto enthusiasts and investors are already anticipating a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-dips-3830/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">potential bullish break out</a> in the price of Ethereum. He disclosed that the majority of the crypto community is sharing a similar sentiment, hoping for <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-surge-3800/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Ethereum’s price</a> to consolidate between the range of $3,600 and $3,700. </p>
<p>Expressing confidence in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-price-prediction-2024-will-cancun-upgrade-ignite-an-upside-trend-for-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum’s price outlook</a>, the analyst has suggested that a surge to over 25% was well within reach before any notable <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-consolidation-3800/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pullback</a> occurred. He shared a chart of Ethereum’s recent price movements, highlighting the cryptocurrency’s apparent determination to enter a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-rallies-2650/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">major bullish position</a>. </p>
<p>“Ethereum wants new all-time highs,” the analyst <a href="https://x.com/crediblecrypto/status/1766005319765835941?s=46" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">wrote</a>, emphasizing the cryptocurrency’s fervent drive to surge to unprecedented heights. This bullish outlook is also underpinned by Ethereum’s robust fundamentals, bolstered further by its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/ethereum-outperforms-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">positive price performance</a> recently. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hsfynNpN/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><b>Crypto Analyst Remains Bullish On XRP </b></h2>
<p>In another X post, CrediBull Crypto <a href="https://x.com/crediblecrypto/status/1767425030286188785?s=46" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">unveiled</a> price predictions for XRP, reaffirming his initial <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-pay-attention-to-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">forecast in February 2024</a>, when he predicted that the price of XRP could achieve a 200% gain over Bitcoin. At the time, the analyst declared that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-xrp-is-poised-to-wildly-outperform-bitcoin-and-ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP was set to potentially outperform both Bitcoin and Ethereum</a> in “the coming days or weeks.”</p>
<p>The analyst confirmed in his recent post that technical indicators were currently aligning with his <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-to-skyrockets-to-1-33-amidst-april-rally-analysts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">bullish projections</a>, potentially signaling a confirmation of his previous <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-proponent-sees-xrp-crashing-to-0-01/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP price prediction</a>. He emphasized that the anticipated window of outperformance mentioned in his initial forecast was “right around the corner.”</p>
<p>This time around the crypto analyst has disclosed a bold target, <a href="https://x.com/crediblecrypto/status/1767443403975925855?s=46" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">projecting</a> a 250% gain against Bitcoin. With unwavering optimism, CrediBull Crypto <a href="https://x.com/crediblecrypto/status/1765442363961315559?s=46" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">anticipates</a> Ethereum soaring to new all-time highs, a sentiment underscored by his strategic move to bolster the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-holding-vs-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP holdings</a> in his portfolio. </p>

<p>At the time of writing, the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-will-remain-flat-even-if-bitcoin-roars/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">price of XRP</a> is reflecting a weekly uptick of 1.78%, standing at $0.639 on CoinMarketCap. The cryptocurrency has been steadily rising out of bearish trends, surging past critical price resistance levels at $0.5, and finally <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-is-primed-for-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">showing signs of a potential bullish rally in the upcoming bull market. </a></p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pixabay, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_18804e.webp?fit=420%2C420" width="420" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287523</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Should Receive A 50-Year Jail Sentence: Prosecutors</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-should-receive-50-year-jail/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX's Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SBF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The prosecutors in the fraud case against the former CEO of the now-defunct FTX exchange, Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), have now suggested a jail sentence to the court. This development comes as the sentencing of the former crypto billionaire is slated for later this month. Prosecutors Says Sam Bankman-Fried Deserves 50 Years In Prison According to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The prosecutors in the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-drops-bombshell-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fraud case against the former CEO of the now-defunct FTX exchange</a>, Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), have now suggested a jail sentence to the court. This development comes as the sentencing of the former crypto billionaire is slated for later this month.</p>
<h2>Prosecutors Says Sam Bankman-Fried Deserves 50 Years In Prison</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://courtlistener.com/docket/66631291/410/united-states-v-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">memorandum</a> submitted on Friday, March 15, to Judge Lewis Kaplan, the prosecutors are proposing a sentence of between 40 to 50 years for Bankman-Fried.  The FTX founder faces up to 100 years in prison after he was found guilty of all the seven fraud charges leveled against him. </p>

<p>The lawyers mentioned that SBF masterminded one of the largest fraudulent schemes in recent years, repeatedly comparing his actions to those of Bernie Madoff. Madoff was an American financier who allegedly ran the largest known Ponzi scheme in history, worth an estimated $65 billion.</p>
<p>Considering the magnitude and duration of<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Sam Bankman-Fried’s financial misdeeds</a>, the prosecutors believe a sentence of 40 to 50 years is “sufficiently severe” to deter others from committing such crimes. “And that will permit the defendant to return to liberty only after society can be assured that he will not have the opportunity to turn back to fraud and deceit,” they added.</p>
<p>The government’s attorneys also emphasized in the 116-page court document how remorseless the former FTX boss has been about his fraudulent activities. “Even now Bankman-Fried refuses to admit what he did wrong,” a part of the memorandum read.</p>
<p>Interestingly, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-fraud/#:~:text=Bankman%2DFried&#039;s%20Lawyers%20Propose%20A,six%20and%20a%20half%20years)." target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Sam Bankman-Fried’s legal counsel proposed to the court</a> that the defendant get a sentence between five years and six and a half years. According to the lawyers, the purpose of a jail term in SBF’s case should be rehabilitation and not punishment.</p>
<h2>Another Exchange In The Works?</h2>
<p>The prosecutors revealed to the court in their sentencing memorandum that Sam Bankman-Fried could launch a new cryptocurrency exchange, saying he had weighed starting an exchange called “Archangel LTD.”</p>
<p>According to the lawyers, the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-cites-autism-disorder/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">former FTX CEO also considered different options to launder his image</a>. Amongst the cited options were media and PR stunts, like “focus on the fact that the Chapter 11 team has no idea how to run FTX,” push a “pro crypto, pro freedom” agenda, or “go on Tucker Carlsen.”</p>

<p>Ultimately, the prosecutors concluded that Sam Bankman-Fried is deserving of a “severe sanction, proportionate to his role in this historic fraud.” A sentence of 40 to 50 years is believed to be the right perfect judgment in this case.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/z0Ccxoi4/" alt="Sam Bankman-Fried" width="2174" height="1434" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/Sam-Bankman-Fried-FTX.jpeg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287479</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Are Hong Kong Firms Preparing For Spot Bitcoin ETFs? OSL Exec Shares Details</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/how-are-hong-kong-firms-preparing-for-spot-bitcoin-etfs-osl-exec-shares-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubmar Garcia]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong Crypto Firm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot Ethereum ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[OSL Group executive Gary Tiu recently joined Bloomberg’s ‘The China Show’ to discuss the spot Bitcoin ETFs (Exchange-Traded Funds) landscape in Hong Kong. During the interview, Tiu also spoke about the prospect of a spot Ethereum ETFs launch in the future. Related Reading: Ethereum ETF Showdown: Hong Kong Plans To Launch First, Overtaking The US [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400;">OSL Group executive Gary Tiu recently joined Bloomberg’s ‘The China Show’ to discuss the spot Bitcoin ETFs (Exchange-Traded Funds) landscape in Hong Kong. During the interview, Tiu also spoke about the prospect of a spot Ethereum ETFs launch in the future.</p>

<h2 style="font-weight: 400;">When Are Spot Bitcoin ETFs Launching In Hong Kong?</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Gary Tiu, OSL’s Executive Director and Head of Regulatory Affairs, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7UuC5JpHv6U" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">spoke</a> with Yvonne Man and Annabelle Droulers about the digital asset firm’s expectation for spot Bitcoin ETFs in Hong Kong and the preparations regarding the investment products.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The executive shared a prediction of when the ETFs will be launched in the interview. Despite not giving an exact timeline, Tiu feels optimistic and considers that the initiatives on spot Bitcoin ETF “that are being talked about” will hit the market in the next few months.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">After the successful launch of ETFs in the US, interest in these products has soared from traditional investors and institutions. Some of the interest has been focused on other countries’ options to launch a Bitcoin ETF and whether the US regulator <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-senators-urge-sec-no-more-crypto-etfs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">will approve</a> other crypto-based Exchange-Traded Products.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Regarding the anticipation around the launch of a spot Ethereum ETF worldwide, the executive deems the race as “more interesting” since the product is yet to be approved in the US by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC):</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">I think there’s definitely a more global race on now for who can actually come to the market with the first product. A lot of the issues we talk about are sensitive to market timing. Being first to market is going to be critical for the players that are investing in that space.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400;">How Is The OSL Group Preparing For An ETF Launch?</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The OSL executive considers that there will be a lot of investor interest in Bitcoin ETFs if launched in Hong Kong. Based on US interests and developments, the digital asset company is taking note of the substantial effort that’s been put into the products and the infrastructure needed to “get an ETF out.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Moreover, Tiu commented on the readiness and broadness of Hong Kong’s ecosystem to advert a “concentration risk” as the legal framework for the ETFs will “rely on Hong Kong’s licensed companies.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The executive believes that OSL Group is ready as it has been operating for over three years as a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/regulatory-showdown-in-hong-kong-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">licensed platform</a>. Tiu highlights that OSL isn’t the only licensed company in the market.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">However, he considers that what’s most important for a successful ETF is a competitive landscape with incentivized market makers:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">So, I guess from another perspective, the ETF isn&#8217;t even just about the trading platforms that have to support the product. The market makers are the ones who support liquidity on the exchange. (…) We want market makers to be properly incentivized so that they can do very, very tight pricing on the exchange because really that&#8217;s how ETFs are distributed on the market.</p>
</blockquote>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the Head of Research commented on the general operating model that will differentiate the US ETFs from Hong Kong’s, considering that these differences will give them an edge regarding fees and execution costs:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The Hong Kong operating model will allow the fund to directly receive BTC from subscribers and to pay out crypto assets or bitcoin in the case of the first products to pay out bitcoin to the investors in the case of redemptions.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">So, this potentially does give the Hong Kong products a bit of an edge in terms of lowering execution costs. As opposed to having to always go into the market to buy, they can directly receive the bitcoin from investors.</p>
</blockquote>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Lastly, Tiu discussed the OSL Group state in the retail side of investments, acknowledging that the digital asset company has been “stronger” as an institutional platform.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Nevertheless, he highlighted that the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-shake-up-is-hong-kong-osl-exchange-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">recent</a> capital injection brought a new management team with extensive retail expertise, potentially allowing the company to launch a “quality retail platform.”</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-287441 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=980&#038;resize=980%2C493" alt="Bitcoin, BTCUSDT, BTC Bitcoin ETF" width="980" height="493" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=1022 1022w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=980&#038;resize=980%2C493 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=360 360w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSDT_2024-03-15_13-50-11.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/ruslan-bardash-WMSvsWzhM0g-unsplash.jpeg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287438</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Adopts Stricter Token-Listing Framework Amid Regulatory Headwinds</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/binance-implements-stricter-token-listing-procedure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, has reportedly introduced stricter requirements for listing new digital tokens. The move aims to strengthen investor protection against &#8220;rug pulls,&#8221; or fraudulent tokens, and address concerns about the alleged &#8220;lack of oversight&#8221; of token listings in the crypto industry.  According to Bloomberg, the changes began rolling [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, has reportedly introduced stricter requirements for listing new digital tokens. The move aims to strengthen investor protection against &#8220;rug pulls,&#8221; or fraudulent tokens, and address concerns about the alleged &#8220;lack of oversight&#8221; of token listings in the crypto industry. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-15/binance-extends-token-listing-cliff-period-requires-deposit-bnb" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Bloomberg, the changes began rolling out late last year, including a longer &#8220;cliff period&#8221; during which coins cannot be sold, increased allocation of coins to market makers, and the introduction of security deposits.</p>
<h2>Binance Extends &#8220;Cliff Period&#8221; To A Year</h2>
<p>During the cliff period, a portion of the total <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/nigeria-detains-binances-crypto-crime-investigator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">coin supply</a> is locked up in a smart contract, gradually releasing tokens according to a vesting schedule. Binance now requests projects to agree to cliff periods of at least a year, up from a maximum of six months. </p>
<p>The exchange also seeks a greater share of tradable tokens to be set aside for market makers to ensure sufficient liquidity.</p>
<p>Binance&#8217;s stricter rules have not yet impacted its share of spot crypto trading, as the platform has been recovering from a yearlong slide. The exchange has also maintained its lead in token listings among major exchanges. </p>

<p>However, some executives involved in listings on Binance have expressed concerns about the changes, citing potential <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-suspends-all-operations-in-nigeria/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">threats to profitability</a> and increased burdens associated with listing new tokens.</p>
<p>Binance&#8217;s recent emphasis on investor protections over attracting coin listings reflects its response to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-ceo-7-days-to-address-terrorism-financing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">regulatory pressure</a> and a commitment to prioritize user safety and security. </p>
<p>The crypto industry faces increasing scrutiny from regulators. Binance, which previously agreed to pay a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binances-4-3b-settlement-marks-crucial-shift/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$4.3 billion fine</a> for alleged money-laundering violations, aims to address regulatory concerns while maintaining its position in the market.</p>
<p>The new listing requirements are communicated verbally to participants and may vary between deals. Binance denies imposing lock-in periods for listed projects, stating that each project independently decides its token vesting schedule. The exchange confirms the introduction of security deposits, which can be withheld if listing conditions are unmet.</p>
<h2>Reward For Information On Corruption</h2>
<p>Token listings are crucial in boosting trading volumes and generating commissions for exchanges. Binance, under the leadership of CEO <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-ceo-affirms-no-changes-to-top-executives/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Richard Teng</a>, has extended its lead in coin listings this year, accounting for approximately 40% of the total across major marketplaces. </p>
<p>Teng, who succeeded co-founder <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-ceo-to-step-down-4-billion-settlement/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Changpeng Zhao</a> (CZ), aims to strengthen compliance efforts and collaborate more closely with global regulators.</p>

<p>Yi He, one of Binance&#8217;s co-founders, oversees overhauling the token listing process to address concerns over transparency and internal management. </p>
<p>According to Bloomberg, Yi He recently offered a reward for information about verified corruption among Binance staff and emphasized the importance of confidentiality within the team responsible for coin listings.</p>
<p>As the exchange tightens its token-listing requirements, it aims to balance fostering innovation and ensuring investor protection. The crypto industry continues to evolve in response to regulatory scrutiny, and exchanges like Binance are adapting their practices to meet <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-expands-crypto-custody-reach/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">emerging challenges</a>.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/BoIHOSu4/" alt="Binance" width="1815" height="858" />
<p>As of the current time, Binance Coin (BNB), the exchange&#8217;s native token, has rebounded to reach the $600 price level after experiencing a significant dip that briefly pushed the token down to $543. This sudden drop triggered liquidations totaling nearly $7 million within the past 24 hours, according to CoinGlass <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/currencies/BNB" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data</a>.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-6-7.jpg?fit=462%2C260" width="462" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287430</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
