<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bitcoinist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:02:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/cropped-cropped-cropped-Icon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">225283986</site>	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Turns Deep Red: Reason Behind Crash?</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-deep-red-reason-crash/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bearish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Coinbase Premium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Crash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Selling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase Premium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin Coinbase Premium has plunged into the red territory, which may explain why the asset&#8217;s price has crashed to under $68,000. Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index Has Turned Red As explained by the on-chain analytics firm CryptoQuant in a post on X, the BTC Coinbase Premium Index dropped into negative territory just hours [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows that Bitcoin Coinbase Premium has plunged into the red territory, which may explain why the asset&#8217;s price has crashed to under $68,000.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index Has Turned Red</h2>
<p>As explained by the on-chain analytics firm CryptoQuant in a <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptoquant_com/status/1768559376602722779" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, the BTC Coinbase Premium Index dropped into negative territory just hours before BTC went through its correction.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-shoots-up-what-45000-break/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Coinbase Premium Index</a>&#8221; here refers to an indicator that tracks the percentage difference between the Bitcoin prices listed on cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase (USD pair) and Binance (USDT pair).</p>

<p>When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is greater than on Binance right now. Such a trend implies that the users of the former platform are doing more buying than those of the latter.</p>
<p>On the other hand, negative values imply the presence of higher selling pressure on Coinbase since the price of the cryptocurrency on Binance is currently greater.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index over the past few days:</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GIsuetQX0AA7D_Z?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index" width="2310" height="1018" /></p>

<p>As the above graph shows, the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index had been positive earlier. Still, yesterday, the indicator dipped into the negative region and has since mostly remained inside it.</p>
<p>Alongside these red values of the metric, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price has taken a deep hit, as it has come back down to the $68,000 level. Given the close timing, the high selling pressure on Coinbase may have something to do with this drawdown.</p>
<p>Coinbase is popularly known to be the preferred platform of US-based institutional investors, while Binance has more global traffic, so the Premium Index&#8217;s value can reflect the difference in the behaviors of American whales and world users.</p>
<p>In this rally, the Coinbase Premium Index has generally remained positive as large US-based entities have accumulated. Given the change to red values, these investors may have now taken to selling instead, thus leading to the coin&#8217;s plunge.</p>

<p>This indicator could be worth watching in the coming days. If it turns back positive for a sustained period of time, it would be a sign that the buyers are back and with them, so it might be an uptrend.</p>
<p>Regarding the latest correction, smart-money tracker <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1768509208750965222" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Lookonchain</a> has pointed out that a Binance deposit wallet has moved BTC worth $329 million to a Binance hot wallet in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Interestingly, this same whale also moved a similar amount of Bitcoin back during the correction earlier in the month, as the below chart shared by the X user shows.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GIsBq1ja4AAE4b3?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Whale" width="2570" height="1188" /></p>

<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $68,100, down 4% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hF2PX0uy/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kanchanara-Lta5b8mPytw-unsplash.jpg?fit=631%2C420" width="631" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287409</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu: Google AI Reveals End Of Year Price Target For SHIB</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-google-ai-price-shib/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google Artificial Intelligence (AI) chatbot Gemini has provided key insights into the future price trajectory of Shiba Inu. The AI model has disclosed three potential price targets for SHIB by the end of 2024. SHIB Price Outlook By End Of The Year Gemini, Google’s most capable AI model has predicted the price of SHIB to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Google Artificial Intelligence (AI) chatbot Gemini has provided key insights into the future price trajectory of Shiba Inu. The AI model has disclosed three potential price targets for SHIB by the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bull-market-huge-bubble/">end of 2024.</a></p>
<h2>SHIB Price Outlook By End Of The Year</h2>
<p>Gemini, Google’s most capable AI model has predicted the price of SHIB to surge by the end of 2024. According to the chat bot, Shiba Inu could <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-0-0008-ath/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">potentially witness a massive rally</a>, pushing it to new all-time highs during this time line.</p>

<p>Sharing three distinct scenarios where Shiba Inu is set to experience a significant price rally, Gemini disclosed that SHIB could <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-breaks-2-month-downtrend/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">break past key resistance levels</a> to surge to $0.0002, shedding off a zero from its current price and reflecting a massive 410% surge. </p>
<p>In the second price outlook, the AI chatbot predicts that the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-0-0001-target/">price of SHIB could witness a surge to $0.0001</a>. This price increase would require SHIB to rally by at least 155%, taking advantage of market’s bullish trends and investor sentiment to push its price upwards. </p>
<p>The third and final price outlook by Google’s Gemini reveals a more <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-optimistic-about-a-shiba-inu-short-term-surge-to-0-000066/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">moderate price increase for SHIB.</a> According to the AI model, SHIB’s price is expected to surge to $0.00005 by December 2024. This price increase depicts a relatively low growth for the cryptocurrency, potentially signaling impending bearish trends in the future. </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Witnesses Major Price Correction</h2>
<p>Since the beginning of the year, the price of SHIB has been on an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/breakout-confirmed-shiba-inu-price-73-surge/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">upward momentum</a>, amassing significant gains that has further solidified its position in the crypto industry. The cryptocurrency has also <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-adoption-crypto-atm/">garnered a considerable amount of interest</a> from both investors and traders, successfully rising to the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-blasts-into-top-10/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">world’s top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization.</a></p>
<p>Despite various crypto analysts <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/why-shiba-inu-pepe-dogecoin-are-far-from-done/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">predicting that SHIB will maintain its bullish trajectory</a>, the cryptocurrency has been witnessing unexpected price declines lately. The price of SHIB experienced a significant drop below $0.00003, trading at $0.000029 at the time of writing, and reflecting a steep decline of 10.75% in the last 24 hours. </p>

<p>The cryptocurrency had previously experienced a price increase of approximately 205.66% over the past month. However, it seems <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-breaks-out-of-downtrend-big-gains-ahead/">bearish trends </a>may be taking over, as SHIB has been displaying mostly red candle sticks on its weekly price charts, according to CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p>While the reason for this unexpected price drop has not yet been determined, Shiba Inu is still on a relatively bullish path, which is evident in its previous price performance over the past few months. Moreover, Shiba Inu’s lead developer, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-lead-dev-shib-bull/">Shytoshi Kusama</a>, has also remained bullish on the doggy-themed meme coin, predicting that SHIB could potentially become the leading cryptocurrency in the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/meme-coin-season-top-meme-coins-for-10x-jump/">upcoming meme coin season. </a></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/RvVMIBkP/" alt="Shiba Inu price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Shiba-Inu-16.jpeg?fit=299%2C168" width="299" height="168" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287338</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Political Candidates Receive Ultimatum From Crypto Lobby: ‘Side With Us Or Risk Defeat At The Ballot Box’</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/us-political-candidates-ultimatum-from-crypto-lobby/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[total crypto market cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to a Bloomberg report, the crypto lobby in the United States has issued a stark warning to political candidates, demanding their support or risk defeat at the ballot box in the November 5, 2024, elections.  Citing the recent defeat of Democratic Representative Katie Porter in California&#8217;s Senate primary as evidence, the digital asset industry [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a Bloomberg report, the crypto lobby in the United States has issued a stark warning to political candidates, demanding their support or risk defeat at the ballot box in the November 5, 2024, elections. </p>
<p>Citing the recent defeat of Democratic Representative Katie Porter in California&#8217;s Senate primary as evidence, the digital asset industry points to its significant financial backing and influence on elections. </p>
<p>With sympathetic billionaires and a well-funded pro-crypto super political action committee (PAC), the industry aims to shape the political landscape in favor of cryptocurrency-friendly candidates.</p>
<h2>Industry Giants Pour $10M Into Securing Pro-Crypto Nominees</h2>
<p>Rich industry players have reportedly contributed $10 million to advertising and get-out-the-vote efforts that allegedly helped defeat Katie Porter in the open primary. That outcome paved the way for fellow Democrat Adam Schiff, perceived as more pro-crypto, to secure the nomination, the report noted. </p>

<p>According to the report, the lobby plans to use Porter&#8217;s loss as an example to pressure other vulnerable Democratic allies, warning that aligning with crypto critic Senator <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sen-warrens-pushing-cbdc-to-crush-bitcoin-existence/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Elizabeth Warren</a> could make their reelection campaigns more difficult.</p>
<p>Digital asset advocates have reportedly garnered significant financial support from sympathetic billionaires and industry leaders. The pro-crypto Super PAC, Fairshake, has amassed a “war chest” of approximately $75 million for use in the US elections. </p>
<p>Notable backers include <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/is-ripple-leaving-the-united-states/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Coinbase </a>CEO Brian Armstrong, Gemini exchange founders Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, and Marc Andreessen of Andreessen Horowitz. With significant resources, the lobby aims to influence political outcomes and promote candidates who support the industry&#8217;s interests.</p>
<h2>Balancing Innovation And Regulation</h2>
<p>The digital asset industry faces legislative proposals to combat illicit finance, with <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sen-warren-crypto-bitcoin-crackdown-gains-support/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">some bills</a> seeking to apply anti-money laundering rules to crypto firms. Groups like the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/blockchain-association-backs-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Blockchain Association</a> and the Chamber of Digital Commerce argue that such requirements would be “unworkable” and potentially “fatal” for the industry in the US. </p>
<p>While criminal networks have exploited cryptocurrencies for illicit activities, the industry emphasizes the need for balanced regulation that addresses concerns without stifling innovation.</p>
<p>Bloomberg observes that the crypto industry&#8217;s growing political influence represents a significant shift from when it faced scandals and business failures a year ago. </p>

<p>Despite <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-commissioner-crypto-regulation-enforcement/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">regulatory scrutiny</a> and challenges in establishing practical use cases for the technology, the industry has rebounded and now wields financial clout. Lawmakers recognize the industry&#8217;s ability to pour millions of dollars into races, making it a force to be reckoned with in the political arena.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/O3PmfwAn/" alt="Crypto" width="1815" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-6-6.jpg?fit=390%2C260" width="390" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287419</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Expert Says Mainstream Demand Will Come For Crypto When Dogecoin Does This</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-when-dogecoin-does-this/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto expert]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expert]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287336</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto expert Scott Melker, also known as the ‘Wolf of All Streets,” has laid down a theory of when mainstream demand for crypto will return in this bull market. Interestingly, his theory revolved around the foremost meme coin, Dogecoin (DOGE), which he believes could attract non-crypto natives back into the crypto space.  Dogecoin’s Role In [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/analyst-predicts-570-billion-inflow-amid-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Crypto expert Scott Melker</a>, also known as the ‘Wolf of All Streets,” has laid down a theory of when mainstream demand for crypto will return in this <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bull-market-glassnode/">bull market</a>. Interestingly, his theory revolved around the foremost meme coin, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-10-largest-meme-coin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a>, which he believes could attract non-crypto natives back into the crypto space. </p>
<h2>Dogecoin’s Role In Attracting Mainstream Demand For Crypto</h2>
<p>Melker mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://x.com/scottmelker/status/1767574234895663410?s=20" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">post</a> that mainstream FOMO (fear of missing out) will return to the crypto market when the foremost meme coin hits a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-predicts-when-dogecoin-will-reach-1/">new all-time high (ATH)</a>. His belief is based on the fact that “mainstream fervor” in the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/rewards-2021-bitcoin-bull-buyers-finally-break-even/">last bull cycle</a> was driven by dog coins and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/nfts-are-seeing-resurgence-signs-crypto-bull-market/">NFTs (non-fungible tokens)</a>.</p>

<p>He alluded to how these individuals joined waiting lists on exchanges just to sign up and buy DOGE. As such, DOGE needs to make a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-10-largest-meme-coin/">similar run to the one in 2021</a> to attract these people back into the space and get them “excited about the market again.” DOGE hitting a new ATH would be a good start since it would put all investments from the previous cycle in profits. </p>
<p>Melker suggested that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-breaks-through-69000-setting-new-record/">Bitcoin hitting new ATHs</a> hasn’t been sufficient enough to attract this class of investors as there is still “seemingly minimal mainstream interest.” He joked that he has so far not gotten calls from old friends and family asking if they should buy Bitcoin. </p>
<p>Although DOGE isn’t exactly at the center of this <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bull-market-glassnode/">bull cycle</a>, meme coins are once again part of the leading narratives, with these crypto tokens gaining much interest from retail investors. However, there is the feeling that DOGE could draw a lot of attention once it makes a parabolic rise that causes it to hit a new ATH. </p>
<h2>What Dogecoin Needs For A New ATH</h2>
<p>In 2021, DOGE surged by over 26,000% to hit an ATH of $0.7376. This price surge was partly due to the broader acceptance the meme coin began to enjoy, with entities like the NBA team Dallas Mavericks <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/mark-cuban-pushes-for-dogecoin-payments-with-new-incentives/">accepting it as a payment option</a>. Therefore, an increase in DOGE’s use case could be critical for <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-highest-level/">its performance</a> in this bull run.</p>

<p>Interestingly, DOGE’s primary supporter and the world’s richest man, Elon Musk, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-tesla-dogecoin/">recently hinted</a> that his company, Tesla, would eventually begin accepting the meme coin as a payment method. Such development would no doubt send bullish signals throughout the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-5-million-doge-holders/">DOGE ecosystem</a> and positively affect its price. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, DOGE is trading at around $0.1635, down over 12% in the last 24 hours, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/dogecoin/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5QHr7VzT/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from Tradingview.com (Crypto)" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Dogecoin_18d57e.jpeg?fit=300%2C168" width="300" height="168" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287336</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bybit Faces Scrutiny: Hong Kong Tags Crypto Exchange As &#8216;Suspicious&#8217; In Regulatory Crackdown</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bybit-faces-scrutiny-hong-kong-tags-crypto-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hong kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong Crypto Firm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEXC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SFC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has recently raised concerns over Bybit, marking it as a platform of suspicion. This move comes amid a broader regulatory push within Hong Kong to oversee and regulate the crypto market. The SFC&#8217;s cautionary note addresses 11 investment products by Bybit, indicating potential risks these might pose [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has recently raised concerns over Bybit, <a href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/alert-list/3015" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">marking</a> it as a platform of <a href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/alert-list/3015" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">suspicion</a>. This move comes amid a broader regulatory push within Hong Kong to oversee and regulate the crypto market.</p>
<p>The SFC&#8217;s cautionary note addresses 11 investment products by Bybit, indicating potential risks these might pose to investors.</p>
<p>Despite Bybit&#8217;s efforts to align with local regulations, including its Hong Kong entity, Spark Fintech Limited, <a href="https://www.bybit.com/press/post/bybit-committed-to-contributing-to-hong-kong-s-thriving-fintech-ecosystem-with-vatp-application-blt10d693474a4a2627" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">applying for a crypto exchange license</a>, the regulator’s spotlight on Bybit underscores the challenging landscape of <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-etf-showdown-hong-kong-plans-to-launch-first-overtaking-the-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crypto regulation</a>.</p>

<h2>Bybit Regulatory Hurdles And Compliance Efforts</h2>
<p>This alert by the SFC highlights a critical moment for Bybit, a crypto exchange with a global footprint, as it navigates the complexities of compliance within different jurisdictions.</p>
<p>The identified &#8220;suspicious&#8221; products span various offerings, from futures and options to wealth management services, emphasizing the regulator’s broad scrutiny.</p>
<p>The SFC&#8217;s statement <a href="https://apps.sfc.hk/edistributionWeb/gateway/EN/news-and-announcements/news/doc?refNo=24PR47" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">clarifies</a> that no entity within the Bybit group holds a license or registration to conduct regulated activities in Hong Kong.</p>
<p>With the deadline for crypto trading platforms to submit license applications looming, the SFC&#8217;s action serves as a reminder of the importance of compliance.</p>
<p>Bybit’s distinction between its international operations and the<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-sfc-raises-alert-over-mexc-imposter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> local entity</a>, Spark Fintech Limited, reflects the complex nature of crypto regulations and platforms&#8217; efforts to adapt to diverse regulatory demands.</p>
<h2>The Broader Context Of Crypto Regulation In Hong Kong</h2>
<p>Notably, the Bybit regulatory hurdle comes at a time when Hong Kong&#8217;s SFC shared a recent mandate that requires all crypto trading platforms within its jurisdiction to<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/regulatory-showdown-in-hong-kong-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> apply for a license by February 29 or risk being shut down by May 31</a>.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, as Hong Kong aims to position itself as a regulated stronghold for the crypto industry, it has <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/hong-kong-trails-singapore-in-crypto-licensing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">attracted license applications from 24 entities</a> eager to operate within the city.</p>
<p>Among these applicants are prominent industry names like OKX, Crypto.com, and even Bybit, all vying for a chance to comply with the city’s stringent regulations to safeguard investors.</p>
<p>However, the regulatory framework&#8217;s focus on investor protection comes with compliance costs that challenge some entities. Given these regulatory shifts, HTX, formerly Huobi Global, has <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-htx-retreats-hong-kong-license-withdrawal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">retracted its application for a crypto exchange license in Hong Kong</a>.</p>

<p>This retreat marks a significant change in direction for HTX, which had previously expressed a strong desire to set up a regulated exchange in Hong Kong, backed by the support of TRON founder Justin Sun.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WnVXITnf/" alt="The global crypto market cap value on TradingView amid Bybit news" width="2770" height="1556" />
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Hong-Kong.jpg?fit=640%2C336" width="640" height="336" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287379</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plunge Under $68,000 Squeezes $668 Million Crypto Longs</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-plunge-68000-squeezes-668-crypto-longs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 23:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Crash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin liquidations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin longs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto liquidations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Longs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Squeeze]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows over $668 million in cryptocurrency long contracts have been squeezed following Bitcoin&#8217;s crash under the $68,000 level. Bitcoin Has Registered A Drop Of 7% In The Last 24 Hours Right after setting a fresh all-time high (ATH) not too far from the $74,000 level, the Bitcoin price has reversed its trajectory sharply during [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows over $668 million in cryptocurrency long contracts have been squeezed following Bitcoin&#8217;s crash under the $68,000 level.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Registered A Drop Of 7% In The Last 24 Hours</h2>
<p>Right after setting a fresh all-time high (ATH) not too far from the $74,000 level, the Bitcoin price has reversed its trajectory sharply during the past day.</p>

<p>The below chart shows how the digital asset has performed recently.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/uEp7WLLZ/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854" /></p>

<p>As is visible in the graph, Bitcoin quickly recovered back towards the $72,400 mark midway through the crash, but the retrace was only temporary, as the coin soon resumed its drawdown and dived under the $67,000 level.</p>
<p>Since this low, BTC has made a slight recovery back to $67,600, meaning that it has experienced a decline of almost 7% in the last 24 hours. As is often the case, Ethereum (ETH) and the altcoins have also followed in the lead of the original cryptocurrency, witnessing crashes of their own.</p>
<p>With all this sharp price action around the market, forceful closure of contracts, or &#8216;liquidations,&#8217; are bound to have piled up on the derivative side of the sector. Indeed, data confirms this.</p>
<h2>Crypto Derivative Market Has Seen $813 Million In Liquidations Today</h2>
<p>According to data from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">CoinGlass</a>, the cryptocurrency derivative market has observed total liquidations amounting to a whopping $813 million during the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The table below shows the relevant numbers related to this latest liquidation flush.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-287373 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/table_e87ead.png?w=558&#038;resize=558%2C296" alt="Bitcoin &amp; Crypto Liquidations" width="558" height="296" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>

<p>As displayed above, around $663 million of these liquidations involved long contracts, meaning that this side of the market contributed an overwhelming 81% of the total flush. This lines up with the price action, as assets across the sector have plunged during this period.</p>

<p>Mass liquidation events like today&#8217;s are popularly known as &#8220;squeezes.&#8221; In these events, liquidations cascade together like a waterfall and amplify the sharp price move that triggered them. As longs took most of the beating in the latest squeeze, it would be categorized as a &#8220;<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bears-strike-333-crypto-longs-squeezed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">long squeeze</a>.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for how the various individual symbols contributed to this squeeze, the table below shows the data for this breakdown.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-287385 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/data_7dd4a5.png?w=640&#038;resize=640%2C293" alt="Bitcoin &amp; Other Cryptos" width="640" height="293" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/data_7dd4a5.png?w=785 785w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/data_7dd4a5.png?w=640&#038;resize=640%2C293 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/data_7dd4a5.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/data_7dd4a5.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>

<p>Unsurprisingly, Bitcoin and Ethereum, the two largest cryptocurrencies by <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/total-crypto-market-cap-to-hit-7-5-trillion-next-year/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market cap</a>, are number one and two, respectively. <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coin-trader/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana (SOL)</a> is the altcoin with the largest amount of liquidations at $41 million.</p>
<p>SOL is the only coin among the top assets that has managed strong positive returns during the last 24 hours, and it&#8217;s also among the best performers for the past week. This strong performance may be why it has more speculative interest behind it than the other alts right now.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_2214995821.jpg?fit=640%2C360" width="640" height="360" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287311</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>$300 Million Crypto Ponzi Scheme Exposed: SEC Files Charges Against 17 Suspects</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/300-million-crypto-ponzi-scheme-exposed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto ponzi scheme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto ponzi schemes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[total crypto market cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken legal action against 17 individuals allegedly involved in a Crypto Ponzi scheme that defrauded more than 40,000 victims and amassed $300 million.  As per the SEC’s press release, Houston-based CryptoFX LLC operated the scheme, primarily targeting Latino investors in the United States and two other countries. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken legal action against 17 individuals allegedly involved in a Crypto <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/120m-crypto-ponzi-scheme-in-india-unearthed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ponzi scheme</a> that defrauded more than 40,000 victims and amassed $300 million. </p>
<p>As per the SEC’s <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2024-35" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">press release</a>, Houston-based CryptoFX LLC operated the scheme, primarily targeting Latino investors in the United States and two other countries. This most recent complaint follows the SEC&#8217;s emergency action in September 2022, which shut down the CryptoFX scheme and charged its leaders, Mauricio Chavez and Giorgio Benvenuto.</p>
<h2>Crypto Ponzi Scheme Targets Latino Community</h2>
<p>According to Gurbir Grewal, director of the SEC&#8217;s Division of Enforcement, CryptoFX operated as a massive Ponzi scheme, enticing Latino investors with promises of financial freedom and guaranteed returns through cryptocurrency and foreign exchange investments. </p>

<p>The SEC&#8217;s investigation revealed that the scheme relied primarily on funds from new investors to repay earlier investors, with only a fraction of the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/money-lost-to-crypto-ponzi-schemes-in-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">funds raised </a>being used for actual trading activities. Grewal, director of the SEC&#8217;s Division of Enforcement, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>In the end, the only thing that CryptoFX guaranteed was a trail of thousands upon thousands of victims stretching across ten states and two foreign countries. A scheme of that size requires lots of participants, and as today’s action demonstrates, we will pursue charges against not just the principal architects of these massive schemes, but all those who further their fraud by unlawfully soliciting victims.</p></blockquote>
<p>The complaint alleges that the 17 individuals from Texas, California, Louisiana, Illinois, and Florida served as leaders within the CryptoFX <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/governor-urges-policy-action-to-combat-crypto-ponzi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">network</a>. They allegedly solicited investors by offering “unrealistic returns” ranging from 15 to 100 percent. </p>
<p>Instead of utilizing the funds as promised, the defendants allegedly used them to pay returns to previous investors, provide commissions and bonuses to themselves and others involved, and finance their lifestyles.</p>
<h2>Defendants Accused Of Defying Court Orders</h2>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s legal action also highlights the involvement of certain defendants in continuing to solicit investments even after court orders were issued to halt the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/airbit-ponzi-scheme-execs-plead-guilty/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">CryptoFX scheme</a>. </p>
<p>Gabriel and Dulce Ochoa, for instance, are accused of instructing investors to retract their complaints to the SEC to recover their investments. Moreover, Maria Saravia allegedly misinformed investors, claiming the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit was fake.</p>

<p>The SEC&#8217;s complaint, filed in the US District Court for the Southern District of Texas, charges various violations against the defendants, including antifraud, securities registration, broker-registration provisions, and whistleblower protection provisions. The SEC seeks permanent injunctions, disgorgement with prejudgment interest, and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/forsage-co-founders-indicted-for-defi-ponzi-scheme/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">civil penalties</a> for each defendant.</p>
<p>While two defendants, Luis Serrano and Julio Taffinder, have consented to the entry of final judgments without admitting or denying the allegations, the court&#8217;s approval is pending. Serrano and Taffinder have agreed to pay over $68,000 combined in civil penalties, disgorgement, and interest.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/5Af3MiDo/" alt="Crypto" width="1815" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-6-5.jpg?fit=336%2C260" width="336" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287400</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Vs SEC: Crucial Dates To Watch Out For In 2024</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-vs-sec-crucial-dates-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC Vs. Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=287337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The long-running legal battle between the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple is set to once again gain steam as key dates approach. The XRP community will no doubt have their eyes on this one and hope that the lawsuit, which has continued to mar the XRP ecosystem, can well be put in the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-xrp-lawsuit-ripple-co-founder/">long-running legal battle</a> between the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/sec-announcement-crypto/#:~:text=What%20The%20SEC&#039;s%20Latest%20Announcement%20Means%20For%20The%20Crypto%20Industry,-by%20Scott%20Matherson&amp;text=A%20recent%20announcement%20by%20the,actions%20have%20had%20on%20it." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> and Ripple is set to once again gain steam as key dates approach. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrps-underperformance-ruffles-feathers-as-community-asks-ripple-to-do-something-about-price/">XRP community</a> will no doubt have their eyes on this one and hope that the lawsuit, which has continued to mar the XRP ecosystem, can well be put in the past. </p>
<h2>The SEC and Ripple Set For Another Showdown</h2>
<p>Former Federal Prosecutor James Filan revealed in an X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://x.com/FilanLaw/status/1768094762425540670?s=20" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">post</a> that the SEC’s opening brief is due on March 22, while Ripple will have until April 22 to file its opposition brief. Once that is done, the SEC’s reply brief will follow with the deadline set for May 6. As noted by Filan, these dates form part of the revised schedule for the remedies briefing. </p>

<p>The previous deadline for the SEC’s opening brief was set for March 13. However, the Commission made a request to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-judge-deems-xrp-sale-non-investment-contract/">Judge Analisa Torres</a>, seeking a one-week extension and citing “good cause” as the reason why the request should be granted. Judge Torres subsequently <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/19857399/940/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-ripple-labs-inc/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">granted</a> the request. </p>
<p>To avoid prejudice, the SEC also requested that Ripple’s deadline to file its opposition brief be moved from April 12 to April 22 to give the defendants ample time to respond appropriately to the Commission’s brief. This remedies briefing stage is a set-off from the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-lawsuit-sec-files-new-demands-ripple/">discovery stage</a>, where the regulator had requested certain documents from the crypto firm. </p>
<p>These documents, which include post-complaint <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/institutional-buyers-of-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">institutional sales</a> contracts, will form the focal point of the SEC’s opening brief. In it, the Commission will also make certain requests regarding the remedies that should be granted in its favor for Ripple’s breach of securities laws. Judge Torres had previously ruled that the crypto firm’s institutional sales were investment contracts. </p>
<h2>How The Remedies Briefing Could Go</h2>
<p>Alongside a monetary fine, the SEC i<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-settlement-lawsuit-gcc/">s expected</a> to request an injunction restraining Ripple from conducting institutional sales that are in breach of securities laws. On the other hand, Ripple will most likely contend what amount the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/sec-700-million-ripple-xrp/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Commission requests</a> that it pays as a fine. There might also be contentions from Ripple that its ODL transactions do not classify as securities. </p>

<p>Pro-XRP legal expert John Deaton had <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ripple-2/sec-700-million-ripple-xrp/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">previously suggested</a> that the remedies briefing might not be so straightforward as both parties might still have to file subsequent briefs. Deaton added that he doesn’t foresee a judgment coming until late summer “at the earliest.” When the judgment is finally given, there is also the likelihood of <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-vs-sec-appeal-delay-until-2024/">an appea</a>l from either (or both) parties. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/M1dA5Uhr/" alt="XRP price chart from Tradingview.com (Ripple vs SEC)" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ripple-SEC.jpeg?fit=322%2C157" width="322" height="157" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">287337</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
