<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Crypto News, Alt Coin News and Cryptocurrency Comparison]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Keep your finger on the pulse of the fast-moving cryptocurrency sector with all the latest crypto news, analysis and reviews from CoinJournal]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:08:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Crypto News, Alt Coin News and Cryptocurrency Comparison]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BlackRock CEO’s ETF comments boosts Ethereum (ETH) and Algotech (ALGT)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceos-etf-comments-boosts-ethereum-eth-and-algotech-algt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceos-etf-comments-boosts-ethereum-eth-and-algotech-algt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink believes a spot Ethereum ETF is possible even if SEC designates ETH a security. Markets are upbeat amid this outlook despite current weakness. Meanwhile, investors eyeing new gems have identified new token Algotech (ALGT). BlackRock CEO Larry Fink has noted his bullish stance on Bitcoin, with the global asset management behemoth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceos-etf-comments-boosts-ethereum-eth-and-algotech-algt/">BlackRock CEO’s ETF comments boosts Ethereum (ETH) and Algotech (ALGT)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink believes a spot Ethereum ETF is possible even if SEC designates ETH a security.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Markets are upbeat amid this outlook despite current weakness.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, investors eyeing new gems have identified new token Algotech (ALGT).</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink has noted his bullish stance on Bitcoin, with the global asset management behemoth seeing massive uptake for its iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) spot Bitcoin ETF. Fink is also optimistic about a spot Ethereum ETF.</p>
<p dir="ltr">What does this mean for Ethereum price? Elsewhere, why is the new decentralized trading platform <a href="https://algotech.trade?utm_source=coinjournal&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=2803" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Algotech (ALGT)</a> attracting so many investors to its presale?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Larry Fink on potential spot ETH ETF</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1773072336884732357" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>comments</u></a> on Wednesday, BlackRock CEO Larry Fink said that designating ETH a security won&rsquo;t be &ldquo;deleterious&rdquo;, noting that an ETH ETF was still possible.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Various analysts have noted that a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/valkyrie-co-founder-says-spot-ethereum-etf-approval-unlikely-in-may/">spot Ethereum ETF nod from the SEC is unlikely in May</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Fink&rsquo;s comments align with the broader anticipation that this will eventually get an approval. As such, the BlackRock CEO&rsquo;s remarks saw a slight flip for Ethereum and other altcoins late Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum price</a> rose slightly to above $3,658. However, it remains choppy amid recent news around the Ethereum Foundation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The outlook was similar across the altcoin market, except for Dogecoin and Bitcoin Cash.</p>
<p dir="ltr">DOGE and BCH were seeing double-digit gains, perhaps helped by the anticipated Coinbase listing of Dogecoin and Bitcoin Cash futures trading on April 1, 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto traders are eyeing the futures listing. Interest in new crypto project Algotech is also rising.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is Algotech (ALGT) attracting investors?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto world offers multiple opportunities, particularly in the trading space. However, many people around the world are unable to tap into this due to various reasons. One of these is the complexity of the trading market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Algotech is a new trading platform that seeks to level the playing field, tapping into <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a> and machine learning to open up opportunities for everyone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The algorithmic crypto trading platforms offer intelligent trading strategies. The AI-powered platform removes the limitations associated with manual trading, including limited analytics, inconsistency in execution and human emotions and biases.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All these factors make crypto trading on traditional platforms largely unappealing for the ordinary user. Algorithmic platforms change this.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Advanced algorithms allow for real-time access and analysis of markets, datasets and trends. Leveraging the automated platform means users can make informed decisions related to the opportunities available.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Algotech, users will tap into speed and efficiency, data-driven decision-making and real-time market data. It&rsquo;s one platform likely to change the crypto trading landscape big time.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you buy ALGT today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The token powering the Algotech ecosystem is ALGT.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Algotech whitepaper, the total supply of ALGT is 350 million. 70% of this is available in presale. The project has raised over $3.3 million from early investors so far, with more than 84.9 million tokens sold.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For a project likely to dominate given its robust technical infrastructure, tokenomics, roadmap and future dominance, the sub-cent presale prices might offer a great entry point.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, the presale is in stage 2, which is 92% sold out with ALGT price at $0.06. Presale participants can access a 20% promotion bonus on all deposits in this stage. Meanwhile, the next stage will see ALGT price rise to $0.08.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Learn more about Algotech <a href="https://algotech.trade?utm_source=coinjournal&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=2803" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceos-etf-comments-boosts-ethereum-eth-and-algotech-algt/">BlackRock CEO’s ETF comments boosts Ethereum (ETH) and Algotech (ALGT)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong-based Asset Manager VSFG aiming for a May spot Bitcoin ETF launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-based-asset-manager-vsfg-aiming-for-a-may-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-based-asset-manager-vsfg-aiming-for-a-may-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-based-asset-manager-vsfg-aiming-for-a-may-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are reports that the Hong Kong SFC is considering to approve Bitcoin ETFs in Q2 2024. VSFG and Value Partners have applied for approval to offer a spot Bitcoin ETF in Hong Kong. VSFG is targeting to launch the spot BTC ETF as early as May this year. Hong Kong&#8217;s financial landscape is set [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-based-asset-manager-vsfg-aiming-for-a-may-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch/">Hong Kong-based Asset Manager VSFG aiming for a May spot Bitcoin ETF launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>There are reports that the Hong Kong SFC is considering to approve Bitcoin ETFs in Q2 2024.</li>
<li>VSFG and Value Partners have applied for approval to offer a spot Bitcoin ETF in Hong Kong.</li>
<li>VSFG is targeting to launch the spot BTC ETF as early as May this year.</li>
</ul>
<p>Hong Kong&rsquo;s financial landscape is set for a potential transformation as Venture Smart Financial Holdings Ltd (VSFG), a prominent asset management company, gears up to launch a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the country as early as May.</p>
<p>Collaborating with local firm Value Partners, VSFG has filed an application with the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) to introduce this innovative investment product to the market.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong&rsquo;s stand on Bitcoin ETFs</h2>
<p>Following regulatory considerations initiated in December 2023, Hong Kong regulators have been actively contemplating the approval of spot crypto ETFs within the region.</p>
<p>Earlier, Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas in a <a href="https://x.com/EricBalchunas/status/1772602019133423921?s=20">post on X</a>, citing a Bloomberg Intelligence report, stated that the SFC is considering allowing in-kind creations and redemptions for spot bitcoin ETFs in the second quarter of this year.</p>
<p>If true, the move will underscore Hong Kong&rsquo;s growing reputation as a crypto-friendly hub where financial institutions can readily offer innovative products to local investors.</p>
<p>Industry leaders have echoed the sentiment, urging regulators to expedite the launch of spot ETFs in Hong Kong to meet the increasing demand from investors.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin ETF boom and its impact</h2>
<p>The approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the United States in January sparked a surge in offerings by major financial institutions such as Grayscale, BlackRock, and Fidelity Investments. Accumulating approximately $50 billion in assets within a few months, these ETFs have significantly boosted investor engagement in the crypto market.</p>
<p>Moreover, the approval of Bitcoin ETFs coincided with a substantial <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">BTC price</a> escalation, with its value skyrocketing from around $30,000 to as high as $73,700 in March. Currently trading at $70,630, Bitcoin&rsquo;s value is poised for further growth, especially with the anticipated approval of spot ETFs in Hong Kong.</p>
<p>VSFG&rsquo;s move to apply for a spot Bitcoin ETF aligns with the broader trend of financial institutions capitalizing on the growing interest in cryptocurrency investment products. If approved, the ETF would streamline the investment process for Hong Kong-based investors, providing them with a regulated and accessible avenue to gain exposure to Bitcoin.</p>
<p>With the potential launch of the spot Bitcoin ETF in May, VSFG aims to position itself at the forefront of Hong Kong&rsquo;s evolving financial landscape, catering to the increasing demand for crypto investment opportunities in the region.</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-based-asset-manager-vsfg-aiming-for-a-may-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch/">Hong Kong-based Asset Manager VSFG aiming for a May spot Bitcoin ETF launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-based-asset-manager-vsfg-aiming-for-a-may-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bybit launches regulated digital asset platform in the Netherlands</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bybit-launches-regulated-digital-asset-platform-in-the-netherlands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=195841</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bybit.nl brings more crypto services and products to Dutch users. The launch follows Bybit&#8217;s partnership with SATOS, a crypto platform with operations in the Netherlands and Belgium since 2013. Bybit has announced the launch of Bybit.nl, a regulated digital asset platform for users in the Netherlands. The crypto news comes as more people look into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bybit-launches-regulated-digital-asset-platform-in-the-netherlands/">Bybit launches regulated digital asset platform in the Netherlands</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit.nl brings more crypto services and products to Dutch users.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400">The launch follows Bybit&rsquo;s partnership with SATOS, a crypto platform with operations in the Netherlands and Belgium since 2013.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit has announced the launch of Bybit.nl, a regulated digital asset platform for users in the Netherlands.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto news</a> comes as more people look into crypto trading and investing amid Bitcoin&rsquo;s surged to above $70k. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Bybit, expansion into Netherlands via <a href="http://Bybit.nl" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bybit.nl</a> is part of the mission to bring crypto to more users across the globe. The new digital asset platform allows for this within the regulatory guidelines of the Netherlands.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&ldquo;<em>We are thrilled to launch our regulated digital asset platform in the Netherlands, furthering our commitment to serving users while upholding regulatory compliance</em>,&rdquo; said Ben Zhou, co-founder and CEO of Bybit.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit taps SATOS to expand in the Netherlands</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit is partnering with SATOS, a crypto service provider that has operated in the Netherlands and Belgium since 2013. SATOS is supervised by the Dutch National Bank and inked its partnership with Bybit in June 2023.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit.nl marks the next step of the collaboration, the companies said in a press release shared with CoinJournal.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This launch means crypto users in the Netherlands can now access various financial products and trading tools, leveraging a trustworthy trading environment. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In this case, Bybit powered by SATOS will offer a number of benefits to the Dutch crypto community.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Apart from a broader range of financial products, the regulated trading platform will also feature advanced trading tools and </span><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bybit-launches-free-crypto-investing-toolkit/"><span style="font-weight: 400">more education resources</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Users will also benefit from localized support, with support services tailored for the local crypto community.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit.nl also offers access to Bybit Web3 features, including the Web3 Wallet and Airdrop Arcade. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bybit.nl users will also access fiat deposits and withdrawals, over 300 trading pairs and enhanced crypto asset security, the exchange noted.</span></p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bybit-launches-regulated-digital-asset-platform-in-the-netherlands/">Bybit launches regulated digital asset platform in the Netherlands</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>$0DOG prediction: Bitcoin Dogs sets a new tone amid robust use cases and BTC link</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/0dog-prediction-bitcoin-dogs-sets-a-new-tone-amid-robust-use-cases-and-btc-link/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=195837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Dogs token is set for listing as post-listing speculation gains mount. Investors have been attracted by Bitcoin Dogs as the first ICO on the Bitcoin blockchain. The token could rise to $1 amid speculation and use cases. As Bitcoin Dogs ($0DOG) presale came to its ultimate halt on March 15, one thing was clear. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/0dog-prediction-bitcoin-dogs-sets-a-new-tone-amid-robust-use-cases-and-btc-link/">$0DOG prediction: Bitcoin Dogs sets a new tone amid robust use cases and BTC link</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Dogs token is set for listing as post-listing speculation gains mount.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Investors have been attracted by Bitcoin Dogs as the first ICO on the Bitcoin blockchain.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The token could rise to $1 amid speculation and use cases.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://bitcoindogs.club/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=price_prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Dogs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> ($</span><span style="font-weight: 400">0DOG) presale came to its ultimate halt on March 15, one thing was clear. The presale had exceeded expectations, raising nearly $13.5 million within a month. Investors were particularly interested in this token, being the first ICO on the Bitcoin blockchain. As such, predictions are rife that this token could surge strongly when it debuts on exchanges. Let&rsquo;s dive in and explore the $0DOG potential as 100x predictions surface.</span></p>
<h2><b>Bitcoin Dogs: A 100x potential token and the first Bitcoin ICO</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20BTC%20today,trading%20volume%20of%20%2440.24B." target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin price</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> hits levels about the 2021 record, attention has shifted to Bitcoin Dogs. Experts predict that as Bitcoin gains in value, Bitcoin Dogs will attract a positive sentiment. That&rsquo;s partly because Bitcoin Dogs is the first-ever BRC-20 minted token. As such, investors looking for a share of the legacy Bitcoin network see Bitcoin Dogs as a sound alternative.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Being a Bitcoin-linked crypto token has won the hearts of Bitcoin Dogs backers. Bitcoin is the oldest blockchain and carries robust security features. This has allowed Bitcoin Dogs to ride the positive reception of Bitcoin and become a trailblazer in the presale.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Besides, a lot of speculation remains in the crypto markets regarding Bitcoin developments in 2024. These include the approvals of the first </span><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-approves-eleven-spot-bitcoin-etfs-as-memeinators-presale-approaches-3-5m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400">spot Bitcoin ETFs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> earlier in the year and the halving event in April. The positive sentiment could flow into Bitcoin Dogs and help in its price discovery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">There is a lot to expect as Bitcoin Dogs eyes the next step in its budding life. That includes a listing on centralised exchanges (CEXs), scheduled for the first quarter. Owing to the strengths of Bitcoin Dogs in the presale, the listing will be met with a lot of token speculation. But Bitcoin Dogs has attracted attention with its exciting use cases.&nbsp;</span></p>
<h2><b>Biggest Bitcoin ordinals and Dogaverse experiences</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Dogs spotlight seems to have also been inspired by its alluring </span><a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-are-nfts-and-how-do-they-work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400">NFT</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> collection. This is a 10,000 unique and collectible tokens that would be available to $0DOG holders. And guess what? The collection will be the biggest Bitcoin ordinals NFT collection.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Users can curate and display their collectibles for sale within the Bitcoin Dogs NFT metaverse. Thanks to this feature, users have found a sound alternative to owning a piece of digital art. This comes even as Bitcoin NFTs gain popularity and Web 3.0 applications recover from the bear market lows. Bitcoin Dogs doesn&rsquo;t stop there.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The platform features virtual interactions through its metaverse-themed Dogaverse. Fans are thrilled that virtual realities are fast gaining attention and Bitcoin Dogs is part of the transition. Once launched, $0DOG holders can immerse themselves in exciting experiences, opening up new opportunities. Fans can engage in dog training sessions, interact with fellow dog holders, and engage in competitions. As the metaverse ecosystem grows, the use case of $0DOG will be strengthened, boasting its price.</span></p>
<h2><b>Bitcoin Dogs ($ODOG) prediction in 2024</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A bullish crypto market, Bitcoin Dogs&rsquo; use cases, and its relationship to Bitcoin make the token attractive. This could allow $0DOG to surge wildly and claim a coveted 100x gain. Tokens that have attracted a lot of FOMO have risen and exceeded the margins in the past.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">With the presale&rsquo;s starting price of $0.015, a possible 100x gain could see the token rise to above $1. Although speculative, favourable factors and investors buying the token on exchanges make the price realistic.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the future, the price of </span><a href="https://bitcoindogs.club/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=price_prediction" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Dogs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> will be pegged on its diverse use cases. The launch of the NFT marketplace and metaverse could see $ODOG deployed more in Web 3.0. Being the first Bitcoin ICO means Bitcoin Dogs will gain fast traction in the application areas. This will see the token continue increasing in value.&nbsp;</span></p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/0dog-prediction-bitcoin-dogs-sets-a-new-tone-amid-robust-use-cases-and-btc-link/">$0DOG prediction: Bitcoin Dogs sets a new tone amid robust use cases and BTC link</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitbot’s presale officially surpasses $1.5m as stage 7 nears completion</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitbots-presale-officially-surpasses-1-5m-as-stage-7-nears-completion/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitbots-presale-officially-surpasses-1-5m-as-stage-7-nears-completion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitbots-presale-officially-surpasses-1-5m-as-stage-7-nears-completion/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitbot has raised more than $1.5 million in its presale so far.&#160; The project is offering $100k free airdrop to users ahead of its token launch. The cryptocurrency market has been bullish this week, with Bitcoin returning to the sub-$70k region. With the market still bullish, investment continues to flow into nascent projects.&#160; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitbots-presale-officially-surpasses-1-5m-as-stage-7-nears-completion/">Bitbot’s presale officially surpasses $1.5m as stage 7 nears completion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitbot has raised more than $1.5 million in its presale so far.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The project is offering $100k free airdrop to users ahead of its token launch.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been bullish this week, with Bitcoin returning to the sub-$70k region. With the market still bullish, investment continues to flow into nascent projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitbot is looking to ease the trading process for traders. The project has so far raised a substantial amount to help it roll out its products.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Bitbot?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitbot is an exciting Web3 project designed to provide excellent services to cryptocurrency traders. It is a Telegram trading bot that offers users access to high-end trading features. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ideally,&nbsp;<a href="https://bitbot.tg/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitbot</u></a> can best be termed as a self-custodial trading bot that enables users to trade via their cold wallets on Telegram. Investors in this project and its users would have a unique value proposition. Bitbot will leverage Telegram&rsquo;s position as a leading social media platform for crypto users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team explained that Bitbot will provide traders with high-end features to help them grow their trading portfolios. These features are institutional-grade and will grant traders access to exceptional trading functions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap stands above $2.6 trillion and is expected to soar higher in the coming months. Bitbot wants to leverage the rising trading volume in the cryptocurrency market to gain massive adoption in the coming months and years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the entry of more retail and institutional traders, Bitbot could become a leading trading tool for them.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitbot&rsquo;s technology to serve crypto traders</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://bitbot.tg/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitbot</u></a> is a tech-savvy tool that could become very useful to cryptocurrency traders. It seeks to ease the trading process for its users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A primary focus for Bitbot is user security. The tool will use Knightsafe to offer a self-custody solution, eliminating the typical risks associated with Telegram trading. Secondly, the team will develop anti-MEV and anti-rug solutions to help users protect their assets. These features enable traders to avoid bots that artificially pump transaction costs and block scam projects from their timelines.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, Bitbot will use ultra-flexible wallet management powered by non-custodial API technology to provide an added layer of security to the users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">New traders can take advantage of Bitbot&rsquo;s copy trading feature. This feature allows them to copy the trades of the strongest-performing wallets based on on-chain activities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Bitbot giving out $100k to 100 lucky winners, new traders can participate in this to help them build a capital base.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Get ready for the ultimate crypto thrill! &#128640; </p>
<p>The Bitbot $100K Airdrop is here! 100 lucky winners will take home $1000 each! </p>
<p>Don't miss your chance to win big! &#128176; </p>
<p>Enter here: <a href="https://t.co/gh7v9mzBER">https://t.co/gh7v9mzBER</a> <a href="https://t.co/v46qwRg55C">pic.twitter.com/v46qwRg55C</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bitbot (@Official_Bitbot) <a href="https://twitter.com/Official_Bitbot/status/1772986922463334756?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 27, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitbot&rsquo;s presale surpasses $1.5m</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://bitbot.tg/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitbot</u></a> presale is in the seventh stage and has already raised more than $1.5m. The 7th stage will end once the amount raised reaches $1.63m.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project&rsquo;s growing presale shows that investors are buying into Bitbot&rsquo;s narrative and potential growth. Currently, the $BITBOT token is going for $0.0134 but is set to increase to $0.0141 once the eighth round commences.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team will hold 20% of the total token supply and will use it to fund ongoing development. 14% of the total token supply has already been allocated to marketing &amp; CEX listings while 3% goes to exchange liquidity provision.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://bitbot.tg/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Click here</u></a> to read more about Bitbot&rsquo;s upcoming presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Could $BITBOT rally higher this year?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto market has been bullish since the start of the year and many analysts expect BTC to surpasses $150k in the coming months. With the Bitcoin halving roughly 20 days away, trading volume in the market could significantly go higher.</p>
<p><a href="https://bitbot.tg/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitbot</u></a> could be a big winner in the market if it rolls out its products. The project can leverage the growing trading volume in the market to obtain a sizable market share. If that happens, its native $BITBOT token could soar higher in the coming months and years.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitbots-presale-officially-surpasses-1-5m-as-stage-7-nears-completion/">Bitbot’s presale officially surpasses $1.5m as stage 7 nears completion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitbots-presale-officially-surpasses-1-5m-as-stage-7-nears-completion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DED Trends on Twitter After Memecoin Snapshot Announcement</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=195804</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lisbon, Portugal, March 28th, 2024, Chainwire Polkadot-backed community coin #DED, made it to the trending charts on X, demonstrating community&#8217;s engagement and interest behind the memecoin. The project has sparked a new-found excitement in the Polkadot ecosystem, seeing over 20,000 await their airdrop in the $DED Telegram channel. With the token&#8217;s snapshot debuting early last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/">DED Trends on Twitter After Memecoin Snapshot Announcement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Lisbon, Portugal, March 28th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Polkadot-backed community coin #DED, made it to the trending charts on X, demonstrating community&rsquo;s engagement and interest behind the memecoin.</p>
<p>The project has sparked a new-found excitement in the Polkadot ecosystem, seeing over 20,000 await their airdrop in the <a href="https://t.me/dedbird" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$DED Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p><strong><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/x6mfMXaMnhKtDlqyKhO7V7su0gVoNp-ekIFAxi7SuNsyX9EFFQ_1711384640m5fzsvELRh.jpeg"></strong></p>
<p>With the token&rsquo;s snapshot debuting early last week, the team hopes $DED signifies a second coming for the Polkadot ecosystem and fresh liquidity.</p>
<p>With partnerships and support from top projects on the network such as <a href="https://x.com/wearetalisman/status/1753949769645342959?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Talisman Wallet</a>, Nova wallet, <a href="https://x.com/subwalletapp/status/1771476245982634144?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SubWallet</a> and others, $DED is showingcasing how powerful and committed the Polkadot community can be.</p>
<p>DED has also launched the biggest Zealy campaign the network has seen, with a total prize pool of over $30,000 in DOT and big crypto personalities have also jumped in on the action. YouTuber <a href="https://x.com/dotisded/status/1755242777166651602?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DataDash</a> noted in part of his latest video that this could &ldquo;Put Polkadot back in centre stage&rdquo;, with others such as Ash Crypto, DubzyXBT and Crypto Banter piling into the action.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/d1syNQgx3X9wxwQz6S7nQ3jVnHh1v70Ku_vZAO77UCtGs-2JYK_17113846408r3PW3Z2ZG.jpeg"></p>
<h2>The Dot is DED Mission Recap</h2>
<p>DOT is $DED was initiated by the community with the purpose of creating the first memecoin on DOT. The community felt that if they worked together they could bring excitement which would onboard a larger community to Polkadot. Figuring out how to do it was the hard part, but after seeing how $BONK acted as a catalyst for the Solana ($SOL), the answer was right in front of the team.</p>
<p>There are now over 1 million DOT holders, and an estimated 100,000 of them have stuck it out to support the DED launch. Now the Snapshot has been taken, DOT is DED will await its airdrop.</p>
<p>For the latest updates and community activity Join the $DED <a href="https://t.me/dedbird" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> channel and follow on <a href="https://twitter.com/dotisded" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">X</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Jack<br>
jack@lunarstrategy.com</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/">DED Trends on Twitter After Memecoin Snapshot Announcement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MyShell Raises $11 Million for its Decentralized AI Consumer Layer</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/myshell-raises-11-million-for-its-decentralized-ai-consumer-layer/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/myshell-raises-11-million-for-its-decentralized-ai-consumer-layer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 19:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=195682</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, March 27th, 2024, Chainwire Funds from the Pre-Series A round led by Dragonfly will further develop MyShell&#8217;s open-source models and agent platform for empowering AI creators MyShell, a decentralized AI consumer layer, announced today that it has raised US$11 million in a Pre-Series A round, with participation from a cohort of high-profile investors, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/myshell-raises-11-million-for-its-decentralized-ai-consumer-layer/">MyShell Raises $11 Million for its Decentralized AI Consumer Layer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tokyo, Japan, March 27th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Funds from the Pre-Series A round led by Dragonfly will further develop MyShell&rsquo;s open-source models and agent platform for empowering AI creators</p>
<p><a href="https://myshell.ai/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MyShell</a>, a decentralized AI consumer layer, announced today that it has raised US$11 million in a Pre-Series A round, with participation from a cohort of high-profile investors, including Dragonfly, Delphi Ventures, Bankless Ventures, Maven11 Capital, Nascent, Nomad Capital, OKX Ventures, etc.</p>
<p>Prominent angel investors, such as former Coinbase CTO Balaji Srinivasan, NEAR Protocol Co-Founder Illia Polosukhin, former Paradigm Investment Partner Casey K. Caruso, and ex-Parafi partner Santiago R. Santos also joined the round, which brought MyShell&rsquo;s total amount raised to date to $16.6 million.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;MyShell is poised to revolutionize the AI creator ecosystem,&rdquo; MyShell CEO Ethan Sun said. &ldquo;With this new funding, we&rsquo;re not just scaling our operations, we&rsquo;re catalyzing a movement towards a more open, collaborative, and democratic AI landscape.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>MyShell, an AI consumer layer that empowers users to build, share, and own AI agents, is home to over 1 million registered users and 50,000 creators. The company plans to use the new funding to add resources to develop its open-source foundational model; empower AI creators; AI assets trading platform; and further support the open-source community.</p>
<p>In contrast to most dominant AI companies such as OpenAI, MyShell is committed to decentralization and open-source development. This focus has already facilitated the growth of several successful projects on the platform, including OpenVoice, which has earned over 15,000 stars on Github; MeloTTS, a pioneering open-source text-to-speech solution that closely mimics the human voice and supports a wide range of languages and accents; and Allice, the open-source agent framework for complicated AI development workflow.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;The demand for personalized AI experiences has grown explosively in the last year, but right now, most of those experiences are centralized with gatekeepers,&rdquo; said Dragonfly Managing Partner Haseeb Qureshi.</p>
<p>&ldquo;MyShell uses crypto and decentralization to put the power over the AI ecosystem back into the hands of users and allows open-source creators and communities to work together to create magical experiences and capture the fruits of their labor. There&rsquo;s a lot of unfounded hype right now at the intersection of crypto and AI, but Ethan and the MyShell team have the technical chops with research backgrounds that allow them to execute their vision.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>The funding reflects MyShell&rsquo;s position as a pioneer in the AI consumer layer with its open-value network that deploys a revenue-share economic model. MyShell also provides unique toolkit features such as the &ldquo;Workshop&rdquo; where users build AI agents through prompts, and &ldquo;Makerspace,&rdquo; a no-code AI workflow builder for creators.</p>
<p>The investment enables MyShell to deepen its commitment to lower the barrier for AI creation, fostering a community where openness and collaboration are paramount. By championing decentralization and supporting the creator economy, MyShell is not just building tools; it is nurturing an ecosystem where every voice has the power to shape the AI landscape.</p>
<h3>About MyShell</h3>
<p>MyShell is the AI consumer layer that empowers users to build, share, and own AI agents. It&rsquo;s Features include an interactive AI app store that stands on multiple open-source foundation models, and integrates other models into a robust model hub, offering a dynamic and engaging user experience.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Co-founder<br>
Ethan Sun<br>
MyShell<br>
ethan@myshell.ai</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/myshell-raises-11-million-for-its-decentralized-ai-consumer-layer/">MyShell Raises $11 Million for its Decentralized AI Consumer Layer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/myshell-raises-11-million-for-its-decentralized-ai-consumer-layer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missed Dogwifhat and SHIB meme coin rally? Milei Moneda might be next in line</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/missed-dogwifhat-and-shib-meme-coin-rally-milei-moneda-might-be-next-in-line/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/missed-dogwifhat-and-shib-meme-coin-rally-milei-moneda-might-be-next-in-line/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[News Team]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/missed-dogwifhat-and-shib-meme-coin-rally-milei-moneda-might-be-next-in-line/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogwifhat (WIF)&#160;surged 60%&#160;due to NFT sales. Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium&#160;significantly boosts&#160;SHIB&#8217;s price.&#160; Milei Moneda ($MEDA)&#160;projected for a surge post-Uniswap launch.&#160; Recently, two meme-inspired tokens, Dogwifhat (WIF) and Shiba Inu (SHIB), made significant waves with their recent price surges and notable achievements. As lucky investors enjoy the gains from the WIF and SHIB price rally,&#160;Milei Moneda ($MEDA), [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/missed-dogwifhat-and-shib-meme-coin-rally-milei-moneda-might-be-next-in-line/">Missed Dogwifhat and SHIB meme coin rally? Milei Moneda might be next in line</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Dogwifhat (WIF)&nbsp;surged 60%&nbsp;due to NFT sales.</li>
<li>Shiba Inu&rsquo;s Shibarium&nbsp;significantly boosts&nbsp;SHIB&rsquo;s price.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Milei Moneda ($MEDA)&nbsp;projected for a surge post-Uniswap launch.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>Recently, two meme-inspired tokens, Dogwifhat (WIF) and Shiba Inu (SHIB), made significant waves with their recent price surges and notable achievements. </p>
<p>As lucky investors enjoy the gains from the WIF and SHIB price rally,&nbsp;<a href="https://mileimoneda.io/?utm_source=cjl&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_id=273">Milei Moneda ($MEDA)</a>, a new player, is emerging on the scene and some analysts believe it could deliver significant&nbsp;profits to investors.</p>
<h2>Dogwifhat (WIF) vs. Shiba Inu (SHIB)</h2>
<p>Solana-based meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) has seen a remarkable surge in its price,&nbsp;jumping by 60%&nbsp;recently. This&nbsp;pump&nbsp;was triggered by the sale of the original picture that inspired the creation of the token as a Non-Fungible Token (NFT). The acquisition was completed by Global Coin Research (GCR), a Web3 Research Group, using&nbsp;$4.3 million&nbsp;worth of Ethereum (ETH).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Likewise, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a>, known for its meme-inspired roots, has garnered attention for its Layer-2 scaling solution, Shibarium. This innovative solution, aimed at enhancing SHIB&rsquo;s ecosystem with faster transactions and reduced costs, has significantly boosted SHIB&rsquo;s price in recent weeks. This surge in the altcoin price has positioned Shiba Inu (SHIB) as one of the top-performing altcoins in the market.</p>
<p>The recent price surges and milestones achieved by Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogwifhat (WIF) yielded significant profits for investors. As these tokens continue to gain traction, investors are anticipating&nbsp;more gains&nbsp;as they watch&nbsp;Milei Moneda ($MEDA), one of the&nbsp;new DeFi projects&nbsp;currently storming the market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Milei Moneda sparks frenzy: early investors optimistic</h2>
<p>Since its public presale debut,&nbsp;<a href="https://mileimoneda.io/?utm_source=cjl&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_id=273">Milei Moneda</a> ($MEDA)&nbsp;has ignited a frenzy among crypto enthusiasts, with some experts forecasting significant profits for early investors. This token not only holds out the promise of&nbsp;explosive potential&nbsp;but also boasts&nbsp;innovative features&nbsp;that set it apart from other&nbsp;top DeFi coins.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Milei Moneda ($MEDA) operates as a true meme coin with its unique amalgamation of humour, politics, and cryptocurrency. Featuring a total token supply of 500,000,000 and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> as its underlying chain, many say Milei Moneda ($MEDA) is positioned for a global impact.</p>
<p>With 60% of its total supply allocated to the public, the meme coin is currently in Stage 1 of its public presale. Currently selling at $0.010, the price will show a&nbsp;100% increase&nbsp;when the token launches on Uniswap at the price of $0.020. With the launch date set for May 21, investors are closely watching, expecting&nbsp;maximum returns&nbsp;on their investments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Looking ahead, market analysts anticipate great gains for&nbsp;$MEDA. Drawing from the project&rsquo;s innovative features, vision, and significant traction it&rsquo;s gaining from its public presale, price projections show that&nbsp;Milei Moneda ($MEDA)&nbsp;has the potential to&nbsp;reenact&nbsp;the bullish moves of its predecessors Dogwifhat (WIF) and Shiba Inu (SHIB).&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>As the crypto community eagerly awaits May 21, the potential for Milei Moneda ($MEDA) to replicate the impressive gains of its forerunners, Dogwifhat (WIF) and Shiba Inu (SHIB), seems increasingly plausible.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors are bracing for what could be the next chapter in the meme coin saga, where Milei Moneda ($MEDA) now takes centre stage.</p>
<p>If you are curious about $MEDA? <a href="https://mileimoneda.io/?utm_source=cjl&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_id=273">Visit the Milei Moneda website</a> or chat on <a href="https://t.me/mileimoneda">Telegram</a> for the inside scoop.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/missed-dogwifhat-and-shib-meme-coin-rally-milei-moneda-might-be-next-in-line/">Missed Dogwifhat and SHIB meme coin rally? Milei Moneda might be next in line</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/missed-dogwifhat-and-shib-meme-coin-rally-milei-moneda-might-be-next-in-line/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom price up ahead of Sonic launch; NuggetRush investors anticipate similar price pattern at launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-price-up-ahead-of-sonic-launch-nuggetrush-investors-anticipate-similar-price-pattern-at-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-price-up-ahead-of-sonic-launch-nuggetrush-investors-anticipate-similar-price-pattern-at-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[News Team]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-price-up-ahead-of-sonic-launch-nuggetrush-investors-anticipate-similar-price-pattern-at-launch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fantom (FTM) has caught market-wide attention as its Sonic upgrade will soon go live. Analysts now debate the possible effects on FTM. NuggetRush&#8217;s (NUGX)&#160;presale performance has given investors a peek at its growth potential. Fantom&#8217;s Sonic upgrade will soon go live, bringing major changes designed to boost its network performance. NuggetRush (NUGX) has joined the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-price-up-ahead-of-sonic-launch-nuggetrush-investors-anticipate-similar-price-pattern-at-launch/">Fantom price up ahead of Sonic launch; NuggetRush investors anticipate similar price pattern at launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul type="disc">
<li>Fantom (FTM) has caught market-wide attention as its Sonic upgrade will soon go live.</li>
<li>Analysts now debate the possible effects on FTM.</li>
<li>NuggetRush&rsquo;s (NUGX)&nbsp;presale performance has given investors a peek at its growth potential.</li>
</ul>
<p>Fantom&rsquo;s Sonic upgrade will soon go live, bringing major changes designed to boost its network performance.</p>
<p><a href="https://nuggetrush.io/?utm_source=PR&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_campaign=cjl&amp;utm_content=67">NuggetRush (NUGX)</a> has joined the list of top meme coins in the gaming industry after its stellar presale numbers. The project has also raised over $3.3 million in token sale revenue. Yet, can NUGX become one of the best DeFi projects? Keep reading.</p>
<h2>Fantom prepares for the official launch of its Sonic upgrade</h2>
<p>Investors are jubilant over <a href="https://coinjournal.net/fantom/">Fantom&rsquo;s recent price surge</a> as it became one of the best-performing bullish altcoins. Data from CoinMarketCap show that Fantom&rsquo;s market capitalization has surged by $1.9 billion since the first week of 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Fantom (FTM) had also crossed the $1.00 range in late March. FTM traded at $0.4343 on February 26. It jumped by 94.4% to $0.8445 on March 7. FTM fell slightly by 5.8% to $0.7953 on March 16 before surging by 30.5% to $1.0385 on March 23.</p>
<p>Fantom&rsquo;s (FTM) surge is due to excitement around its Sonic upgrades. Details about the upgrade show that Fantom will get improved EVM efficiency. It could also boost DeFi activity on Fantom, pushing FTM&rsquo;s value up by 38.5% to $1.4385. This could make it one of the best cryptocurrency investments.</p>
<h2>NuggetRush remains one of the most in-demand gaming tokens</h2>
<p>Blockchain gaming has generated high interest in 2024, causing a shift in investor behaviour. After predictions of surging GameFi activity, investors have flocked to presale tokens like <a href="https://nuggetrush.io/?utm_source=PR&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_campaign=cjl&amp;utm_content=67">NuggetRush.</a> Built on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, NuggetRush (NUGX) is a collection of exciting challenges that revolve around building a business from artisanal mining.</p>
<p>NuggetRush (NUGX) recreates the thrill of artisanal mining, providing an ecosystem where gamers can amass gold rewards while building high-value business operations. Each gamer must rise from a novice to a mining entrepreneur with viable resource excavation sites.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In return, they get raw mineral resources that can be refined and traded on the game&rsquo;s marketplace. How efficient you are at mining depends on a few factors, which include your equipment and workforce.</p>
<p>Thankfully, opportunities to boost your mining operations exist throughout NuggetRush&rsquo;s (NUGX) landscape. You can purchase better equipment or choose to upgrade your old inventory. Whatever you choose, having upgraded or improved NFT assets will directly boost your mining efficiency and reward eligibility.</p>
<p>Extra rewards on NuggetRush (NUGX) translate to higher earning potential. This allows gamers to sell or stake more NFT collectibles. Staking, in particular, pays an interest rate of up to 20% APY, depending on how long you hold your NFTs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Such benefits have attracted many eyes to NuggetRush (NUGX), leading to the sale of 248 million tokens in its presale. NUGX&rsquo;s value has also jumped to $0.019 as its token sale revenue exceeds $3.3 million. It&nbsp;could remain bullish long after its official launch, which will follow its value increase to $0.020. This could make NUGX one of the best gaming tokens right now.</p>
<p>To keep updated ahead of the NuggetRush launch, <a href="https://nuggetrush.io/?utm_source=PR&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_campaign=cjl&amp;utm_content=67">visit the NuggetRush Presale Website</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-price-up-ahead-of-sonic-launch-nuggetrush-investors-anticipate-similar-price-pattern-at-launch/">Fantom price up ahead of Sonic launch; NuggetRush investors anticipate similar price pattern at launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-price-up-ahead-of-sonic-launch-nuggetrush-investors-anticipate-similar-price-pattern-at-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
