<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoSlate</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptoslate.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptoslate.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News and Real-time Coin Data</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 18:49:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cropped-cryptoslate-transparent-icon-256x256-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CryptoSlate</title>
	<link>https://cryptoslate.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Op-ed: Funding isn’t the core solution to bridging the gender gap in Web3</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/op-ed-funding-isnt-the-core-solution-to-bridging-the-gender-gap-in-web3/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/op-ed-funding-isnt-the-core-solution-to-bridging-the-gender-gap-in-web3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sonia Shaw]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guest Post]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Op-Ed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Web3 has always felt like an inclusive and empowering community to be a part of. In making the transition from traditional finance to DeFi, there has been no lack of support, encouragement, and guidance. Embodying a leadership role as a female has also felt free from obstacles or adversity. Gender Gap Still Evident However, despite [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/op-ed-funding-isnt-the-core-solution-to-bridging-the-gender-gap-in-web3/">Op-ed: Funding isn’t the core solution to bridging the gender gap in Web3</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Web3 has always felt like an inclusive and empowering community to be a part of. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">In making the transition from traditional finance to <a href="http://cryptoslate.com/defi">DeFi</a>, there has been no lack of support, encouragement, and guidance. Embodying a leadership role as a female has also felt free from obstacles or adversity.</span></p>
<h2><b>Gender Gap Still Evident</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, despite personal experience, it cannot be ignored that the evident gender gap in <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/web3/">Web3</a> has been brought to attention recently. With the recent celebration of International Women&#8217;s Day, the community must acknowledge that </span><strong><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/09/13/from-glass-ceiling-to-digital-frontier-women-in-web3-and-ai-are-essential/?sh=2babbd765065">only 13% of founding teams in Web3 include at least ONE woman. </a></strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">2023 data from Swiss Fintech Innovations also highlighted that </span><strong><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jemmagreen/2024/03/06/why-women-matter-in-shaping-the-future-of-web3-innovation/?sh=304a7087d370">only 3.5% of Web3 investment reached women-led Web3 business </a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">in the first half of 2023.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Clearly, there is a disparity and a balance that needs amending. Powerful female leaders, with the innovative approaches they can bring, are needed for Web3’s continued evolution. But does the answer to bridging the gap simply lie in providing more funding?</span></p>
<h2><b>Beyond Funding: Self-Empowerment As A Multi-Sided Solution</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Partially, yes. But more money for female startups isn’t a complete solution. That’s one-dimensional. All women in Web3, founders or not, can continue to empower themselves in day-to-day approaches.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Three main areas to consider are: embracing fear, leveraging existing expertise, and building connections.</span></p>
<h2><b>Embracing the Fear</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blockchain technology, decentralization, and <a href="http://cryptoslate.com/web3">Web3 ecosystems</a> can be confusing areas to navigate. Nonetheless, acquiring new knowledge should breed excitement alongside any potential fear or doubt. It&#8217;s easy to allow thoughts of “not knowing enough&#8221; and “not being up to speed” take over. This can trigger feelings of inadequacy or overwhelm in a male-dominated industry. But women should embrace their unique ability to learn.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With a fluid and curious approach, women&#8217;s compassionate abilities often shine through in taking on diverse information. Complexities in understanding should not be feared to the point of freeze or flight. Instead, women must recognize their capabilities and choose to fight through them. Study; ask questions &#8211; with confidence. The more knowledge acquired, the more empowerment comes. The dissolution of boundaries and barriers follow, and the playing field will naturally level out.</span></p>
<h2><b>Leveraging Existing Experience</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because Web3 is such a novel, unique space &#8211; it’s easy to slip into the idea that fresh and unique personalities, approaches, and ideas will be the only route to success. Again, doubt can creep in.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But women in Web3 need to remind themselves of the wealth of experience, leadership skills, and knowledge they’ve carried over from Web2 industries. Communication counts in Web3. Marketing counts in Web3. Creative arts count in Web3.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traditional financial knowledge counts in Web3. HR counts in Web3. Event management counts in Web3. Gender is irrelevant when it comes to niche professional strengths. Women should constantly be supported to self-advocate for what they can bring from past careers. They must identify and utilize their strengths; this will serve best as they continue learning in conjunction. </span></p>
<h2><b>Building Genuine and Empowering Connections</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ideas are the currency of Web3, and creative individuality is the compass. It doesn&#8217;t matter who it is coming from &#8211; so long as direction and purpose are expressed with confidence and conviction. That said, the opportunity to form potential partnerships and connections is abundant. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Women in Web3 should consciously sharpen their ability to spot and capitalize on this potential everywhere. It&#8217;s important to recognize and place faith in the mutual respect, collaborative energy, and inclusive environment found in abundance in Web3 communities. It is the cornerstone for the exponential innovation that has occurred in such a short period within the space.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Women in Web3 should consciously sharpen their ability to spot and capitalize on this potential everywhere. Strength in unity extends beyond any gender divide, and the more it is nurtured, the easier it gets for everyone.</span></p>
<h2><b>Steering The Ship</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overall, Web3 is progressing in many different verticals, and inclusion must be one of them. Women in Web3 play a crucial role in upholding and nourishing the broader ecosystem. Whether within regulatory landscapes, creative industries, educational reform, or digital asset development, Web3 needs women. Funding is welcomed </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8211; but there is no need to wait for it.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Females can take the lead and be assured that the community will support and nurture their efforts. Initiative, confidence, and commitment will be the most significant determinants of an improved female influence &#8211; not money.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/op-ed-funding-isnt-the-core-solution-to-bridging-the-gender-gap-in-web3/">Op-ed: Funding isn’t the core solution to bridging the gender gap in Web3</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/op-ed-funding-isnt-the-core-solution-to-bridging-the-gender-gap-in-web3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/women-web3.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/women-web3.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana CEO Anatoly Yakovenko denounces influx of racist and offensive memecoins</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/solana-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko-denounces-influx-of-racist-and-offensive-memecoins/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/solana-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko-denounces-influx-of-racist-and-offensive-memecoins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Members of the Solana community and the crypto ecosystem denounced the recent surge in inflammatory memecoins on March 22. Unknown parties recently took advantage of Solana&#8217;s token creation feature to introduce thousands of memecoins with racist and antisemitic terminology in their names, some tokens also contained anti-China descriptions and other broadly offensive material. Solana founder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/solana-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko-denounces-influx-of-racist-and-offensive-memecoins/">Solana CEO Anatoly Yakovenko denounces influx of racist and offensive memecoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Members of the Solana community and the crypto ecosystem denounced the recent surge in inflammatory memecoins on March 22.</p>
<p>Unknown parties recently took advantage of Solana&#8217;s token creation feature to introduce thousands of memecoins with racist and antisemitic terminology in their names, some tokens also contained anti-China descriptions and other broadly offensive material.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/solana/">Solana</a> founder and CEO <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/anatoly-yakovenko/">Anatoly Yakovenko</a> spoke out against the trend on X, <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko/status/1771222385242317299">simply stating</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;F’ these anti-Semitic racist incels.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>DEX Screener responds</h2>
<p>DEX Screener, a popular third-party service that monitors tokens on various blockchains, including Solana, <a href="https://twitter.com/dexscreener/status/1771232117134905478">said</a> it would review its policies following the high rate of offensive memecoin launches in recent days.</p>
<p>The company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We won&#8217;t be the gatekeepers of what happens on-chain, but we&#8217;re definitely not here to spread hate.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The platform&#8217;s <a href="https://docs.dexscreener.com/">documentation</a> indicates that all data is currently handled in real time &#8220;without any human moderation or intervention.&#8221;</p>
<p>As of press time, the trend has slightly diminished. However, it is unclear whether DEX Screener has taken action against it.</p>
<p>Molly White of web3isgoinggreat <a href="https://www.web3isgoinggreat.com/?id=solana-racist-memecoins">suggested that</a> the offensive tokens initially filled DEX Screener, few of those tokens are currently trending on the platform&#8217;s main page. Furthermore, memecoins representing backlash against the harmful content are trending, including &#8220;Stop Racism on Solana&#8221; and &#8220;F— DEX Screener.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Memecoin frenzy</h2>
<p>The crypto industry has been gripped by a memecoin frenzy for months now, driven primarily by the blistering surge in value seen by BONK and WIF, among others.</p>
<p>Solana&#8217;s cheap costs and fast transactions have positioned it as the main benefactor of the surge in memecoin trading, with a significant percentage of the trading volume occurring on the network.</p>
<p>SolanaFM <a href="https://twitter.com/solanafm/status/1770836758462189656">recently reported</a> that more than 20,000 new tokens are created daily on the network. Solana&#8217;s rising token count is accommodated by its comparatively low transaction fees, which make creating new tokens more affordable than on other blockchains.</p>
<p>For example, whereas the <a href="https://etherscan.io/chart/avg-txfee-usd">average Ethereum transaction fee</a> is above $9.00, Solana transactions typically cost a fraction of a cent — though actual transaction costs on each chain may vary.</p>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, all but 5 of the 50 top trending cryptos on DEX Screener circulated, at least in part, on Solana.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/solana-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko-denounces-influx-of-racist-and-offensive-memecoins/">Solana CEO Anatoly Yakovenko denounces influx of racist and offensive memecoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/solana-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko-denounces-influx-of-racist-and-offensive-memecoins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/anatoly-yakovenko-memes-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/anatoly-yakovenko-memes-1.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthropic founders block Saudi Arabia from buying FTX-owned stake</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-founders-block-saudi-arabia-from-buying-ftx-owned-stake/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-founders-block-saudi-arabia-from-buying-ftx-owned-stake/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bankruptcy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406513</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AI firm Anthropic has blocked Saudi Arabia from engaging in the sale process of 8% of its shares — currently owned by defunct crypto exchange FTX, CNBC reported on March 22, citing people familiar with the matter. FTX is selling the stake as part of its bankruptcy proceedings to repay its creditors, who lost billions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-founders-block-saudi-arabia-from-buying-ftx-owned-stake/">Anthropic founders block Saudi Arabia from buying FTX-owned stake</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AI firm <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/ftx/">Anthropic</a> has blocked Saudi Arabia from engaging in the sale process of 8% of its shares — currently owned by defunct crypto exchange <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/ftx/">FTX</a>, CNBC reported on March 22, citing people familiar with the matter.</p>
<p>FTX is <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ftx-secures-court-approval-to-sell-8-anthropic-stake/">selling the stake</a> as part of its bankruptcy proceedings to repay its creditors, who lost billions due to its collapse. Investment bank Perella Weinberg is managing the sale, which has reportedly drawn interest from multiple sovereign wealth funds.</p>
<p>The sale is expected to be completed in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>National security risk</h2>
<p>Saudi Arabia, despite its aggressive investment diversification efforts under Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman&#8217;s “Vision 2030 Initiative,&#8221; has been barred from investing in Anthropic.</p>
<p>According to the report, Anthropic founders Dario and Daniela Amodei, who have ties to FTX founder and former CEO <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/sam-bankman-fried/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> through the effective altruism community, told bankers not to sell the stake to Saudi Arabia. The two are broadly uninvolved in the discussions but retain the right to vet potential investors.</p>
<p>Anthropic&#8217;s decision reportedly stems from considerations of national security and geopolitical complexities, including Saudi Arabia&#8217;s relations with China and its controversial human rights record, highlighted by incidents such as the alleged assassination of journalist Jamal Khashoggi in 2018.</p>
<p>The AI firm may be wary of selling the shares to Saudi Arabia as AI is considered a &#8220;dual-risk&#8221; technology that has both civilian and military use cases.</p>
<p>However, the company has not attempted to exclude other countries from participating in the sale — with the UAE&#8217;s Mubadala still in the running.</p>
<p>The US government has also <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/openais-sam-altman-seeking-7t-to-solve-the-global-chip-shortage-issue/">raised concerns</a> about the sensitive nature of AI in relation to national security in recent weeks.</p>
<p>The Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States (CFIUS) has the authority to block foreign investments that are deemed a threat to national security and may choose to intervene in the sale process considering the heightened interest from foreign state-backed entities.</p>
<h2>Shares now worth $1 billion</h2>
<p>Originally purchased by FTX for $500 million in 2021, the stake&#8217;s value has significantly increased in the wake of the AI sector&#8217;s rapid expansion and is worth more than $1 billion as of press time.</p>
<p>The sale of class B shares, which do not offer voting rights, is priced based on Anthropic&#8217;s last valuation of $18.4 billion and amounts to more than $1 billion as of March.</p>
<p>The sale of FTX&#8217;s Anthropic stake is part of the former company&#8217;s bankruptcy case. A court ruled that FTX could sell the stake in February. Sale proceeds will partially go toward compensating investors affected by the collapse of FTX, satisfying a concern that was raised when the court greenlit the sale last month. Estimates from mid-2023 suggest FTX owes customers about $8.7 billion.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-founders-block-saudi-arabia-from-buying-ftx-owned-stake/">Anthropic founders block Saudi Arabia from buying FTX-owned stake</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-founders-block-saudi-arabia-from-buying-ftx-owned-stake/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/ai-anthropic.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/ai-anthropic.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood doubles down on $1.5 million Bitcoin as institutional exposure looms</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-doubles-down-on-1-5-million-bitcoin-as-institutional-exposure-looms/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-doubles-down-on-1-5-million-bitcoin-as-institutional-exposure-looms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Assad Jafri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Watch]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ark Invest CEO Cathie Wood said Bitcoin could be worth more than $1.5 million per coin if institutions allocate roughly 5% of their portfolios to the digital asset. Wood made the statement during the Bitcoin Investor Day conference in New York on March 22. She said: &#8220;Since the SEC gave Institutions the green light to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-doubles-down-on-1-5-million-bitcoin-as-institutional-exposure-looms/">Cathie Wood doubles down on $1.5 million Bitcoin as institutional exposure looms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/ark-invest/">Ark Invest</a> CEO <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/cathie-wood/">Cathie Wood</a> said Bitcoin could be worth more than <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-believes-bitcoin-will-hit-1-5m-by-2030-in-a-bull-scenario/">$1.5 million</a> per coin if institutions allocate roughly 5% of their portfolios to the digital asset.</p>
<p>Wood made the statement during the Bitcoin Investor Day conference in New York on March 22.</p>
<p>She said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Since the SEC gave Institutions the green light to Bitcoin, if they were to allocate more than 5% of their portfolios to Bitcoin as we think they will – that would add $2.3M to the $1.5M price target we initially gave.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The firm&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-sees-bitcoin-at-1-million-sooner-than-2030-after-record-etf-performance/">revised outlook</a>, suggesting a potential surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price beyond the $1.5 million mark, aligns with broader expectations for its integration into the global financial system.</p>
<p>With major financial institutions yet to fully embrace Bitcoin, Wood anticipates further upward momentum in its value.</p>
<h2>Mathematically plausible</h2>
<p>This stance builds upon Wood&#8217;s earlier predictions, notably her assertion in January that Bitcoin could ascend to $1.5 million by 2030 in a bullish scenario. This was shortly after the US SEC approved the first spot Bitcoin ETFs, a move Wood hailed as pivotal for mainstream Bitcoin adoption.</p>
<p>Wood has long been a proponent of Bitcoin&#8217;s growth potential, having previously set an ambitious price target of $1.5 million for the flagship crypto.</p>
<p>Despite the buzz around institutional investments potentially driving Bitcoin&#8217;s value to even higher summits, Wood has chosen not to revise her forecast but suggests the pathway to surpassing $3.5 million is mathematically plausible.</p>
<h2>Financial stabilizer</h2>
<p>Wood also emphasized the rising significance of Bitcoin, particularly in emerging markets amid the global economic fluctuations spurred by heightened US Federal Reserve interest rates.</p>
<p>Wood said that Bitcoin has acted as a financial stabilizer in economies faced with currency devaluation, like Nigeria. Wood&#8217;s insights reflect her view of Bitcoin as a safeguard against economic instability (a risk-off asset) and a viable investment in growth times (a risk-on asset).</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s performance as a <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-believes-bitcoin-will-hit-1-5m-by-2030-in-a-bull-scenario/">hedge against economic uncertainty</a> is further highlighted by its surge during the US regional banking crisis. Bitcoin&#8217;s finite supply further cements its stance against inflation and positions it as a unique asset in the financial domain.</p>
<p>Wood&#8217;s vision for Bitcoin transcends its current status, seeing it as a cornerstone in the future financial landscape, especially as it gains traction as a risk mitigation asset in volatile economies.</p>
<p>Her forecasts, bolstered by the advent of Bitcoin ETFs and the digital currency&#8217;s innate attributes, sketch a future where Bitcoin challenges traditional investment paradigms and offers a new blueprint for financial stability and growth across the globe.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-doubles-down-on-1-5-million-bitcoin-as-institutional-exposure-looms/">Cathie Wood doubles down on $1.5 million Bitcoin as institutional exposure looms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/cathie-wood-doubles-down-on-1-5-million-bitcoin-as-institutional-exposure-looms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/cathie-wood-bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/cathie-wood-bitcoin.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock sees Bitcoin as integral part of financial system – little interest in other crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-sees-bitcoin-as-integral-part-of-financial-system-little-interest-in-other-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-sees-bitcoin-as-integral-part-of-financial-system-little-interest-in-other-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406480</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlackRock believes that Bitcoin (BTC) will become an integral part of the financial system over the coming decade as it increasingly melds with the best parts of the traditional financial system. The asset manager&#8217;s Head of Digital Assets, Robert Mitchnick, made the statement during Reflexivity Research&#8217;s Bitcoin Investor Day on March 22. FOX Business reporter [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-sees-bitcoin-as-integral-part-of-financial-system-little-interest-in-other-crypto/">BlackRock sees Bitcoin as integral part of financial system – little interest in other crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/blackrock/">BlackRock</a> believes that Bitcoin (<a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">BTC</a>) will become an integral part of the financial system over the coming decade as it increasingly melds with the best parts of the traditional financial system.</p>
<p>The asset manager&#8217;s Head of Digital Assets, Robert Mitchnick, made the statement during Reflexivity Research&#8217;s Bitcoin Investor Day on March 22. FOX Business reporter Eleanor Terrett <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1771191203012153808">reported</a> his comments via X.</p>
<p>Mitchnick said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Eventually we expect there will be a convergence where the best of the old system and the new technology will become fused into a new infrastructure system in finance.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Mitchnick also revealed that the company&#8217;s clients have minimal interest in crypto beyond Bitcoin and Ethereum (<a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/ethereum/">ETH</a>).</p>
<p>According to Mitchnick, Bitcoin is &#8220;overwhelmingly the number one priority&#8221; for clients, while Ethereum receives a &#8220;little bit&#8221; of priority and other crypto see &#8220;very little&#8221; interest.</p>
<p>He added that the company is not focused on other digital assets despite the crypto industry&#8217;s desire to see a &#8220;long tail&#8221; of such products.</p>
<h2>BlackRock&#8217;s crypto journey</h2>
<p>Mitchnick&#8217;s position is relevant due to BlackRock&#8217;s lead role in spot Bitcoin ETFs. The company currently offers the <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/products/ishares-bitcoin-trust/">iShares Bitcoin Trust</a> (IBIT) — the second-largest spot Bitcoin ETF, boasting $15.85 billion in assets under management (AUM).</p>
<p>BlackRock is also one of the firms pursuing a spot Ethereum ETF, with an application already submitted to the SEC. The regulator is expected to make a decision on the ETH ETF applications in May.</p>
<p>BlackRock has limited plans to support products for other crypto, it is expanding its focus on Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, recent media reports revealed that the firm plans to <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-looking-to-include-bitcoin-exposure-in-its-other-funds/">add Bitcoin exposure</a> to its other products.</p>
<p>Reports from <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-launches-100-million-tokenized-asset-fund-using-ethereum/">March 19</a> additionally indicate that BlackRock launched a tokenized asset fund that is in part funded by USDC on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-sees-bitcoin-as-integral-part-of-financial-system-little-interest-in-other-crypto/">BlackRock sees Bitcoin as integral part of financial system – little interest in other crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-sees-bitcoin-as-integral-part-of-financial-system-little-interest-in-other-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/blackrock-ibit.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/blackrock-ibit.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#8217;s legal woes mount as vulnerability threatening crypto security comes to light</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/apples-legal-woes-mount-as-vulnerability-threatening-crypto-security-comes-to-light/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/apples-legal-woes-mount-as-vulnerability-threatening-crypto-security-comes-to-light/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DoJ]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Academic researchers have unearthed a significant vulnerability within Apple&#8217;s M-series computing chips, potentially jeopardizing the security of private crypto keys. On the same day, the US Department of Justice (DOJ) filed an antitrust case against the iPhone maker, alleging monopoly practices detrimental to consumers, developers, and competitors. The vulnerability The research team identified the chips&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/apples-legal-woes-mount-as-vulnerability-threatening-crypto-security-comes-to-light/">Apple&#8217;s legal woes mount as vulnerability threatening crypto security comes to light</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Academic researchers have unearthed a significant vulnerability within <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/apple/">Apple&#8217;s</a> M-series computing chips, potentially jeopardizing the security of private crypto keys.</p>
<p>On the same day, the US Department of Justice (DOJ) filed an antitrust case against the iPhone maker, alleging monopoly practices detrimental to consumers, developers, and competitors.</p>
<h2>The vulnerability</h2>
<p>The research team identified the chips&#8217; data memory-dependent prefetcher (DMP) vulnerability.</p>
<p>Crypto analyst George <a href="https://twitter.com/odysseus0z/status/1771086795532280225">explained</a> that DMP is a hardware optimization that anticipates and preloads data into the CPU cache ahead of demand. However, it faces an issue where it occasionally confuses sensitive data, such as encryption keys, for memory addresses.</p>
<p>This phenomenon, known as &#8220;dereferencing pointers,&#8221; creates a vulnerability known as &#8220;side-channel attacks.&#8221;</p>
<p>The researchers demonstrated the capability to extract various encryption keys — including RSA, Diffie-Hellman, Kyber, and Dilithium — within 1 to 10 hours using a GoFetch attack. However, this exploit needs malicious and targeted <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/metamask-is-back-on-apples-app-store-after-briefly-leaving-the-platform/">crypto apps</a> to operate on the same CPU cluster.</p>
<p>For the attack to succeed, the malicious app must provide inputs to the crypto app and prompt it to execute operations, thereby gradually leaking the key. This exploit is interactive rather than passive and must bypass macOS security measures to perform on the system.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, rectifying this flaw is not straightforward as it originates from the microarchitectural design of the chips, rendering it unpatchable. However, implementing defensive measures within third-party encryption software can mitigate the risk.</p>
<h2>Legal trouble</h2>
<p>US authorities, supported by 16 state attorney generals, <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.njd.544402/gov.uscourts.njd.544402.1.0_3.pdf">filed</a> legal actions against Apple for its &#8220;walled garden&#8221; business model, which helped establish an allegedly illegal monopoly in the smartphone market.</p>
<p>The lawsuit alleged that Apple implemented &#8220;shapeshifting rules and restrictions in its App Store guidelines and developer agreements that would allow Apple to extract higher fees, thwart innovation, offer a less secure or degraded user experience, and throttle competitive alternatives.&#8221;</p>
<p>They added that these suppressive rules were implemented across <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/apple-teases-generative-ai-plans-hints-at-user-devices-playing-a-role/">varying products</a>, including text messaging, smartwatches, and digital wallets, among many others.</p>
<p>Crypto community members have highlighted the <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/apple-entered-anti-crypto-agreements-with-competitors-class-action-suit-claims/">importance of this lawsuit to the indust</a>ry, with Hish Bouabdallah, the founder of Tribes Protocol, <a href="https://twitter.com/hishboy/status/1771160416351092943?s=46&amp;t=aw6ZR-6aD050XLPVXY8AQA">saying</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;If Apple loses this battle, it could pave the way for crypto payments in the U.S., enabling seamless transactions using services like <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/products/coinbase-wallet/#:~:text=Coinbase%20Wallet%20is%20a%20software,cryptocurrency%2C%20and%20send%20crypto%20to">Coinbase Wallet</a> with just a double tap and FaceID.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/apples-legal-woes-mount-as-vulnerability-threatening-crypto-security-comes-to-light/">Apple&#8217;s legal woes mount as vulnerability threatening crypto security comes to light</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/apples-legal-woes-mount-as-vulnerability-threatening-crypto-security-comes-to-light/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/apple-computer-chip.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/apple-computer-chip.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Recent Bitcoin buyers show unyielding optimism, pushing cost basis upward despite price surges</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/insights/recent-bitcoin-buyers-show-unyielding-optimism-pushing-cost-basis-upward-despite-price-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James Van Straten]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?post_type=crypto_insight&#038;p=406299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Quick Take Utilizing data from Glassnode to estimate a market-wide cost basis reveals intriguing trends in the average price at which coins are withdrawn from exchanges. The information, segregated into cohorts, uncovers an upward trajectory on a cost basis, indicating a trend of purchasing Bitcoin at incrementally higher prices. Most notably, the 2024 cohorts experienced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/recent-bitcoin-buyers-show-unyielding-optimism-pushing-cost-basis-upward-despite-price-surges/">Recent Bitcoin buyers show unyielding optimism, pushing cost basis upward despite price surges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Quick Take</h2>
<p>Utilizing data from <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/workbench/7246fcba-ca1f-42d8-5a84-4312ae4fc784?s=1710514315&amp;u=1711119115&amp;zoom=7">Glassnode</a> to estimate a market-wide cost basis reveals intriguing trends in the average price at which coins are withdrawn from exchanges. The information, segregated into cohorts, uncovers an upward trajectory on a cost basis, indicating a trend of purchasing Bitcoin at incrementally higher prices.</p>
<p>Most notably, the 2024 cohorts experienced a significant upswing, seeing an average profit margin of about $10,500, which translates to an approximately 20% gain from their initial cost basis ($52,478), according to data from Glassnode.</p>
<figure id="attachment_406391" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-406391" style="width: 1800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-406391 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-1.png" alt="Exchange Average Withdrawal Price (by Year): (Source: Glassnode)" width="1800" height="1013" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-1.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-1-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-1-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-1-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1800px) 100vw, 1800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-406391" class="wp-caption-text">Exchange Average Withdrawal Price (by Year): (Source: Glassnode)</figcaption></figure>
<p>Interestingly, the 2021 cohort managed to significantly reduce their cost basis from $47,000 to a more conservative $36,971, as highlighted by recent <em>CryptoSlate</em> <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/2021-bitcoin-investors-showcase-long-term-holding-resilience/">data analysis</a>. Despite the reduction, the cost basis for all cohorts has risen in recent months, showing an unwavering dedication to buying Bitcoin regardless of increasing prices.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Year</th>
<th>Price</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>All-time</td>
<td>$13,689</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2017+</td>
<td>$18,082</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2018+</td>
<td>$21,758</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2019+</td>
<td>$25,018</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2020+</td>
<td>$29,173</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2021+</td>
<td>$36,971</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2022+</td>
<td>$32,139</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2023+</td>
<td>$36,058</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2024+</td>
<td>$52,478</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center; font-size: small;">Source: Glassnode</p>
<p>The 2023 cohort, exhibiting the most bullish behavior, showcased a dramatic rise in cost basis from roughly $26,500 in October 2023 to a present figure of $36,058, suggesting a potential to surpass the 2021 cohort.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/recent-bitcoin-buyers-show-unyielding-optimism-pushing-cost-basis-upward-despite-price-surges/">Recent Bitcoin buyers show unyielding optimism, pushing cost basis upward despite price surges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-2.png" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/RP-2.png" length="1800" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Foundation makes ORB software open-source</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-foundation-makes-orb-software-open-source/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-foundation-makes-orb-software-open-source/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Assad Jafri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Watch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Worldcoin Foundation has released the core software components of its ORB technology into the open-source domain, providing a key technological step forward in verifying human identity online with enhanced privacy and security. The release, now available on GitHub under MIT/Apache 2.0 licenses, supports the Foundation&#8217;s ongoing efforts to improve transparency in the digital verification [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-foundation-makes-orb-software-open-source/">Worldcoin Foundation makes ORB software open-source</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/worldcoin/">Worldcoin Foundation</a> has released the <a href="https://worldcoin.org/blog/engineering/worldcoin-foundation-open-sources-core-components-orb-software">core software components</a> of its ORB technology into the open-source domain, providing a key technological step forward in verifying human identity online with enhanced privacy and security.</p>
<p>The release, now available on GitHub under MIT/Apache 2.0 licenses, supports the Foundation&#8217;s ongoing efforts to improve transparency in the digital verification process, alongside its hardware and iris recognition technology that had previously gone public.</p>
<p>The move is part of the Foundation&#8217;s efforts to be more <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-clarifies-legality-issues-following-spains-ban/">transparent</a> about its biometric data collection process after multiple countries raised concerns over the practice.</p>
<p>Worldcoin (<a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/worldcoin-org-wld/">WLD</a>) responded positively to the announcement and recorded gains for the day despite the overall crypto market bleeding to recent lows.</p>
<p>As of press time, WLD was trading at $8.26, up 4% over 24 hours — with a market cap of $1.28 billion, based on CryptoSlate data.</p>
<h2>Comprehensive compute stack</h2>
<p>The ORB&#8217;s function is to authenticate users by processing their eye and face images, distinguishing genuine human users from automated systems or artificial intelligence.</p>
<p>The latest open-source release focuses on the software responsible for capturing images and securely transmitting them to the World App, underlining the Foundation&#8217;s commitment to open and verifiable processes.</p>
<p>Worldcoin&#8217;s initial developer, Tools for Humanity (TFH), has built a comprehensive compute stack for the ORB around the NVIDIA Jetson platform, enabling real-time processing of camera feeds for quick World ID verification.</p>
<p>This setup utilizes Rust applications and NVIDIA&#8217;s TensorRT engine, emphasizing high performance and security in handling sensitive biometric data.</p>
<p>The code release provides insights into the Orb&#8217;s functionality, including image capture, biometric processing, and the secure encryption and transmission of user data. By making these components public, the Worldcoin Foundation aims to showcase the underlying technology&#8217;s robustness and reliability in privacy and security matters.</p>
<h2>ORB audit</h2>
<p>Trail of Bits has completed a <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/trail-of-bits-completes-worldcoin-security-audits-finds-no-vulnerabilities/">security audit</a> of ORB technology, following <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/kenyan-authorities-claim-worldcoins-activities-amount-to-espionage/">concerns</a> raised by <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-files-lawsuit-to-appeal-spains-ban/">global regulators</a> over its biometric data collection practices.</p>
<p>The audit identified 12 vulnerabilities, including one severe issue, but affirmed the technology&#8217;s adherence to privacy standards in handling personally identifiable information. Worldcoin has addressed the high-severity issue post-audit and is implementing further improvements based on the recommendations.</p>
<p>The Foundation plans to continue enhancing the software&#8217;s transparency and reducing dependence on proprietary components. This initial release includes critical elements such as orb-core, orb-attest, and orb-firmware.</p>
<p>Future endeavors will likely involve further opening the development process and improving the Orb&#8217;s security and privacy framework, potentially serving as a model for similar technological initiatives.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-foundation-makes-orb-software-open-source/">Worldcoin Foundation makes ORB software open-source</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/worldcoin-foundation-makes-orb-software-open-source/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/worldcoin-orb.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/worldcoin-orb.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Montenegro&#8217;s Supreme Court stalls Do Kwon&#8217;s extradition amid legal tussle</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/montenegros-supreme-court-stalls-do-kwons-extradition-amid-legal-tussle/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/montenegros-supreme-court-stalls-do-kwons-extradition-amid-legal-tussle/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[montenegro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=406428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Montenegro&#8217;s Supreme Court has intervened in Do Kwon&#8217;s extradition to South Korea, putting the process on hold indefinitely, according to a March 22 translation of the Court notice. The Court said it overturned previous decisions from two lower courts that had greenlit Kwon&#8217;s extradition to South Korea because of the Supreme State Prosecutor&#8217;s Office&#8217;s request. Consequently, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/montenegros-supreme-court-stalls-do-kwons-extradition-amid-legal-tussle/">Montenegro&#8217;s Supreme Court stalls Do Kwon&#8217;s extradition amid legal tussle</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Montenegro&#8217;s Supreme Court has intervened in <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/do-kwon/">Do Kwon&#8217;s</a> extradition to South Korea, putting the process on hold indefinitely, according to a March 22 translation of the Court <a href="https://sudovi-me.translate.goog/vrhs/sadrzaj/ONBM?_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;_x_tr_hl=en-US&amp;_x_tr_pto=wapp">notice</a>.</p>
<p>The Court said it overturned previous decisions from two lower courts that had greenlit Kwon&#8217;s extradition to South Korea because of the Supreme State Prosecutor&#8217;s Office&#8217;s request.</p>
<p>Consequently, Kwon&#8217;s extradition process to South Korea would remain suspended &#8220;until a decision is made on the submitted request for the protection of legality.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Supreme Court Council said the ruling was in line with its powers &#8220;to postpone or stop the execution of the final court decision.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Extradition battle</h2>
<p>On March 21, Montenegro&#8217;s Supreme State Prosecutor&#8217;s Office <a href="https://sudovi-me.translate.goog/vrdt/sadrzaj/W8V9?_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;_x_tr_hl=en-US&amp;_x_tr_pto=wapp">contested</a> the decision of the High Court of Podgorica and Appellate Court to <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/montenegro-decides-to-extradite-do-kwon-to-south-korea-in-retrial/">extradite</a> the Terraform Labs co-founder to South Korea instead of the US.</p>
<p>The prosecutor&#8217;s office asserted that the High Court overstepped its authority by conducting a hasty legal process in reaching the decision, which should have fallen under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Justice.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the prosecutor&#8217;s office criticized the Appellate Court for neglecting to consider the state prosecutor&#8217;s position in the appeal process, which <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/montenegro-court-rejects-do-kwons-appeal-clears-way-for-extradition-to-south-korea/">upheld</a> Kwon&#8217;s extradition to South Korea.</p>
<p>Over the past year, Kwon has been in Montenegrin custody following his <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/terras-do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-imprisonment-in-montenegro/">arrest</a> and imprisonment for attempting to use fake travel documents in the Balkan country.</p>
<p>Since then, South Korea and the United States have been <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/montenegrin-appeals-court-overturns-do-kwon-extradition-decision/">competing</a> to bring Kwon to their shores to answer for his role in the collapse of the <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/terra-classic/">Terra</a> ecosystem in 2022.</p>
<p>In the US, the SEC <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sec-file-lawsuit-against-terraform-labs-do-kwon/">alleged</a> that Terraform Labs and Kwon offered and sold unregistered securities and engaged in fraud.</p>
<p>Similarly, South Korean authorities are trying Terra co-founder Daniel Shin for <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/south-korea-indicts-terra-co-founder-daniel-shin/">fraud</a>, illegal fundraising, and violating capital market laws.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/montenegros-supreme-court-stalls-do-kwons-extradition-amid-legal-tussle/">Montenegro&#8217;s Supreme Court stalls Do Kwon&#8217;s extradition amid legal tussle</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/montenegros-supreme-court-stalls-do-kwons-extradition-amid-legal-tussle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/montenegro-court.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/montenegro-court.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is the anticipated post-halving Bitcoin hash rate correction?</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/insights/anticipated-post-halving-hash-rate-correction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James Van Straten]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?post_type=crypto_insight&#038;p=406237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Quick Take As the Bitcoin halving nears, now just under 4,300 blocks away and slated for April 20, the network has experienced a notable surge in hash rate, registering a 15% increase in 2024. The 14-day moving average hash rate is approaching record levels, currently peaking at approximately 598 eh/s. This upswing in hash rate suggests [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/anticipated-post-halving-hash-rate-correction/">What is the anticipated post-halving Bitcoin hash rate correction?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Quick Take</h2>
<p>As the Bitcoin <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoins-next-halving-could-spell-a-surge-in-price-as-demand-outpaces-supply/">halving</a> nears, now just under 4,300 blocks away and slated for April 20, the network has experienced a notable surge in <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoins-hash-rate-hits-record-high/">hash rate</a>, registering a 15% increase in 2024. The 14-day moving average hash rate is approaching record levels, currently peaking at approximately 598 eh/s.</p>
<figure id="attachment_406330" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-406330" style="width: 1800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-406330 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/HR-2.png" alt="Hash Rate: (Source: Glassnode)" width="1800" height="1013" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/HR-2.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/HR-2-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/HR-2-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/HR-2-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/HR-2-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1800px) 100vw, 1800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-406330" class="wp-caption-text">Hash Rate: (Source: Glassnode)</figcaption></figure>
<p>This upswing in hash rate suggests that miners are ramping up their operations to optimize earnings before the halving event, a sentiment echoed by <a href="https://x.com/mikealfred/status/1770892564679295252?s=20">Mike Alfred</a>, a board member at IREN Energy. Alfred predicts a notable post-halving correction in the global hash rate, attributing this to the widespread use of older mining equipment struggling to remain profitable.</p>
<p>Supporting this observation, <em>CryptoSlate</em> <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoins-network-sees-a-380-increase-in-hash-rate-since-the-start-of-the-current-cycle/">previously highlighted</a> the trend of increasing hash rate as a halving event nears, noting that such growth is typical in the 4-6 months leading up to a halving.</p>
<p>Historical analysis shows a consistent pattern of miner capitulation post-halving, with significant drops in hash rate: 39% in December 2012, 11% in August 2016, and 26% in May 2020. Considering these precedents, a similar downturn, approximately 25% based on the average of past events, is a reasonable expectation following the next halving.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Halving</th>
<th>Capitulation</th>
<th>Hash Rate drop %</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Nov 2012</td>
<td>Dec 2012</td>
<td>39</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>July 2016</td>
<td>August 2016</td>
<td>11</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>May 2020</td>
<td>May 2020</td>
<td>26</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>The Hash Ribbon analysis, a notable market indicator for predicting Bitcoin&#8217;s price bottoms linked to miner capitulation, further illuminates the anticipated trend. This indicator identifies shifts from negative to positive price momentum when the 30-day moving average (MA) of the hash rate crosses above the 60-day MA. Such a crossover signals the conclusion of the most intense phase of miner capitulation.</p>
<p>Examining three distinct instances, it&#8217;s observed that miner capitulation typically begins when the 30-day MA falls below the 60-day MA, a pattern often seen post-halving. Approximately a month following this crossover, the 30-day MA tends to rise above the 60-day MA. An appreciation of Bitcoin&#8217;s value usually accompanies this transition.</p>
<figure id="attachment_406311" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-406311" style="width: 1800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-406311 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2012-1.png" alt="Hash Ribbon: 2012 Halving: (Source: Glassnode)" width="1800" height="1013" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2012-1.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2012-1-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2012-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2012-1-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2012-1-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1800px) 100vw, 1800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-406311" class="wp-caption-text">Hash Ribbon: 2012 Halving: (Source: Glassnode)</figcaption></figure>
<figure id="attachment_406307" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-406307" style="width: 729px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-406307 " src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2016.png" alt="Hash Ribbon: 2016 Halving: (Source: Glassnode)" width="729" height="407" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2016.png 1222w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2016-300x167.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2016-1024x571.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2016-768x429.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 729px) 100vw, 729px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-406307" class="wp-caption-text">Hash Ribbon: 2016 Halving: (Source: Glassnode)</figcaption></figure>
<figure id="attachment_406313" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-406313" style="width: 752px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-406313 " src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020.png" alt="Hash Ribbon: 2020 Halving: (Source: Glassnode)" width="752" height="423" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 752px) 100vw, 752px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-406313" class="wp-caption-text">Hash Ribbon: 2020 Halving: (Source: Glassnode)</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/anticipated-post-halving-hash-rate-correction/">What is the anticipated post-halving Bitcoin hash rate correction?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020.png" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2020.png" length="1800" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
