<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptonews</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptonews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptonews.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:45:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Indonesian College Student Behind NFT Selfies Success Returns with $1.8 Million Meme Coin Presale</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/indonesian-college-student-behind-nft-selfies-success-returns-with-1-8-million-meme-coin-presale.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188490</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sultan Gustaf Al Ghozali, the Indonesian college student who became an internet sensation in 2022 for selling millions of dollars worth of NFTs featuring his daily selfies, is back in the spotlight with a meme coin project.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/indonesian-college-student-behind-nft-selfies-success-returns-with-1-8-million-meme-coin-presale.htm">Indonesian College Student Behind NFT Selfies Success Returns with $1.8 Million Meme Coin Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sultan Gustaf Al Ghozali, the Indonesian college student who became an internet sensation in 2022 for selling millions of dollars worth of NFTs featuring his daily selfies, is back in the spotlight with a meme coin presale.</p>
<p>Ghozali <a href="https://x.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771717570586095647?s=20">announced</a> the second edition of &#8220;Ghozali Everyday&#8221; on March 224th. This project uniquely blends meme coins with NFTs on the Base blockchain. The project&#8217;s presale surpassed its initial target of 400 Ether (ETH), reaching 527 ETH.</p>
<h2>Ghozali Returns to X with Meme Coin and NFT Hybrid Project: Announces Second Iteration of &#8216;Ghozali Everyday&#8217;</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Uploading my photo into nft lol<a href="https://t.co/E3Q4sBmN26">https://t.co/E3Q4sBmN26</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NFT?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NFT</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/opensea?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#opensea</a> <a href="https://t.co/rD51rdcpzp">pic.twitter.com/rD51rdcpzp</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1480524562609573892?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 10, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In January 2022, Sultan Gustaf Al Ghozali, a 22-year-old computer science student from Semarang, Indonesia, made waves in the crypto world by minting nonfungible tokens (NFTs) featuring daily selfies he took over five years. He captured nearly 1,000 self-portraits that chronicled his journey from 18 to 22.</p>
<p>These selfies, taken as a personal reflection on his academic journey, depicted him sitting or standing in front of his computer in various poses. This collection, named &#8220;Ghozali Everyday,&#8221; quickly gained traction within the crypto community, earning Ghozali, a student at the time, more than $1 million.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Just took the last selfie when I graduated from college and finally i can stop this doing this shit almost every day </p>
<p>6 years taking selfies every day is the stupidest idea I ever came up with, but luckily I can make money from it <a href="https://t.co/qftRH6WRua">pic.twitter.com/qftRH6WRua</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1694679286182293848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Reflecting on his success, Ghozali expressed gratitude for the support and opportunity to turn a personal project into a profitable venture. He announced on X that with his graduation, he would no longer continue the daily selfie tradition, marking the end of an era that unexpectedly brought him financial success and recognition in the NFT space.</p>
<p>On March 22, after being absent from X for several months, Ghozali returned amidst the rising interest in meme coins. He made a significant announcement about the second iteration of his project, &#8220;Ghozali Everyday,&#8221; which now combined meme coins and NFTs in an ERC-404 format on the Base blockchain. To kick things off, he <a href="https://x.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771178492442312969?s=20">initiated an airdrop for the holders</a> of the first Ghozali Everyday NFTs.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">TuRn On NOtIfIcaTioN, Drop sOmE NeWs SoOn <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6ce.png" alt="🛎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/7zJ7BIrA2j">pic.twitter.com/7zJ7BIrA2j</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771178492442312969?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Following this, on March 24, Ghozali unveiled the launch of the second part of &#8220;Ghozali Everyday.&#8221; He disclosed the presale address with an intended cap set at 400 ETH. However, the presale quickly exceeded this limit, <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x4553555f6a451EC415f698A524B5e02E38acFB6C">reaching 527 ETH</a>, equivalent to around $1.8 million at the time of writing.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">launching the second part of Ghozali Everyday: a memecoin and nft hybrid on Base 🛜</p>
<p>PRESALE is open, send eth to 0x4553555f6a451EC415f698A524B5e02E38acFB6C (eth mainnet/base only) <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64f-1f3fb.png" alt="🙏🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>min 0.05 ETH <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f448-1f3fb.png" alt="👈🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />max 2 ETH <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2705.png" alt="✅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />cap 400 ETH <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6ce.png" alt="🛎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />100% of ETH raised goes to LP 🛜</p>
<p>Ghozali 404    <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f646-1f3fb-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🙆🏻‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />… <a href="https://t.co/HYAfHkh1z3">pic.twitter.com/HYAfHkh1z3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771717570586095647?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Despite the overwhelming response, Ghozali took to X to <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771724578005340402">announce</a> that he would refund those who sent more than 2 ETH after the cap was reached. He also clarified that the cap would not increase, ensuring fairness and transparency in the project&#8217;s execution.</p>
<h2>Solana&#8217;s Meme Coin Craze: Traders Flock Amid Bitcoin&#8217;s Bullish Surge</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Amidst the recent bullish run of Bitcoin (BTC) prices, there has been a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-solana-meme-coins/">resurgence of interest in meme coins</a>, mainly driven by traders on the Solana blockchain. Notably, data indicates that presale projects on Solana raised an astounding $100 million within just three days, from March 15 to 18.</p>
<p>This surge in funding reflects a trend where meme coin founders are leveraging t<a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-memecoin-sector-surges-by-45-as-traders-pour-100-million-in-72-hours.htm">oken presales to raise significant amounts</a> for unreleased coins. The presale mechanism typically involves investors sending cryptocurrency to a specified wallet address in exchange for the distribution of tokens once the coin is officially launched. Nevertheless, there&#8217;s no guarantee of receiving tokens in return, making <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-presale-scams-take-a-toll-as-meme-coin-season-continues.htm">presales susceptible to fraud and scams.</a></p>
<p>The recent frenzy surrounding meme coin presales peaked with the launch of Book of Meme on March 14. Created by the pseudonymous artist Darkfarms1, the coin initially held a valuation of approximately $4 million but skyrocketed by an astonishing 36,000% within just 56 hours, reaching a peak market capitalization of $1.45 billion.</p>
<p>While the profitability of meme coins has captivated the crypto space, concerns about the presale model and its associated risks surfaced.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/indonesian-college-student-behind-nft-selfies-success-returns-with-1-8-million-meme-coin-presale.htm">Indonesian College Student Behind NFT Selfies Success Returns with $1.8 Million Meme Coin Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123548/1711370147-1711370134479_processed.jpg" length="82747" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dead or Alive: Number of Cryptocurrencies Worldwide from 2013 to January 2024</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-globally-2013-2024.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sead Fadilpašić]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exclusives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2024 crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2024 began with over 9,000 cryptocurrencies available globally, 13% fewer projects ‘alive’ compared to the all-time high reached in 2022, accordign to Statista data.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-globally-2013-2024.htm">Dead or Alive: Number of Cryptocurrencies Worldwide from 2013 to January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>2024 began with over 9,000 cryptocurrencies created and still available globally, </span><a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/863917/number-crypto-coins-tokens/"><span>according</span></a><span> to </span><b>Statista</b><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>This is 13% fewer projects ‘alive’ compared to the all-time high reached in February 2022.</span></p>
<p><span>That said, between February 2023 and January 2024, there was a 4% increase in the number of available projects. </span></p>
<p><span>The road to the current volume was turbulent, yet it witnessed only four significant drops.</span></p>
<p><span>This is impressive, given that that that road started at 66 coins in 2013. </span></p>
<p><span>Therefore, the crypto world has seen a 13,573% jump in the number of cryptocurrencies between 2013 and 2024.</span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="2cb9d6fa-78aa-40de-9377-dcddeb7cb085" data-type="interactive" data-title="Dead Coins PR"></div>
<p><span>Individuals, groups, or companies can create a coin on an existing blockchain or create a new chain entirely. </span></p>
<p><span>Reasons for creating cryptocurrencies vary, but generally speaking, they may serve as a solution to specific real-world payment issues, or the creators seek to make a profit at the detriment of the users and the sector.</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, when we talk about cryptocurrencies, we actually talk about several different kinds of coins. Besides the most popular </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/"><b>Bitcoin (BTC)</b></a><span> and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ethereum/"><b>Ethereum (ETH)</b></a><span>, there are thousands of altcoins, including the (in)famous meme coins, as well as stablecoins, governance and utility tokens, and many more.</span></p>
<p><span><div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"> </span></p>
<h3><b><i>How is cryptocurrency created?</i></b></h3>
<p><em>It is worth noting that creating a cryptocurrency is a relatively easy process, and anybody can do it.</em></p>
<p><em>Whether that project achieves any significance – or survives at all – is a different story. Most do not.</em></p>
<p><em>There are several different<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/how-to-make-a-cryptocurrency-5215343"> options</a> for making a cryptocurrency. Creating a blockchain and a native token or modifying the existing blockchain are the more difficult options and require more technical knowledge and training.</em></p>
<p><em>Meanwhile, making a coin on an existing chain, or paying a developer to make it, is a lot easier.</em></p>
<p><em>Many will opt to create a cryptocurrency on an existing chain, and there are even<a href="https://www.walletbuilders.com/"> online tools</a> that allow the creation of tokens and blockchains without programming knowledge.</em></p>
<p><em>The more one wishes to customize the coin, the more knowledge is needed.</em></p>
<p><em>Once the crypto is created, the coins are minted for issuance.</em></p>
<p><em>This is the simplest, most basic explanation. Serious projects will invest a lot of time and money into their crypto, they will have a highly skilled team of developers constantly working on it, and the project will be thoroughly audited.</em></p>
</div></div>
<p><span>Meanwhile, there are other estimates out there per which there may be some 20,000 cryptocurrencies in existence. “Most of these are either inactive or discontinued,” said Statista.</span></p>
<p><span>These coins are typically referred to as ‘dead.’ They cease to exist due to a number of reasons, including halted development, lack of users or traders, fraud exposure, and more.</span></p>
<p><span>Per </span><b>99bitcoins</b><span>, as of February 2023, </span><a href="https://99bitcoins.com/deadcoins/"><span>there are at least 1,774 dead coins</span></a><span>. And these are the reported projects.</span></p>
<p><span>A 2024 report </span><a href="https://alphaquest.io/blog/dead-coins-report-2024/"><span>conducted by </span><b>AlphaQuest</b><span> and </span><b>Storible</b></a><span>, which analyzed 12,343 cryptos, found that nearly two-thirds of cryptocurrencies created over the past several years “have met their demise.”</span></p>
<h2><b>2013-2020: From 66 Coins to 4,000</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The crypto industry has seen significant growth in the seven years up to early 2021, as per Statista data. </span></p>
<p><span>While it may be difficult to fathom today, there was no </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/"><span>top 100 coins per market capitalization</span></a><span> to talk about in 2013. At the time, there were only 66 available cryptos.</span></p>
<p><span>However, within a single year, the 66 jumped 666.6 % to 506 in 2014.</span></p>
<p><span>Over the following two years, the market saw a more modest increase: there were 562 coins recorded in 2015 and 644 in 2016.</span></p>
<p><span>This is where we notice another sharp increase in the number of cryptocurrencies, surpassing the 1,000 mark. In 2017, it increased 107% compared to 2016, hitting 1,335 coins.</span></p>
<p><span>Two years later, in 2019, the 2,000 mark was surpassed, with the number of coins reaching 2,817. </span></p>
<p><span>Between November 2019 and February 2021, another 1,694 coins were added to the available lot – nearly doubling the amount and totaling 4,501.</span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="dd37dae5-fd09-452b-953b-bcd2f250289b" data-type="interactive" data-title="Copy: Dead Coins PR- 2013-20"></div>
<p><span>This 2020-2021 period and the bull run that marked it were very significant for the industry. </span></p>
<p><b>CoinGecko</b> <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/how-many-cryptocurrencies-failed"><span>found</span></a><span> that most dead cryptocurrencies came from projects launched during this bull run.</span></p>
<p><span>The data aggregator stated in a January 2024 report that, </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“7,530 cryptocurrencies from that period have died, accounting for 53.6% of all dead cryptocurrencies on CoinGecko. Over 11,000 cryptocurrencies were listed on CoinGecko during the previous bull run, with ~70% having shut down since.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>However, when the researchers looked at the results of the 2017-2018 bull run, they discovered that 1,450 projects shut down. “This is on the back of over 3,000 cryptocurrencies listed, resulting in a similar fail rate of ~70%.”</span></p>
<p><span>As for the reasons behind the high rates of dead coins, CoinGeko identified the ease of deploying tokens and the rise in popularity of meme coins as contributing factors.</span></p>
<p><span>Many <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-ecosystem-boasts-over-2500-monthly-active-developers-reports-solana-foundation.htm">meme coin projects</a> launched but without a product to offer and were soon abandoned entirely.</span></p>
<h2><b>2021-2022: Hitting the All-Time-High</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>2021 saw major increases in the number of available cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span>While there were 4,501 coins in February, by July that same year, the number was up to 6,044.</span></p>
<p><span>Soon after, we notice the first drop in this ten-year time frame. In August 2021, the number fell to 5,840. </span></p>
<p><span>That said, just two months after that, it surpassed the July level, climbing to 6,826, and ended the year with 7,557.</span></p>
<p><span>This ‘rally’ resulted in a new all-time high (ATH) at the beginning of 2022. </span></p>
<p><span>Between November 2021 and January 2022, the number was up 31.4% to 9,929.</span></p>
<p><span>Then in February 2022, it hit its final ATH to date: 10,397 different coins existing in the nascent ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span>Therefore, between February 2021 and February 2022, the number of coins increased by 131%. </span></p>
<p><span>Following the ATH, the space recorded a 10.5% fall in November 2022 to 9,310. </span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="f3950e6a-7ef0-46b1-94d2-a082d5057bd6" data-type="interactive" data-title="Copy: Copy: Dead Coins PR- 2021-22"></div>
<p><span>According to CoinGecko, nearly 6,000 cryptocurrencies from 2021 failed. The report stated that,</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“Cryptocurrencies created in 2021 have suffered the worst, with 5,724 having died as of January 2024. Over 70% of cryptocurrencies listed on CoinGecko in 2021 have died, making it the worst year for project launches.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>2022 follows it as another bad year: 3,520 listed coins died (~60%) by January 2024.</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, the AlphaQuest and Storible report also found that most cryptocurrencies born during the 2020-2021 bull run failed, saying:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“In particular, out of the 4,834 crypto projects introduced during the bullish trend, 72% failed to survive.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><b>2023-2024: 13% Drop from ATH</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>A notable development in 2023 is that the year saw two more drops in the number of cryptocurrencies. This is as many drops as recorded over the previous nine years combined.</span></p>
<p><span>All in all, the numbers haven’t moved much since the November 2022 level of 9,310.</span></p>
<p><span>February 2023 saw a decrease to 8,685, followed by a slight increase to 9,321, then dropping again to 8,866 by the end of the year. </span></p>
<p><span>January 2024 began with 9,024 cryptocurrencies. Compared to February 2023, this is a 3.9% increase.</span></p>
<p><span>However, compared to the February 2022 ATH, January 2024 saw a 13.2% fall in the number of cryptocurrencies available.</span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="a87432b1-597a-476e-af69-ad74b085f516" data-type="interactive" data-title="Copy: Copy: Copy: Dead Coins PR- 2021-22"></div>
<p><span>That said, between 2013 and 2024, the crypto space witnessed a 13,572.7% rise in the number of cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span>CoinGecko found that 289 cryptocurrencies listed on the platform in 2023 subsequently died, stating:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“This represents a failure rate of &lt;10%, with over 4,000 cryptocurrencies listed, a sharp decline from previous years.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>The AlphaQuest and Storible report stated that, among 12,343 crypto projects investigated, 8,854 have become defunct in the past year.</span></p>
<p><span>Leading up to 2023, it said, there has been a decrease in the cryptocurrency market, leading to the death of 65% of projects.</span></p>
<p><span>Per this report, “2023 is the toughest year in the 2020-2023 cycle, with nearly 60% of dead coins disappearing during that period.”</span></p>
<p><span>That said, 2023 was indeed a difficult year for crypto projects, bearing the brunt of the 2022 crypto industry crisis. </span></p>
<p><span>The entire space suffered due to the bear market fallout and the domino effect that began in 2022 with the collapse of the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-appeals-extradition-decision-amid-claims-of-political-pressure.htm"><b>Terra/Luna</b></a><span> ecosystem, followed by the infamous fall of the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-ceo-slams-attempt-to-reduce-sbf-sentence.htm"><b>FTX</b></a><span> exchange and its sister company </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/alameda-research-drops-lawsuit-against-grayscale-amid-gbtc-outflows.htm"><b>Alameda Research</b></a><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>These events were so monumental that their effects are still felt, and the companies’ executives are facing prison time.</span></p>
<p><span>Then, after months of struggling, crypto lending and trading firm </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-agrees-to-pay-21m-fine-to-settle-sec-crypto-lending-charges.htm"><b>Genesis</b></a><span>, a unit of the </span><b>Digital Currency Group</b><span> (DCG), </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-files-for-bankruptcy-as-it-seeks-protection-from-its-creditors-which-dcg-unit-next-fail.htm"><span>filed for bankruptcy</span></a><span> following a significant loan loss to the now also defunct </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis-seeks-court-help-to-reduce-settlement-payout-to-3ac.htm"><b>Three Arrows Capital</b></a><span>.</span></p>
<p><span>The aftershocks impacted numerous projects and coins. Companies like </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-network-announces-unstaking-of-ethereum-holdings-to-facilitate-distribution-to-creditors.htm"><b>Celsius</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-digital-announces-liquidation-shutdown-following-failed-ftx-binanceus-deals.htm"><b>Voyager</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-clients-can-now-submit-withdrawal-requests-as-bankruptcy-plan-takes-effect.htm"><b>BlockFi</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-platform-recur-to-shut-down-after-raising-50m-two-years-ago/"><b>RECUR</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-firm-lbry-ceases-operations-cites-insurmountable-debt.htm"><b>LBRY</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-niftys-shuts-down-tel-aviv-stock-exchange-signs-ground-breaking-deal-with-fireblocks-aventus-partners-with-vodafone-htm.htm"><b>Nifty’s</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bittrex-global-to-halt-all-trading-in-december.htm"><b>Bittrex Global</b></a><span>, and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billion-dollar-crypto-payments-firm-wyre-shut-down-amid-market-conditions.htm"><b>Wyre</b></a><span> all announced they’d wind down their operations in 2022 and 2023, citing hostile market conditions and/or debts.</span></p>
<p><span>Therefore, </span><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/659195da8efdab762672810b/"><span>according</span></a><span> to </span><b>CoinMarketCap</b><span>, these project’s coins are just some of those that died over 2023.</span></p>
<p><span>Losses from these various collapses numbered in the billions. FTX alone had an $8 billion hole in its accounts.</span></p>
<p><span>The collapses also showcased how interconnected the crypto ecosystem was at the time. </span></p>
<p><span>Poor management, mismanagement of funds, lack of liquidity, and cyberattacks contributed to the fallout, fueling the bear market, which in turn increased the pressure on the market participants until many buckled under it and went bankrupt.</span></p>
<h2><b>2025: Could This Be The Year of the Most Crypto Projects Launched?</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>After the Terra crash, 35% of crypto projects were deemed defunct, the AlphaQuest and Storible report said. And after the FTX fall, 32% of crypto projects closed shop. </span></p>
<p><span>Half of the cryptocurrencies backed by Three Arrows Capital subsequently failed.</span></p>
<p><span>“Other top-tier VCs with over half of their projects in their portfolio having died include </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-supports-coinbases-case-against-the-sec-files-amicus-curiae-brief.htm"><b>Paradigm</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-blockchain-cryptogpt-secures-10-million-in-funding-valued-at-250-million-bull-market-back.htm"><b>DWF Labs</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/polychain-warns-users-against-engaging-with-ceos-x-account-following-hack.htm"><b>Polychain Capital</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/a16z-backed-projects-sold-tokens-and-nfts-contrary-to-claims-by-general-partner-chris-dixon.htm"><b>a16z</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/animoca-brands-and-hashkey-sign-strategic-partnership-deal-more-crypto-news.htm"><b>Animoca Brands</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-investor-binance-splits-from-venture-capital-arm.htm"><b>Binance Labs</b></a><span>, and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/investor-letter-shocker-multicoin-capitals-hedge-fund-reports-914-loss-2022-heres-what-happened.htm"><b>Multicoin Capital</b></a><span>,” it said.</span></p>
<p><span>No ecosystem was safe. </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/cardano/"><b>Cardano</b></a><span> witnessed 74% of the projects in its ecosystem go defunct. For Terra, it was 74% of the projects. Furthermore, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/celo/"><b>Celo</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/harmony-one/"><b>Harmony</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/near-near-protocol/"><b>Near</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/zilliqa/"><b>Zilliqa</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/moonriver/"><b>Moonriver</b></a><span>, and others all experienced “notable losses.”</span></p>
<p><span>Meanwhile, the report found that a whopping 93% of the dead projects suffered from low liquidity or trading volume. </span></p>
<p><span>58% of them had </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/over-65-of-crypto-related-tweets-and-84-of-conversations-on-reddit-were-positive-in-2023.htm"><b>Twitter</b></a><span> accounts or websites that were either inactive or deleted, and 48% were removed from major tracking platforms such as </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinmarketcap-launches-chatgpt-plugin-simplify-crypto-analysis.htm"><b>CoinMarketCap</b></a><span>.</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, the average lifespan of a crypto project is three years, “which means an average project can barely survive through a market cycle of 4 years,” the report said.</span></p>
<p><span>Commenting on the decrease in the number of cryptocurrencies, Ramy Bekhiet, Senior Advisor and Commercial Partnerships Coordinator at </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/castle-fund-just-because-bitcoin-etfs-are-allowed-doesnt-mean-theyll-succeed.htm"><b>PDX</b></a><span>, told </span><i><span>Cryptonews</span></i><span> that projects are realizing that they need to offer real-world utility.</span></p>
<p><span>“Also, with regulations looming around, projects are becoming more careful in how they operate and launch new coins/tokens,&#8221; he said.</span></p>
<p><span>Aaron Rafferty, co-founder and CEO of technology incubation hub </span><a href="https://www.standarddao.finance/"><b>Standard</b></a><span>, said that,</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“The drop is clearly the tail end of the last bull market and aftermath of overspeculation, hype cycles that failed, and fraudsters that ran pump-and-dump schemes. Many of these individuals are still in the market under alternative personas, and the creation of new tokens and projects is far from over.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>In fact, with Large Language Models, the gap to launch a crypto project is lower than ever, said Rafferty, and requires zero coding experience. </span></p>
<p><span>Platforms like </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-presale-scams-take-a-toll-as-meme-coin-season-continues.htm"><b>Solana</b></a><span> are attracting hundreds of millions of consumer investor dollars, speculating on the next pump-and-dump scheme. This week alone, we saw $149.2 million in funding go directly to 33 project presales where personalities on Twitter effectively shared a wallet address to which people sent their </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-bounces-11-from-recent-bottom-is-the-sell-off-over.htm"><b>SOL</b></a><span> tokens. </span></p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/propykeys-launches-base-dapp-rwa-ai-nft-features-for-minting-addresses-and-deeds-onchain.htm"><b>Base</b></a><span> chain will have a similar moment as it is even easier and cheaper to launch a project there, with fees costing less than $1 for the entire process, Rafferty argued, adding:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“Couple these two factors together along with the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-spot-etfs-see-net-outflow-on-third-consecutive-day.htm"><span>ETF</span></a><span> [exchange-traded fund] approvals and lack of regulatory clarity from the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-reportedly-probing-key-crypto-companies-in-push-to-make-eth-a-security-fortune.htm"><b>SEC</b></a><span> [US Securities and Exchange Commission], and 2025 will be the year of the most crypto projects launched that we have ever seen. The gap now seems to be the size of one&#8217;s audience and ability to draw a crowd.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/etfs-are-inevitable-but-not-imminent-crypto-expert-argues.htm"><span>Peter Eberle</span></a><span>, President and Chief Investment Officer of </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/castle-fund-just-because-bitcoin-etfs-are-allowed-doesnt-mean-theyll-succeed.htm"><b>Castle Funds</b></a><span>, commented that the reason we are excited about some cryptocurrencies is the underlying technology that some of these have developed. </span></p>
<p><span>This includes Bitcoin as a means of transferring large amounts of money across borders without middlemen and on a public distributed ledger. Also, there’s Ethereum and its smart contracts that can be executed based on predetermined rules. </span></p>
<p><span>However, said Eberle,</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“Unfortunately, many others provide nothing of value. Meme coins are cheap to issue and extract money from people chasing quick riches, enriching the issuers. New coins will continue to be released, and others will collapse. Investors must do their own research and due diligence. Don&#8217;t be someone else’s exit liquidity.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>Meanwhile, the AlphaQuest and Storible report noted that, despite the downfall of numerous coins, many new projects and narratives emerge each month. </span></p>
<p><span>It stated that “the cryptocurrency field still holds promise for the future” and “the enduring relevance of cryptocurrencies cannot be underestimated.”</span></p>
<h2><b>Conclusion</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Between 2013 and 2024, there was a 13,572.7% rise in the number of cryptocurrencies, from 66 to 9,024, according to Statista.</span></p>
<p><span>Compared to the February 2022 ATH of 10,397, there was a 13% drop by January 2024 in the number of cryptocurrencies available.</span></p>
<p><span>Year-on-year, from February 2023 until January 2024, the space saw a 3.9% increase in the number of available coins worldwide.</span></p>
<p><span>There were four recorded drops over the past decade: August 2021, November 2022, February 2023, and December 2023.</span></p>
<p><span><div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"></span></p>
<h3><em>Why do cryptocurrencies fail?</em></h3>
<p><span>Some of the key reasons why the cryptocurrencies fail and end up dying include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span> crypto volatility</span></li>
<li><span>unpredictability</span></li>
<li><span>lack of investment and trading volume</span></li>
<li><span>abandonment by developers</span></li>
<li><span>lack of regulations</span></li>
<li><span>over-speculation</span></li>
<li><span>hype cycle fails</span></li>
<li><span>hacks</span></li>
<li><span>fraud (such as rug pulls).</span></li>
</ul>
</div></div>
<p><span>Most projects created during the 2020-2021 bull run have died by now. Most new coins don’t even last one four-year cycle. </span></p>
<p><span>Per various reports, 2021 and 2023 were particularly bad years for crypto projects. Bear markets, as well as a string of bankruptcies that began in 2022, led to the fall of numerous projects.</span></p>
<p><span>All that said, more cryptocurrencies are being created every day. Following the improvements in the crypto space and approval of ETFs, 2025 may see the most cryptocurrencies created yet.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-globally-2013-2024.htm">Dead or Alive: Number of Cryptocurrencies Worldwide from 2013 to January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122728/1711369648-dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-worldwide-from-2013-to-january-2024.jpg" length="124541" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bonk Price Prediction as $100,000,000 Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying Again?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bonk-price-prediction-as-100000000-trading-volume-comes-in-are-whales-buying-again.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arslan Butt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bonk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>With a trading volume soaring past $100M, Bonk (BONK) coin's rapid ascent sparks speculation: Are cryptocurrency whales driving this unprecedented growth once again?</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bonk-price-prediction-as-100000000-trading-volume-comes-in-are-whales-buying-again.htm">Bonk Price Prediction as $100,000,000 Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying Again?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-188508" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2.webp" alt="BONK" width="1792" height="1024" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2.webp 1792w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2-300x171.webp 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2-1024x585.webp 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2-768x439.webp 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2-1536x878.webp 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2-150x86.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1792px) 100vw, 1792px" /></p>
<p><span>Amidst a surging interest and a trading volume that has recently crossed the $100 million mark, <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BONKUSD/">Bonk (BONK) coin&#8217;s price</a> trajectory has caught the eye of investors worldwide. With a remarkable 160% increase in the last month and an unprecedented 640% upswing since the start of 2024, holders of Bonk are reaping the benefits of its explosive growth. </span></p>
<p><span>As Bitcoin&#8217;s value climbs, it catalyzes a market-wide enthusiasm, propelling investments into various cryptocurrencies, including meme-driven Bonk. The coin&#8217;s listing on the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/1397099233745#:~:text=listing%20of%20BONK.-,Binance%20is%20set%20to%20list%20Bonk%20(BONK)%20with%20the%20implementation,to%20prepare%20for%20trading%20activities.">Binance exchange in 2023</a>, which saw trading volumes soar to $600 million, has bolstered beliefs in its potential to stand toe-to-toe with established memecoins, further amplifying its allure to a global pool of investors. </span></p>
<p><span>Despite the market&#8217;s inherent volatility, the outlook on Bonk remains optimistic, with predictions suggesting a possible rise to $0.0000385 by the end of March, underscored by a growing demand and positive sentiment within the meme coin sector.</span></p>
<h2>Bonk (BONK) Surges Amidst Bitcoin Rally and Growing Altcoin Interest</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://cryptonews.com/price-predictions/bonk-price-prediction/">Bonk (BONK)</a> has recently witnessed significant growth, propelled by the rising tide of alternative cryptocurrencies and the influential wake of Bitcoin&#8217;s market movements. The link between Bitcoin&#8217;s rallies and heightened interest in altcoins, including meme-themed Bonk, has been unmistakable.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin climbs, it fuels speculation and investment across the broader cryptocurrency spectrum, benefiting coins like Bonk. A notable milestone in 2023 was Bonk&#8217;s addition to the Binance exchange, a development that drew investor focus, boosting its liquidity and trading volumes.</p>
<p>Despite occasional setbacks, Bonk&#8217;s trajectory remains predominantly upward, driven by investor enthusiasm and a general bullish outlook on meme cryptocurrencies, underpinned by Bitcoin&#8217;s enduring market impact.</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin&#8217;s performance influencing altcoin market dynamics.</li>
<li>Binance listing elevating investor interest and market activity.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Dovish Comments from Fed Officials: Impact on Bonk (BONK) Coin Price</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
When <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/20/fed-meeting-today-live-updates-on-march-fed-rate-decision.html">Federal Reserve officials</a> lean towards dovish policies, favoring economic growth over curbing inflation, it spells good news for cryptocurrencies like Bonk (BONK). Such policies often lead to lower interest rates and more money flowing in the economy, making borrowing cheaper and investments in assets like Bonk more attractive. As investors look for alternative places to park their funds, Bonk&#8217;s price could see an uptick.</p>
<p>The dovish comments also tend to weaken the US Dollar (USD), as lower interest rates make it less appealing. This decrease in the dollar&#8217;s strength further enhances the attractiveness of cryptocurrencies as alternative investments.</p>
<ul>
<li>Fed&#8217;s growth-focused stance potentially lowers interest rates.</li>
<li>Bonk (BONK) becomes more appealing with increased liquidity and a weaker USD.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bonk Price Prediction</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>In today’s <a href="https://cryptonews.com/price-predictions/bonk-price-prediction/">technical analysis of BONK</a>, the asset closed at $0.00002312, marking a 4.06% decline. The analysis reveals critical price levels to watch: a pivot point at $0.000024 sets the immediate tone, with resistance levels poised at $0.000026, $0.000027, and $0.000029.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_188502" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188502" style="width: 1747px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-188502 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106.png" alt="Bonk Price Prediction" width="1747" height="913" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106.png 1747w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106-300x157.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106-1024x535.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106-768x401.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106-1536x803.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123547/1711370147-image-106-150x78.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1747px) 100vw, 1747px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188502" class="wp-caption-text">Bonk Price Prediction</figcaption></figure>
<p><span>Support levels are established at $0.000022, $0.000021, and $0.000020. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) stands at 50, indicating a balanced force between buyers and sellers. </span><span>The 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) at $0.000024 corroborates with the symmetrical triangle pattern observed, signaling a consolidation phase within a $0.000024 to $0.000021 range. </span></p>
<p><span>A breach beyond this range could catalyze a decisive price movement. Presently, BONK exhibits a bearish outlook below $0.000024, yet a surge above this threshold could shift the momentum towards a bullish stance.</span></p>
<h2>Embracing the Future: Dogecoin20 Unleashed</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" rel="sponsored nofollow">Dogecoin20 ($DOGE20)</a><span> </span>revolutionizes the meme coin domain by integrating Dogecoin&#8217;s charm with Ethereum&#8217;s cutting-edge capabilities. As an ERC-20 token, it offers staking for passive income, aligning with the original Dogecoin ethos while harnessing Ethereum&#8217;s proof-of-stake for eco-friendly, efficient transactions.</p>
<p><strong>Stake and Earn with Dogecoin20: </strong>Dedicated to rewarding its community, Dogecoin20 allocates 15% of its supply to staking rewards within the first two years, providing a generous first-year reward pool. This initiative underscores the Dogecoin principle of &#8220;Do Only Good Everyday,&#8221; through engaging and rewarding participation.</p>
<p><strong>Embrace Eco-Friendly Transactions: </strong>Utilizing Ethereum&#8217;s platform, Dogecoin20 provides a sustainable transaction solution that is both fast and secure, fostering a community-driven ecosystem centered around decentralization and environmental responsibility.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><strong>Presale Opportunity: Join Now!</strong></a></p>
<p>The Dogecoin20 presale is rapidly progressing, with $6,740,996.07 already raised towards a $7,247,843 target. At just $0.000207 per DOGE20, seize the opportunity to be part of this innovative meme coin&#8217;s journey before the next price hike.</p>
<h3><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong>Get DOGE20 Here</strong></a></h3>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bonk-price-prediction-as-100000000-trading-volume-comes-in-are-whales-buying-again.htm">Bonk Price Prediction as $100,000,000 Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying Again?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124103/1711370462-bonk-2.webp" length="779558" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Coinbase Prepares to Launch DOGE Futures – $1 Incoming?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-coinbase-prepares-to-launch-doge-futures-1-incoming.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Chandler]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme Coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Dogecoin price has barely moved in the past 24 hours, with its current level of $0.173 representing an 18% gain in a week.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-coinbase-prepares-to-launch-doge-futures-1-incoming.htm">Dogecoin Price Prediction as Coinbase Prepares to Launch DOGE Futures – $1 Incoming?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/dogecoin/">Dogecoin price</a> has barely moved in the past 24 hours, with its current level of $0.173 representing an 18% gain in a week.</p>
<p>Much of this gain has followed the news that major crypto-exchange <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-derivatives-plans-cash-settled-futures-for-dogecoin-litecoin-and-bitcoin-cash.htm">Coinbase will launch DOGE-based futures on April 1</a>, an announcement that has seen the coin&#8217;s trading volume rise from under $2 billion to over $3 billion in a couple of days.</p>
<p>DOGE is now also up by 100% in a month, with the famous meme coins also marking a 130% gain in a year.</p>
<p>Yet the announcement of DOGE futures points to a near future that could see the token&#8217;s volumes and price rise significantly, as more traders enter its market.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Coinbase Prepares to Launch DOGE Futures – $1 Incoming?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
DOGE&#8217;s chart is in an interesting position, insofar as its resistance (red) and support (green) levels are converging towards each other.</p>
<p>This implies that the Dogecoin price will either break out towards higher levels or face a further dump, with its rising RSI (purple) suggesting that a breakout is a touch more likely.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188430" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188430" style="width: 4310px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188430" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart.png" alt="Dogecoin price chart." width="4310" height="2396" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart.png 4310w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart-300x167.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart-1024x569.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart-768x427.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart-1536x854.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart-2048x1139.png 2048w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25103656/1711363012-dogecoin-price-chart-150x83.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 4310px) 100vw, 4310px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188430" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s also encouraging that DOGE&#8217;s price has climbed over its 30-day average (yellow), something which is likely to pull up the latter and put further distance between it and the 200-day (blue).</p>
<p>In other words, DOGE remains in the middle of an expansionary period, one which could see its price reach new yearly heights.</p>
<p>It will be helped by the aforementioned news that Coinbase will be adding DOGE futures next week, something which could herald a big rise in the coin&#8217;s volumes.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">April 1st coinbase launches doge futures</p>
<p>it would be a shame if it front ran that launch</p>
<p>&mdash; Dyme (@CryptoParadyme) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoParadyme/status/1771345838318715255?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>It continues to attract interest from large investors, as indicated by <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1769895451497484685">recent transfer data</a>, and it&#8217;s possible that the ability to trade futures on Coinbase will only help it in this respect.</p>
<p>DOGE is also likely to benefit from the market&#8217;s return to growth, with the total cap of all cryptocurrencies rising by 3% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>As momentum returns to the market, and as we approach the next Bitcoin halving, positivity is likely to increase, with the Dogecoin price rising along with others.</p>
<p>DOGE may also receive help from Elon Musk and X, which <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/social-media-powerhouse-x-paves-way-for-digital-transactions.htm">continues to prepare for the launch of digital payments on its social network</a>.</p>
<p>If X does bring DOGE payments to its platform, then the Dogecoin price will undoubtedly rocket.</p>
<p>Under this scenario it could certainly reach $1, while Tesla enabling DOGE payments may also help.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&quot;Tesla will enable Doge payments at some point&quot;</p>
<p>一 Elon Musk <a href="https://t.co/CVDwUnW6XZ">pic.twitter.com/CVDwUnW6XZ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; MyDoge Wallet (@MyDogeOfficial) <a href="https://twitter.com/MyDogeOfficial/status/1771388534395670769?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>If not, it will rise more modestly, potentially touching $0.3 by the summer.</p>
<h2>New Meme Tokens May Rally Harder</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
DOGE continues to hold potential for future rallies, yet it&#8217;s arguable that newer meme coins may rise more aggressively this year.</p>
<p>This is particularly the case for new meme tokens that are holding their respective presales and looking to list on exchanges soon.</p>
<p>One such token is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20">Dogecoin20 (DOGE20)</a>, an ERC-20 cryptocurrency that has raised over $8 million in its presale.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Think <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$DOGE</a> might be getting a bit jealous! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f914.png" alt="🤔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f436.png" alt="🐶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Dogecoin20</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Memecoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Memecoins</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Altcoins</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cryptomemes?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Cryptomemes</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE</a> <a href="https://t.co/Q3QMhqsh6f">pic.twitter.com/Q3QMhqsh6f</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dogecoin20 (@DOGE_COIN20) <a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20/status/1772186719292387636?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Not only is Dogecoin20 an Ethereum-based version of the original Dogecoin, but it also aims to provide stronger fundamentals and tokenomics than its namesake.</p>
<p>For one, it will operate according to Dogecoin&#8217;s &#8216;Do Only Good Everyday&#8217; ethos, with the token providing regular transfers and support to charitable causes and community projects.</p>
<p>In contrast to Dogecoin (which remains a proof-of-work crypto), its use of Ethereum makes it a proof-of-stake token, meaning that it will use much, much less energy.</p>
<p>Aside from being more environmentally friendly, its tokenomics will be stronger, with the coin having a hard cap of 140 billion DOGE20.</p>
<p>This limited supply will combine with DOGE20&#8217;s staking system, which provides greater rewards to those who stake more for longer.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Utilizing Ethereum-powered smart contracts, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE20</a> transcends its <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Memecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Memecoin</a> origins. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f31f.png" alt="🌟" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Empowering the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> Community with passive rewards! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4b8.png" alt="💸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Optimize your $DOGE20 holdings by engaging in staking and earning rewards. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f48e.png" alt="💎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/cTbZcfRJjO">pic.twitter.com/cTbZcfRJjO</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dogecoin20 (@DOGE_COIN20) <a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20/status/1771884728561385652?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>By incentivizing long-term holding, more DOGE20 will exit circulation, potentially pushing up its price in parallel.</p>
<p>This could make DOGE20 one of the most bullish new tokens of the year, with investors able to join its sale at <a style="font-size: 16px;" href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20">the official Dogecoin20 website</a>.</p>
<p>They can buy the coin at $0.000209 per token, in exchange for ETH, USDT or fiat currency.</p>
<p>And because DOGE20 has a capped supply (unlike Dogecoin), this price could rise massively once the token starts listing on exchanges.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20">Buy Dogecoin20 Now</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-coinbase-prepares-to-launch-doge-futures-1-incoming.htm">Dogecoin Price Prediction as Coinbase Prepares to Launch DOGE Futures – $1 Incoming?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25111650/1711365410-dogecoin-price-prediction-as-coinbase-prepares-to-launch-doge-futures-1-incoming.jpg" length="165345" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s The Latest NFT News Today</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news-today.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sead Fadilpašić]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=170308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here's the latest form NFT news today:</p>
<ul>
<li><span>NFT Market Data Today</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>OKX and Immutable Partner to Unveil GameFi Launchpad</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>Bybit Reveals Miner's Point Plaza with a Shot at $1 Million</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>Cat-Themed Blockchain Game ETHxCAT Launches with NFT Rewards</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news-today.htm">Here’s The Latest NFT News Today</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of NFT news today – investigating the stories flying under the radar among the latest NFT news.</em></p>
<div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;">
<p>Here&#8217;s the latest form NFT news today:</p>
<ul>
<li><span>NFT Market Data Today</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>OKX and Immutable Partner to Unveil GameFi Launchpad</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>Bybit Reveals Miner&#8217;s Point Plaza with a Shot at $1 Million</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>Cat-Themed Blockchain Game ETHxCAT Launches with NFT Rewards</span></li>
</ul>
</div></div>
<h2>NFT Market Data Today</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The non-fungible token (</span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptopunks-recent-nft-sale-breaks-record-sold-for-4850-eth-or-16-4m.htm"><span>NFT</span></a><span>) market is down today, but very slightly:  0.3% to $29,337,228.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/"><span>According</span></a><span> to </span><b>CryptoSlam</b><span>, over the past 24 hours, the number of buyers is down 3.5%, sellers are up 5.5%, and transactions fell 5.5%.</span></p>
<p><span>After being shortly overthrown, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-will-play-a-pivotal-role-in-2024-more-top-nft-news-2.htm"><b>Uncategorized Ordinals</b></a><span> are back in the first place per sales volume with $2.2 million. This is despite a 34% drop.</span></p>
<p><span>As for the rest of the top ten collections, six have seen their sales volume increase over the past day. </span></p>
<p><span>The best performer is </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brc-20-inscription-growth-key-for-bitcoins-continued-dominance-in-2023-binance-research.htm"><b>$?? BRC-20 NFTs</b></a><span>: up 143% to $1.9 million. </span></p>
<p><span>At the same time, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-nfts-eclipse-ethereum-with-168-5-million-in-weekly-sales.htm"><b>NodeMonkes</b></a><span> dropped the most, 54% to $559,385.</span></p>
<p><span>BRC-20 collections are generally having a good day. Two of them are in the top 10 today, and seven in the top 20.</span></p>
<p><span>When it comes to the best-performing blockchains, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/"><b>Bitcoin</b></a><span> has once again overtaken </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/ethereum/"><b>Ethereum</b></a><span>. The former is up nearly 10% to $10.3 million, while the latter decreased 4% to $8.3 million.</span></p>
<h2><b>OKX and Immutable Partner to Unveil GameFi Launchpad</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>In NFT news today, crypto exchange </span><a href="https://www.okx.com/join?channelid=ACE519987"><b>OKX</b></a><span> and popular gaming platform </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/king-river-capital-immutable-and-polygon-labs-launch-100m-gaming-fund.htm"><b>Immutable</b></a><span> announced a new strategic partnership, which includes the introduction of a </span><b>GameFi NFT Launchpad</b><span>. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/okx-and-immutable-partner-to-unveil-gamefi-launchpad-paving-the-way-for-the-next-billion-users-in-web3-gaming-302096175.html"><span>Per</span></a><span> the press release, the partnership aims to “transform how more than 50 million users engage with and access NFTs and digital assets within the gaming space.”</span></p>
<p><span>The launch of OKX’s GameFi Launchpad is scheduled in the upcoming months. It will support the global gaming launches planned for </span><b>Immutable </b><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/immutable-zkevm-mainnet-early-access-polygon-web3-gaming-goes-live.htm"><b>zkEVM</b></a><span>, including </span><b>Guild of Guardians</b><span>, </span><b>Shardbound</b><span>, and </span><b>Metalcore</b><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>Games building on Immutable will now be able to tap into the OKX ecosystem, including its educational resource </span><b>Cryptopedia</b><span>, said the announcement.</span></p>
<p><span>Furthermore, the partnership includes the integration of Immutable&#8217;s gaming-focused zkEVM chain into </span><b>OKX Marketplace</b><span> and </span><b>OKX Wallet</b><span>.</span></p>
<p><span>The benefits that game studios, players, and gaming ecosystem participants will see include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span> A dedicated GameFi launchpad on the OKX NFT Marketplace; </span></li>
<li><span>The integration of gaming-centric Immutable zkEVM, a scaling solution powered by </span><b>Polygon</b><span>; </span></li>
<li><span>The integration of OKX’s Web3 Wallet into Immutable’s player identity solution, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-gaming-company-immutable-debuts-passport-with-google-and-apple-integration.htm"><b>Passport</b></a><span>; </span></li>
<li><span>Тhe inclusion of the OKX NFT Marketplace in Immutable’s </span><b>Orderbook </b><span>and </span><b>Marketplace Network</b><span>; </span></li>
<li><span>The support of Immutable zkEVM on the OKX ecosystem.</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Immutable <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f91d.png" alt="🤝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/okx?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@okx</a></p>
<p>With OKX, we are unveiling a brand new GameFi launchpad to pave the way for the next billion users in web3 gaming.</p>
<p>This partnership will integrate OKX Wallet and OKX NFT Marketplace into Immutable Passport and Immutable Orderbook, all on Immutable zkEVM.</p>
<p>We… <a href="https://t.co/PhF8AtPAGi">pic.twitter.com/PhF8AtPAGi</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Immutable (@Immutable) <a href="https://twitter.com/Immutable/status/1770844205251805318?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>Robbie Ferguson, Co-founder and President of Immutable, commented that working with OKX aligns with Immutable’s mission to “bring digital proprietorship to every gamer in the world.” </span></p>
<p><span>This partnership, he added, will open new gaming experiences for millions of players worldwide.</span></p>
<p><span>OKX Chief Innovation Officer Jason Lau noted that Web3 gaming is “on the verge of becoming mainstream.”</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, “with over 270 titles in development on Immutable&#8217;s zkEVM, OKX wallet users will enjoy a smooth onboarding process, gameplay, and management of their in-game assets,” Lau said.</span></p>
<h2><b>Bybit Reveals Miner&#8217;s Point Plaza with a Shot at $1 Million</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>To celebrate the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-halving/"><span>Bitcoin Halving</span></a><span>, crypto exchange </span><a href="https://partner.bybit.com/b/73494"><b>Bybit</b></a><span> has launched </span><b>Miner’s Points Plaza</b><span> – a gamified event where users complete tasks, earn points, and mine a 2 BTC prize pool.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.prnewswire.co.uk/news-releases/bitcoin-halving-frenzy-join-bybits-miners-point-plaza-for-a-shot-at-1-million-and-witness-history-302096936.html"><span>Per</span></a><span> the press release, each user will receive a collectible NFT. They can upgrade it by unlocking new levels, culminating in the ‘Queen Katherine’ level.</span></p>
<p><span>The team explained that Miner’s Points Plaza is a game where players ‘mine’ BTC and swap their earnings for rewards. This includes the opportunity to get a share of a $1,000,000 prize pool. </span></p>
<p><span>Crypto rewards include BTC and ETH on a first-come, first-served basis.</span></p>
<p><span>Additionally, every participant will receive “a small USDT prize just for showing up, before the real fun begins.”</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ride the <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> wave to victory <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c6.png" alt="📆" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Campaign starts today March 22, 2024, 10AM UTC</p>
<p>Join here: <a href="https://t.co/RFIpoZrQ12">https://t.co/RFIpoZrQ12</a> <a href="https://t.co/oKiYSo1Jzt">pic.twitter.com/oKiYSo1Jzt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bybit (@Bybit_Official) <a href="https://twitter.com/Bybit_Official/status/1771016489912459571?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>The game began on March 22 and will last until April 22, 2024. Winners will need to exchange their points for prizes until May 2.</span></p>
<p><span>Bybit co-founder and CEO Ben Zhou said that the Miner’s Points Plaza offers a platform to the community “to maximize their gains during the Bitcoin Halving, reinforcing our commitment to leading the way in gamified experiences.”</span></p>
<h2><b>Cat-Themed Blockchain Game ETHxCAT Launches with NFT Rewards </b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/major-setback-smart-contract-exploit-results-over-200-ethscriptions-being-nabbed.htm"><span>Ethscriptions</span></a><span>-empowered Web3 game built on </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-to-unlock-2-32-billion-in-vested-arb-tokens-on-march-16.htm"><b>Arbitrum</b></a><span> chain, </span><b>ETHxCAT</b><span> announced its recent launch, saying that it blends </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/david-johansson-ceo-of-blocklords-on-blockchain-gaming-web3-gaming-airdrops-and-user-acquisition-for-web3-games-ep-310.htm"><span>gaming</span></a><span> and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/merging-crypto-and-tradfi-mastercard-backs-fideum-group-as-winner-of-lighthouse-finitiv-program.htm"><span>finance</span></a><span>.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240322494259/en/ETHxCAT-Launches-the-Ultimate-Cat-Themed-Blockchain-Game"><span>According</span></a><span> to the press release, players enter a universe where they raise their feline companions, embark on quests, and gain rewards in TOKEN and NFT forms.</span></p>
<p><span>Game NFTs include Genesis Cats, Gems, and Plots.</span></p>
<p><span>Players can get TOKEN and NFT by planting crops, mining resources, trading with other players, and expanding territory. </span></p>
<p><span>They can then use their earnings to upgrade their cats, land plots, and buildings.</span></p>
<p><span>Players can further customize their cats with different outfits, accessories, and skills, as well as breed them to create new and rare cats.</span></p>
<p><span>“Designed to captivate cat lovers and blockchain enthusiasts alike, ETHxCAT stands out with its extensive selection of thousands of distinctively charming cats,” said the team.</span></p>
<p><span>Furthermore, players can join the MINT of the land plots. These are either centralized, meaning they are controlled by game non-player characters (NPCs), or decentralized and thus tradable by users. </span></p>
<p><span>They can use their cats to help other players with their land plots and earn tokens. </span></p>
<p><span>Also, they can form alliances with adjacent land plot owners and compete with other alliances for the most valuable TOKEN and NFT in the game.</span></p>
<p><span>“Users with inscriptions will receive regular airdrops of Tokens and NFTs to their corresponding ARB wallet addresses,” the team said.</span></p>
<p><span>There will be regular airdrops of NFTs, including game decorative items, and a special discount for minting NFTs, the website </span><a href="https://www.ethxcat.io/"><span>stated</span></a><span>. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news-today.htm">Here’s The Latest NFT News Today</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/21134226/1708522945-1708522402870_processed.jpg" length="109619" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance to Discontinue Support for USDC Stablecoin on Justin Sun&#8217;s Tron</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-to-discontinue-support-for-usdc-stablecoin-on-justin-suns-tron.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance will no longer facilitate deposits and withdrawals of the USD-pegged stablecoin USDC using the Tron blockchain network.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-to-discontinue-support-for-usdc-stablecoin-on-justin-suns-tron.htm">Binance to Discontinue Support for USDC Stablecoin on Justin Sun&#8217;s Tron</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/reviews/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> will no longer facilitate deposits and withdrawals of the USD-pegged stablecoin </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">USDC</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> using the Tron blockchain network. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a Monday </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-cease-support-for-deposits-and-withdrawals-of-usdc-via-the-tron-network-trc20-33df0ff0e2e94259950b5c4b1f4952f7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">press release</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the crypto exchange announced its decision to cease support for <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/tron/">Tron’s TRC-20</a>-based USDC deposits and withdrawals from April 5.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The platform gave investors 12 days to convert, transfer, or cash out their TRC-20 USDC tokens from Binance. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance clarified that users would still be able to trade USDC on their platform. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, deposits and withdrawals of USDC through other supported networks would remain unaffected. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Circle Drops Support for USDC on Tron</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance&#8217;s move to drop support for USDC on Tron comes as Boston-based crypto firm Circle </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-drops-tron-support-usdc-risk-management.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">made a similar decision</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to halt the creation of USDC tokens on the Tron blockchain. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Following Circle’s discontinuation of USDC support on the Tron network (TRC20), Binance will cease support for USDC deposits and withdrawals via TRC20 starting from 5 April 2024, 02:00 am UTC.</p>
<p>Users may continue trading USDC on Binance. Deposits and withdrawals of USDC via other…</p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1772155615772602857?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Circle cited the need to ensure the transparency, trustworthiness, and safety of USDC as the reason behind their move. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Our decision to discontinue support for USDC on TRON is the result of an enterprise-wide approach that involved the business organization, compliance and other functions across our company,” the company said on X.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tron, founded by prominent crypto entrepreneur Justin Sun, has not yet responded to Reuters&#8217; request for comment regarding Binance&#8217;s decision.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Last year, Sun faced a lawsuit filed by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which accused him of artificially inflating trading volumes and selling Tron tokens as unregistered securities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sun vehemently denied the allegations, stating that they lacked merit.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">With a circulation of approximately $32.1 billion, USDC currently stands as the eighth-largest cryptocurrency and the second-largest stablecoin after Tether. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Most USDC tokens in circulation are based on the Ethereum blockchain, according to Circle&#8217;s website. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/new-crypto-front-emerges-israels-militant-financing-fight-2023-11-27/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reuters report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> from December further complicated TRON’s image. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the report, TRON outshined its competitor Bitcoin, as the preferred platform for organizations labeled as terrorist groups to transfer crypto.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prior to Circle&#8217;s discontinuation of Tron-based USDC support, approximately $335 million in USDC was hosted on the Tron blockchain.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tether Surpasses $100 Billion Market Cap</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">In early March, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/tether/">Tether’s USDT</a> surpassed a market capitalization of $100 billion, with an impressive growth of 9% year-to-date.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Comparatively, USDT maintains a lead of over $71 billion in market cap when compared to its closest competitor, USD Coin (USDC).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the success, concerns about the quality of assets backing USDT have lingered in the crypto space. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-is-gaining-popularity-among-money-launderers-un-report.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">United Nations report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> highlighted Tron’s popularity among cyber fraud and money laundering activities in Southeast Asia. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tether </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-responds-to-un-report-alleging-involvement-in-illicit-activity-disputes-claims.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">has refuted these claims</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, emphasizing its collaboration with law enforcement and the traceability of its token.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In response to the UN report, Tether said that its collaboration with global law enforcement, including the Department of Justice (DOJ), the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), and the United States Secret Service (USSS), has resulted in unparalleled monitoring capabilities, surpassing traditional banking systems. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-to-discontinue-support-for-usdc-stablecoin-on-justin-suns-tron.htm">Binance to Discontinue Support for USDC Stablecoin on Justin Sun&#8217;s Tron</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25105731/1711364251-1711364239711_processed.jpg" length="97824" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sophisticated Email Phishing Targets Bankrupt Crypto Firms’ BlockFi, FTX Creditors</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sophisticated-email-phishing-targets-bankrupt-crypto-firms-blockfi-ftx-creditors.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sujha Sundararajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Creditors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phishing scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX and BlockFi claimants received legit-looking fraudulent emails luring them with a promise of instant withdrawals of their remaining balances.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sophisticated-email-phishing-targets-bankrupt-crypto-firms-blockfi-ftx-creditors.htm">Sophisticated Email Phishing Targets Bankrupt Crypto Firms’ BlockFi, FTX Creditors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto scammers are targeting the creditors of bankrupt digital asset firms FTX and BlockFi, according to online blockchain sleuth Plumferno.</p>
<p>FTX and BlockFi claimants received legit-looking fraudulent emails luring them with a promise of instant withdrawals of their remaining balances.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188437" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188437" style="width: 467px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class=" wp-image-188437" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25104830/1711363709-blockfi-letter.webp" alt="" width="467" height="421" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25104830/1711363709-blockfi-letter.webp 1508w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25104830/1711363709-blockfi-letter-300x271.webp 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25104830/1711363709-blockfi-letter-1024x924.webp 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25104830/1711363709-blockfi-letter-768x693.webp 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25104830/1711363709-blockfi-letter-150x135.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 467px) 100vw, 467px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188437" class="wp-caption-text">Source: X</figcaption></figure>
<p>“The emails appear to come from the BlockFi restructuring team with an update on their court case and offer affected users the chance to withdraw their remaining balances,” security expert Plumferno <a href="https://twitter.com/Plumferno/status/1771346183715266927">flagged in a thread</a> on X (Twitter).</p>
<p>Creditors of these beleaguered exchanges have been waiting for their reimbursements ever since a New Jersey bankruptcy court <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-complies-with-court-order-permits-crypto-withdrawals-for-eligible-us-users.htm">approved BlockFi&#8217;s plan to refund Wallet customers</a> in full in October 2023.</p>
<p>The scammers have made use of creditor’s frustrations to amass at least $7 million worth of digital assets and <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/nft/">NFTs</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Sophisticated ongoing phishing scam carried out by one of PinkDrainer&#8217;s customers, with losses (so far) of nearly $7 million over the last 5 days.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">With the help of a few friends, I&#39;ve uncovered a rather sophisticated ongoing phishing scam carried out by one of PinkDrainer&#39;s customers, with losses (so far) of nearly $7 million over the last 5 days. </p>
<p>The source? Fake BlockFi emails, offering settlement claims for users. <a href="https://t.co/sCSNGtcHaA">pic.twitter.com/sCSNGtcHaA</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Plum (@Plumferno) <a href="https://twitter.com/Plumferno/status/1771346180615577621?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Pink Drainer is a threat group which are predominantly phishing-oriented, targeting cryptocurrency investors.</p>
<p>The blockchain analyst further noted that some of the creditors are even unaware that they are being robbed.</p>
<p>“The worst part of this scam is that most of the assets have been stolen from dormant wallets &#8211; people who were likely affected by the BlockFi bankruptcy and haven&#8217;t touched the funds since,” the analyst wrote.</p>
<p>Additionally, this email scam is also prevailing among FTX creditors. The reimbursement update from legit-looking FTX mail said that the company is undergoing “restructuring efforts.”</p>
<p>“FTX is now moving forward with allowing all users to fully withdraw their assets,” the mail read.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Have received a DM that this is also going to FTX customers &#8211; unsure of any domains yet, however, be careful! <a href="https://t.co/fogK79qNfU">pic.twitter.com/fogK79qNfU</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Plum (@Plumferno) <a href="https://twitter.com/Plumferno/status/1771385918060142629?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>BlockFi, FTX Creditors&#8217; Email List Stolen From Mailer Lite’s Scam</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Plumferno added that the perpetrators utilized a network of compromised emails from <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mailerlite-confirms-breach-leading-to-3-3m-crypto-phishing-attacks.htm">Mailer Lite’s data breach</a> that occurred in January.</p>
<p>“It is very likely these emails are due to the MailerLite database breach in January,” Plumferno noted. “This is because the same sender info is present on both these fake BlockFi emails.”</p>
<p>The blockchain investigator first took notice of the scam after an influx of nearly $4.5 million in Ether entered the scammer’s wallet last week.</p>
<p>Additionally, per reports, scammers also received blue-chip NFTs, including Mutant Apes, and Otherdeed.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sophisticated-email-phishing-targets-bankrupt-crypto-firms-blockfi-ftx-creditors.htm">Sophisticated Email Phishing Targets Bankrupt Crypto Firms’ BlockFi, FTX Creditors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25105901/1711364340-1711364320450_processed.jpg" length="187145" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Prediction as SOL Bounces 6.7% – New Rally Starting?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-bounces-6-7-new-rally-starting.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Chandler]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SOL has jumped by over 6% in the past 24 hours, with the Solana price rising to $186 on a day when the market as a whole has recovered by 3%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-bounces-6-7-new-rally-starting.htm">Solana Price Prediction as SOL Bounces 6.7% – New Rally Starting?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOL has jumped by over 6% in the past 24 hours, with <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/sol-solana/">the Solana price</a> rising to $186 on a day when the market as a whole has recovered by 3%.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s lift means that SOL is still down by 7.5% in a week, yet it sits on a 25% gain in a fortnight and an 83% increase in the last 30 days.</p>
<p>The coin has also ballooned by 800% in the past year, making it the best-performing top-20 coin of this period.</p>
<p>And with the market looking as though it&#8217;s about to bounce back after a short-term correction, the Solana price could rally considerably in the coming weeks and months.</p>
<h2>Solana Price Prediction as SOL Bounces 6.7% – New Rally Starting?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
SOL&#8217;s chart has reached a point where the token is ready for a recovery breakout, with its indicators moving in positive directions.</p>
<p>Its 30-day average (yellow) flipped its 200-day average (blue) this morning, forming a golden cross that often signals stroke rallies to new levels.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188399" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188399" style="width: 4310px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188399" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart.png" alt="Solana price chart." width="4310" height="2396" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart.png 4310w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart-300x167.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart-1024x569.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart-768x427.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart-1536x854.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart-2048x1139.png 2048w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25092423/1711358658-solana-price-chart-150x83.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 4310px) 100vw, 4310px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188399" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s in this context that SOL&#8217;s relative strength index (purple) is also suggesting bullish things, with its level rising from 30 at the end of last week to nearly 70 today.</p>
<p>This suggests strong buying pressure, with a level of 70 allowing for further gains before the coin enters decidedly overbought territory.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s also interesting is that Solana&#8217;s trading volume has risen from $2.5 billion to $3.5 billion in just under 24 hours.</p>
<p>This is potentially a signal that big volume is about to return to the token, with the past few days witnessing several big SOL transfers.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  1,000,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SOL?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SOL</a> (184,925,857 USD) transferred from unknown wallet to unknown new wallet<a href="https://t.co/sYJP8ufpmz">https://t.co/sYJP8ufpmz</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1772041548642840640?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>SOL undoubtedly remains one of the most in-demand alts in the market, which will help the coin push to new heights as it regains its momentum from earlier in the month and from February.</p>
<p>There are a number of factors that could help boost the market and, by extension, the Solana price.</p>
<p>These include an improving macroeconomic picture (in particular <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fomc-interest-rate-decision-signals-all-clear-for-bitcoin-bull-run.htm">a softening Federal Reserve</a>), <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/standard-chartered-predicts-up-to-45-billion-inflows-to-ethereum-etfs-within-1-year.htm">hopes of Ethereum ETFs</a>, and the upcoming Bitcoin halving.</p>
<p>Solana will benefit more than many other alts during any market surge, given its strong fundamental position.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Solana meme coins are unbelievable!</p>
<p>My life getting crazy tbh <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f92f.png" alt="🤯" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/WxLjJBrbZf">pic.twitter.com/WxLjJBrbZf</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gordon (@AltcoinGordon) <a href="https://twitter.com/AltcoinGordon/status/1770513635749568786?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 20, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Its TVL now <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Solana">stands at $4.4 billion</a>, with its 1,500% increase in the past year following from spikes in NFT and meme coin usage on its network.</p>
<p>Its price could therefore continue to rise steadily in the near future, potentially reaching $200 in a couple of weeks and $250 by the summer.</p>
<h2>Diversification into New Low-Cap Alts</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
SOL is undoubtedly one of the major altcoins to watch this year, yet traders can widen their exposure to upside by diversifying their portfolios into smaller cap alts as well as bigger tokens.</p>
<p>There are numerous highly promising new tokens in the market right now, with several presale coins looking particularly good as they prepare to list.</p>
<p><span>For example, </span><a style="font-size: 16px;" href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin">Green Bitcoin (GBTC) is an ERC-20 token</a> <span>that has raised over $8 million in its sale, which is entering its final stretch.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">With Decentralized and Centralized exchange listings not far away, the momentum Green Bitcoin is generating is getting intense.</p>
<p>We love the movement! <a href="https://t.co/QeOhyUA35f">pic.twitter.com/QeOhyUA35f</a></p>
<p>&mdash; GreenBitcoin (@GreenBTCtoken) <a href="https://twitter.com/GreenBTCtoken/status/1771637913387958733?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Styled as an environmentally friendly version of Bitcoin (BTC), Green Bitcoin has the same hard cap of 21 million tokens that has helped to make BTC the biggest cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Yet it adds an environmentally friendly twist on this deflationary formula, in that it operates on the proof-of-stake Ethereum blockchain, which is much less energy intensive.</p>
<p>It also enables staking, meaning that the coin may become even more deflationary than BTC itself, since holders will be locking their tokens up for long periods.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s interesting about Green Bitcoin&#8217;s staking model is that it offers a unique predict-to-earn form of staking, which invites stakers to predict future BTC price movements.</p>
<p>If they predict correctly they receive greater rewards, something which should incentivize more staking.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Nothing can stop the GREEN REVOLUTION!</p>
<p>Join the Green Bitcoin presale TODAY <a href="https://t.co/YgwUk11Ay8">pic.twitter.com/YgwUk11Ay8</a></p>
<p>&mdash; GreenBitcoin (@GreenBTCtoken) <a href="https://twitter.com/GreenBTCtoken/status/1767252113716097448?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>So because of the hard cap and strong staking incentives, the GBTC price could rally substantially and sustainably once it lists.</span></p>
<p><span></span>Investors can buy it as part of the its presale by visiting <a style="font-size: 16px;" href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin">the official Green Bitcoin website</a>, where 1 GBTC costs $1.1062.</p>
<p>This the final price before the sale ends, so interested traders are advised to act quickly, otherwise they may miss out on one of the biggest launches of 2024.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin">Visit Green Bitcoin Now</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-bounces-6-7-new-rally-starting.htm">Solana Price Prediction as SOL Bounces 6.7% – New Rally Starting?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25101155/1711361514-solana-price-prediction-as-sol-bounces-6-7-new-rally-starting.jpg" length="202764" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Tax Evasion Charges in Nigeria, Executives Detained</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-faces-tax-evasion-charges-in-nigeria-executives-detained.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigeria]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, is facing tax evasion charges in Nigeria, as the dispute between the exchange and Nigerian authorities escalates. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-faces-tax-evasion-charges-in-nigeria-executives-detained.htm">Binance Faces Tax Evasion Charges in Nigeria, Executives Detained</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/reviews/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, is facing tax evasion charges in Nigeria, as the dispute between the exchange and Nigerian authorities escalates. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The country&#8217;s tax watchdog, the Federal Inland Revenue Service (FIRS), announced the charges against Binance and revealed that two Binance executives have been detained by the government, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://guardian.ng/breakingnews/nigeria-files-tax-evasion-charges-against-binance/?utm_term=Autofeed&amp;echobox=twitter_post&amp;utm_medium=Social&amp;utm_source=Twitter#Echobox=1711355227" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">local media outlets</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> reported Monday.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The charges were filed at the Federal High Court in Abuja and include four counts of tax evasion, encompassing allegations of non-payment of Value-Added Tax (VAT), Company Income Tax, failure to file tax returns, and complicity in aiding customers to evade taxes through the Binance platform.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance Executives Detained by Authorities in Nigeria</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">The two detained executives, Tigran Gambaryan and Nadeem Anjarwalla, both senior officials at Binance, are currently in custody under the Economic and Financial Crimes Commission (EFCC). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Nigerian government accuses Binance of neglecting to register with the FIRS for tax purposes and violating tax regulations within the country.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the charges focuses on Binance&#8217;s alleged failure to collect and remit various types of taxes as required by Section 40 of the FIRS Establishment Act 2007.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This section specifically addresses the non-deduction and non-remittance of taxes, outlining penalties and potential imprisonment for entities found in violation.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">After these binance guys already pleaded guilty for evading tax, why the guy come elope? </p>
<p>It is very sad sha. However, the tax must be paid! . The federal government must not let this go</p>
<p>Same you who paid $4.3 billion in the US, must pay in Nigeria for too. Lobatan</p>
<p>&mdash; Queen of the West (@TheAbisolaa) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheAbisolaa/status/1772190445935694040?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The charges detail specific instances where Binance is accused of violating tax laws, such as the failure to issue VAT invoices, hindering the determination and payment of taxes by its subscribers. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the FIRS, any company conducting business exceeding N25 million annually is obligated under the Finance Act to pay taxes like Company Income Tax (CIT) and collect and remit Value Added Tax (VAT).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Any company that conducts business exceeding N25 million annually is deemed, by the Finance Act, to be present in Nigeria,” the FIRS noted in a statement.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“According to this rule, Binance falls into that category. So, it is obligated to pay taxes like Company Income Tax (CIT) and also collect and remit Value Added Tax (VAT). However, Binance did not adhere to these requirements, thus violating Nigerian laws and potentially facing investigation and legal action for this infraction.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">US Pressured to Assist Detained Binance Executives</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">There has been </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pressure-mounts-on-biden-to-assist-in-release-of-detained-binance-executives.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">mounting pressure on the Biden administration</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to intervene and secure the release of the detained Binance executives.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The administration is facing increasing calls to take swift action in securing the release of Gambaryan and Anjarwalla, who have been detained by the Nigerian government since February 26, 2024.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The U.S. Chamber of Digital Commerce made an appeal through a blog post on its website on March 15, leading the charge for urgent diplomatic intervention to address what it deems a grave injustice.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As reported, Binance recently had to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-to-exit-nigerian-market-discontinues-all-ngn-services.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">discontinue all services involving Nigerian</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> local fiat currency, the Nigerian naira (NGN), after regulatory scrutiny. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange said it would suspend NGN withdrawals after March 8. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Earlier, the Nigerian government </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerian-government-slaps-binance-with-10-billion-fine-amid-crypto-crackdown.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">imposed a staggering $10 billion fine</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on Binance as part of a crackdown on the platform in an effort to stabilize the nation’s local currency.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-faces-tax-evasion-charges-in-nigeria-executives-detained.htm">Binance Faces Tax Evasion Charges in Nigeria, Executives Detained</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25100224/1711360944-1711360880067_processed.jpg" length="79353" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore-Licensed DigiFT Introduces US Treasury Bill Depository Receipt Tokens</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/digift-introduces-us-treasury-bill-depository-receipt-token.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asset tokenization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DigiFT, a Singapore-based fintech company, has made a foray into the digital asset realm with the launch of the its US Treasury bill depository receipt (DR) tokens. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digift-introduces-us-treasury-bill-depository-receipt-token.htm">Singapore-Licensed DigiFT Introduces US Treasury Bill Depository Receipt Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DigiFT, a Singapore-based fintech company, has made a foray into the digital asset realm with the launch of the its US Treasury bill depository receipt (DR) tokens. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The DR tokens offer investors fractional ownership in the underlying US Treasury bills, enabling investors to gain exposure to the traditionally secure US debt market without the need for substantial upfront capital, the firm </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.digift.sg/announcements/first-rwa-depository-receipt-tokens.html?ref=blockhead.co" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said in a Monday press release</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Traditionally, investing in US Treasury bills has required significant financial resources. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DigiFT&#8217;s DR tokens aim to dismantle this barrier by allowing investors to purchase fractional shares of these bills. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;DigiFT&#8217;s innovative DR structure addresses a pain point in the current RWA market, empowering investors with direct ownership of underlying assets and returns,&#8221; Henry Zhang, the founder and CEO of DigiFT, said. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He further emphasized DigiFT&#8217;s commitment to expanding the range of traditional financial assets in the Web3 space through the DR model, which offers enhanced investor protection and transparency.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DigiFT Says its DR Tokens Are Regulated</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">One key aspect emphasized by DigiFT is compliance with regulations, providing investors with peace of mind, the company said. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Traditional asset ownership often involves navigating complex legal and regulatory frameworks. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">By adhering to regulations, DigiFT aims to streamline the investment process and make it more accessible for investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company detailed that the DigiFT US Treasury Tokens (DRUST) is the first offering of a series, under the DR structure. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Each DRUST is directly backed by AA+ rated, highly liquid and short-term U.S. Treasury Bills, tailor-made for stablecoin issuers and Web3 product developer / managers seeking regulatory compliant treasury as well as cash management solutions.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Institutional and accredited investors can access DRUST from their authorised self-custodial wallets using fiat or stablecoins anytime anywhere. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Established in 2021 and previously a participant in the Monetary Authority of Singapore&#8217;s FinTech Regulatory Sandbox, DigiFT obtained the Capital Markets Services (CMS) license and recognition as a Recognized Market Operator (RMO) in December 2023. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tokenized Funds Continue to Gain Popularity</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a report earlier this year, Moody’s, a leading investment risk assessment firm, revealed the value of tokenized funds </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tokenized-funds-skyrocketed-to-800m-value-in-2023-sparked-by-us-treasury-tokenization-moodys.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">surged from $100 million</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at the beginning of 2023 to approximately $800 million, driven by the rising tokenization of U.S. treasuries.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report highlighted that both public and private blockchains are witnessing the inclusion of various assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some of the more notable examples include Franklin Templeton’s U.S. Government Money Fund </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/14-trillion-asset-management-firm-franklin-templeton-announces-blockchain-fund-ii-targeting-institutional-investors.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">expanding from Stellar to Polygon</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Backed Finance launching a tokenized short-term U.S. treasury bond exchange-traded fund (ETF), and UBS Asset Management deploying a tokenized money market fund (MMF) on the Ethereum blockchain.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to Moody’s, the tokenization of MMFs offers the potential to combine their stability with the technological advantages of stablecoins.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, the applications of tokenized MMFs extend beyond simple purchasing and holding until maturity, indicating the potential for a wider range of uses.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report also suggested that tokenized funds can enhance market liquidity and accessibility, reduce costs, enable fractionalization, decrease dependence on intermediaries, shorten settlement times, automate processes through smart contracts, and enhance transparency.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">RWA &amp; Tokenization: Moody&#39;s highlighted the growing adoption of blockchain-based tokenized funds, stating that it improves the efficiency of investing in assets like government bonds, funds and represents untapped market potential.</p>
<p>These are one of many reasons why RWA should be… <a href="https://t.co/v9FueHXeFd">pic.twitter.com/v9FueHXeFd</a></p>
<p>&mdash; The Real Lifestyle (@Trl_co) <a href="https://twitter.com/Trl_co/status/1747073070698009085?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 16, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digift-introduces-us-treasury-bill-depository-receipt-token.htm">Singapore-Licensed DigiFT Introduces US Treasury Bill Depository Receipt Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25081154/1711354314-1711354259317_processed.jpg" length="93084" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Expert Clarifies No EU-Wide Ban on Anonymous Crypto Wallets</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-clarifies-no-eu-wide-ban-on-anonymous-crypto-wallets.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sujha Sundararajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anti-money laundering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European Union]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188375</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Industry expert Patrick Hansen clarified that the EU’s recent anti-money laundering (AML) law does not specifically target banning anonymous crypto accounts.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-clarifies-no-eu-wide-ban-on-anonymous-crypto-wallets.htm">Expert Clarifies No EU-Wide Ban on Anonymous Crypto Wallets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An industry expert, on Sunday, has ‘debunked’ claims that the European Union has banned anonymous crypto wallets and transactions.</p>
<p>On Saturday, reports spread across the industry, claiming that the <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/meetdocs/2014_2019/plmrep/COMMITTEES/CJ12/AG/2024/03-19/1297044EN.pdf">EU’s recent anti-money laundering (AML) law</a> specifically targets banning anonymous crypto accounts.</p>
<p>However, industry expert Patrick Hansen addressed these claims, clarifying that the law does not specifically target cryptos.</p>
<p>“Yesterday was a prime example of why crypto Twitter (and often crypto media) should not be trusted when it comes to crypto policy,” he wrote on X (Twitter).</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ Yesterday was a prime example of why crypto Twitter (and often crypto media) should not be trusted when it comes to crypto policy. Let&#39;s debunk claims that the EU is banning anonymous crypto transactions or self-custodial wallets.</p>
<p>Here is what’s actually in the EU Anti Money… <a href="https://t.co/dsNZQzl9Mx">pic.twitter.com/dsNZQzl9Mx</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Patrick Hansen (@paddi_hansen) <a href="https://twitter.com/paddi_hansen/status/1771929859704389954?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<blockquote><p>“Let&#8217;s debunk claims that the EU is banning anonymous crypto transactions or self-custodial wallets.”</p></blockquote>
<p>He stressed that the law “is not a crypto regulation,” but a broad framework that applies to all financial institutions. These includes CASPs (crypto-asset service providers), as well as services that are prone to AML risks such as gambling services.</p>
<p>“The AMLR will apply to all CASPs (exchanges, brokers etc.) that are regulated under MiCA,” Hansen wrote. “These CASPs will need to follow standard KYC/AML procedures like customer due diligence (CDD) etc.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">4/ The AMLR will apply to all CASPs (exchanges, brokers etc.) that are regulated under MiCA. These CASPs will need to follow standard KYC/AML procedures like customer due diligence (CDD) etc.</p>
<p>This is nothing new, as all crypto exchanges &amp; custodial wallet providers in the EU are… <a href="https://t.co/ZN1AsWdBpw">pic.twitter.com/ZN1AsWdBpw</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Patrick Hansen (@paddi_hansen) <a href="https://twitter.com/paddi_hansen/status/1771929868541767907?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Further, on contrary to the rumors regarding an outright ban on anonymous crypto wallets, the AML includes provision for them. According to Hansen, this rule is already included in the existing AML regulation where custodial wallets cannot provide services to anonymous users.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Also, CASPs will not be allowed to provide accounts for privacy coins. This is already existing business practice across the world &#8211; not only in the EU.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Additionally, the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/markets-in-crypto-assets-mica-framework-signed-into-law-by-eu-officials.htm">Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation</a>, already prohibits crypto listing with built-in anonymisation function. “As such, this is nothing new either,” he added.</p>
<h2>EU’s AML Law Has Nothing New for Cryptos?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Hansen wrote that the regulation largely reaffirms existing AML rules for CASPs. The law poses an &#8220;extremely limited&#8221; impact on the crypto sector in the EU region, he noted.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the law has not introduced radically new restrictions on self-custody payments, wallets or peer-to-peer transfers.</p>
<p>“Therefore, you will be able to use your self-custody wallets for buying goods/services in the EU without any restrictions.”</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/meetdocs/2014_2019/plmrep/COMMITTEES/CJ12/AG/2024/03-19/1297044EN.pdf">final text</a> was agreed by the ECON committee in the EU in March and it only needs to pass final approval in the EU Parliament’s plenary and the EU Council.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-clarifies-no-eu-wide-ban-on-anonymous-crypto-wallets.htm">Expert Clarifies No EU-Wide Ban on Anonymous Crypto Wallets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25081152/1711354312-1711354296144_processed.jpg" length="129825" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marathon Digital CEO Warns of Challenges Ahead for Small Miners Post Bitcoin Halving</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-ceo-warns-bitcoin-halving-challenges-small-miners.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shalini Nagarajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marathon Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miners]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marathon Digital CEO Fred Thiel warned that smaller miners will face financial strain following the Bitcoin halving event in April.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-ceo-warns-bitcoin-halving-challenges-small-miners.htm">Marathon Digital CEO Warns of Challenges Ahead for Small Miners Post Bitcoin Halving</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marathon Digital Holdings CEO Fred Thiel warned that smaller miners will face financial strain following the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/tags/bitcoin-halving/"><span>Bitcoin halving</span></a> event in April.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2024/03/22/large-scale-bitcoin-miners-are-competing-head-on-with-ai-companies-for-power-marathon-digital-ceo.html"><span>In a CNBC interview</span></a> published Friday, Thiel highlighted the disparity in access to capital and equipment financing between smaller and larger miners in the current mining market cycle.</p>
<p>He noted that while larger miners have had the opportunity to raise capital, smaller miners have faced challenges in scaling due to limited access to financing options.</p>
<p>“Post halving I think you&#8217;ll see the smaller miners come under financial stress, which will enable the bigger miners to consolidate the industry,” he said.</p>
<h2>Marathon Digital’s Expansion Strategy in Anticipation of Bitcoin Halving Stress</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
He added that Marathon has prioritized addressing this issue and recently finalized two acquisitions, with intentions to continue acquiring assets in the future.</p>
<p>“We have quite a heavy balance sheet. We’re ready to go as opportunities arise. But you have to be very prudent, you have to do these things at the right prices,” he said.</p>
<p>Marathon recently announced its acquisition of a <a href="https://ir.mara.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1347/marathon-digital-holdings-enters-definitive-agreement-to"><span>Texas Bitcoin mining facility</span></a> from Applied Digital for about $87m in cash. This facility, situated adjacent to a wind farm, boasts a capacity of 200 megawatts (MW).</p>
<p>In January, the company <a href="https://ir.mara.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1335/marathon-digital-holdings-enters-definitive-agreement-to"><span>finalized the acquisition</span></a> of two mining facilities located in Texas and Nebraska. This transaction, totaling around $179m, secured 390 MW of mining capacity and involved the termination of competitor Hut 8&#8217;s management of the facilities.</p>
<p>Marathon&#8217;s acquisitions align with its goal of expanding its operations before the upcoming Bitcoin halving, expected around April 20. This event, which occurs every four years, will halve block rewards from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC. Consequently, smaller companies in the sector are expected to face challenges like capital access and high energy expenses.</p>
<h2>Marathon Achieves Record Revenue in 2023</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
In 2023, the company <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-reports-record-387-5-million-revenue-in-2023.htm"><span>experienced a surge in revenue</span></a>, culminating in substantial profitability. Its fourth quarter and annual earnings report unveiled record-breaking revenue of $387.5m for the year, marking a 229% increase compared to the previous year.</p>
<p>“2023 was a record-breaking year for Marathon, during which we achieved our primary objectives of energizing our fleet of previously purchased mining rigs and optimizing our performance,” Thiel said.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-ceo-warns-bitcoin-halving-challenges-small-miners.htm">Marathon Digital CEO Warns of Challenges Ahead for Small Miners Post Bitcoin Halving</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25060313/1711346593-1711346561473_processed.jpg" length="30783" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ParaSwap Resolves Vulnerability in Newly-Launched Smart Contract, Returns Crypto Assets to Users</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paraswap-resolves-vulnerability-in-newly-launched-smart-contract.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ParaSwap has addressed a critical vulnerability in its recently launched Augustus v6 smart contract and has commenced the process of returning cryptocurrency assets to affected users. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paraswap-resolves-vulnerability-in-newly-launched-smart-contract.htm">ParaSwap Resolves Vulnerability in Newly-Launched Smart Contract, Returns Crypto Assets to Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Decentralized finance aggregator ParaSwap has addressed a critical vulnerability in its recently launched Augustus v6 smart contract and has commenced the process of returning cryptocurrency assets to affected users. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/paraswap/status/1771964824542441528" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">recent post on X</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the team said that all assets have been returned to wallets that were successfully recovered by white hat hackers. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, permissions to the Augustus v6 contract have been revoked to prevent further exploitation.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">213 Addresses Yet to Receive Funds</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the majority of users have had their assets returned, ParaSwap has identified 213 addresses that have yet to revoke allowances to the flawed contract. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Revoking allowances involves disabling or terminating the contract&#8217;s functionality on the blockchain, ensuring it no longer has access to users&#8217; wallets and tokens.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If your wallet &#8220;have not received them yet, your wallet is still vulnerable, PLEASE REVOKE ALL RELEVANT PERMISSIONS!&#8221; they wrote. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">White hack recovery update: Assets have been returned to wallets which have revoked their permissions </p>
<p>If your wallet had assets transferred to 0x66e90d840d7c4f3473e25dd8ca361747058c6db0 and have not received them yet, your wallet is still vulnerable, PLEASE REVOKE ALL RELEVANT… <a href="https://t.co/zraj3tSFNe">https://t.co/zraj3tSFNe</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ParaSwap (@paraswap) <a href="https://twitter.com/paraswap/status/1771964824542441528?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The vulnerability in the newly launched smart contract was discovered by ParaSwap last week. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thanks to the timely intervention of white hat hackers, a significant loss of assets was prevented. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The platform promptly took action by submitting a comprehensive report to the appropriate authorities, initiating an investigation into the stolen funds.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ParaSwap is working closely with blockchain analytics and security firms, Chainalysis and TRM Labs, in an effort to identify the hacker addresses and trace the movement of the funds. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The team has also reached out to the identified hacker addresses through on-chain messaging, urging the return of the stolen user funds.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If the hacker fails to respond by March 27, ParaSwap will assume that the funds have been unlawfully appropriated, and they will pursue all available legal avenues to recover them.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Initially, the losses incurred were relatively small, with preliminary findings indicating that the hackers managed to abscond with only $24,000 before the vulnerability was discovered.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The vulnerability was detected in ParaSwap&#8217;s Augustus v6 smart contract on March 20, just days after its launch on March 18.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> The contract aimed to enhance token swaps and reduce transfer fees. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Upon discovering the vulnerability, ParaSwap promptly paused the application programming interface (API) and secured the funds through the assistance of white hat hackers.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hacks Continue to Haunt Crypto Industry</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hacks and exploits have become a mounting concern in the crypto industry, particularly within the realm of decentralized finance (DeFi) applications. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/record-losses-in-web3-may-be-coming-as-crypto-prices-rise-immunefi.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report by Immunefi</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, a total of $1.8 billion was lost to crypto hacks and scams in 2023, with 17% of the losses attributed to the North Korean Lazarus Group. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In individual incidents, hacking accounted for over $65 million (97.54%) of the stolen funds in February 2024.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As reported, bad actors </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-lost-38-9-million-to-bad-actors-in-first-month-of-2024-quantstamp.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">have stolen $38.9 million</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> from various Web3 projects in the first month of 2024.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the first major crypto hacks of the year occurred when Radiant Capital experienced a $4.5 million loss due to an empty market exploit.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gamma Strategies, another affected platform, fell victim to a flash loan attack on January 4, shortly after the Radiant Capital incident.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paraswap-resolves-vulnerability-in-newly-launched-smart-contract.htm">ParaSwap Resolves Vulnerability in Newly-Launched Smart Contract, Returns Crypto Assets to Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25060552/1711346752-1711346506848_processed.jpg" length="73157" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Sees Spike in Crypto Options Engagement Among Hedge Funds</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-hedge-fund-spike-crypto-options-engagement.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shalini Nagarajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Derivatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Goldman Sachs' hedge fund clients are reportedly showing increased interest in crypto derivatives, spurred by the resurgence of the crypto market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-hedge-fund-spike-crypto-options-engagement.htm">Goldman Sachs Sees Spike in Crypto Options Engagement Among Hedge Funds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Goldman Sachs&#8217; hedge fund clients are reportedly showing increased interest in crypto derivatives, spurred by the resurgence of the crypto market.</p>
<p>The bank officially launched its crypto trading desk in 2021. It then began to facilitate various <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/"><span>Bitcoin</span></a>-linked trades, including Bitcoin non-deliverable futures and CME BTC futures, following years of contemplation dating back to 2017.</p>
<p>Currently, Goldman offers cash-settled Bitcoin and <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ethereum/"><span>Ether</span></a> option trading, alongside CME-listed Bitcoin and Ether futures. However, it does not directly trade the actual underlying crypto tokens themselves.</p>
<p>Max Minton, Goldman’s Asia Pacific head of digital assets, told <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-24/goldman-s-hedge-fund-clients-get-more-active-in-crypto-options"><span>Bloomberg in a recent interview</span></a> that the recent approval of ETFs has reignited interest and activity among the bank&#8217;s clients. Minton noted that many clients are either currently active in the crypto space or are considering entering it.</p>
<h2>Goldman Sachs Clients Embrace Crypto Derivatives for Diverse Purposes</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
According to Minton, there has been a noticeable increase in client interest, onboarding, pipeline, and trading volume since the beginning of the year.</p>
<p>A majority of this demand stems from Goldman&#8217;s existing clients, particularly traditional hedge funds. However, the bank is also broadening its client base to include asset managers, banking clients, and specific digital asset firms.</p>
<p>He mentioned that clients are using crypto derivatives for various purposes, such as directional bets, yield enhancement, and hedging.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin ETF Launch Sparks Market Optimism</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The development follows Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge to a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-record-high-72k-signals-strong-crypto-rebound.htm"><span>record high above $72,000</span></a>, triggered by the Bitcoin ETF launch and anticipation around the upcoming halving event.</p>
<p>Despite Bitcoin retracing to around $67,075 as of Monday, the outlook for crypto derivatives remains bullish. A quarterly report from Genesis Trading last year <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-report-crypto-derivatives-emerge-as-next-key-growth-driver-2023.htm"><span>predicted substantial expansion in this sector</span></a>, driven by a significant decrease in spot market liquidity and a growing trend towards the use of derivative instruments.</p>
<p>Currently, most Goldman clients appear to be primarily focused on Bitcoin-related products. However, there is potential for a shift in interest towards Ether-related products if Ether ETFs receive approval in the US.</p>
<p>Mathew McDermott, Goldman&#8217;s head of digital assets, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spot-ether-etf-goldman-sachs-sec-approval-confident.htm"><span>expressed optimism</span></a> about the approval of Ether ETFs back in January.</p>
<p>The SEC is expected to make its initial ruling on a spot Ethereum ETF by May 23.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-hedge-fund-spike-crypto-options-engagement.htm">Goldman Sachs Sees Spike in Crypto Options Engagement Among Hedge Funds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25044646/1711342006-1711341861669_processed.jpg" length="187203" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Kwon Released From Montenegro Prison With Extradition Verdict Still Underway: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwon-released-from-prison-with-extradition-verdict-underway.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tanzeel Akhtar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 04:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188312</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Do Kwon was released from prison in Montenegro on Saturday as the Supreme Court deliberates on extradition requests from the United States and South Korea, according to a Bloomberg report citing prison officials. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwon-released-from-prison-with-extradition-verdict-underway.htm">Do Kwon Released From Montenegro Prison With Extradition Verdict Still Underway: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon was released from prison in Montenegro on Saturday as the Supreme Court deliberates on extradition requests from the U.S. and South Korea, according to a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-23/crypto-fugitive-do-kwon-out-of-jail-but-his-next-destination-is-unclear?embedded-checkout=true">Bloomberg report</a> citing prison officials.</span></p>
<p><span>Kwon’s recent ruling mandating his extradition to South Korea is being challenged by Montenegro’s top prosecutor. </span>Last week it emerged the<span> </span><span><a href="https://sudovi-me.translate.goog/vrdt/sadrzaj/W8V9?_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;_x_tr_hl=en&amp;_x_tr_pto=wapp">Supreme State Prosecutor’s Office in Montenegro</a> is escalating the case to the </span><span>Supreme Court for review claiming errors were made. </span></p>
<p><span>Do Kwon was arrested in Montenegro in March 2023 after being caught using a fake Costa Rican passport traveling to Dubai, United Arab Emirates.</span></p>
<p><span>&#8220;We released Do Kwon from prison as his regular prison term for traveling with fake papers ended,” Montenegro prison director Darko Vukcevic told the news outlet. “Since he is a foreign citizen and his documents were withheld, he was taken for an interview to police directorate for foreigners, and they will deal with him further,&#8221; said Vukcevic.</span></p>
<p><span>Both </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwon-should-be-extradited-to-south-korea-not-united-states-lawyer-argues.htm">South Korea and the U.S. had appealed</a><span> to extradite Kwon, however, Montenegro’s minister of justice gave preference to South Korea. This decision is being challenged by Montenegro’s top prosecutor.  </span></p>
<h2>Do Kwon’s Arrest and Terra’s Collapse</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span>Do Kwon is the architect behind the failed crypto project<span> </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terrausd-stablecoin-scandal-sec-sues-terraform-labs-do-kwon-for-deceiving-investors-heres-what-happened.htm">TerraUSD stablecoin,</a><span> </span>launched in 2022. As a stablecoin designed to be a utility token on the blockchain, Terra USD was pegged algorithmically 1:1 to the U.S. dollar.</p>
<p>The stablecoin lost its pegging, however, resulting in its collapse alongside LUNA, the Terra sister token. The United States and South Korean authorities went after Kwon, who escaped to<span> </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-officials-banned-from-leaving-south-korea-as-do-kwon-may-apply-for-singaporean-citizenship.htm">Singapore to avoid South Korean prosecutors</a><span> </span>from opening his fraud charges.</p>
<p>Kwon was later apprehended in Montenegro and sentenced to four months imprisonment after he was caught trying to escape using a forged Costa Rican passport.</p>
<p>As it stands, South Korean authorities are escalating efforts to ensure Kwon faces prosecution for his alleged fraud cases and tax evasion.</p>
<p>Kwon, who denied the charges, claimed that the $40 billion implosion of the Terra ecosystem resulted from market forces and doesn’t indicate any criminal action.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwon-released-from-prison-with-extradition-verdict-underway.htm">Do Kwon Released From Montenegro Prison With Extradition Verdict Still Underway: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25035044/1711338644-1711338618314_processed.jpg" length="174691" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Central Bank, Ministry of Finance to Settle Crypto Policy Differences</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-ministry-of-finance-to-settle-crypto-policy-differences.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Alper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 03:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188171</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Ministry of Finance says it wants to settle its long-standing crypto policy differences with the nation’s Central Bank.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-ministry-of-finance-to-settle-crypto-policy-differences.htm">Russian Central Bank, Ministry of Finance to Settle Crypto Policy Differences</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Ministry of Finance says it wants to settle its long-standing crypto policy differences with the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-government-to-create-crypto-confiscation-platform.htm">nation</a>’s Central Bank.</p>
<p>According to the media outlet <a href="https://www.rbc.ru/crypto/news/65fd7cc69a7947fb94c51d1c">RBC</a>, Finance Minister Anton Siluanov said he was “sure” his ministry and the bank would soon “come to an agreement” on crypto regulation-related matters.</p>
<h2>Russian Central Bank Eager to Break Crypto Impasse?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Speaking at an event held at a state-run financial university, Siluanov said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I am sure that [the ministry] and the Central Bank will come to an agreement. This issue has been discussed for several years. We cannot prohibit the circulation of cryptocurrencies. Therefore, we need to regulate this [market]. I am sure that we will find a solution.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The Ministry of Finance and the Central Bank have been locked in <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-still-saying-no-use-of-crypto-settlements.htm">an unproductive crypto policy-related impasse</a> for years.</p>
<p>The government agency wants to regulate and tax crypto exchanges and traders, but the bank has previously called for a China-style blanket ban.</p>
<p>The ministry tried to break through this impasse in early 2022, when it unveiled a comprehensive draft bill on crypto regulation.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Crypto in Russia: More People Using Tokens for Payments, Claims Academic</p>
<p>More people are using crypto in Russia than ever before, a leading Moscow-based academic has claimed.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CryptoNews?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CryptoNews</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Russia?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Russia</a><a href="https://t.co/XtzNVWeN7h">https://t.co/XtzNVWeN7h</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Cryptonews.com (@cryptonews) <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptonews/status/1759869949940519392?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 20, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The bank shot back with its own rival bill, proposing an almost total ban on all crypto-related activities.</p>
<p>Neither bill made it past the committee stage at the State Duma, and the crypto sector has remained in limbo ever since.</p>
<p>This led to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russia-fatf-rating-downgraded-due-to-insufficient-crypto-regulation.htm">a downgrading in the nation’s FATF compliance rating last month</a>, and calls from government bodies to fast-track regulation.</p>
<p>However, the war in Ukraine and resulting Western <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-firms-already-doing-business-crypto-say-theyve-every-right-do-so.htm">sanctions</a> appear to have forced the Russian Central Bank’s hand.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia will hit back at the US and its allies if its foreign assets are seized, says the country&#39;s finance minister <a href="https://t.co/O4uRvW74KD">https://t.co/O4uRvW74KD</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg Economics (@economics) <a href="https://twitter.com/economics/status/1762035949960061086?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The bank has grudgingly conceded to soften its stance on <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-miners-tell-lawmakers-hurry-up-legalize-our-industry.htm">industrial crypto mining</a>, which is now booming in Russia.</p>
<p>It has also agreed to make some concessions on the use of crypto as a payment tool in international trade.</p>
<p>And it is here that Siluanov sees common ground for legislation. He said there was a “need to work together with the Central Bank on the issue of identifying possible options for using cryptocurrencies for settlements, both within the country and abroad.”</p>
<figure id="attachment_188173" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188173" style="width: 628px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188173" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24122228/1711282947-as1.jpg" alt="The Russian Finance Minister Anton Siluanov, speaking in 2023." width="628" height="376" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24122228/1711282947-as1.jpg 628w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24122228/1711282947-as1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24122228/1711282947-as1-150x90.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 628px) 100vw, 628px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188173" class="wp-caption-text">The Russian Finance Minister Anton Siluanov, speaking in 2023. (Source: CGTN/YouTube)</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Russian Crypto Mining Industry Booms – Will Bank Make Concessions?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The minister also claimed that the bank had “agreed to hold a meeting to discuss [crypto] mining.” He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We need to talk about what can and cannot be done with cryptocurrency. We have now agreed, with the Central Bank, to discuss the issue of mining. We must talk about whether [mined coins] can be used to make settlements within the country and in international settlements.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the bank is unlikely to make such sweeping concessions. The bank’s long-serving Governor Elvira Nabiullina has repeatedly stated that she will not tolerate crypto’s “entry into the Russian economy.”</p>
<p>Indeed, Siluanov admitted that both the ministry and the bank were “inclined” to ensure that mined tokens were used “for external payments.”</p>
<p>Such talk could <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-lawmakers-want-to-create-a-state-run-crypto-exchange.htm">resurrect plans to create a state-owned crypto exchange</a> that essentially buys Russian miners’ coins and sells them to firms that pay for overseas goods in crypto.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia’s central bank holds interest rates unchanged as it navigates inflation risks <a href="https://t.co/7Dxbt4PVIu">https://t.co/7Dxbt4PVIu</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg (@business) <a href="https://twitter.com/business/status/1771123959645212712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Russian Mining Tax Windfall on the Cards?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Russian crypto miners have said legalizing their industry could provide the state with a $540.3 million windfall in tax revenue.</p>
<p>Industry chiefs have <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-mining-industry-could-be-set-for-4bn-boost.htm">claimed they are ready to invest $4 billion</a> in new multi-purpose data centers, which could also save Moscow $32.4 million in tech investment.</p>
<p>Miners have become frustrated at Moscow’s refusal to legalize their industry, instead leaving it in a quasi-legal grey zone.</p>
<p>Crypto mining is neither legal nor illegal in Russia, a fact that has led to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-mining-hotspot-cracks-down-on-illegal-miners.htm">much legal frustration in the nation</a>.</p>
<p>They have <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-miners-fume-at-moscows-plans-to-raise-their-electricity-tariffs.htm">also hit back</a> at the Ministry of Energy’s controversial plans to hike their electricity tariffs by up to five times.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-ministry-of-finance-to-settle-crypto-policy-differences.htm">Russian Central Bank, Ministry of Finance to Settle Crypto Policy Differences</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24121926/1711282766-1711268825676_processed.jpg" length="159420" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bithumb IPO Plans ‘Accelerate’ as South Korean Crypto Exchange Eyes Public Listing</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bithumb-ipo-plans-accelerate-as-south-korean-crypto-exchange-eyes-public-listing.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Alper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 23:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The South Korean exchange Bithumb is looking to step up its IPO plans – and could look to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-exchange-bithumb-still-aiming-for-ipo-despite-deep-troubles.htm">launch a fast-tracked initial public offering</a> as the crypto bull market continues.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bithumb-ipo-plans-accelerate-as-south-korean-crypto-exchange-eyes-public-listing.htm">Bithumb IPO Plans ‘Accelerate’ as South Korean Crypto Exchange Eyes Public Listing</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The South Korean exchange Bithumb is looking to step up its IPO plans – and could look to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-exchange-bithumb-still-aiming-for-ipo-despite-deep-troubles.htm">launch a fast-tracked initial public offering</a> as the crypto bull market continues.</p>
<p>Per <a href="https://www.hankyung.com/article/202403220305O" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hanguk Kyungjae</a>, Bithumb is looking to “accelerate” its proposed KOSPI listing.</p>
<h2>Bithumb IPO: Exchange Takes Decisive Steps</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The media outlet reported that Bithumb announced that the exchange will spin off its holdings operations into a separate company. It is tentatively naming this firm Bithumb Investment.</p>
<p>The firm published a regulatory filing document on March 22 detailing its plans.</p>
<p>The new firm will take control of Bithumb’s holdings, investments, and real estate operations.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the entity currently known as Bithumb Korea will focus on operating the crypto trading platform.</p>
<p>The company plans to divide shares in Bithumb using a 6:4 ratio. It will put the plan before a meeting of shareholders on May 10.</p>
<p>If the shareholders approve, Bithumb Investment will officially launch on June 13, the media outlet reported.</p>
<p>Shareholders will reportedly be told they will “receive new shares in the new corporation in proportion to their existing shares.”</p>
<p>The firm made no mention of ongoing court cases, including <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-prosecutors-seek-arrest-warrants-for-golf-star-bithumb-exec.htm">a probe into alleged market manipulation supposedly conducted by the mysterious “real” owner of Bithumb</a>.</p>
<p>Instead, it appears the firm wants to distance itself from such matters. It seems to want the IPO’s success or otherwise to stem from its core exchange business.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Foreign investors have extended their buying streak, acquiring a net purchase of 14.401 trillion won in <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/KOSPI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#KOSPI</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/stocks?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#stocks</a> so far this year, according to the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Korea?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Korea</a> Exchange. This figure far exceeds last year’s total net purchases of 11.424 trillion won.<a href="https://t.co/LiPQxxVfCW">https://t.co/LiPQxxVfCW</a></p>
<p>&mdash; The Chosun Daily (@EnglishChosun) <a href="https://twitter.com/EnglishChosun/status/1771774496996774044?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Could Bithumb Bring Forward its Listing Plans?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Bithumb-related business has <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-exchange-bithumb-reinstates-commission-fees-after-four-months.htm">boomed in recent months</a>. The firm was, until recently, offering commission-free trading in a bid to claw back market share from its biggest rival Upbit.</p>
<p>A retail <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> trading <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kimchi-premium-returns-bitcoin-trades-at-10-price-premium-in-south-korea-against-global-exchanges.htm">renaissance</a> has also seen trading volumes rise in South Korea. The nation is famously crypto-keen. But it has a tiny pool of platforms that have fiat-crypto trading licenses.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188145" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188145" style="width: 1804px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188145" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403.png" alt="A graph showing trading volumes on the Bithumb crypto exchange over the past 12 months." width="1804" height="591" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403.png 1804w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403-300x98.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403-1024x335.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403-768x252.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403-1536x503.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110329/1711278209-bithumb-2403-150x49.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1804px) 100vw, 1804px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188145" class="wp-caption-text">Trading volumes on the Bithumb crypto exchange over the past 12 months. (Source: CoinGecko)</figcaption></figure>
<p>The exchange hopes that the spinoff will “further increase the possibility of IPO launch” by creating an entity that is “centered on the exchange business,” the media outlet noted. It added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“New businesses outside core exchange operations will be pursued with speed through new corporations – without being restricted by the Bithumb IPO bid.”</p></blockquote>
<p>A Bithumb spokesperson said the move would “promote efficiency.” The official added that it would also “boost the growth” of “exchange operations” with “separate ownership” models.</p>
<p>Bithumb has previously said it is eyeing a 2025 KOSPI debut. The new move could potentially see the exchange fast-track its listing.</p>
<p>Regardless of the timing, however, the exchange is likely to win its bid to become the first South Korean trading platform to go public.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1f0-1f1f7.png" alt="🇰🇷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> South Korea’s Crypto-keen K Bank Aims for IPO Amid BTC Boom</p>
<p>K Bank, a South Korean neobank that has seen rapid growth thanks largely to its crypto operations, is set to make an initial public offering (IPO) bid.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CryptoNews?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CryptoNews</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/news?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#news</a><a href="https://t.co/C0HqMWCHSL">https://t.co/C0HqMWCHSL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Cryptonews.com (@cryptonews) <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptonews/status/1767121840143524173?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Upbit’s operator Dunamu is considered “too large” to debut on the KOSPI. Talk of a Coinbase-inspired <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/upbit-operator-may-follow-coinbase-with-nasdaq-ipo-bid-analy-9686.htm">NYSE Dunamu listing</a> went cold during the 2022 bear market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188146" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188146" style="width: 1798px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188146" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403.png" alt="A graph showing trading volumes on the Upbit crypto exchange over the past 12 months." width="1798" height="589" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403.png 1798w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403-300x98.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403-1024x335.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403-768x252.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403-1536x503.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24110556/1711278356-upbit-2403-150x49.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1798px) 100vw, 1798px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188146" class="wp-caption-text">Trading volumes on the Upbit crypto exchange over the past 12 months. (Source: CoinGecko)</figcaption></figure>
<p>However, another Upbit-related firm is also looking to launch its own IPO bid, namely the neobank K Bank.</p>
<p>K Bank provides fiat on/off ramp-style banking services to Upbit customers. The <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-banks-earned-usd-312m-crypto-transaction-fees-last-year.htm">partnership has seen K the Bank user base grow exponentially over the past few years</a>, and could also see the bank launch on the KOSPI in the near future.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bithumb-ipo-plans-accelerate-as-south-korean-crypto-exchange-eyes-public-listing.htm">Bithumb IPO Plans ‘Accelerate’ as South Korean Crypto Exchange Eyes Public Listing</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24105057/1711277457-1711268797055_processed.jpg" length="146625" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 Platform Friend.tech Transforms Ownership, Shares Stake with Users</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-platform-friend-tech-transforms-ownership-shares-stake-with-users.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 15:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech, a social platform leveraging Web3 technology, has proposed a new ownership model by </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">offering its shares to its</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> users. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-platform-friend-tech-transforms-ownership-shares-stake-with-users.htm">Web3 Platform Friend.tech Transforms Ownership, Shares Stake with Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech, a social platform leveraging Web3 technology, has proposed a new ownership model by </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/65ff51ecd6931a6575152ed4/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">offering its shares to its</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> users. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The move is intended to empower platform users, who were previously mere participants, to become investors with a vested interest in the company&#8217;s prosperity. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This shift reflects a broader transformation in investment dynamics towards democratization within the digital realm.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech Users Become Investors</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech users will now transition from being solely content creators or consumers to becoming actual investors in the platform. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The move strengthens the bond between users and the company, fostering a stronger sense of community.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This initiative was made possible through an agreement with previous shareholders, including Paradigm, who have consented to transfer the rights of selling tokens directly to the platform&#8217;s users.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">By enabling this transfer, Friend.tech takes a significant step towards a user-centric model, where users not only shape the platform&#8217;s future but also share in its success.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The shift by Friend.tech opens up new avenues for user engagement and investment within the crypto industry. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">By providing users with ownership stakes and control over tokens, the company advocates for a more inclusive and equitable approach to technology entrepreneurship and governance. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The move challenges the status quo of venture capital financing and signals a shift towards broader user participation and investment. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Users are now empowered to directly impact the platform&#8217;s trajectory, fostering a cooperative culture.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is also important to note that Paradigm played a key role in the move. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Known for investing in innovative technology ventures, the crypto VC agreed to distribute shares among users, signaling a rise in more decentralized and user-focused business models.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech’s Popularity Drops After Splashy Debut</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech, launched on August 10, 2023, has become one of the top decentralized applications (dApps) on the Base layer, attracting over 200,000 users and facilitating a trading volume exceeding $230 million.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The platform uniquely converts user influence into tradable tokens known as “keys,” allowing users to gain access to a creator’s attention or influence.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The model has attracted not only cryptocurrency influencers but also NBA players and esports personalities, broadening its appeal beyond the crypto space.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One significant factor contributing to Friend.tech’s popularity was the hype surrounding the Base network, a Layer 2 solution associated with Coinbase.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The involvement of Paradigm, an investment firm connected to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/reviews/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, further increased confidence in Friend.tech’s potential.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, the platform has also faced privacy concerns, particularly regarding the potential for user doxxing due to the link between Twitter profiles and Ethereum addresses.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Friend.tech has addressed these concerns by clarifying that the information deemed leaked was actually from their public API, showcasing the platform’s open nature while also highlighting the importance of user caution in protecting personal information.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nevertheless, Friend.tech has seen its popularity drop as of late.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dune.com/tk-research/friendtech" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dune analytics dashboard</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the project raked in more than $1 million in revenue at its peak last year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, its revenue has recently fallen to under $15,000 over the past couple of months.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-platform-friend-tech-transforms-ownership-shares-stake-with-users.htm">Web3 Platform Friend.tech Transforms Ownership, Shares Stake with Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24151329/1711293209-1711293194387_processed.jpg" length="66583" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Meme Coin Pundu Raises $37m While Dogecoin20 Powers Past $7.6m</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-meme-coin-pundu-raises-37m-while-dogecoin20-powers-past-7-6m.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arslan Butt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 11:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Solana meme coin $PUNDU has closed out its presale with a whopping $37 million raise, but Dogecoin20 is still open, and contributors are pushing its presale towards a $10 million hard cap sellout.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-meme-coin-pundu-raises-37m-while-dogecoin20-powers-past-7-6m.htm">Solana Meme Coin Pundu Raises $37m While Dogecoin20 Powers Past $7.6m</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-188150" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge.jpg" alt="" width="1431" height="823" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge.jpg 1431w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge-300x173.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge-1024x589.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge-768x442.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge-150x86.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1431px) 100vw, 1431px" /></p>
<p><i><span>Sunday, March 24th, 2024</span></i><span> –  Solana meme coin $PUNDU has closed out its presale with a whopping $37 million raise, but Dogecoin20 is still open, and contributors are pushing its presale towards a $10 million hard cap sellout.</span></p>
<p><span>At the time of writing </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><span>Dogecoin20</span></a><span> ($DOGE20) – an upgraded better version of Dogecoin – has amassed more than $7.6 million from investors in barely a week as meme coin fever continues. </span></p>
<p><span>Luckily for those arriving late at the party or may have missed $PUNDU, the creators of $DOGE20 have extended the presale. </span></p>
<p><span>Nevertheless, given the hype and FOMO developing around the token, the initial coin offering is highly likely to sell out early this week given its past fundraising performance, so buyers need to move fast.</span></p>
<p><span>Dogecoin20 is bringing $DOGE to the Ethereum blockchain and dispensing with the inflationary supply that could hold it back in the future and the computationally expensive mining system the coin still uses. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE20</a> = The new <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Memecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Memecoin</a> way forward! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f415.png" alt="🐕" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Altcoins</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cryptomemes?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Cryptomemes</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE</a> <a href="https://t.co/YEzOm9lQGK">pic.twitter.com/YEzOm9lQGK</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dogecoin20 (@DOGE_COIN20) <a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20/status/1771824307766808781?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>Ethereum is still the No.1 blockchain for decentralized applications and its recent Dencun software revamp has been a roaring success that is already reducing the transaction fees from Layer 2s like Polygon and Optimism. </span></p>
<p><span>All of this makes Dogecoin20 token even more attractive because it is built on a future-proof architecture that is constantly improving.</span></p>
<h2><span>Dogecoin price is up 7% today as its march higher continues… and Dogecoin20 is coming up fast in its slipstream</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Meanwhile, the world’s best-known and most valuable meme coin, Dogecoin, sees its price maintain an upward trajectory despite consolidation in the crowded bitcoin trade.</span></p>
<p><span>$DOGE is 7% higher at the beginning of the European session on Sunday, priced at $0.1733.</span></p>
<p><span>Dogecoin20 is currently $0.000208 priced at $0.000164 in what is now the 14th stage of the presale price ladder. Such has been the demand for the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><span>$DOGE20</span></a><span> token that the presale has been extended, with the hard cap target moved out to $10 million so that the voracious appetite of legions of buyers can be satisfied.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Dogecoin20</a> embodies the lively spirit of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Memecoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Memecoins</a>, captivating the imagination of the crypto world. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1fa90.png" alt="🪐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Marrying memes with on-chain staking, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Dogecoin20</a> charts its own distinctive course, attracting a diverse array of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> fans. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f517.png" alt="🔗" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/vizZbyFKKq">pic.twitter.com/vizZbyFKKq</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dogecoin20 (@DOGE_COIN20) <a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20/status/1771582749129797818?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>But with the Dogecoin20 presale run rate regularly exceeding more than half a million dollars per day, prospective contributors will need to move in a spritely fashion to secure the lowest available prices. </span></p>
<p><span>Stage 14 ends either in two days or when the target of $8,183,163 is reached, whichever comes first. The previous hard cap total was </span><span>$6,315,663</span><span> but has now been updated to $10,068,663. </span></p>
<h2><span>On-chain staking passive income means Dogecoin20 is better than Dogecoin  </span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>You get more woof with </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><span>$DOGE20</span></a><span> – it has the foundation to build a meme coin like nothing that has come before in the Shiba Inu-inspired token world, thanks to its built-in on-chain staking feature.</span></p>
<p><span>Unlike Dogecoin, this upgraded version deploys Ethereum smart contracts to underpin the mechanics of what is a passive income vehicle, where stakers of $DOGE20 are rewarded with an income stream denominated in $DOGE20. </span></p>
<p><span>You can start staking as soon as you buy in the presale. Estimated rewards are currently 132$ per annum and more than 21 billion $DOGE20 tokens have been staked.</span></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-188153" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112743/1711279662-screenshot_15.jpg" alt="" width="1414" height="602" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112743/1711279662-screenshot_15.jpg 1414w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112743/1711279662-screenshot_15-300x128.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112743/1711279662-screenshot_15-1024x436.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112743/1711279662-screenshot_15-768x327.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112743/1711279662-screenshot_15-150x64.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1414px) 100vw, 1414px" /></p>
<h2><span>$DOGE20 fixes the $DOGE inflation problem and is attracting big Chinese money</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Another aspect to the improvements that Dogecoin20 is bringing is the problem of the infinite supply of Dogecoin. $DOGE20 fixes this emissions problem by introducing a fixed supply of 140,000,000,000.</span></p>
<p><span>Much of the new money flowing into crypto is coming from China and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><span>Dogecoin20</span></a><span> with its ‘best Doge upgrade’ appeal is attracting substantial funding from that quarter, along with Pundu and another coin called $PUMP. </span></p>
<p><span>In what could be among the biggest presales ever, $PUMP, which is a BNB Smart Chain coin with a massive Chinese following, has raised $280 million.  </span></p>
<p><span>Whichever chain meme coins are launching on, then, there is a more than ample supply of willing buyers from China and elsewhere – providing a coin can demonstrate it has the potential to hit the mark in the virality stakes, as Dogecoin20 does.</span></p>
<h2><span>Top finance news sites and YouTube crypto are excited about $DOGE20</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<iframe loading="lazy" title="The Presale Token Is Better Than Dogecoin!!! Dogecoin20 Fixes $Doge FOREVER!!!" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eT9AkEpzu-w?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><span data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;The Presale Token Is Better Than Dogecoin!!! Dogecoin20 Fixes $Doge FOREVER!!!&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/eT9AkEpzu-w?si=7dJVb9zbS3nGunv3&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}"></span><span>Dogecoin20 media coverage spans top crypto and finance sites, from </span><a href="https://m.economictimes.com/wealth/invest/dogecoin20-after-raising-5-5m-in-one-week-just-1m-remains-for-doge20-presalewhy-are-traders-buying-big-bags/articleshow/108714984.cms"><span>The Economic Times</span></a><span>,  </span><a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/dogecoin20-meme-coin-launches-ico-and-raises-200k-within-hours-1033169308"><span>Business Insider</span></a><span>, </span><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/24/03/37770721/dogecoin20-meme-coin-launches-ico-and-raises-200k-within-hours"><span>Benzinga</span></a><span> and the </span><a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/newly-launched-fast-growing-dogecoin20-doge20-presale-raises-2-million-in-four-days-why-are-traders-backing-it/articleshow/108588572.cms"><span>Times of India</span></a><span> to the likes of </span><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/market-releases/new-crypto-presale-dogecoin20-launches-on-ethereum-with-staking-rewards"><span>Cointelegraph</span></a><span> and </span><a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dogecoin-and-shiba-inu-pumping-again-as-dogecoin20-ico-nears-2m/"><span>Bitcoin.com</span></a><span>.  </span></p>
<p><span>Elsewhere, Youtuber Matthew Perry has been letting his 217k subscribers know all about Dogecoin20, going as far as to say it is better than $DOGE. </span></p>
<p><span>Without a doubt, Dogecoin is still the king of the meme coins and the one to watch. It is this brand power that makes Dogecoin20’s focus on bettering ‘the Doge’ such an investible opportunity. </span></p>
<p><span>Those who snapped up Dogecoin at its all-time low in May 2015 and held it until today are sitting on gains of 202,045%, according to Coinmarketcap data. With that sort of ROI on the table in the meme coins sector, the sky’s the limit for Dogecoin20. The $DOGE20 price could 100x at launch. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><span>$DOGE20</span></a><span> can be bought with ETH, USDT, BNB or with fiat using a card. Sign up to the Dogecoin20 community on its </span><a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20"><span>X/Twitter</span></a><span> and </span><a href="https://t.me/DOGE_COIN20"><span>Telegram</span></a><span> channels.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><strong>Buy DOGE20 Here</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-meme-coin-pundu-raises-37m-while-dogecoin20-powers-past-7-6m.htm">Solana Meme Coin Pundu Raises $37m While Dogecoin20 Powers Past $7.6m</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24112542/1711279542-doge.jpg" length="151693" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PUMP Chinese Meme Coin Raises 280m in Crypto Presale, Where Will Funds Rotate Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pump-chinese-meme-coin-raises-280m-in-crypto-presale-where-will-funds-rotate-next.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arslan Butt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 10:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PUMP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>BakerySwap's PUMP Chinese Meme Coin presale hits a groundbreaking $280 million, sparking curiosity about the next big move in crypto investments.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pump-chinese-meme-coin-raises-280m-in-crypto-presale-where-will-funds-rotate-next.htm">PUMP Chinese Meme Coin Raises 280m in Crypto Presale, Where Will Funds Rotate Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_188140" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188140" style="width: 1402px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188140" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485.jpg" alt="PUMP" width="1402" height="686" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485.jpg 1402w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-300x147.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-1024x501.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-768x376.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-130x63.jpg 130w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-104x50.jpg 104w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-83x40.jpg 83w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485-150x73.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1402px) 100vw, 1402px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188140" class="wp-caption-text">BakerySwap, a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-decentralized-exchanges/">decentralized exchange</a>, has set a new benchmark in the meme coin sector with its PUMP Chinese Meme Coin presale. Garnering over $280 million, this launch represents a record-breaking venture into the volatile yet tantalizing world of digital assets.</figcaption></figure>
<p>This substantial figure not only surpassed initial expectations but also underscored the crypto community&#8217;s growing appetite for such speculative investments.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A memecoin on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BNB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BNB</a> just raised:</p>
<p>$280 MILLION in a presale!!</p>
<p>How am I just hearing about this now <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f633.png" alt="😳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/iz7MTtttkU">pic.twitter.com/iz7MTtttkU</a></p>
<p>&mdash; borovik.sol (@3orovik) <a href="https://twitter.com/3orovik/status/1771573950281142329?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The presale drew an extensive commitment from BNB Chain&#8217;s prominent cryptocurrency holders, amassing 363,000 BNB, 9 million CAKE, 24 million BAKE, 1.5 trillion 1CAT, and 73 trillion IQ50, reflecting a blend of confidence and speculative interest in PUMP&#8217;s potential market impact.</p>
<h2><strong>PUMP&#8217;s Intriguing Appeal in the Crypto Ecosystem</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Defined by BakerySwap as a meme coin devoid of utility, PUMP embodies the quintessential crypto dream: significant asset appreciation.</p>
<p>Despite its speculative nature and lack of a development team, PUMP&#8217;s launch parallels the early days of <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>, which evolved from a joke to a major cryptocurrency with a $21.3 billion market cap.</p>
<p>This trajectory underscores the speculative and community-driven aspects that often fuel meme coins&#8217; popularity and success.</p>
<h2><strong>Speculative Surge or Ephemeral Hype? The PUMP Dilemma</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
As PUMP navigates the volatile crypto market, its future hinges on the community&#8217;s sentiment and speculative investment trends.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/bakery_swap/status/1771122074976923753">BakerySwap&#8217;s recent tweets</a> confirm the completion of the PUMP presale and the upcoming start of trading, sparking widespread anticipation for its market performance.</p>
<p>The significant presale participation and the sheer volume of committed assets indicate a potent mix of confidence and speculative interest in PUMP&#8217;s journey on the BNB Chain.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Get ready for the big <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PUMP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PUMP</a>! </p>
<p>We will complete token distribution by 10AM (UTC) on March 25th, with trading starting at 11AM (UTC) the same day!<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PUMP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PUMP</a> Contract Address:<br />0x22b4fA9a13A0D303Ad258Ee6D62A6ac60364B0C9</p>
<p>Time to pump it up! Let’s make <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BNBChain?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BNBChain</a> great again! <a href="https://t.co/BIcS8ZGXb9">pic.twitter.com/BIcS8ZGXb9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BakerySwap (@bakery_swap) <a href="https://twitter.com/bakery_swap/status/1771475429205192821?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>PUMP&#8217;s emergence as a Chinese Meme Coin and its record-setting presale reflect the crypto market&#8217;s continued fascination with high-risk, high-reward digital assets. Whether PUMP will ascend to viral fame or fade into obscurity remains to be seen.</p>
<h2>Embracing the Future: Dogecoin20 Unleashed</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" rel="sponsored nofollow">Dogecoin20 ($DOGE20)</a><span> </span>revolutionizes the meme coin domain by integrating Dogecoin&#8217;s charm with Ethereum&#8217;s cutting-edge capabilities. As an ERC-20 token, it offers staking for passive income, aligning with the original Dogecoin ethos while harnessing Ethereum&#8217;s proof-of-stake for eco-friendly, efficient transactions.</p>
<p><strong>Stake and Earn with Dogecoin20: </strong>Dedicated to rewarding its community, Dogecoin20 allocates 15% of its supply to staking rewards within the first two years, providing a generous first-year reward pool. This initiative underscores the Dogecoin principle of &#8220;Do Only Good Everyday,&#8221; through engaging and rewarding participation.</p>
<p><strong>Embrace Eco-Friendly Transactions: </strong>Utilizing Ethereum&#8217;s platform, Dogecoin20 provides a sustainable transaction solution that is both fast and secure, fostering a community-driven ecosystem centered around decentralization and environmental responsibility.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20"><strong>Presale Opportunity: Join Now!</strong></a></p>
<p>The Dogecoin20 presale is rapidly progressing, with $6,740,996.07 already raised towards a $7,247,843 target. At just $0.000207 per DOGE20, seize the opportunity to be part of this innovative meme coin&#8217;s journey before the next price hike.</p>
<h3><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong>Get DOGE20 Here</strong></a></h3>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pump-chinese-meme-coin-raises-280m-in-crypto-presale-where-will-funds-rotate-next.htm">PUMP Chinese Meme Coin Raises 280m in Crypto Presale, Where Will Funds Rotate Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/24104625/1711277184-pump-e1711277499485.jpg" length="229612" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
