<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptonews</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptonews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptonews.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 08:52:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>London Stock Exchange to Roll Out Crypto ETNs on May 28</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/london-stock-exchange-to-roll-out-crypto-etns-on-may-28.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sujha Sundararajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 08:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange-Traded Notes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[London Stock Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=189057</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>London Stock Exchange signalled that it would start accepting applications for physically-backed crypto ETNs from April 8.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/london-stock-exchange-to-roll-out-crypto-etns-on-may-28.htm">London Stock Exchange to Roll Out Crypto ETNs on May 28</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London Stock Exchange (LSE) is set to lunch <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/ethereum/">Ether</a> (ETH) exchange-traded notes (ETNs) from May 28. The announcement follows <a href="https://docs.londonstockexchange.com/sites/default/files/documents/n0224.pdf">FCA’s approval on March 11</a>, to allow LSE list crypto offerings for pro investors.</p>
<p><a href="https://docs.londonstockexchange.com/sites/default/files/documents/n0324.pdf">Announced Monday</a>, LSE signalled that it would start accepting applications for physically-backed crypto ETNs from April 8. Further, the market for crypto ETN will be subject to the approval of the UK regulator – FCA, the notice read.</p>
<p>The exchange has selected May 28 to ensure that issuers get enough time to meet the requirements for consideration.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have decided to launch the market in Crypto ETNs on 28 May 2024 to enable the maximum number of issuers to be present in the market on the first day of trading.”</p></blockquote>
<p>London Stock Exchange noted that applications will not be accepted beyond April 15, including a base prospectus for FCA approval.</p>
<p>Additionally, per LSE’s “<a href="https://docs.londonstockexchange.com/sites/default/files/documents/crypto_etn_admission_factsheet.pdf">Crypto ETN Admission Factsheet</a>,” the exchange would only consider physically-backed BTC and Ether ETNs with its assets held in cold storage. Also, the admission guidance set out in this Factsheet donot apply to crypto ETNs, “given the nature of the product.”</p>
<p>“Issuers and their advisers should therefore liaise with the Exchange at the earliest opportunity to discuss their proposed admission.”</p>
<h2>Industry Criticize FCA For Limiting ETNs to “Professional Investors”</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Despite FCA’s approval to list crypto ETNs, industry players are not happy with its availability to only “professional investors.” The FCA continues its ban on retail investors buying crypto ETPs.</p>
<p>The regulator’s stance is in contrast with several other jurisdictions that have opened the door for such vehicles to individual investors.</p>
<p>Bradley Duke, chief strategist of ETC Group hopes that the retail ban will be lifted soon after. “The LSE is such an important market for us we definitely will list products when possible and preparation is under way,” he told FT.</p>
<p>FCA stressed early this month that it “continued to believe that crypto ETNs and crypto derivatives are <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/news/statements/fca-updates-position-cryptoasset-exchange-traded-notes-professional-investors">ill-suited for retail consumers</a> due to the harm they pose.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/london-stock-exchange-to-roll-out-crypto-etns-on-may-28.htm">London Stock Exchange to Roll Out Crypto ETNs on May 28</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26084358/1711442637-1711442621603_processed.jpg" length="151460" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Asset Managers Continue to Embrace Bitcoin as Key Portfolio Diversification Tool: QCP</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/asset-managers-embrace-bitcoin-as-key-portfolio-diversification-tool.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[QCP Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=189017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recognizing the potential benefits of Bitcoin's role as a portfolio diversifier, asset managers have been actively increasing their Bitcoin allocations.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/asset-managers-embrace-bitcoin-as-key-portfolio-diversification-tool.htm">Asset Managers Continue to Embrace Bitcoin as Key Portfolio Diversification Tool: QCP</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recognizing the potential benefits of <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>&#8216;s role as a portfolio diversifier, asset managers have been actively increasing their Bitcoin allocations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent note, crypto asset trading firm QCP Capital revealed that asset managers continue to add Bitcoin allocations as a &#8220;portfolio diversifier.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, requests for structured products such as Accumulators and FCNs have flooded in, revealing a strong appetite for diversifying investment portfolios with BTC, the Singapore-based crypto firm wrote. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">⁠&#8221;Anecdotally, wealth desks at major banks have been pleasantly shocked at the tremendous demand from clients for BTC spot ETFs, along with requests for structured products like Accumulators and FCNs.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">QCP: Wealth desks at major banks have been pleasantly shocked at the tremendous demand from clients for BTC spot ETFs, along with requests for structured products like Accumulators and FCNs. Asset managers also continue to add BTC allocations as a “portfolio diversifier”.…</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1772435704867586290?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Sets Sight on $100,000 Mark</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin has recently surpassed $70,000 following news that the London Stock Exchange plans to introduce Exchange-Traded Notes (ETNs) for BTC and ETH in May.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, QCP expects the leading cryptocurrency to maintain momentum, breaking all-time highs and potentially reaching the coveted $100,000 mark. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It noted that amidst the unpredictable nature of the market, Bitcoin&#8217;s ability to offer potential returns independent of traditional assets has become an attractive proposition for these managers.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Meanwhile, the potential for Bitcoin to continue its upward trajectory may hinge on broader macroeconomic factors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unless there is a significant shift toward risk aversion in the market, many analysts believe that the next leg higher for BTC is becoming increasingly inevitable.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">With this in mind, the QCP report offers two trade ideas for consideration. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Firstly, the BTC Spot-Forward Basis is currently elevated, with the front-end yield exceeding 20%, presenting an opportunity for strategic positioning in the market. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Secondly, deploying Accumulators, which allow investors to acquire BTC at a discounted price, could prove advantageous ahead of the anticipated interest from traditional finance players.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At the time of writing, the leading cryptocurrency is trading at $70,584, up by 5.12% over the past 24 hours.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The flagship cryptocurrency is up by almost 9% over the past week and by around 37% over the past month. It is just 4.6% away from its all-time high of $73,750 registered on March 14. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin ETNs to Debut on LSE</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">The LSE has announced plans to debut exchange-traded notes (ETNs) for Bitcoin and Ethereum on May 28. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decision follows the exchange&#8217;s previous announcement that it would </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/london-stock-exchange-accepting-crypto-etn-apps-positive-step-say-providers.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accept applications for crypto ETNs</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> during the second quarter of this year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://docs.londonstockexchange.com/sites/default/files/documents/n0324.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">notice released by the LSE</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, companies interested in listing their Bitcoin and Ethereum ETNs on the new market can begin submitting their applications starting from April 8, marking a significant step forward for the mainstream adoption of digital assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While both ETFs (exchange-traded funds) and ETNs offer exposure to a collection of assets, they differ in structure. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ETFs represent partial ownership of the underlying assets, similar to a basket of stocks. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, ETNs function more like unsecured debt notes issued by a bank. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">When investors purchase an ETN, they effectively lend money to the bank in exchange for a note that guarantees returns based on the performance of a specific index or assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that the upcoming Bitcoin and Ethereum ETNs on the LSE will be subject to Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) regulations, limiting participation to &#8220;professional investors&#8221; only. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This designation encompasses credit institutions and authorized investment firms operating within financial markets, while excluding retail investors from accessing these ETNs.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/asset-managers-embrace-bitcoin-as-key-portfolio-diversification-tool.htm">Asset Managers Continue to Embrace Bitcoin as Key Portfolio Diversification Tool: QCP</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26074627/1711439187-1710417484-analyst-spot-bitcoin-etfs-anticipated-to-attract-220-billion-in-three-years.jpg" length="88757" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Maintains $70,500 as GBTC Net Outflows Exceed $14.1 Billion</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-maintains-70k-as-gbtc-net-outflow-exceeds-14-1-billion.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The price of Bitcoin has maintained a level around $70,500 despite recent outflows from spot ETFs led by Grayscale's GBTC. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-maintains-70k-as-gbtc-net-outflow-exceeds-14-1-billion.htm">Bitcoin Price Maintains $70,500 as GBTC Net Outflows Exceed $14.1 Billion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The price of <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> has maintained a level around $70,500 despite recent outflows from spot ETFs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At the time of writing, the leading cryptocurrency is trading at $70,584, up by 5.12% over the past 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The flagship cryptocurrency is up by almost 9% over the past week and by around 37% over the past month. It is just 4.6% away from its all-time high of $73,750 registered on March 14. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Maintains Momentum Despite GBTC Outflows</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin&#8217;s current price stability around $70,500 comes amidst the backdrop of significant outflows from the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://farside.co.uk/?p=997" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">data from Farside</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, GBTC has seen more than $14.1 billion in outflows since the fund was converted from a trust to an ETF.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Furthermore, the US spot bitcoin ETFs experienced a continuous streak of net outflows for five consecutive days. The outlflow streak ended on Monday with spot bitcoin ETFs reporting a net inflow of $15.4 million. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to data from BitMEX Research, these funds witnessed a total of $888 million in investor withdrawals over the course of the last week.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The largest outflows occurred on March 19 and March 20, with $326 million and $262 million leaving the funds, respectively. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, the pace of net outflows gradually slowed down later in the week, with $94 million withdrawn on Thursday and $52 million on Friday.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Notably, BlackRock&#8217;s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) reported its lowest single-day flow total on Friday, with a meager $19 million. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Alongside the Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin ETF, both IBIT and Fidelity&#8217;s offering managed to attract net inflows during each of their first 50 days of trading, an accomplishment that has not been seen before in the realm of new ETFs.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This recent outflow streak represents the first time the sector has witnessed five consecutive days of net outflows. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It follows a record-breaking week during which the ETFs experienced an influx of $2.5 billion in net inflows, highlighting the volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Grayscale Outflows Might be Nearing End</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Analysts believe that the trend of outflows from Grayscale’s fund may soon come to an end. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Senior Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas speculated that the majority of the outflows are a result of bankruptcies in the crypto industry and that the worst may be close to being over. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Balchunas suggested that any outflows from Gemini or Genesis, two prominent players in the industry, are likely being used to buy Bitcoin, thereby supporting the market.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Takeaway: the worst is prob close to being over. Once it is, only retail will be left and flows should look more like the Feb trickle,” Balchunas wrote on X. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The more I think about it the more likely the uptick in flows is related to the bankruptcies bc of the size and consistency. The flows in Feb showed what retail outflows look like, smaller and random pattern. Also any Gemini/Genisis outflows likely buying btc w cash hence market…</p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1770968531632357789?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Likewise, independent researcher ErgoBTC noted that approximately $1.1 billion worth of recent GBTC outflows seem to be associated with bankrupt crypto lender Genesis. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Resulting activity volumes and timings of funds out of GBTC and into Genesis match pretty well,” Ergo said. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Simply there just aren’t that many 2k BTC txs per day so likely the GBTC outflows and Genesis inflows are related.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-maintains-70k-as-gbtc-net-outflow-exceeds-14-1-billion.htm">Bitcoin Price Maintains $70,500 as GBTC Net Outflows Exceed $14.1 Billion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26064659/1711435618-1711107786-1711107233547_processed.jpg" length="110094" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Treasury Targets Russian Blockchain Companies for Sanctions Evasion</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-russia-blockchain-firms-sanctions-evasion.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shalini Nagarajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OFAC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) on Monday sanctioned 13 entities and two individuals. They are accused of developing crypto-related services that could facilitate sanctions evasion on behalf of Russian nationals.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-russia-blockchain-firms-sanctions-evasion.htm">US Treasury Targets Russian Blockchain Companies for Sanctions Evasion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Treasury&#8217;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) on Monday <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy2204"><span>sanctioned 13 entities</span> and two individuals</a>. They are accused of developing crypto-related services that could facilitate sanctions evasion on behalf of Russian nationals.</p>
<p>OFAC&#8217;s designations aim to curb Russia&#8217;s use of the global financial system in its conflict with Ukraine. Brian Nelson, Under Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence, said in a statement that:</p>
<p>“Russia is increasingly turning to alternative payment mechanisms to circumvent US sanctions and continue to fund its war against Ukraine.&#8221; The Treasury “will continue to expose and disrupt the companies that seek to help sanctioned Russian financial institutions reconnect to the global financial system,” he added.</p>
<p>OFAC&#8217;s rules essentially forbid US individuals from transacting with designated entities within the US. Financial institutions and others are required to adhere to these sanctions to avoid serious repercussions. Engaging with the sanctioned parties via transactions can lead to severe consequences.</p>
<h2>US Treasury’s Allegations Against Netex24 and Bitpapa</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
B-Crypto, Netex24, Tokentrust Holdings, Bitpapa, and Crypto Explorer are among the newly-designated entities.</p>
<p>According to OFAC, the listed entities developed or operated blockchain services in Russia. It alleges that Netex24 and Bitpapa used crypto to transact with sanctioned banks, crypto exchanges, and darknet markets.</p>
<p>Separately, <a href="https://www.chainalysis.com/blog/ofac-sanctions-russia-blockchain-companies-netex24-bitpapa/"><span>Chainalysis released a blog</span></a> elaborating on the sanctioned entities&#8217; activities. Per the report, Netex24 and Bitpapa allegedly facilitated transactions for several pro-Russian militia and propaganda groups. These include an OFAC-designated militia group called MOO Veche.</p>
<p>Per Chainalysis, the entities operate in regions like Donetsk, Luhansk, or Crimea in Ukraine.</p>
<h2>US Government Escalates Scrutiny on Crypto Activities</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The OFAC&#8217;s latest move follows the US government&#8217;s intense focus on the crypto space in the past two years. It has sanctioned crypto traders who assisted North Korea&#8217;s Lazarus Group in converting millions of dollars worth of crypto into fiat currency.</p>
<p>Additionally, in January, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-announces-new-sanctions-against-hamas-linked-crypto-companies.htm"><span>OFAC imposed a fifth round of sanctions</span></a> on networks associated with Palestinian militant group Hamas. This action was a response to Hamas&#8217; attacks on Israel that occurred in October last year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-russia-blockchain-firms-sanctions-evasion.htm">US Treasury Targets Russian Blockchain Companies for Sanctions Evasion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26054327/1711431806-image-1800x1200-1.jpg" length="414732" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South American Gold Miner Nilam Resources Plans to Buy 24,800 Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-american-gold-miner-plans-to-buy-24800-bitcoin.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hongji Feng]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nilam Resources enters a letter of intent with Xyberdata to acquire MindWave, securing 24,800 Bitcoin and expanding its digital assets holdings to issue a new stock.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-american-gold-miner-plans-to-buy-24800-bitcoin.htm">South American Gold Miner Nilam Resources Plans to Buy 24,800 Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nilam Resources has signed a letter of intent with Xyberdata to buy $1.70 billion worth of bitcoin amid the ongoing crypto <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fomc-interest-rate-decision-signals-all-clear-for-bitcoin-bull-run.htm">market rally</a>.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/03/25/2851986/0/en/Nilam-Resources-Enters-Letters-of-Intent-to-Acquire-24-800-Bitcoin.html">Nilam Resources, Inc.&#8217;s announcement</a> on March 25, the acquisition involves the Mauritius-based special purpose entity MindWave, which holds 24,800 Bitcoin and other digital assets.</p>
<h2>Nilam Resources Acquires 24,800 Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The acquired 24,800 Bitcoin will act as collateral for Nilam Resources to raise capital for high-yield projects. The company also plans to issue a newly authorized Preferred Class of Series C Stock at a rate discounted from current market prices.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Company and team have been working diligently over the last several months to finalize all agreements and due diligence necessary to proceed to a legally binding Letter of Intent (LOI),&#8221; said Nilam Resources CEO Pranjali More.</p>
<p>Amid the current market rally and financial markets&#8217; recognition of Bitcoin, this transaction would position Nilam Resources&#8217; assets at a valuation exceeding one billion USD. The company is stated to reiterate its focus on inclusive, sustainable, and transparent economy.</p>
<p>“Transparency, innovation, and sustainability define us. We prioritize clear communication, embrace cutting-edge ideas, and invest in projects with enduring social and environmental impact,” said More.</p>
<h2>New <span>Preferred Class of Series C Stock</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The acquisition details and terms will be outlined in forthcoming definitive agreements. This arrangement will grant Nilam Resources full ownership of MindWave, transforming it into a subsidiary.</p>
<p>MindWave shareholders are set to exchange their shares for Nilam Resources&#8217; newly authorized Preferred Shares (Class C) as a strategic equity shift.</p>
<p>This new Preferred Stock Class C will offer holders conversion rights for events such as <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-announces-post-bankruptcy-comeback-to-return-to-nasdaq.htm">NASDAQ</a> listings or similar liquidity opportunities, distributed proportionally among shareholders.</p>
<p>Class C shares, designated as &#8220;restricted securities&#8221; under Rule 144 of the Securities Act of 1933, will be subject to certain conditions and limitations post-issuance.</p>
<p>“This Letter of Intent (LOI) allows our team to work in unison with some of the best minds in Fintech. The Xyberdata Ltd.team has a proven track record of strategic partnerships, acquisitions and continued support innovation for the industry,” stated Xyberdata Director Keshwarsingh Nadan.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-american-gold-miner-plans-to-buy-24800-bitcoin.htm">South American Gold Miner Nilam Resources Plans to Buy 24,800 Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26061828/1711433907-bitcoin-5.jpg" length="140014" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prediction Hits $70,550 Amid ETF Speculation &#038; LSE&#8217;s Crypto Move</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-30.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arslan Butt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188939</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Bitcoin's ascent to $70,550 amid ETF buzz and LSE's pioneering ETNs signals a bullish horizon, igniting fervent price predictions and investor interest.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-30.htm">Bitcoin Price Prediction Hits $70,550 Amid ETF Speculation &amp; LSE&#8217;s Crypto Move</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-188966" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction" width="1280" height="720" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2.jpg 1280w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2-150x84.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-dwpwr-1n7m0yu">
<div class="flex flex-col text-sm pb-9">
<div class="w-full text-token-text-primary sm:AIPRM__conversation__response" data-testid="conversation-turn-83">
<div class="px-4 py-2 justify-center text-base md:gap-6 m-auto">
<div class="flex flex-1 text-base mx-auto gap-3 md:px-5 lg:px-1 xl:px-5 md:max-w-3xl lg:max-w-[40rem] xl:max-w-[48rem] group final-completion">
<div class="relative flex w-full flex-col agent-turn">
<div class="flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3">
<div class="flex flex-grow flex-col max-w-full">
<div class="min-h-[20px] text-message flex flex-col items-start gap-3 whitespace-pre-wrap break-words [.text-message+&amp;]:mt-5 overflow-x-auto" data-message-author-role="assistant" data-message-id="4eb27d6b-c536-488a-a4a0-d256bb6e124e">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert dark AIPRM__conversation__response">
<p>During the Asian session, <a href="http://tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/">Bitcoin price</a> has showcased its resilience, ascending over 1% to reach $70,550, reigniting discussions around <a href="https://cryptonews.com/price-predictions/bitcoin-price-prediction/#:~:text=As%20more%20and%20more%20people,by%20the%20end%20of%202025.">Bitcoin price prediction</a>. Amidst a financial landscape punctuated by anticipation for regulatory decisions and the adoption of digital currencies on traditional exchanges, Bitcoin&#8217;s value trajectory becomes a focal point.</p>
<p>This environment, combined with institutional investment signals and strategic market moves, underlines the crypto asset&#8217;s bullish momentum, setting the stage for future valuation explorations.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Grayscale Eyes May Approval for Ether ETFs Amid SEC Speculation</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Grayscale remains hopeful about securing approval for spot Ether (ETH) ETFs in May, despite perceived communication gaps with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). <a href="https://twitter.com/CraigSalm/status/1772360837094691302">Chief Legal Officer Craig Salm is optimistic</a>, drawing parallels from the firm&#8217;s experiences with Bitcoin ETFs.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">3/ All of these issues were figured out and are identical when comparing spot <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> to  <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Ethereum</a> ETFs. The only difference is rather than the ETF holding bitcoin, it holds ether. So in many ways, the SEC already has engaged and issuers simply have less to engage on this time.</p>
<p>&mdash; Craig Salm (@CraigSalm) <a href="https://twitter.com/CraigSalm/status/1772360840643059895?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>Yet, the inclusion of staking in Ether ETFs presents a unique hurdle. While Bloomberg analysts see only a 25% chance of approval due to concerns over SEC engagement, the recent green light for Ether Futures ETFs, regulated as commodity futures, offers a glimmer of hope.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">There’s no reason to sour hopes for a spot <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Ethereum</a> ETF, says <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Grayscale</a>’s <a href="https://twitter.com/CraigSalm?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CraigSalm</a>. <a href="https://t.co/I3QDOODl72">https://t.co/I3QDOODl72</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Cointelegraph (@Cointelegraph) <a href="https://twitter.com/Cointelegraph/status/1772414565407674850?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>Key industry figures align with this positive outlook, awaiting the SEC&#8217;s decisive verdict by May 23, which will significantly influence Ether and Bitcoin&#8217;s market sentiment.</span></p>
<h2>London Stock Exchange to Launch Bitcoin and Ether ETNs, Boosting Crypto Accessibility</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The London Stock Exchange (LSE) is <a href="https://www.londonstockexchange.com/news-article/market-news/n03-24-admission-of-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etns/16394208">set to introduce</a> a market for bitcoin and ether exchange-traded notes (ETNs) on May 28, with applications for trading starting April 8. This move, regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), targets professional investors and follows the FCA&#8217;s March decision to allow such market segments.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Breaking <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />: London Stock Exchange Will Start Market for Bitcoin and Ether ETNs May 28. </p>
<p>The stock exchange will accept applications for trading <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bitcoin</a> and ether crypto exchange traded notes from April 8. <a href="https://t.co/fVXQUEICa0">pic.twitter.com/fVXQUEICa0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; KoinX (@getkoinx) <a href="https://twitter.com/getkoinx/status/1772466613461070110?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>This initiative aligns with the UK&#8217;s ambition to create a crypto-friendly environment. Launching bitcoin and ether ETNs could enhance institutional cryptocurrency engagement, potentially increasing BTC&#8217;s value by making it more accessible and reputable within traditional finance.</span></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Surges Past $70,000 Amid Historic Low Supply on Coinbase</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Bitcoin&#8217;s price soared past $70,000 on March 25, as a resurgence in BTC accumulation led to the lowest supply on Coinbase in nine years. Coinbase&#8217;s BTC reserves dropped to 344,856 BTC by March 18, a figure not seen since 2015. </span></p>
<p><span>Additionally, accumulation addresses—holding over 10 BTC without selling or exchanging—saw their balances surpass 3.2 million BTC, nearing a historic peak. A significant inflow of 25,300 BTC to these addresses on March 22 suggests institutional investors anticipate further gains.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The decrease in Coinbase&#39;s Bitcoin reserves to 344,856 BTC on March 18 signals a strong trend of investors withdrawing BTC for long-term holding, reminiscent of similar accumulation patterns observed in 2015. <a href="https://t.co/3xxejEfN0f">https://t.co/3xxejEfN0f</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Cointelegraph (@Cointelegraph) <a href="https://twitter.com/Cointelegraph/status/1772356530181918845?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>With Bitcoin exchange reserves hitting a three-year low of 1.92 million BTC on March 25, the stage is set for potential price increases driven by a tightening supply and growing institutional interest, particularly from ETFs.</span></p>
<p><span> This confluence of dwindling Bitcoin availability and heightened institutional buying underscores a robust bullish market outlook, possibly propelling BTC&#8217;s price even higher in the near term.</span></p>
<h2 class="c-message_attachment">Bitcoin Price Prediction</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
On today&#8217;s date, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC/USD)&#8217;s</a> pivot point holds around $69,700, indicating bullish momentum. Critical resistance levels are set at $72,368, $73,887, and $75,692, marking potential hurdles in the upward trajectory.</p>
<p>Conversely, support is found at $68,183, followed by lower thresholds at $66,529 and $63,917, which could stabilize any pullbacks. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) reads at 68, suggesting an approach towards overbought territory but still signaling strength in the current trend.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188940" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188940" style="width: 1726px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188940" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction" width="1726" height="899" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13.png 1726w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13-300x156.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13-1024x533.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13-768x400.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13-1536x800.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26051529/1711430129-image-13-150x78.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1726px) 100vw, 1726px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188940" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price Prediction</figcaption></figure>
<p>The 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) at $66,749 underlines a solid uptrend, reinforced by Bitcoin&#8217;s breakout from a symmetrical triangle pattern that previously capped gains around the $66,500 level.</p>
<p>The current technical setup projects a bullish outlook for Bitcoin, indicating further upside potential above $69,750, while a descent below this benchmark could pivot to a bearish scenario.</p>
<h2><strong>Top 15 Cryptocurrencies to Watch in 2024</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Stay up-to-date with the world of digital assets by exploring our handpicked collection of the best 15 alternative cryptocurrencies and ICO projects to keep an eye on in 2024. Our list has been curated by professionals from Industry Talk and <i>Cryptonews</i>, ensuring expert advice and critical insights for your cryptocurrency investments.</p>
<p>Take advantage of this opportunity to discover the potential of these digital assets and keep yourself informed.</p>
<div class="raw-html-embed">
<div style="background: #920047;margin-bottom: auto;width: 50%;text-align: center;padding: 8px;border-radius: 5px;background-image: linear-gradient(107deg,#930046,#59008a);color: white;padding-left: 1em;padding-right: 1em;font-size: 16px" data-darkreader-inline-bgcolor="" data-darkreader-inline-bgimage="" data-darkreader-inline-color=""><a style="text-decoration: none;color: white" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noindex noopener" data-darkreader-inline-color="">See the 15 Cryptocurrencies</a></div>
</div>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-30.htm">Bitcoin Price Prediction Hits $70,550 Amid ETF Speculation &amp; LSE&#8217;s Crypto Move</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26062900/1711434540-26-2.jpg" length="202607" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SWIFT to Launch CBDC Platform in 2025-26: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/swift-to-launch-cbdc-platform-in-2025-26-report.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tanzeel Akhtar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SWIFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188945</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>SWIFT, the global messaging network used by banks, service providers, clearinghouses, corporate business houses, brokers, is planning to launch a new platform to connect central bank digital currencies in the next one to two years.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/swift-to-launch-cbdc-platform-in-2025-26-report.htm">SWIFT to Launch CBDC Platform in 2025-26: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SWIFT, the global messaging network used by banks, service providers, clearinghouses, corporate business houses, brokers, is planning to launch a new platform to connect central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) in the next one to two years, according to a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swift-planning-launch-new-central-bank-digital-currency-platform-12-24-months-2024-03-25/">Reuters report</a> citing the firm’s head of innovation, Nick Kerigan.</p>
<p>Central banks around the world are tinkering with their own CBDCs and the race for who will launch a digital currency has a geopolitical component to it.</p>
<p>China has a digital yuan in the works and has been trialing the currency for many years. The Bahamas, Nigeria and Jamaica already have CBDCs. Sweden’s Riksbank recently released its final report on its CBDC, the e-Krona, and the European Central Bank is developing the digital Euro too.</p>
<h2>SWIFT&#8217;s Trials and Roadmap to Launch New Platform</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
&#8220;We are looking at a roadmap to productize (launch as a product) in the next 12-24 months,&#8221; Kerigan told the newswire in an interview. &#8220;It&#8217;s moving out of experimental stage towards something that is becoming a reality,&#8221; added Kerigan.</p>
<p>Kerigan explained in SWIFT&#8217;s latest platform trial it took six months and involved a 38-member group of central banks, commercial banks and settlement platforms, all collaborating on national digital currencies.</p>
<p>The trial was focused on making sure that all the different countries&#8217; CBDCs can all be used together even if built on different underlying technologies and this in turn would reduce payment system fragmentation risks.</p>
<p><span>The timeframe set out by SWIFT could change if CBDC launches around the world are delayed but for now the global payments firm is developing a new platform.</span></p>
<h2 class="mb-10">Bank of International Settlements CBDC Plans</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<p class="mb-10">In January the Bank of International Settlements (BIS) unveiled that its <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bis-unveils-2024-cbdc-plans-project-aurum-enters-new-phase.htm">CBDC project is entering a new phase this year</a>. The BIS&#8217;s ‘Aurum’ project is exploring “the privacy of payments in retail CBDCs.” &#8212; BIS said this is one of the <a href="https://www.bis.org/about/bisih/about.htm">first six projects for 2024</a> being developed under its Innovation Hub work programme.</p>
<p>The BIS is also working on <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/central-banks-of-china-uae-sign-mou-strengthen-digital-currency-cooperation.htm">Project mBridge, </a>a multi-CBDC common platform for wholesale cross-border payments. In September, BIS and central banks of France, Singapore, and Switzerland announced a successful testing of cross-border settlement for wholesale-CBDCs. <a href="https://www.bis.org/about/bisih/topics/cbdc/mariana.htm">Project Mariana,</a> tested and demonstrated the frictionless transfer of CBDCs across the different networks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/swift-to-launch-cbdc-platform-in-2025-26-report.htm">SWIFT to Launch CBDC Platform in 2025-26: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/1706837317-adobestock_627494418.jpeg" length="154741" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: March 25, 2024</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-march-25-2024.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mao Orillana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><em><span>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today.</span></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-march-25-2024.htm">Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: March 25, 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-123207" src="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/1698676212-listings-and-delisting.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" srcset="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/1698676212-listings-and-delisting.jpg 1280w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/1698676212-listings-and-delisting-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/1698676212-listings-and-delisting-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/1698676212-listings-and-delisting-768x432.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em><span>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today.</span></em></p>
<p><em><span>Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? </span></em><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/have-a-story.htm"><em>Let us know here</em></a><em>.</em></span></p>
<p><span>_________________________________________</span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/mexc/en"><strong>MEXC</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772111385301782742">DemonWar (DAT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772125171328950728">DaVinciGraph (DAVINCI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772140648927265277">i don&#8217;t know (IDK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772159720763408704">Sylo (SYLO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772162686375051433">BeFi Labs (BEFI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772188867241689125">Sealwifhat (SI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772189745780539603">AIPandora (AIPANDORA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772194951599956394">Venom (VENOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772205022518116500">Legendary Meme (LME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772231523863024069">Multi AI (MULTIAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772246240685617479">Azure Wallet (AZURE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772249319048941813">Non-Playable Coin (NPC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771434970155721013">Wag the dog (WTD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771448154916823547">BitLex (BL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771460912467054671">ZeroVirtual (ZVI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771476751165628427">MOMO 2.0 (MOMO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771490746974994910">GAMER (GMR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771524737149407609">Scamfari (SCM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771732680796680413">Kermit (KERMIT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771735462673047791">dogewifhat (DIF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771762748675751995">iMe Lab (LIME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771763527725834289">ARBUZ (ARBUZ)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771780687667880363">CreaTiveAISwap (CTAS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771809429119438987">Toadie Meme Coin (TOAD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771827036551610490">Ocher (OCHER)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771839481923932536">Dimitra (DMTR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771870801110732884">Kitchen Haimer (KHAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772086599804686538">SquadSwap (SQUAD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1772097655746797790">NEXUS (NEX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770739521178550476">Arkadiko (DIKO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770756450316345798">smole (SMOLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770763658206822624">Colana (COL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770769225361072224">Andy (ANDY)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770784585493659869">BVM Network (BVM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770802224194568304">Marpto (MRPT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770809116048388395">Chatni (CHATNI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771012604799991963">DeepBrain Chain (DBC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771015529639092721">Atlas Navi (NAVI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771031452005880005">Pandora GPT (PANDORAGPT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771034223065125017">EsCoin (ELG)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771058111815483434">EACC (EACC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771070907261374577">NodeFreedToken (NF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771085416357089520">Tyrel Derpden (TYREL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771103228878311913">Frogonsol (FROGONSOL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771114526521585859">GIB (GIB)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771115741863092271">MILLI (MILLI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771146946956452076">Pikamoon (PIKA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771161789020987427">Sovryn (SOV)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771373162120568897">TrollVerse (TV)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771376883122442374">DRUNK Token (DRUNK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771387178956009835">Circuitry (CIRCRUITY)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771400062045941928">Brainers (BRAINERS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1771420872710263015">Shaunt Gaming (SUT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1769925999599472893">WCD (WCD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1769938427989115127">Aventis AI (AVENTISAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1769954469436182923">Kalichain (KALIS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1769969849785106799">LFG2024 (LFG2024)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1769984216115355721">XLV (XA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770001274240643577">TokHit (TH)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770022482113933661">Quantum PAWS (PAWS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770036676376572081">TAO Inu (TAONU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770045485249855841">TOPAI (TOPAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770059655211073900">Sheertopia (AMBO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770060777581621402">AutoAir AI (AAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770074910507122943">K9 Finance DAO (KNINE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770085045925204315">Polyhedra Network (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770091309463974105">UWON (UWON)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770307308926705876">MEGE (TREMP1)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770324290883195016">Ecoterra (ECOTERRA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770333103162069218">Variation Pepe (VT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770360339894575144">DooDoo (DOODOO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770386195367051723">GRE Labs (GRE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770396336875295080">Super Best Friends (SUBF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770404197894389863">Oracle AI (ORACLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770421225246130507">Danol Tremp (TRWP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770435453893964256">SORAI (SORAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770439297797439524">Gorilla In A Coupe (GIAC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770635687139693001">PunkAI (PUNKAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770656247982747930">BABYDOGWIFHAT (BABYWIF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770669113192632531">LICKGOAT (LICK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770677109834518687">Sam Altman Project (SAM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770697863678373913">Source Code AI (SCAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Official/status/1770728749794832594">MinerGate (MGT)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/binance/en"><strong>Binance</strong></a><br />
<u>Delistings:<br />
</u></span><a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1770330331876409706">DREP (DREP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1770330331876409706">Mobilecoin (MOB)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1770330331876409706">pNetwork (PNT)</a><span><u></u></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/kucoin/en"><strong>KuCoin</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1772162978894557672">Gaimin (GMRX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1771101433087316144">BeFi Labs (BEFI)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/bitrue/en"><strong>Bitrue</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1769923075615949187">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1770679585962885322">Diamond Standard Co. (CARAT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1770747944179773820">Smole (SMOLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1770752214308360236">Grimace (GRIMACE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1771059533005377590">Degen (DEGEN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772204595479273684">Brett (BRETT)</a><br />
<span><span>Delistings:</span><br />
</span><a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Adax (ADAX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Aergo (AERGO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">ArivaSwap (ARVS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Bitcoin (BITCOIN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">BlockWorkz (BLKZ)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Celsius (CEL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Celestial (CELT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">ChorusX (CX1)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Duck DAO (DUCK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Coinerr (ERR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Strategy Engine (FSE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Gifthands (GHD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Greyhound (GREYHOUND)</a><br />
</span><span><a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">HXAcoin (HXA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">JD Coin (JD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Open Exchange (OX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Lyra (LYRA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Milk Token (MILK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Mone Coin (MONE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">MotionWreck (MWG)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Envelop (NIFTSY)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">0xDAO (OXD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">PepeCoin (PEPECOIN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Pepe 2.0 (PEPE2)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Shiba Predator (QOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Sea Token (SEA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Strong Inu (SINU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">SmartLOX (SMARTLOX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">SmartNFT (SMARTNFT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">TERA (TERA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Tornado Cash (TORN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">ZKBase (ZKS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">ShapeShift (FOX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">Metagalaxy (MEGALAND)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">PLC Ultima (PLCU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitrueOfficial/status/1772218460065661271">PLC Ultima Classic (PLCUC)</a><br />
</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="http://cryptonews.com/ext/okx/en"><strong>OKX</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:<br />
</u><a href="https://twitter.com/okx/status/1770027707226534280">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/okx/status/1772171835234251171">Venom Network (VENOM)</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/poloniex/en"><strong>Poloniex</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770006581582917800">SNAP (NAP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770024960377147671">Dupe (DUPE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770367384706236904">Kermit (KERMIT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770435693623562675">AVAX Has No Chill (NOCHILL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770727213739934050">Smole (SMOLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770746988906135835">Grimace Coin (GRIMACE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770790427228049889">Briun Armstrung (BRIUN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770791371122647125">Degen (DEGEN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770798553817919853">Normie (NORMIE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770802495721177486">Echelon Prime (PRIME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1770815453809520808">Pnut (PNUT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771021371092738283">Entangle (NGL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771083967770636666">Matr1x Fire (FIRE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771085114505588988">LOOM (LOOMSOL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771117014524014847">Trippy Labs (SHROOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771131855397597327">Community of Meme (COME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771147355120926917">MoonlandMeta (MTK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771186513994567705">Venom (VENOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771417092040057221">PIPI (PIPI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1771433696337510653">Panda Swap (PANDA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1772169625905590767">Catwifhat (CWIF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1772220228426162387">DogWifCat (DWIFC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/1772226607815573629">Basenji (BENJI)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/coinex/en"><strong>CoinEx</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:<br />
</u><a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1770032758490010031">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1770365158528840088">Mumu The Bull (MUMU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1770415413660434603">DUKO (DUKO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1770747091641393555">Smole (SMOLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1771016757198873047">MOCHI on BASE (MOCHI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1771020606856945974">DooDoo (DOODOO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1771107371844248054">Gecko Inu (GEC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1772167645313568858">Fluence DAO (FLT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1772176603000479778">Zero1 Labs (DEAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1772184420272984297">Venom (VENOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1772203279411560572">BeFi Labs (BEFI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/coinexcom/status/1772206850353897675">Realio (RIO)</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/gate-io/en"><strong>Gate.io</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/gate_io/status/1769983477900779587">IQ.wiki (IQ)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/gate_io/status/1770766329231901015">Smole (SMOLE)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/bitmart/en"><strong>BitMart</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1769920637643215130">Billion Dollar Inu (BINU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1769988075772596612">Polyhedra Network (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770001736733983134">KmonCoin (KMON)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770002279489478740">WAGMI (WAGMI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770042692291932230">i dont know (IDK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770104351257677832">Genius Crypto Token (GNUS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770180183795867905">HUND (HUND)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770181279410962722">JC Coin (JCC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770205434755870786">Trump Inu (TRUMPINU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770299936149754207">Kermit (KERMIT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770321710954459441">Meme 2.0 (BOME2)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770341327835648503">RunTuCoin (RTC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770372928158433434">LAVA (LAVA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770378229645553695">Degen (DEGEN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770383672946167940">ApeWifHat (APEWIFHAT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770525516992241683">Camel Tec (CAMELTEC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770736887579263163">ShibaAi Club (SHIBAAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770747485859815599">Loom (LOOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770797800072024442">Smole (SMOLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770824499966906586">Parifi (PRF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770899986881851758">BABA (BABA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1770924955212922968">Miss Flokita (FLOKITA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1771114467394470248">Normie (NORMIE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1771118104007131242">Based Shiba Inu (BSHIB)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1771118330080035281">doginme (DOGINME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1771713279875793320">Lynex (LYNX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772147246282260878">Public Meme Token (PMT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772173171304599608">TrumpJr (TRUMPJR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772184523067023739">Zero1 Token (DEAI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772248273270735342">Shina Inu (SHI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772275327726723136">Lumerin (LMR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772314745405604268">Querio (QRO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772326213144744113">Obi Real Estate (OBICOIN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772329704395080162">catwifbag (CATWIFBAG)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772344937461203072">Sonic Goat (sGOAT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange/status/1772360201737326723">Timpi (NTMPI)</a><br />
</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/lbank/en"><strong>LBank</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1769997382530617502">Lithosphere (LITHO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1770359744123044199">Mumu The Bull (MUMU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1770404115463749810">Dimitra (DMTR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1770414848259895554">Normie (NORMIE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1770422958441508985">Trump Inu (TRUMPINU)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1770692823454515693">Book of Meme 2.0 (BOME2)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1770787149270434174">Grimace (GRIMACE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1771067028524376428">Walk Up Token (WUT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1771084400928735656">300FIT Network (FIT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1771122315163759049">AI Dragon (CHATGPT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1771124533308907655">Ladyf (LADYF)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1772173902547972352">PDT (PDT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/LBank_Exchange/status/1772193477927059772">Big Pump (PUMP)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/p2b/en"><strong>P2B Crypto Exchange</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/p2b_exchange/status/1770193532176777630">Climacoin (CLICO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/p2b_exchange/status/1770435124749808077">Zbyte (DPLAT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/p2b_exchange/status/1770455181894783236">MAGA VP (MVP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/p2b_exchange/status/1771144800693035519">Metamui (MMUI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/p2b_exchange/status/1771190097859244391">London Coin Gold (LDXG)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/p2b_exchange/status/1772262442258604420">HugeWin (WIN)</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><span>AscendEX</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:<br />
</u><a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1770062463557681297">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1770451293624270862">Solidus Ai Tech (AITECH)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1770773659570901074">Loom on Solana (LOOM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1770782416510009833">Stash Inu (STASH)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1771054582501867862">Degen (DEGEN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1771055242320482517">doginme (DOGINME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1771058231798063244">PIPI (PIPI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1772119207280558092">Damex (DAMEX)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/AscendEX_/status/1772143778788212853">Voltage Finance (VOLT)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span><span>  </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/bitfinex/"><strong>Bitfinex</strong></a><br />
<u>Added Trading Pairs:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/bitfinex/status/1770055690440036641">LYM/USDT</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span><span> </span></p>
<p><strong><span>catEx</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/catexofficial/status/1769672145209012572">BFIC Gold (BFICGOLD)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><strong><span>CEX.io</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1772282366888653220">The Render Network (RNDR)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1771220295678112208">ORDI (ORDI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770888106805182647">ether.fi (ETHFI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770827720320008672">Book Of Meme (BOME)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770857912010940557">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1769785845668536687">Worldcoin (WLD)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770118031412519006">Mask Network (MASK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770661737559150829">Qtum (QTUM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770586119937122664">ens.eth (ENS)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770510743374266635">Sui (SUI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cex_io/status/1770797519867380058">eCash (XEC)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/changelly/"><strong>Changelly</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Changelly_team/status/1770416755153989909">Cheelee (CHEEL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Changelly_team/status/1770773483917611034">AltLayer (ALT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Changelly_team/status/1771131959189930485">Ondo Finance (ONDO)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Changelly_team/status/1772227255479226675">Symbiosis (SIS)</a></span><span> </span></p>
<p><span> </span><span> </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/crypto-com/"><strong>Crypto.com</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cryptocom/status/1770093408868085903">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<span>Added Trading Pairs:</span><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cryptocom/status/1772449241203372238">ORAI/CDCETH</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/cryptocom/status/1772449241203372238">ORAI/ETH</a><br />
</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><strong><span>Crypto.com Institutional</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:<br />
</u><a href="https://twitter.com/Cryptocom_Insto/status/1770096921308278799">Polyhedra (ZK)</a><br />
<span>Added Trading Pairs:</span><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Cryptocom_Insto/status/1769946886411046937">MOG/USDT</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Cryptocom_Insto/status/1769946886411046937">MYRO/USDT</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Cryptocom_Insto/status/1771013930522910784">SOL/ETH</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><strong><span>DigiFinex</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:<br />
</u><a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1769958917818245289">ether.fi (ETHFI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1770025478080045558">SNAP (NAP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1770299848912503214">MAGA VP (MVP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1770424469494038819">Entreep Token (ENTT)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1771492957297733964">MAGA Trump (MAGATRUMP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1771839697720856931">Money Gold Coin (MOGC)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/DigiFinex/status/1772185596762665214">Ondo (ONDO)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span><span> </span><span> </span></p>
<p><strong><span>HTX</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/HTX_Global/status/1770448982902509776">Ice Network (ICE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/HTX_Global/status/1770664662331519314">Smole (SMOLE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/HTX_Global/status/1770799379131044199">Normie (NORMIE)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span><span>    </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/nexo/en"><strong>Nexo</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Nexo/status/1770794385187189078">Sei (SEI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/Nexo/status/1770834192470786169">Sui (SUI)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span><span>   </span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/probit/"><strong>ProBit</strong></a><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770359624165949483">Xensei (XSEI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1771064646058774900">Techno (TCN)</a><br />
<span>Delistings</span>:<br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770330327245844875">Moeda (MDA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770330327245844875">Medium Token (MDM)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770330327245844875">MONK (MONK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770330327245844875">MS Token (MST)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770330327245844875">PLANET (PLA)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/ProBit_Exchange/status/1770330327245844875">Quiztok (QTCON)</a><br />
</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><span>VinDax</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/VinDAXOfficial/status/1771111956289654805">DNApet Infinity (PET)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/VinDAXOfficial/status/1772204019076718613">Gemini Coin (GEMINI)</a></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><strong><span>WazirX</span></strong><span><br />
<u>Listings:</u><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/WazirXIndia/status/1770038828683653252">ether.fi (ETHFI)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/WazirXIndia/status/1770398056946585641">Pixels (PIXEL)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/WazirXIndia/status/1770769386011308068">Pyth Network (PYTH)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/WazirXIndia/status/1771063044593828202">Sui (SUI)</a><br />
<span>Delistings:</span><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/WazirXIndia/status/1770797554390691888">pNetwork (PNT)</a><br />
</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><strong>XT</strong><br />
<u>Listings:<br />
</u><a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1770366098271359418">Mixin (XIN)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1770622679785288077">milestoneBased (MILE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1771008277591302396">Lunar Storm (LUST)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1771100391176089886">Cobak Token (CBK)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1771552080345624675">MAGA VP (MVP)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1771778110809383410">Somdej Coin (SOMDEJ)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1772150845280485810">ST Protocol (ST)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1772193336755151003">Jake (JAKE)</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/XTexchange/status/1772206462351343881">Egochain (ESTA)</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-march-25-2024.htm">Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: March 25, 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/1698676212-listings-and-delisting.jpg" length="119088" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Strikes Deal to Offload Two-Thirds of Anthropic Stake for $884M</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-anthropic-deal-884m-majority-stake-mubadala.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shalini Nagarajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX agreed to sell the majority of its shares in AI startup Anthropic for $884m, according to court filings from Friday.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-anthropic-deal-884m-majority-stake-mubadala.htm">FTX Strikes Deal to Offload Two-Thirds of Anthropic Stake for $884M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX agreed to sell the majority of its shares in AI startup Anthropic for $884m, according to <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/ExternalCall-DownloadPDF?id1=MzA4OTEyMQ==&amp;id2=0&amp;cid=0"><span>court filings</span></a> from Friday.</p>
<p>The filing from Maarch 22 outlines the sale to 24 buyers. ATIC Third International Investment Co., an investment firm owned by Abu Dhabi&#8217;s sovereign wealth fund, Mubadala, is acquiring the largest portion.</p>
<p>As per the document, ATIC agreed to acquire 16,664,167 shares of Anthropic from FTX for nearly $500m. The second largest buyer is Jane Street Global Trading, where FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried previously worked.</p>
<p>Additional investors include certain funds managed by Fidelity Management and The Ford Foundation.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">WSJ: FTX has struck $884 million in deals with two dozen buyers, including an Abu Dhabi investor, to sell most of its shares in Anthropic, an artificial-intelligence startup that counts Amazon and Google among its backers. FTX invests $500 million in Anthropic in 2021.…</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1772293971244630420?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>FTX&#8217;s Anthropic Stake Sale Awaits Final Clearance</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Reports indicate that numerous sovereign wealth funds were vying for a share of FTX&#8217;s Anthropic stake. CNBC revealed last week that <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/saudi-investors-barred-from-ftxs-anthropic-stake-sale-over-national-security-concerns.htm"><span>Saudi Arabia was excluded</span></a> due to national security concerns. The kingdom has been investing heavily in tech funds to attract talent from the UAE and diversify its economy away from oil dependency.</p>
<p>The Anthropic stake deal is pending final approval from Judge John Dorsey, who is overseeing FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy proceedings. The deal would represent nearly two-thirds of FTX&#8217;s total shares in Anthropic if approved.</p>
<h2>FTX&#8217;s $500M Investment in Anthropic Doubles in Value Amid AI Surge</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
In 2021, FTX and its sister firm Alameda invested $500m in the AI firm, holding a 7.84% stake. The subsequent surge in the artificial intelligence sector, driven in part by the popularity of ChatGPT, led to a doubling in the value of these shares.</p>
<p>In February, a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-cleared-to-sell-its-stake-in-ai-startup-anthropic-report.htm"><span>New York bankruptcy judge granted permission</span></a> for the estate to sell the shares after FTX reached a compromise in court with a group of customers who had initially opposed the sale.</p>
<p>Anthropic has secured significant funding, totaling around $7b, from major tech players like Amazon, Alphabet, and Salesforce.</p>
<p>For FTX, the Anthropic share sale marks a significant victory. In January, the estate committed to reimbursing customers of the defunct exchange in full. It promised to return 100% of the value of their assets at the time of the exchange&#8217;s collapse.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-anthropic-deal-884m-majority-stake-mubadala.htm">FTX Strikes Deal to Offload Two-Thirds of Anthropic Stake for $884M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/26043555/1711427754-image-1800x1200-1.jpg" length="148150" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Happens if the SEC Brands ETH a Security?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-happens-if-the-sec-brands-eth-a-security.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tanzeel Akhtar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exclusives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The status of Ethereum is in limbo – currently Eth is not considered a security by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) -- but this could all change very quickly.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/what-happens-if-the-sec-brands-eth-a-security.htm">What Happens if the SEC Brands ETH a Security?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The status of Ethereum is in limbo – currently ETH is not considered a security by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) &#8212; but this <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-reportedly-probing-key-crypto-companies-in-push-to-make-eth-a-security-fortune.htm">could all change very quickly</a>.</p>
<p>Ethereum is viewed as a decentralized cryptocurrency, rather than a security. However, regulatory agencies like the SEC continue to monitor the cryptocurrency space and may provide further guidance and sudden change or new rulings in the future. It&#8217;s essential to stay updated on regulatory developments.</p>
<p>It has been <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-reportedly-probing-key-crypto-companies-in-push-to-make-eth-a-security-fortune.htm">widely reported</a> that a number of U.S. based companies have received subpoenas attempting to label ETH as a security.</p>
<h2>Highly Unlikely SEC Will Classify ETH as a Security</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Kenzi Wang, the co-founder and general partner at Symbolic Capital, told Cryptonews, it is highly unlikely the SEC will classify Ethereum as a security. Wang explains, the SEC now classifying ETH as a security would not only undo years of precedent, but also be directly contradictory to their partner regulatory body the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).</span></p>
<p><span>“While the SEC continues to levy vague statements about the potential security status of ETH, the CFTC has clearly stated that they view ETH as a commodity &#8212; most clearly in 2022 filings around the FTX/Alameda investigation,” said Wang. </span></p>
<h2><span>SEC Approved ETH Futures ETFs in 2023  </span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The SEC itself approved ETH futures trading on regulated exchanges more recently in late 2023. During this approval process, the SEC took no action to change the commodity classification of ETH by the CFTC, explains Wang. </span></p>
<p><span>&#8220;Misalignment between these two regulators [SEC and CFTC] is not only harmful to the public, but also a major reason why we don&#8217;t see the SEC moving forward with security classification of ETH,&#8221; argues Wang.</span></p>
<h2>What Would Happen to ETH ETF Applications?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Several applications have been submitted for a Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the SEC and the decision for approving or denying the products has been pushed back which is in line with analyst expectations.</p>
<p>The SEC now has until May 23 to approve or reject VanEck’s ETF application for an Ethereum ETF tracking the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>SEC Will &#8220;Kick the Can Down the Road&#8221;</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>HANetf founder and co-CEO Hector McNeil told Cryptonews, the SEC will use the review of ETH as a security to delay its decision to approve ETH ETFs by “kicking the can down the road.”</span></p>
<p><span>If the SEC moves ahead to reclassify ETH as a security this </span><span>would terminate any SEC applications with ETH ETFs in its current form, explains Laurent Kssis, head of CEC Capital.</span></p>
<p>“You cannot change an asset overnight from commodity to securities as the ETH futures are considered defacto non-security and not within the scope of the CFTC and not within its regulatory framework,&#8221; adds Kssis.</p>
<h2>So What Is a Security Token?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
&#8220;A security is a representation of a slice of ownership of or rights to an asset or a company. Transferring ownership of an asset to a blockchain and assigning it a token is called tokenisation,&#8221; explains Kssis.</p>
<p>Combining the two ideas creates a security token, a digital representation of ownership of or rights to an asset that has been tokenised and stored on a blockchain.  An investment asset, a security token is a digital asset that represents ownership or other rights. It transfers value from an asset or bundle of assets to whoever holds the private keys to the token.</p>
<p>&#8220;In plain language, security tokens are the digital form of traditional investments like stocks and bonds. Tokens are viewed as securities by regulators when they meet the criteria set by the <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/howey-test.asp">Howey test;</a> that is, there is an investment of money, a common enterprise, and a reasonable expectation of profit through the effort of others,&#8221; adds Kssis.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s native token, ETH, was developed to be used to pay transaction fees within the Ethereum network therefore ETH is a cryptocurrency. However, because it is being traded on exchanges and held for its increasing value, investors treat it as a security token. These tokens, like stocks, must be registered with the SEC.</p>
<p>If the SEC does re-classify ETH as a security this will trigger de-listing.</p>
<p>Oliver Gale, co-founder and CEO of Panther, explains: &#8220;ETH is not a security &#8211; the ICO was a sale of securities,&#8221; adding &#8220;long term, decentralisation and global competition wins.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/what-happens-if-the-sec-brands-eth-a-security.htm">What Happens if the SEC Brands ETH a Security?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122024/1711369223-1711369202077_processed.jpg" length="134562" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Crypto Industry Sends Government Draft Mining Bill</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-industry-sends-government-draft-mining-bill.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Alper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188610</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Russian crypto industry chiefs have teamed up with business leaders to create a draft bill that could legalize the nation’s booming mining sector.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-industry-sends-government-draft-mining-bill.htm">Russian Crypto Industry Sends Government Draft Mining Bill</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Russian crypto industry chiefs have teamed up with business leaders to create a draft bill that could legalize the nation’s <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-miners-fume-at-moscows-plans-to-raise-their-electricity-tariffs.htm">booming mining sector</a>.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.comnews.ru/content/232225/2024-03-25/2024-w13/1008/mayning-rossii-ischet-put-oficialnoe-pole" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ComNews</a>, Alexander Brazhnikov, the Executive Director of the Russian Association of Cryptocurrency and Blockchain (RACIB), spoke about the bill at a crypto-related event on March 22.</p>
<h2>Russian Crypto Industry: Time to Legalize Mining</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Brazhnikov said he expected 2024 to “bring many changes for the industry. He explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I have spoken with regulators. They said that we should not wait for their proposals on the formation of a bill on mining in Russia. Instead, they suggested proposing ideas ourselves.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Brazhnikov said that RACIB had done just that. He said the industry body had “sent letters” to ministries proposing “developing the crypto-economy and crypto mining in Russia.”</p>
<p>The industry chief said the body had sent draft regulation proposals to the Ministry of Energy and the Ministry of Economic Development.</p>
<p>And Brazhnikov added that he would also send the draft bill to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russia-fatf-rating-downgraded-due-to-insufficient-crypto-regulation.htm">Rosfinmonitoring</a>, the nation’s anti-money laundering agency.</p>
<p>The RACIB chief said the Ministry of Finance would also be invited to “consider” the proposals.</p>
<p>Industry leaders will be hopeful of a breakthrough after <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-miners-tell-lawmakers-hurry-up-legalize-our-industry.htm">years of fruitless discussions and pleading with Moscow to legalize their business operations</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188622" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188622" style="width: 781px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188622" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144705/1711378024-bitriver2.jpg" alt="BitRiver’s data center in Bratsk." width="781" height="340" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144705/1711378024-bitriver2.jpg 781w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144705/1711378024-bitriver2-300x131.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144705/1711378024-bitriver2-768x334.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144705/1711378024-bitriver2-150x65.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 781px) 100vw, 781px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188622" class="wp-caption-text">BitRiver’s data center in Bratsk. (Source: BitRiver/YouTube)</figcaption></figure>
<p>However, they will be hopeful this latest bid could succeed where others have failed. The RACIB bill has already won the support of State Duma lawmakers Anton Tkachev, Vladimir Plyakin, Grigory Shilkin, and Sardana Avksentyeva.</p>
<p>The bill claims that, per “expert estimates,” Russian citizens “have opened more than 12 million cryptocurrency wallets” as the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-in-russia-more-people-using-tokens-for-payments-claims-academic.htm">nation becomes increasingly crypto-keen</a>.</p>
<h2>Russians Turn to Crypto?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
RACIB says Russians are currently holding a combined total of $108 billion worth of coins in crypto wallets.</p>
<p>It explained that the nation “is among the world’s leaders in terms of mining capacity.”</p>
<p>By contrast, the bill’s authors noted, “all transactions” with crypto are “carried out in a ‘gray’ (unregulated) zone.”</p>
<p>This means that people who want to conduct legitimate business operations with crypto risk criminal prosecution.</p>
<p>Miners have already tried – and failed – to win Moscow over to their cause. A bill reached the floor of the Duma in 2022. However, this bill was abandoned after its first reading.</p>
<p>Undeterred, RACIB has resolved to try again. On November 20, 2023, the body created a working group to work on crypto mining policy.</p>
<p>The group’s members included representatives from government agencies, as well as energy industry insiders.</p>
<p>Senior members of the Russian mining community also joined the working group.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188620" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188620" style="width: 790px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188620" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144537/1711377936-bitriver1.jpg" alt="A BitRiver crypto mining facility." width="790" height="511" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144537/1711377936-bitriver1.jpg 790w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144537/1711377936-bitriver1-300x194.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144537/1711377936-bitriver1-768x497.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25144537/1711377936-bitriver1-150x97.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 790px) 100vw, 790px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188620" class="wp-caption-text">A BitRiver crypto mining facility. (Source: BitRiver/YouTube)</figcaption></figure>
<p>The same group drafted a bill that first materialized on March 4, 2024. The body first sent this to the Minister of Economic Development of the Russian Federation, Maxim Reshetnikov.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-mining-industry-could-be-set-for-4bn-boost.htm">previously reported</a>, miners appear keen to sweeten the deal with Moscow by promising ministers access to their new data centers.</p>
<p>These centers, miners say, could help ministers save $32.4 million on new tech development plans.</p>
<p>Industry chiefs have also claimed they are prepared to invest $4 billion in new multi-purpose data centers.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">About 6,000 older Bitcoin mining machines in the US will soon be idled and sent to a warehouse in Colorado Springs where they’ll be refreshed and resold to buyers overseas looking to profit from mining in lower-cost environs <a href="https://t.co/FxqFHMlV9m">https://t.co/FxqFHMlV9m</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg Crypto (@crypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto/status/1771540781783773632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Companies Ready to Invest?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Mining firms like BitRiver are <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitriver-to-build-new-100mw-crypto-mining-center-in-russia.htm">already building expensive new facilities in the Russian South</a>.</p>
<p>The miners’ primary goal is securing an official classification for mining as a “form of economic activity.”</p>
<p>This would mean that the Russian state could begin taxing crypto miners. But it would also ensure a safe future for companies who are trying to expand their operations in the country.</p>
<p>The Russian crypto industry also wants Moscow to “create an experimental legal sandbox” for the “centralized conversion of digital assets obtained as a result of mining.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia holds a day of mourning following a terrorist attack that killed at least 137 in Moscow <a href="https://t.co/zOfiKacgUO">https://t.co/zOfiKacgUO</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg (@business) <a href="https://twitter.com/business/status/1772140687019888906?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>This would suggest that some lawmakers are still keen on <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-lawmakers-want-to-create-a-state-run-crypto-exchange.htm">creating a “state-run” crypto exchange</a> for miners.</p>
<p>Some want the exchange to serve <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-firms-already-doing-business-crypto-say-theyve-every-right-do-so.htm">Russian firms that use crypto as a payment tool in cross-border trade</a>.</p>
<h2>CBDC a Stumbling Block?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The media outlet quoted the independent financial advisor Elena Savina as stating that there was still a chance the bill could fall on deaf ears.</p>
<p>Moscow, Savina said, is currently fast-tracking <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/major-russian-companies-will-be-forced-to-accept-digital-ruble-payments.htm">its CBDC project</a>, and could frown on efforts to legitimize the crypto sector. She explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is necessary to take into account that the state is currently focusing much of its efforts on the development of operations with the digital ruble.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-crypto-industry-sends-government-draft-mining-bill.htm">Russian Crypto Industry Sends Government Draft Mining Bill</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25143841/1711377521-1711354079717_processed.jpg" length="128174" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ Duped Financier Out of $4.1m</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-fraudsters-duped-financier-out-of-4-1m.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Alper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188567</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Suspected South Korean crypto fraudsters allegedly fooled a wealthy financier into parting with over $4.1 million, the nation’s police force said on March 25.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-fraudsters-duped-financier-out-of-4-1m.htm">South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ Duped Financier Out of $4.1m</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Suspected South Korean crypto fraudsters allegedly fooled a wealthy financier into parting with over $4.1 million, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bithumb-ipo-plans-accelerate-as-south-korean-crypto-exchange-eyes-public-listing.htm">the nation</a>’s police force said on March 25.</p>
<p>Per <a href="https://www.chosun.com/national/regional/yeongnam/2024/03/25/FVRT27FQDVFSXFMXRJF5CDAYLM/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chosun Ilbo</a>, officers in Busan’s Haeundae District arrested a “group of people in their 20s and 30s.”</p>
<p>Police think the group “defrauded a financier in his 60s” by convincing him that he would receive 70% profits on his investment.</p>
<h2>South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ Said Profits Would Materialize ‘in a Month’</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The group of suspects were arrested on charges of aiding and abetting fraud.</p>
<p>Officers said that the group approached the financier in September 2022. Between the same month and December 2022, police said, the group convinced the alleged victim to make six separate payments.</p>
<p>They also told the financier that he could expect to receive his profits in just four weeks, police said.</p>
<h2>Group Used Fake Documents, Police Claim</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The group allegedly told the man that he should capitalize on “a boom time for crypto.” Police said the suspects “forged balance certificate files” to make it look like they were holding around $15 million worth of tokens.</p>
<p>The reality, police said, was that the group “barely had any virtual currency in their trading accounts.”</p>
<p>The group, police claimed, also sought to win the man’s confidence by using an accomplice to pose as a rich real estate agent working in Seoul’s affluent Gangnam District.</p>
<p>The accomplice pretended to sign a $3 million contract with the group, supposedly entrusting them with his money.</p>
<p>This contract also proved to be “forged,” police spokespeople explained.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Do Kwon went from crypto king to fugitive to the subject of an extradition contest between the US and South Korea. Here&#39;s what you need to know. <a href="https://t.co/2ghUBxJLL0">https://t.co/2ghUBxJLL0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg Crypto (@crypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto/status/1772080995715486116?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Fraud Cases Rise as Crypto Booms</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
South Korean crypto fraudsters are becoming increasingly active in the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kimchi-premium-returns-bitcoin-trades-at-10-price-premium-in-south-korea-against-global-exchanges.htm">crypto-keen nation</a>. Earlier this month, a law firm manager was <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-law-firm-chief-jailed-for-stealing-customer-money-to-invest-in-crypto.htm">jailed for stealing customer money to make private crypto investments</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188582" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188582" style="width: 1801px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188582" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503.png" alt="Trading volumes on the Upbit crypto exchange over the past week." width="1801" height="601" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503.png 1801w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-300x100.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-1024x342.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-768x256.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-1536x513.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-150x50.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1801px) 100vw, 1801px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188582" class="wp-caption-text">Trading volumes on the South Korean Upbit crypto exchange over the past week. (Source: CoinGecko)</figcaption></figure>
<p>Also this month, police <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-consultancy-firm-duped-elderly-investors-out-of-7-5m.htm">launched a probe into a crypto consultancy that reputedly preyed on elderly investors</a>.</p>
<p>Officers think the firm fooled people in their late 50s and 60s into paying the firm for bogus “insider crypto tips.”</p>
<p>OTC-related crypto thefts are also on the rise, with officers <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-police-arrest-multinational-gang-of-otc-crypto-thieves.htm">last month arresting a “multinational” gang of suspected thieves</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-fraudsters-duped-financier-out-of-4-1m.htm">South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ Duped Financier Out of $4.1m</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142026/1711376426-1711353992286_processed.jpg" length="145386" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE Introduces CBDC Implementation Strategy &#8211; Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Inside</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-central-bank-cbdc-strategy.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188841</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>The UAE's central bank has announced a comprehensive strategy to implement a central bank digital currency (CBDC) for retail and wholesale use. In partnership with technology providers R3 and G42 Cloud, the UAE envisions that digital dirham will streamline cross-border transactions, enhance financial inclusion, and prepare the nation for a tokenized future.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-central-bank-cbdc-strategy.htm">UAE Introduces CBDC Implementation Strategy &#8211; Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Inside</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United Arab Emirates (UAE) is now readying a central bank digital currency (CBDC) for retail and wholesale use, according to a Central Bank of UAE (CBUAE) announcement on Saturday.</p>
<p>The national bank kicked off its <a href="https://www.centralbank.ae/media/q5nldmrv/cbuae-launches-the-central-bank-digital-currency-strategy-the-digital-dirham-en.pdf">digital dirham implementation strategy</a> during a signing event on March 23 with R3 and G42 Cloud, companies that will serve as the digital currency’s infrastructure and technology providers.</p>
<h2>Implementing A UAE CBDC</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
R3 is a major CBDC tech developer that’s been involved with numerous Bank of International Settlements (BIS) projects. Meanwhile, G42 Cloud is part of the AI holding company G42, which agreed to cooperate with OpenAI on financial services technology in October.</p>
<p>“As part of the UAE&#8217;s digital transformation, CBDC will help address the pain points of domestic and cross-border payments, enhance financial inclusion, and the move towards a cashless society,” read the CBUAE’s weekend statement.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The latest update to our CBDC Tracker shows that all of the founding members of BRICS are in the pilot phase of CBDC exploration. </p>
<p>New members–Saudi Arabia, Iran and the UAE–are also developing wholesale CBDCs.</p>
<p>Check out more of our takeaways: <a href="https://t.co/WORkdfYL09">https://t.co/WORkdfYL09</a> <a href="https://t.co/CBJHSVp5sg">pic.twitter.com/CBJHSVp5sg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Atlantic Council GeoEconomics Center (@ACGeoEcon) <a href="https://twitter.com/ACGeoEcon/status/1772252619798442344?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The first phase of UAE CBDC implementation marks one of nine initiatives in the CBUAE’s Financial Infrastructure Transformation (FIT) Programme. It also features three “pillars” intended for construction over the next 12 to 15 months.</p>
<p>The first is the soft launch of mBridge, which will help the bank facilitate real-time cross-border transactions to settle international trades. Last month, the central bank completed its very first <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-and-china-complete-first-13-6m-cross-border-cbdc-transaction.htm">cross-border transaction</a> using the digital dirham and Chinese digital yuan, valued at $13.6 million, through mBridge.</p>
<p>After that, the bank will begin proof of concept work on CBDC bridges with India, whose <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/reserve-bank-of-india-furthers-cbdc-efforts-report.htm">Reserve Bank</a> is making technological advances surrounding the privacy of its own developing CBDC. Finally, the bank will begin proof of concept work around domestic CBDC use cases, including retail and wholesale payments.</p>
<h2>Why CBUAE Wants A Digital Dirham</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Aside from strengthening the nation’s payment infrastructure, CBUAE claims it will prepare the country for a potential “tokenized” world in the future, where normal people interact with blockchain-based tokens for financial and non-financial purposes.</p>
<p>“CBDC will accelerate our digitalization journey and promote financial inclusion,” said CBUAE Governor H.E. Khaled Mohamed Balama. “We look forward to exploring the opportunities that CBDC will bring to the wider economy and society.”</p>
<p>Last month, Bridge Tower Capital and Deus X launched a $250 million joint venture to build digital asset infrastructure in the UAE. The venture, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bridgetower-capital-and-deus-x-capital-launch-250-million-digital-asset-platform-in-uae.htm">BridgeTower Middle East</a>, promotes institutional crypto adoption across the region.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-central-bank-cbdc-strategy.htm">UAE Introduces CBDC Implementation Strategy &#8211; Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Inside</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/1707379145-uae.jpg" length="197371" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU Launches Probe into Tech Giants Apple, Google, Meta, and Amazon Over Digital Markets Act Violations</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-launches-probe-tech-giants-over-digital-markets-act-violations.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Commission has begun an extensive investigation targeted at Apple, Amazon, Alphabet, and Meta over non-compliance practices under the new Digital Markets Act (DMA). The notice of the inquiry was disclosed by the commission on March 25, and it represents the EU’s first major attempt to curb anti-competitive practices by big tech companies labeled as "gatekeepers" by the commission.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-launches-probe-tech-giants-over-digital-markets-act-violations.htm">EU Launches Probe into Tech Giants Apple, Google, Meta, and Amazon Over Digital Markets Act Violations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The European Commission began an extensive investigation targeted at Apple, Amazon, Alphabet, and Meta over non-compliance practices under the new Digital Markets Act (DMA) on March 25.</p>
<p>The commission inquiry represents the EU’s first major attempt to curb anti-competitive practices by big tech companies labeled as &#8220;gatekeepers&#8221; by the commission.</p>
<h2>EU Targets Apple, Google, Meta Practices</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_24_1689">According to the announcement</a>, the European Commission has opened five separate investigations to scrutinize the business practices of Apple, Google, and Meta, which may violate the DMA rules on fair competition.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today, we&#39;ve opened five non-compliance investigations under the Digital Markets Act.</p>
<p>It concerns:<br />Alphabet’s rules on steering in Google Play <br />Alphabet’s self-preferencing on Google Search<br />Apple’s rules on steering in the App Store <br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f539.png" alt="🔹" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Apple&#39;s choice screen for Safari… <a href="https://t.co/kiZ7sLQa8B">pic.twitter.com/kiZ7sLQa8B</a></p>
<p>&mdash; European Commission (@EU_Commission) <a href="https://twitter.com/EU_Commission/status/1772207590212063397?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The investigation will examine Alphabet (Google&#8217;s parent company) and <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/02/28/eu-antitrust-regulators-target-apples-anti-steering-developer-restrictions-but-drop-in-app-purchases-case/">Apple&#8217;s restrictive “anti-steering” policies</a>. Under these rules, tech firms are forbidden from blocking businesses from providing cheaper purchase alternatives outside their app stores.</p>
<p>“Today, the Commission has opened non-compliance investigations under the Digital Markets Act (DMA) into Alphabet’s rules on steering in Google Play and self-preferencing on Google Search, Apple’s rules on steering in the App Store and the choice screen for Safari and Meta’s ‘pay or consent model,&#8221; the commission explained.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, an investigation has commenced into Apple&#8217;s user preference. This probe would confirm if Apple has fully allowed its users to uninstall its default apps and change default settings for services like web browsers on iOS devices.</p>
<p>Alphabet is also facing non-compliance scrutiny over the claim that it abused dominance in its <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitfinder-next-generation-crypto-search-engine.htm">search engine recommendations</a> for users.</p>
<p>The inquiry is to ensure Google does not only recommend its specialized Google Shopping data to users over other comparable search results from competitors.</p>
<p>The final investigation would see the EU probe Meta’s “pay or consent” model for Facebook and Instagram. The policy requires users to either purchase a subscription for an ad-free experience or consent to data tracking on the free version.</p>
<h2>Rigorous Enforcement of the Digital Markets Act (DMA)</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The DMA was launched in November 2022 and fully took effect on March 7, 2024. It was created to allow fair competition in digital markets, which <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/big-tech-joins-hands-to-foster-the-creation-of-metaverse-standards.htm">big tech companies</a> have long dominated.</p>
<p>EU Commissioner for Competition Margrethe Vestager has disclosed that, despite the market law launch in 2022, tech firms &#8220;seem to be at odds with the DMA&#8217;s intent.&#8221;</p>
<p>She warned that any company found culpable for violating the tech law would incur a potential fine of up to 10% of the company&#8217;s global revenue and 20% for repeated offenses.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Apple seems to be the first company to be fined for its anti-steering provisions by the EU.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/04/apple-hit-with-more-than-1point95-billion-eu-antitrust-fine-over-music-streaming.html">EU fined the iPhone maker $1.95 billion</a> earlier this month for restricting app developers from suggesting cheaper music subscription services to iOS users.</p>
<p>The company was also accused of offering “higher fees” and a less secure and unresponsive user experience. This even came earlier before the US Department of Justice <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-files-lawsuit-against-apple-over-unfair-rules-targeting-crypto-apps.htm">(DOJ) filed a lawsuit against Apple</a> on unfair rules targeting crypto apps.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Alphabet has insisted it&#8217;s operating in conformity with the digital regulations. This follows Alphabet Director of Competition <a href="https://www.pymnts.com/cpi_posts/google-addresses-criticism-over-changes-imposed-by-eu-tech-rules/">Oliver Bethell&#8217;s statement</a> that the tech company has made &#8220;significant changes&#8221; to its operations in Europe.</p>
<p>The EU investigation is expected to be completed within 12 months, which would give an insight into whether the tech giants have opened up the digital market for fair competition or made changes that best suit their operations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-launches-probe-tech-giants-over-digital-markets-act-violations.htm">EU Launches Probe into Tech Giants Apple, Google, Meta, and Amazon Over Digital Markets Act Violations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25191019/1711393819-1711381335585_processed.webp" length="80318" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senator Elizabeth Warren Criticizes Crypto, Claims It Threatens U.S. Security and &#8220;Helps Terrorists</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-criticizes-crypto-says-it-threatens-u-s-security.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julia Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pig butchering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) criticized North Korea’s crypto usage and the rise of crypto “pig butchering” scams at a Thursday hearing of the Senate of Armed Services, claiming that cryptocurrency as a whole poses “a threat to our national security.” Warren has long been openly anti-crypto, going so far as to push her Digital Assets Anti-Money Laundering Act (DAAMLA) once </span>more on Thursday ahead of Congress' two-week recess.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-criticizes-crypto-says-it-threatens-u-s-security.htm">Senator Elizabeth Warren Criticizes Crypto, Claims It Threatens U.S. Security and &#8220;Helps Terrorists</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) criticized North Korea’s crypto usage and the rise of crypto “pig butchering” scams at a Thursday hearing of the Senate of Armed Services, claiming that cryptocurrency as a whole poses “a threat to our national security.”</span></p>
<h2>Senator Elizabeth Warren Blasts Crypto, Calls Out North Korea</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Questioning </span><span>Admiral John C. Aquilino of the United States Indo-Pacific Command, <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/icymi-at-hearing-warren-warns-of-threats-posed-by-north-koreas-crypto-funded-weapons-program-and-pig-butchering-scams-to-national-security">Warren alleged</a> that North Korea could pay for over 56 intercontinental ballistic missiles with the $1.7 billion worth of crypto the country stole in 2022.</span></p>
<p><span>When asked by Warren if the number surprised him, Aquilino confessed it did not. </span></p>
<p><span>North Korea has long been known for its crypto malware groups, with state-sponsored hacking collective the <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy1933">Lazarus Group</a> and crypto mixer Sinbad sanctioned </span><span>by the U.S. Treasury Department’s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) in November 2023 </span><span>for illicit activities.</span></p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="At Hearing, Warren Warns of North Korea’s Crypto-Funded Weapons Program and Pig-Butchering Scams" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tXEWNIIwiTw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><span>“(Crypto) is helping rogue states,” said Warren. “It’s helping terrorists. It&#8217;s helping criminal organizations fund their operations on a scale like we have never seen before.”</span></p>
<p><span>However, blockchain intelligence firm </span><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-money-laundering-dropped-almost-30-in-2023-chainalysis.htm">Chainalysis’ 2024 Crypto Crime Report</a> found that funds sent to crypto mixers from illicit addresses decreased by nearly half a billion dollars last year “likely due to law enforcement and regulatory efforts.”</span></p>
<h2>Senate Hearing Address Pig Butchering Scams And More</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Warren’s criticism of crypto did not stop with North Korea, however. In her testimony Thursday, the senator claimed that </span><span>“more than 40,000 people in the United States lost more than $3.5 billion dollars in pig butchering crypto scams that we know of” in last year alone.</span></p>
<p><span>Common across southeast Asia, “pig butchering” involves perpetrators </span><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/cryptocurrency-scams.htm">exploiting a victim&#8217;s trust</a> in order to increase the amount of funds a given victim will send to them.</span></p>
<p><span>“Now, pig butchering is just one scam,” Warren continued. “There are many more. A recent study found that these criminal gangs have stolen and laundered more than $75 billion dollars in crypto in just the last four years.”</span></p>
<p>As Senator Elizabeth Warren criticizes crypto, not everyone may agree with her, but she paints a vivid picture of the far-reaching consequences of crypto-related crimes.</p>
<h2>Warren Pushes DAAMLA Yet Again</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Additionally, Senator Elizabeth Warren used the hearing to push her bipartisan bill known as the <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/warren-marshall-introduce-bipartisan-legislation-to-crack-down-on-cryptocurrency-money-laundering-financing-of-terrorists-and-rogue-nations">Digital Assets Anti-Money Laundering Act</a> (DAAMLA), which seeks to close loopholes in anti-terrorist funding while subjecting key players in the digital asset industry to tougher regulations.</span></p>
<p><span>“I&#8217;ve got a bipartisan bill, Republicans and Democrats, with 20 senators that would put a stop to it,” she said. “I think it is time to pass this bill.”</span></p>
<p>The senator&#8217;s comments come amidst increased conversations about <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/crypto-regulations/">cryptocurrency regulation</a> in light of last October&#8217;s terrorist attack in Israel that saw Hamas claim the lives of over 1200 Israelis.</p>
<p>As Senator Elizabeth Warren criticizes crypto and pushes for stronger oversight, she faces a formidable challenger in her upcoming senate race: pro-crypto Republican candidate John Deaton.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-criticizes-crypto-says-it-threatens-u-s-security.htm">Senator Elizabeth Warren Criticizes Crypto, Claims It Threatens U.S. Security and &#8220;Helps Terrorists</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25201015/1711397414-julia_63915_the_capitol_building_in_dc_with_cryptocurrencies_ou_fb6c6e8f-a1e4-4d77-9e68-6329d59aca1f-2.jpg" length="150091" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – wTAI, EPICBOTS, ISHI</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dexscreener-wtai-epicbots-ishi.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188801</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While blue-chip cryptos are pumping on Monday, with Bitcoin (BTC) pushing back above $70,000 and Ether (ETH) back in the $2,600s, traders looking for even faster gains continue to turn to the on-chain shitcoin markets in the hunt for top crypto gainers today.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dexscreener-wtai-epicbots-ishi.htm">Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – wTAI, EPICBOTS, ISHI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While blue-chip cryptos are pumping on Monday, with Bitcoin (BTC) pushing back above $70,000 and Ether (ETH) back in the $3,600s, traders looking for even faster gains continue to turn to the on-chain shitcoin markets in the hunt for top crypto gainers today.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and Ether are both up over 7% in the past 24 hours. And while both could go a lot higher, some traders don’t want to wait 6-12 months for 2x gains.</p>
<p>Many would prefer to bet on newly launched shitcoins that can potentially double their money in a few hours, or 10x their money in a day.</p>
<p>On-chain markets refer to the market for digital assets that have been issued directly on top of an existing blockchain.</p>
<p>For example, the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/price-predictions/shiba-inu-price-prediction/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) token</a> is issued on Ethereum as an ERC-20 token.</p>
<p>These tokens can then be traded on <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-decentralized-exchanges/">decentralized exchanges</a> (DEX) and perhaps on centralized exchanges if they get big enough.</p>
<p>They are often referred to as <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-meme-coins.htm">meme coin</a> (or shitcoin) markets and virtually anyone can issue a token at any time.</p>
<p>As a result, these <a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/cryptocurrency-scams.htm">on-chain markets are replete with scams</a> and pump-and-dump schemes.</p>
<p>But <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-shitcoins-buy/">shitcoin markets</a> are the only place to find tokens that can rally in the 50-100x region.</p>
<p>Here are a few of the top crypto gainers today on Ethereum that traders will be monitoring, as per <a href="https://dexscreener.com/">DEXScreener</a>.</p>
<h2>Top Crypto Gainers Today</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<h3><strong>Wrapped Trade AI (wTAI)</strong></h3>
<p>A just-launched shitcoin called Wrapped Trade AI (wTAI), which appears to be attempting to piggyback off of the growin tokenization narrative, has been pumping since its launch on Monday.</p>
<p>The token’s market cap was last around $7.4 million, with $330,000 in liquidity.</p>
<p>wTAI doesn’t appear to be a scam. But it could be a pump-and-dump designed to siphon money from speculators. That’s because it has 20% buy and 20% sell taxes.</p>
<p>Traders need to make sure to do their due diligence always. That includes looking deeply into the legitimacy of a project before investing.</p>
<h3><strong>EPICBOTS ($EPICBOTS)</strong></h3>
<p>EPICBOTS, a supposed AI-infused Telegram bot protocol, is pumping hard on Monday, and is one of the top crypto gainers today. <a href="https://dexscreener.com/ethereum/0xb5d3ed5e7cf8d0f4000cef0ab80e96e066c0f8c8">It was last up 100% in 24 hours</a> with a market cap of $3.4 million.</p>
<p>The token has $350,000 in locked liquidity, reducing rug pull risk.</p>
<p>But that doesn’t mean the token isn’t a scam. DEXScreener’s smart contract audit reveals four aspects of the token’s contract that are concerning.</p>
<p>These include a modifiable tax, a whitelist function, and a 5% buy-and-sell tax.</p>
<h3><strong>Ishi ($ISHI)</strong></h3>
<p>A recently launched Shiba Inu-themed meme coin called Ishi ($ISHI) is making a comeback on Monday.</p>
<p>It rose 30% in 24 hours, and its market cap <a href="https://dexscreener.com/ethereum/0x048d3180ecf61b82f47078f6ebb3298326d70431">recovered to around $2.1 million</a>.</p>
<p>The token has $200,000 in locked liquidity, reducing rug pull risk. But the token has a modifiable tax, a blacklist, and a whitelist.</p>
<p>It could still easily be a scam token. So, potential investors must never risk more than they can afford to lose, and they should do their due diligence.</p>
<h2><strong>Crypto Alternatives to Consider</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Investing in low-cap shitcoins is a very risky strategy.</p>
<p>An innocent-looking project could easily be a scam, and a few big sell orders could easily drive the price 80% lower.</p>
<p>A strategy that is still risky, but arguably has a better risk reward is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">getting involved in crypto presales</a>.</p>
<p>The idea is that investors secure tokens of up-and-coming, high-potential crypto projects/protocols at a discounted early price.</p>
<p>These projects then put those funds to work, paying for protocol development and marketing.</p>
<p>While lots can go wrong when investing in crypto presales—unforeseen circumstances can prevent a project from delivering on its vision—savvy presale investors routinely secure gains of 10x or more.</p>
<p>With hundreds of presale projects vying for investor funds, analysts at Cryptonews have been combing the market.</p>
<p>Here are 14 of the presale projects with the highest potential.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">See the 14 Cryptocurrencies</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dexscreener-wtai-epicbots-ishi.htm">Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – wTAI, EPICBOTS, ISHI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/20231622/1710976582-screenshot-2024-03-20-181516.png" length="73226" type="image/png" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Whales Bet on New Web3 VR Crypto – The Next Major Trend?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-bet-on-new-web3-vr-crypto-the-next-major-trend.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Hakki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5scape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5thscape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investors who want an early lead in Web3&#8217;s game-changing technological landscape are accumulating VR token 5thScape (5SCAPE) in the second stage of a presale that has so far raised $2.4 million. 5thScape is the world’s first virtual and augmented reality cryptocurrency gaming ecosystem, offering a wealth of immersive experiences with hyper-realistic gameplay. The $5SCAPE token that investors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-bet-on-new-web3-vr-crypto-the-next-major-trend.htm">Crypto Whales Bet on New Web3 VR Crypto – The Next Major Trend?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investors who want an early lead in Web3&#8217;s game-changing technological landscape are accumulating VR token 5thScape (5SCAPE) in the second stage of a presale that has so far raised $2.4 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cryptonews.com/ext/5thscape/en" rel="sponsored nofollow">5thScape</a><span> </span>is the world’s first virtual and augmented reality cryptocurrency gaming ecosystem, offering a wealth of immersive experiences with hyper-realistic gameplay.</p>
<p>The $5SCAPE token that investors are snapping up gives holders access to an exclusive selection of VR games, educational resources, and blockbuster movies.</p>
<p>One of the early standout titles is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/5th-scape-5scape-presale-picking-up-as-team-reveals-info-about-upcoming-vr-game.htm">Cage Conquest</a>, expected later this year. It&#8217;s a warts-and-all VR MMA fighting game where players can step in the ring to participate in strategic training sessions and online tournaments to earn crypto rewards.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Official Trailer: MMA Cage Conquest | Step into the Cage and Become a Champion" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SS3vuTOKrmg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>The ICO only began a few weeks ago and it has already taken in millions of dollars and tens of thousands of curious followers across social media, but what exactly is 5thScape?</p>
<h2>5thScape is a Pioneering VR and Web 3 Application</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span>Web 3 is a kind of singularity moment for its believers. That&#8217;s because it promises to unlock the full gamut of what crypto is capable of as web interfaces become more interactive and more transactions come on chain.</p>
<p>In industry that is itself an innovation, cryptocurrency projects that nurture and pioneer the development of blockchain’s utility potential ultimately have the most staying power.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s through the interaction, integration and intersections of blockchain, virtual and augmented realities, and AI that we find the Web 3&#8217;s full potential. A vision of the smart, responsive, decentralized internet that users interface with in three dimensions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5thScape, the cutting-edge crypto project poised to revolutionize augmented and virtual reality, offers investors an opportunity to dive into the future of immersive gaming. </p>
<p>With plans for innovative VR hardware and a diverse range of games, including Cage Conquest and Epic… <a href="https://t.co/FaIicOGq3w">pic.twitter.com/FaIicOGq3w</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 5th Scape (@5th_scape) <a href="https://twitter.com/5th_scape/status/1771437391716180079?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>If adoption is the endgame for every player, then Web 3 is the promised land. Now, we already have a small and developing corner of Web 3: the metaverse.</p>
<p>While a fully virtual and augmented reality metaverse is still a long way away—current popular metaverse titles like Axie Infinity and The Sandbox are closer to conventional video games—5thScape drags the metaverse out of the future and into the present day.</p>
<p>As a tokenized gaming platform, 5thScape is already at the forefront of the metaverse.</p>
<p>Participation is easy, gamers simply buy and hold tokens to get access to the platform, where they will be able to game and stream for free.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the project team took development back to first principles and designed all the software and hardware in-house.</p>
<h2>Unpacking 5thScape&#8217;s (5SCAPE) Upside Potential</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span>5SCAPE has a market capitalization of $15 million and is currently priced at<span> </span><span>$</span><span>0.00215, although this is due to rise 15% to $0.00248 when the third round begins soon.</span></p>
<p><span>The team has allocated eighty percent of the total token supply for the ongoing presale.</span></p>
<p><span>When it ends, 5SCAPE’s fixed listing price will be $0.01, giving the token a possible prelaunch upside potential of over 365%. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Exciting news from 5th Scape! The VR-focused cryptocurrency has raised $1.7 million in its presale phase, and has showcased the potential for innovation in the digital space. </p>
<p>Get ready to explore hyper-realistic experiences and next-gen gaming with 5th Scape&#39;s groundbreaking… <a href="https://t.co/5DrCHwVm77">pic.twitter.com/5DrCHwVm77</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 5th Scape (@5th_scape) <a href="https://twitter.com/5th_scape/status/1770721210449412167?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The 5thScape platform and its native 5SCAPE token are fully audited, with KYC compliance. The team behind it are<span> also </span><a href="https://docs.5thscape.com/team">transparent</a>.</p>
<p>Join the community over on the project’s social channels can stay informed of tasks to claim even more 5SCAPE rewards before the protocol launches.</p>
<p>5thScape has already clocked tens of thousands of followers for a social media presence spread across on<span> </span><a href="https://discord.com/invite/5thscape"><span>Discord</span></a><span>, </span><a href="https://t.me/fifthScape"><span>Telegram</span></a><span>, </span><a href="https://twitter.com/5th_scape"><span>X/Twitter</span></a><span> and </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@5thScape"><span>YouTube</span></a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/5thscape" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong>Interested? Buy 5thScape Here</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-bet-on-new-web3-vr-crypto-the-next-major-trend.htm">Crypto Whales Bet on New Web3 VR Crypto – The Next Major Trend?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25153753/1711381073-1711380808514_processed.jpg" length="57089" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert Kiyosaki Recommends Buying One-Tenth Of A Bitcoin, Backs Michael Saylor</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/robert-kiyosaki-recommends-bitcoin-backs-michael-saylor.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Famed 'Rich Dad Poor Dad' author Robert Kiyosaki doubles down on Bitcoin, plans to buy more ahead of April's halving event. He anticipates a price surge to $100K by September, driven by dollar weakness. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/robert-kiyosaki-recommends-bitcoin-backs-michael-saylor.htm">Robert Kiyosaki Recommends Buying One-Tenth Of A Bitcoin, Backs Michael Saylor</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>Bestselling author of &#8216;Rich Dad Poor Dad,&#8217; Robert Kiyosaki, urged followers on Monday to purchase Bitcoin (BTC) ahead of the April halving event.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1772115533502259692">In a post to Twitter</a>, the author promised to buy 10 more BTC before the start of April due to his conviction around the event, which will cut the rate at which new BTC is produced in half.</p>
<h2>Get Bitcoin While You Can, Says Robert Kiyosaki</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
“If you can’t afford a whole Bitcoin, you may want to consider buying 1/10 of a coin, via the new ETFs or Satoshi’s,” wrote Kiyosaki. “If the Bitcoin process works as designed you may own a whole Bitcoin by the end of this year.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I am buying 10 more Bitcoin before April. Why?  The “Having.” If you can’t afford a whole Bitcoin  you may want to consider buying 1/10 of a coin, via the new ETFs or Satoshi’s.</p>
<p>If the Bitcoin process works as designed you may own a whole Bitcoin by the end of this year. </p>
<p>I…</p>
<p>&mdash; Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1772115533502259692?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Bitcoin’s price surged by over 3.5% to $69,700 on Monday, carrying momentum from its weekend rebound from below $64,000. This followed a massive pullback for the cryptocurrency over the last two weeks as Bitcoin spot ETFs – which have proven remarkably successful since launching in January – suffered <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-lose-326-million-in-largest-daily-outflow-since-launch.htm">unusually large outflows</a> of over $800 million last week.</p>
<p>Kiyosaki said he expects Bitcoin to reach $100,000 by September – not merely because of the ETFs, but because of the weakness of the US dollar. In that spirit, he recommended silver coins and gold as the next best buys for those who are “not into Bitcoin.”</p>
<p>“The ‘smart money’ knows the US is the biggest debtor nation in the world,” he said, citing high consumer and small business debt, domestic bank troubles, and a world “on the brink of war.”</p>
<h2>Stay Away From Cash</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Bitcoin is often compared to precious metals by proponents who view its limited supply of 21 million coins as a defense against the debasement of the US dollar, whose increasing supply devalues the currency against more scarce assets over time.</p>
<p>Kiyosaki echoed the words of MicroStrategy executive chairman <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-is-not-currency-but-still-plans-to-hodl-for-100-years.htm">Michael Saylor</a>, who said in a recent interview that those who save in cash or fiat currency are best labeled as “poor.”</p>
<p>“Please start acquiring gold, silver, Bitcoin, if you already have not started,” said Kiyosaki. “Please don’t be a poor person saving fake money.”</p>
<p>According to blockchain data, there are currently over 4.5 million Bitcoin addresses holding over 0.1 BTC, as Kiyosaki recommends. That said, one investor can store their holdings across multiple Bitcoin addresses, and one address could represent the holdings of thousands or millions of investors (ex. Binance’s Bitcoin address).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/robert-kiyosaki-recommends-bitcoin-backs-michael-saylor.htm">Robert Kiyosaki Recommends Buying One-Tenth Of A Bitcoin, Backs Michael Saylor</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/1708326452-1708326415236_processed.jpg" length="77392" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles as Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Takes Effect</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/philippines-to-block-binance-exchange-amid-regulatory-concerns.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philippines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>The Philippines SEC's Ban on Binance prohibits local access to the exchange's website and applications. This decision stems from Binance's alleged unlicensed operations and offering of investment opportunities to Filipinos.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/philippines-to-block-binance-exchange-amid-regulatory-concerns.htm">Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles as Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Takes Effect</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Philippines Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has revealed its plan to block local access to Binance, effectively implementing the Philippines SEC&#8217;s ban on Binance. This was contained in a notice published by the financial regulator on March 25.</p>
<p>This decision follows the SEC’s accusation of the exchange&#8217;s continuous offering of various investment and trading opportunities to Filipinos without obtaining the necessary license from the commission.</p>
<h2>Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Urges Google &amp; Meta to Restrict Binance-related Adverts</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/pr-2024/sec-proceeds-with-blocking-of-binance/#gsc.tab=0">According to the published media briefing</a>, the Philippines SEC had previously filed a formal request to the National Telecommunication Commission (NTC) on March 12, 2024, to block access to the Binance website, applications, and other web pages used by the exchange.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">JUST IN : The Philippine SEC stated that it will continue to block Binance and block citizens’ access to Binance’s main website and related platforms, saying that Binance is a threat to the security of the Philippines.</p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto News Updates (@CryptoNewsUpd8s) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoNewsUpd8s/status/1772226888674463920?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The commission has now deepened its ban on Binance by requesting Google and Meta to block all marketing campaigns related to the crypto exchange in the Philippines.</p>
<p>As stated by the SEC, all previous campaigns and trade offerings were done illegally as the exchange is yet to secure a license from its agency to solicit investment or create/operate an exchange as required by <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/377527899/REPUBLIC-ACT-NO-8799-THE-SECURITIES-REGULATION-CODE">Republic Act No. 8799</a> or the <a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/2019Legislation_RA-8799-Securities-Regulation-Code-2000.pdf">Securities Regulation Code (SRC)</a>.</p>
<p>The regulatory agency had, however, informed residents that the crypto exchange is not authorized to sell or offer securities in the Philippines while also stating that Binance&#8217;s continuous crypto promotions may have criminal liability.</p>
<p>The notice read,</p>
<blockquote><p>“Those who act as salesmen, brokers, dealers or agents, representatives, promoters, recruiters, influencers, endorsers, and enablers of Binance in selling or convincing people to invest in its platform within the Philippines, even through online means, may be held criminally liable under Section 28 of the SRC.”</p></blockquote>
<p>This ban is expected to be effective within a three-month period – providing ample time for Filipino traders to close their investment positions held on Binance.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the SEC Chair Emilio B. Aquino has reiterated that the regulatory body believes that Filipinos&#8217; continuous access to Binance websites and associated mobile applications &#8220;poses a threat to the security of the funds of investing Filipinos.&#8221;</p>
<p><span>It should be noted this latest move by the Philippines SEC came after <a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023Advisory-against-Binance.pdf">issuing a </a></span><a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023Advisory-against-Binance.pdf"><span>warning notice </span></a><span><a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023Advisory-against-Binance.pdf">to Binance</a> on November 28, 2023. </span></p>
<p>The Philippines SEC&#8217;s ban on Binance serves as a clear warning to other unregulated exchanges operating within the country, underlining the importance of compliance with local securities laws.</p>
<h2>Binance Regulatory Blows Continue</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The Philippines SEC&#8217;s ban on Binance is not an isolated incident, as the exchange has faced increasing regulatory scrutiny worldwide.</p>
<p>In 2023, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) filed charges against Binance for allegedly operating an illegal digital asset derivatives exchange and evading federal laws.</p>
<p>Similarly, the US Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101">charged Binance Holdings LTD and ex-CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ)</a> for allegedly operating unregistered exchanges, broker exchanges, clearing houses, and the unregistered offer and sale of securities.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/binance-and-ceo-plead-guilty-federal-charges-4b-resolution">Binance and CZ pleaded guilty to a range of federal charges</a>, including anti-money laundering violations and unlicensed money transmission, on November 21, 2023. This was after a series of investigations by the SEC, the US Department of Justice (DOJ), and the CFTC.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/changpeng-cz-zhao-steps-down-from-binance-us-board-of-directors.htm">CZ later resigned as the CEO of Binance</a>, which was part of the agreement with the DOJ.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> CEO CZ Steps Down as CEO<br />As Part Of $4 Billion Settlement With US <a href="https://t.co/63nqhU1dPh">pic.twitter.com/63nqhU1dPh</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ahmed CEO (@Ahmedxmtj) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ahmedxmtj/status/1727066068202762664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8837-23">CFTC announced on December 18, 2023</a>, that the US District Court for the Northern District of Illinois ordered CZ to pay $150 million, and the exchange ruled to pay $2.7 billion to conclude enforcement action.</p>
<p>At press time, CZ is free on a $175 million release bond but awaits court sentence in reaction to his role in Binance money laundering charges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/philippines-to-block-binance-exchange-amid-regulatory-concerns.htm">Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles as Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Takes Effect</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25165842/1711385922-1711380765008_processed.webp" length="41810" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Crypto to Buy Today March 25 – Arweave, Internet Computer, Dogwifhat</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-25-arweave-internet-computer-dogwifhat.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Best Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As crypto prices pick up on Monday and Bitcoin (BTC) pushes back to the north of $70,000, investors are hunting feverishly for the best crypto to buy today to secure quick gains.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-25-arweave-internet-computer-dogwifhat.htm">Best Crypto to Buy Today March 25 – Arweave, Internet Computer, Dogwifhat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>As crypto prices pick up on Monday and Bitcoin (BTC) pushes back to the north of $70,000, investors are hunting feverishly for the best crypto to buy today to secure quick gains. </span>For investors taking their first steps into the market, Bitcoin is certainly a candidate for <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-crypto-to-buy/">best crypto to buy today</a>.</p>
<p>BTC is likely to soon retake its all-time highs thanks to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/great-central-bank-policy-reversal-kicks-off-2024-03-22/">optimism surrounding central bank easing</a>. Sell pressure from GBTC may also be easing, meaning spot Bitcoin ETFs could become a tailwind once again.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-halving/">With the halving just around the corner</a>, Bitcoin remains odds on to test $100,000 at some point this year.</p>
<p>That means possible 40% gains from current levels.</p>
<p>But many crypto investors have already built up sizeable exposure to major blue-chip cryptos like Bitcoin.</p>
<p>They may instead be looking to up their risk and gain exposure to assets with 5-10x potential.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/best-altcoins.htm">Here are some altcoins with strong bullish momentum</a> that could be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h2><strong>Best Crypto to Buy Today</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<h3><strong>Arweave (AR)</strong></h3>
<p>Decentralized storage network (DSN) Arweave’s native token AR has pumped a considerable 20% on Monday, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/arweave/">as per CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Last at $43, AR is eyeing a near-term retest of its all-time highs around $48. A retest of all-time highs above $90 is also on the cards for 2024.</p>
<p>Its modest market cap of still under $3 billion suggests plenty of upside room for the crypto. The prospect of 3-4x gains makes AR one of the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h3><strong>Internet Computer (ICP)</strong></h3>
<p>Up nearly 20% in 24 hours, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/internet-computer/">Internet Computer (ICP)</a> is one of the best-performing cryptos on Monday.</p>
<p>Last at $17, ICP is attempting to break convincingly out of its multi-week $10-16 range.</p>
<p>But ICP is still down over 96% down from its record peaks from 2021 around $350.</p>
<p>Its modest market cap of currently under $8 billion suggests there is plenty of room for growth.</p>
<p>ICP may not hit its 2021 highs soon, but 10x gains are certainly in the cards. That means it could easily be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h3><strong>Dogwifhat (WIF)</strong></h3>
<p>Dogwifhat (WIF) is leading the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-meme-coins.htm">meme coin market</a> on Monday, up 18% in the past 24 hours <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/dogwifhat/">as per CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Last at $2.80, WIF is eyeing a retest of its all-time highs above $3.50. WIF’s market cap was last $2.8 billion.</p>
<p>With Dogecoin’s market cap last around $24 billion, WIF could have a lot higher yet to run.</p>
<p>The prospect of 10x gains from here ranks WIF as potentially the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h2><strong>Crypto Alternatives to Consider</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
All of the above coins offer potential investors a great chance to make 10x gains.</p>
<p>But, for those looking for a better probability of near-term gains, an alternative high-risk, high-reward investment strategy to consider is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">getting involved in crypto presales</a>.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Top 3 Pre-Sales You Need to Jump on NOW! &#x1f4b0;" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c2ZI1XD9Pq0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>This is where investors buy the tokens of upstart crypto projects to help fund their development.</p>
<p>These tokens are nearly always sold cheaply, and there is a long history of presales delivering huge exponential gains to early investors.</p>
<p>Many of these projects have fantastic teams behind them and a great vision to deliver a one-of-a-kind crypto application/platform.</p>
<p>The team at Cryptonews.com spends a lot of time combing through presale projects to help out investors.</p>
<p>Here is a list of what the team deems to be the best crypto presales of 2024.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">See the 13 Cryptocurrencies</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-25-arweave-internet-computer-dogwifhat.htm">Best Crypto to Buy Today March 25 – Arweave, Internet Computer, Dogwifhat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1704831868-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__2__720.jpg" length="65337" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
