<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:40:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Fantom: Market Slowdown Chops Off 10% From Gains &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/fantom-market-slowdown-chops-off-10-from-gains-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fantom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sonic Network Upgrade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Leading the downturn today, Fantom (FTM) contributes to the 2% drop in the crypto market after weeks of growth. Related Reading: From $90 To $400 Litecoin: Analysts Bullish On LTC Soaring Trajectory Fantom is one of those altcoins that followed the broader momentum of the market. The latest market data shows that the token is down 10% in the past 24 hours, but is still on the green in the bi-weekly timeframe at 14%. However, Fantom has a trick up its sleeve to curb this brewing bearishness potentially.  Fantom CEO Michael Kong Unveils Sonic Launch  Sonic is the brand-new technology that the Fantom has been developing in the past 2 years. According to their latest blog post, Sonic was able to surpass the network’s 200 transactions per second metric. Although 200 TPS was already impressive compared to Ethereum’s 12 TPS, the network was quickly congested, and user experience deteriorated.  Kong said in the blog post:  “​​Sonic will be used to create a new best-in-class shared sequencer for L1 and L2 chains, capable of processing over 180 million daily transactions with real, sub-second confirmation times, and serve as the foundation to relaunch Fantom as an entirely new community-centric brand.”  This brand-new tech will cover all parts of the Fantom network, from bridging to a stablecoin launch, Sonic has it all.  Sonic Labs will also gain a slice of the pie as the foundation ultimately adds grant programs alongside the network upgrades.  Bitcoin is now trading at $70.396. Chart: TradingView “We will continue to significantly scale and accelerate our Sonic Labs grant program for developers who build unique and valuable applications and public goods in categories including gaming, DeFi, social media, streaming, and now distributed AI,” Kong added.  This will significantly increase the size of Fantom’s user base, boosting investor confidence, and giving more room for developers to innovate.  Furthermore, the advancements brought forth by Sonic Labs in covering all aspects of the Fantom network, from bridging to the launch of a stablecoin, are poised to have a notable impact on Fantom&#8217;s market dynamics. By streamlining processes, enhancing interoperability, and introducing new functionalities, these developments are likely to enhance the network&#8217;s attractiveness to investors and users alike. Related Reading: Hold Onto Your Seats: XRP Primed For 90% Rally, According To Top Analyst We are thrilled to announce the first of many angel investors that have joined our round! Sam Kazemian (@samkazemian ) is the founder of @FraxFinance ✦, one of the largest DeFi protocols with over $1.6bn in assets such as sfrxETH and the FRAX stablecoin. 🌐 Frax is committed… pic.twitter.com/zSL1XFNHYR — Fantom Foundation (@FantomFDN) March 27, 2024 The Fantom Foundation X account announced today that Frax Finance Founder Sam Kazemain is the first angel investor for Sonic, stating that Frax will deploy natively issued assets on Sonic on its eventual launch. Short-Term Gains Slashed In Favor Of The Long-Term Meanwhile, the bears have completely taken over the FTM market in the short to medium term. Investors in FTM could only hope that the broader market downturn will reverse in the coming weeks.  Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading the downturn today, Fantom (FTM) contributes to the 2% drop in the crypto market after weeks of growth.</p>

<p>Fantom is one of those altcoins that followed the broader momentum of the market. The latest <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/fantom" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">market data</a> shows that the token is down 10% in the past 24 hours, but is still on the green in the bi-weekly timeframe at 14%. However, Fantom has a trick up its sleeve to curb this brewing bearishness potentially. </p>
<h2><b>Fantom CEO Michael Kong Unveils Sonic Launch </b></h2>
<p>Sonic is the brand-new technology that the Fantom has been developing in the past 2 years. According to their latest <a href="https://blog.fantom.foundation/michael-kong-unveils-sonics-launch-and-beyond/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">blog post</a>, Sonic was able to surpass the network’s 200 transactions per second metric. Although 200 TPS was already impressive compared to Ethereum’s 12 TPS, the network was quickly congested, and user experience deteriorated. </p>
<p>Kong said in the blog post: </p>
<blockquote>
“​​Sonic will be used to create a new best-in-class shared sequencer for L1 and L2 chains, capable of processing over 180 million daily transactions with real, sub-second confirmation times, and serve as the foundation to relaunch Fantom as an entirely new community-centric brand.” 
</blockquote>
<p>This brand-new tech will cover all parts of the Fantom network, from bridging to a stablecoin launch, Sonic has it all. </p>
<p>Sonic Labs will also gain a slice of the pie as the foundation ultimately adds grant programs alongside the network upgrades. </p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VoNawxso/" width="1835" height="883" loading="lazy"/></p>

<p>“We will continue to significantly scale and accelerate our Sonic Labs grant program for developers who build unique and valuable applications and public goods in categories including gaming, DeFi, social media, streaming, and now distributed AI,” Kong added. </p>
<p>This will significantly increase the size of Fantom’s user base, boosting investor confidence, and giving more room for developers to innovate. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the advancements brought forth by Sonic Labs in covering all aspects of the Fantom network, from bridging to the launch of a stablecoin, are poised to have a notable impact on Fantom&#8217;s market dynamics.</p>
<p>By streamlining processes, enhancing interoperability, and introducing new functionalities, these developments are likely to enhance the network&#8217;s attractiveness to investors and users alike.</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are thrilled to announce the first of many angel investors that have joined our round!</p>
<p>Sam Kazemian (<a href="https://twitter.com/samkazemian?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@samkazemian</a> ) is the founder of <a href="https://twitter.com/fraxfinance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@FraxFinance</a> ✦, one of the largest DeFi protocols with over $1.6bn in assets such as sfrxETH and the FRAX stablecoin.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f310.png" alt="🌐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Frax is committed… <a href="https://t.co/zSL1XFNHYR" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/zSL1XFNHYR</a></p>
<p>— Fantom Foundation (@FantomFDN) <a href="https://twitter.com/FantomFDN/status/1773116898651115814?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 27, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>The Fantom Foundation X account <a href="https://x.com/FantomFDN/status/1773116898651115814?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">announced</a> today that Frax Finance Founder Sam Kazemain is the first angel investor for Sonic, stating that Frax will deploy natively issued assets on Sonic on its eventual launch.</p>
<h2><b>Short-Term Gains Slashed In Favor Of The Long-Term</b></h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the bears have completely taken over the FTM market in the short to medium term. Investors in FTM could only hope that the broader market downturn will reverse in the coming weeks. </p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_262650.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600147</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exec Reveals Why Meme Coins Are The Next ‘Trojan Horse’ For Crypto Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/meme-coins/meme-coins-next-trojan-horse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coins news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600143</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Maartje Bus, Vice President of Research at Messari, a prominent crypto market intelligence company, has declared meme coins as the Trojan Horse of the cryptocurrency space. She has highlighted their potential to foster massive adoption and increase engagement within the cryptocurrency space.  Why Meme Coins Are Crypto’s Trojan Horse For Adoption Speaking at BUIDL Asia, a global developer community in Seoul, South Korea, on Thursday, March 28, Bus gave a presentation on the emerging trends in crypto in 2024. The Messari crypto executive had primarily focused on the impact and potential benefits of meme coins in driving adoption within the crypto space.  Related Reading: Fifth Largest Bitcoin Whale Moves $6 Billion In BTC, Here’s The Destination According to Bus, meme coins have become an integral part of the crypto market and are evolving towards potentially establishing themselves as a distinct asset class. The Messari executive has described these humor themed coins as a “Trojan horse” which could potentially facilitate the entry of new users into the realm of cryptocurrency, effectively boosting adoption. During her speech, Bus disclosed that the introduction of these coins has successfully attracted the attention of both crypto and non-crypto enthusiasts. This is seen in the cryptocurrency’s ability to capture the attention of investors, utilizing its meme-based marketing strategies to fuel engagement while also providing opportunities for massive profitability due to its speculative nature.  Bus believes that meme coins could be likened to a long tail speculative service like lottery tickets which attract investors seeking high risk, high reward opportunities. Additionally, owing to their relatively low price value, they cater to individuals across various income brackets, who are willing to take speculative bets in the hopes of securing significant returns.  Moreover, according to the Messari executive, meme coins serve as a gateway for newcomers to the Web3 space, exposing them to fundamental crypto concepts like decentralization.   The Growing Allure In Crypto Space Lately, the rise in interest in meme coins has been growing at an exceptional rate, attracting both investors and traders from all over the world. This surge in interest has propelled meme coins in the spotlight, pushing their prices to unprecedented highs.  Related Reading: The Road To $100,000: Bitcoin Whale Accumulation Explodes Unlike traditional cryptocurrencies, which are backed by underlying projects and practical use cases, meme coins derive their value largely from their community and speculative appeal. Additionally, these cryptocurrencies offer a more approachable entry point into the realm of crypto investments, utilizing their affordability and susceptibility to social media trends and user sentiments to attract seasoned investors and newcomers alike.  Total market cap at $2.5 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Featured image from Finbold, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Maartje Bus, Vice President of Research at Messari, a prominent crypto market intelligence company, has declared meme coins as the Trojan Horse of the cryptocurrency space. She has highlighted their potential to foster massive adoption and increase engagement within the cryptocurrency space. </p>
<h2>Why Meme Coins Are Crypto’s Trojan Horse For Adoption</h2>
<p><a href="https://x.com/maartjebus/status/1773195784319615203?s=46" rel="nofollow">Speaking</a> at BUIDL Asia, a global developer community in Seoul, South Korea, on Thursday, March 28, Bus gave a presentation on the emerging trends in crypto in 2024. The Messari crypto executive had primarily focused on the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/impact-of-meme-coins-in-2024-which-meme-coin-is-expected-to-net-20x-returns/">impact and potential benefits of meme coins</a> in driving adoption within the crypto space. </p>

<p>According to Bus, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/meme-coins-winners/" rel="nofollow">meme coins have become an integral part of the crypto market</a> and are evolving towards potentially establishing themselves as a distinct asset class. The Messari executive has described these <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/meme-coins-are-fun-but-the-real-money-is-made-with-utility-driven-tokens/" rel="nofollow">humor themed coins</a> as a “Trojan horse” which could potentially facilitate the entry of new users into the realm of cryptocurrency, effectively boosting adoption.</p>
<p>During her speech, Bus disclosed that the introduction of these coins has successfully <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/social-media-storm-gives-dogecoin-14-price-boost-details/">attracted the attention of both crypto and non-crypto enthusiasts</a>. This is seen in the cryptocurrency’s ability to capture the attention of investors, utilizing its meme-based marketing strategies to fuel engagement while also <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-1-6-million-bsc-meme-coin/" rel="nofollow">providing opportunities for massive profitability </a>due to its speculative nature. </p>
<p>Bus believes that meme coins could be likened to a long tail speculative service like lottery tickets which <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-investing-meme-coins/" rel="nofollow">attract investors seeking high risk, high reward opportunities.</a> Additionally, owing to their relatively low price value, they cater to individuals across various income brackets, who are willing to take speculative bets in the hopes of <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-3-meme-coins-bull-market/" rel="nofollow">securing significant returns</a>. </p>
<p>Moreover, according to the Messari executive, meme coins serve as a gateway for newcomers to the Web3 space, exposing them to fundamental crypto concepts like decentralization.  </p>
<h2>The Growing Allure In Crypto Space</h2>
<p>Lately, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/pepecoin-pepe-rallies-by-42-as-interest-in-memecoins-rises/">rise in interest in meme coins</a> has been growing at an exceptional rate, attracting both investors and traders from all over the world. This surge in interest has propelled meme coins in the spotlight, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/meme-coins-market-cap-soar-to-over-54-billion/">pushing their prices to unprecedented highs</a>. </p>

<p>Unlike traditional cryptocurrencies, which are backed by underlying projects and practical use cases, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coins-myro-wif/" rel="nofollow">meme coins</a> derive their value largely from their community and speculative appeal. Additionally, these cryptocurrencies offer a more approachable entry point into the realm of crypto investments, utilizing their affordability and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/meme-coins-shib-pepe-viral/" rel="nofollow">susceptibility to social media trends</a> and user sentiments to attract seasoned investors and newcomers alike. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UWRK77UE/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com (Meme coins)" width="3286" height="1530" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Meme-coins.jpeg?fit=300%2C168" width="300" height="168" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600143</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>From $90 To $400 Litecoin: Analysts Bullish On LTC Soaring Trajectory</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/from-90-to-400-litecoin-analysts-bullish-on-ltc-soaring-trajectory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC), the silver to Bitcoin&#8217;s gold, has enjoyed a recent price surge, leaving investors cautiously optimistic about its future trajectory. Over the past week, LTC has seen a 13% increase, with its value hovering nearly $96 at the time of writing. This bullish run has been accompanied by technical indicators suggesting a potential continuation of the uptrend, but some analysts warn of lurking risks. LTC maintains a strong weekly performance. Source: Coingecko Related Reading: Hold Onto Your Seats: XRP Primed For 90% Rally, According To Top Analyst Potential Litecoin Price Bump In The Offing One key driver of optimism is the apparent breakout from a bullish triangle pattern. This technical indicator, identified by popular analyst World of Charts, suggests a potential price surge in the coming months, with some analysts even predicting a climb to $400. $Ltc #Ltc Breakout &#38; Retest Has Already Confirmed Send It Towards 400$ Now https://t.co/6ZJxAgZjVJ pic.twitter.com/xW3xDrgHAZ — World Of Charts (@WorldOfCharts1) March 26, 2024 Further fueling the bullish sentiment are on-chain metrics like the MVRV ratio, which suggests the coin might not be overvalued yet. Additionally, a rise in Daily Active Addresses and transaction volume indicates increased investor activity and trading. This is further corroborated by a bullish crossover on the MACD indicator and a rising Money Flow Index (MFI), both suggesting potential for further price hikes. Bitcoin is now trading at $70.714. Chart: TradingView However, not all signals are green. The Network-to-Value (NVT) ratio, which indicates potential overvaluation, has also spiked alongside the price increase. This raises concerns about a possible price correction if the market deems LTC to be overvalued. While the recent price action for Litecoin is encouraging, it&#8217;s crucial to maintain a balanced perspective, analysts caution. Technical indicators can be helpful, but they shouldn&#8217;t be the sole decision-making factors, they said. LTC Hashrate Remains Stable Meanwhile, the hashrate, a measure of computing power dedicated to mining LTC, has remained stable, suggesting no significant changes in miner activity. However, some analysts worry that a potential drop in hashrate could hinder future growth. Related Reading: XRP ETF Premium Primed For Monumental Leap: Eyes Set On $500 The overall picture for Litecoin presents both opportunities and challenges. The recent price surge and positive on-chain metrics are encouraging signs. However, potential overvaluation concerns and conflicting technical signals urge caution. Investors should closely monitor both technical and fundamental factors before making any investment decisions. The coming weeks will be crucial for LTC. If the uptrend continues and the price breaks through key resistance levels, a significant rally could be on the horizon. If overvaluation concerns materialize or the broader market takes a downturn, a price correction could occur. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:411">Litecoin (LTC), the silver to Bitcoin&#8217;s gold, has enjoyed a recent price surge, leaving investors cautiously optimistic about its future trajectory.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:411">Over the past week, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">LTC has seen a 13% increase</a>, with its value hovering nearly $96 at the time of writing.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:411">This bullish run has been accompanied by technical indicators suggesting a potential continuation of the uptrend, but some analysts warn of lurking risks.</p>


<h2 data-sourcepos="3:1-3:411"><strong>Potential Litecoin Price Bump In The Offing</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:265">One key driver of optimism is the apparent breakout from a bullish triangle pattern. This technical indicator, identified by popular analyst World of Charts, suggests a potential price surge in the coming months, with some analysts even predicting a climb to $400.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24Ltc&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$Ltc</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ltc?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Ltc</a> Breakout &amp; Retest Has Already Confirmed Send It Towards 400$ Now <a href="https://t.co/6ZJxAgZjVJ" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/6ZJxAgZjVJ</a> <a href="https://t.co/xW3xDrgHAZ" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/xW3xDrgHAZ</a></p>
<p>— World Of Charts (@WorldOfCharts1) <a href="https://twitter.com/WorldOfCharts1/status/1772543150118031667?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:415">Further fueling the bullish sentiment are on-chain metrics like the MVRV ratio, which suggests the coin might not be overvalued yet.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:415">Additionally, a rise in Daily Active Addresses and transaction volume indicates increased investor activity and trading.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:415">This is further corroborated by a bullish crossover on the MACD indicator and a rising Money Flow Index (MFI), both suggesting potential for further price hikes.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:415"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/MkisG8iR/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:385">However, not all signals are green. The Network-to-Value (NVT) ratio, which indicates potential overvaluation, has also spiked alongside the price increase. This raises concerns about a possible price correction if the market deems LTC to be overvalued.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:388">While the recent price action for Litecoin is encouraging, it&#8217;s crucial to maintain a balanced perspective, analysts caution. Technical indicators can be helpful, but they shouldn&#8217;t be the sole decision-making factors, they said.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="11:1-11:388"><strong>LTC Hashrate Remains Stable</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:232">Meanwhile, the hashrate, a measure of computing power dedicated to mining LTC, has remained stable, suggesting no significant changes in miner activity. However, some analysts worry that a potential drop in hashrate could hinder future growth.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:354">The overall picture for Litecoin presents both opportunities and challenges. The recent price surge and positive on-chain metrics are encouraging signs.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:354">However, potential overvaluation concerns and conflicting technical signals urge caution. Investors should closely monitor both technical and fundamental factors before making any investment decisions.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:283">The coming weeks will be crucial for LTC. If the uptrend continues and the price breaks through key resistance levels, a significant rally could be on the horizon.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:283">If overvaluation concerns materialize or the broader market takes a downturn, a price correction could occur.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:283"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_867688.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600118</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin ETF Inflows Could Eclipse $1 Trillion, Predicts Bitwise CIO</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etf-inflows-1-trillion-predicts-bitwise-cio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 08:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot Bitcoin ETFs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Following a week of net outflows, the spot Bitcoin ETF market has rebounded with impressive net inflows this week, highlighting a growing investor confidence in Bitcoin and its associated financial products. This week&#8217;s market activities have shown a remarkable reversal from the previous 5-day net outflow streak, with Tuesday witnessing a substantial net inflow of $480 million, followed by $243.5 million on Wednesday. Yesterday’s resurgence in investor interest was notably boosted by Blackrock&#8217;s massive inflow of $323.8 million, effectively offsetting Grayscale GBTC&#8217;s $299.8 million outflows. Moreover, Ark Invest’s ARKB reported its best day yet, with $200 million in inflows, despite Fidelity experiencing its worst day with a mere $1.5 million in outflows. Nevertheless, Fidelity managed to bounce back with significant inflows of $261 million and $279 million on Monday and Tuesday, respectively. Yesterday&#39;s ETF flows were positive for $243.5 million. Blackrock finally woke up again for $323.8 million completely cancelling out $GBTC&#39;s $299.8 million outflows. Ark had their best day yet with $200 million. Fidelity had its worst day with $1.5 million. Price dumped on… pic.twitter.com/LLChkITN7q &#8212; WhalePanda (@WhalePanda) March 28, 2024 1% Down, 99% To Go For Bitcoin ETFs However, according to Bitwise Chief Investment Officer (CIO) Matt Hougan, this is just the mere beginning of what is to come in the upcoming months. Hougan’s commentary, part of his weekly memo to investment professionals, sheds light on the current market dynamics and the colossal potential that lies ahead. “1% Down; 99% to Go,” Hougan wrote, highlighting the nascent yet promising journey of Bitcoin ETFs. Related Reading: $9.5 Billion In Bitcoin Options Poised To Expire This Friday: Market Turbulence Ahead? Lately, the market has been characterized by its volatility, with Bitcoin&#8217;s price oscillating between $60,000 and $70,000. Hougan advises a calm and long-term perspective amidst this fluctuation, especially as the sector anticipates the upcoming Bitcoin halving around April 20, the approval of Bitcoin ETFs on national account platforms, and the soon-to-come completion of due diligence by various investment committees. Despite the current sideways movement of Bitcoin&#8217;s price, Hougan remains bullish about its long-term trajectory. &#8220;Bitcoin is in a raging bull market,&#8221; he asserts, noting a nearly 300% increase over the past 15 months. The launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs in January has marked a significant milestone, opening up the Bitcoin market to investment professionals on an unprecedented scale. Hougan&#8217;s analysis points to a profound shift as global wealth managers, who collectively control over $100 trillion, begin to explore investments in the “digital gold.” He suggests that even a conservative allocation of 1% of their portfolios to Bitcoin could result in approximately $1 trillion of inflows into the space. Related Reading: Bitcoin “Liquid Inventory Ratio” Hits All-Time Low, What It Means This perspective is backed by historical data showing that even a 2.5% allocation to Bitcoin has enhanced the risk-adjusted returns of traditional 60/40 portfolios in every three-year period of Bitcoin&#8217;s history. The recent inflows into Bitcoin ETFs, though impressive, are seen by Hougan as merely the beginning of a much larger movement. &#8220;We are all excited about the $12 billion that has flowed into ETFs since January. And it is exciting: Collectively, the most successful ETF launch of all time..But imagine global wealth managers allocate just 1% of their portfolios to bitcoin on average,&#8221; Hougan elaborates, emphasizing the scale of potential growth awaiting the cryptocurrency market. He concludes: Think about the implications. [&#8230;] A 1% allocation across the board would mean ~$1 trillion of inflows into the space. Against this, $12 billion is barely a down payment. 1% down, 99% to go. At press time, BTC traded at $70,644. Featured image created with DALL·E, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following a week of net outflows, the spot Bitcoin ETF market has rebounded with impressive net inflows this week, highlighting a growing investor confidence in Bitcoin and its associated financial products. This week&#8217;s market activities have shown a remarkable reversal from the previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-reclaims-66000-despite-4-day-etf-outflow-streak/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">5-day net outflow streak</a>, with Tuesday witnessing a substantial net inflow of $480 million, followed by $243.5 million on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Yesterday’s resurgence in investor interest was notably boosted by Blackrock&#8217;s massive inflow of $323.8 million, effectively offsetting Grayscale GBTC&#8217;s $299.8 million outflows. Moreover, Ark Invest’s ARKB reported its best day yet, with $200 million in inflows, despite Fidelity experiencing its worst day with a mere $1.5 million in outflows. Nevertheless, Fidelity managed to bounce back with significant inflows of $261 million and $279 million on Monday and Tuesday, respectively.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Yesterday&#39;s ETF flows were positive for $243.5 million.</p>
<p>Blackrock finally woke up again for $323.8 million completely cancelling out <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GBTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$GBTC</a>&#39;s $299.8 million outflows.</p>
<p>Ark had their best day yet with $200 million. Fidelity had its worst day with $1.5 million.</p>
<p>Price dumped on… <a href="https://t.co/LLChkITN7q" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/LLChkITN7q</a></p>
<p>&mdash; WhalePanda (@WhalePanda) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhalePanda/status/1773206774599889207?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 28, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>1% Down, 99% To Go For Bitcoin ETFs</h2>
<p>However, according to Bitwise Chief Investment Officer (CIO) Matt Hougan, this is just the mere beginning of what is to come in the upcoming months. Hougan’s <a href="https://twitter.com/BitwiseInvest/status/1773005602752491548" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">commentary</a>, part of his weekly memo to investment professionals, sheds light on the current market dynamics and the colossal potential that lies ahead. “1% Down; 99% to Go,” Hougan wrote, highlighting the nascent yet promising journey of Bitcoin ETFs.</p>

<p>Lately, the market has been characterized by its volatility, with Bitcoin&#8217;s price oscillating between $60,000 and $70,000. Hougan advises a calm and long-term perspective amidst this fluctuation, especially as the sector anticipates the upcoming <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/when-is-the-next-btc-halving-date-bitcoin-halving-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin halving</a> around April 20, the approval of Bitcoin ETFs on national account platforms, and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etf-floodgates-just-opening-bitwise-cio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">soon-to-come completion</a> of due diligence by various investment committees.</p>
<p>Despite the current sideways movement of Bitcoin&#8217;s price, Hougan remains bullish about its long-term trajectory. &#8220;Bitcoin is in a raging bull market,&#8221; he asserts, noting a nearly 300% increase over the past 15 months. The launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs in January has marked a significant milestone, opening up the Bitcoin market to investment professionals on an unprecedented scale.</p>
<p>Hougan&#8217;s analysis points to a profound shift as global wealth managers, who collectively control over $100 trillion, begin to explore investments in the “digital gold.” He suggests that even a conservative allocation of 1% of their portfolios to Bitcoin could result in approximately $1 trillion of inflows into the space.</p>

<p>This perspective is backed by historical data showing that even a 2.5% allocation to Bitcoin has enhanced the risk-adjusted returns of traditional 60/40 portfolios in every three-year period of Bitcoin&#8217;s history.</p>
<p>The recent inflows into Bitcoin ETFs, though impressive, are seen by Hougan as merely the beginning of a much larger movement. &#8220;We are all excited about the $12 billion that has flowed into ETFs since January. And it is exciting: Collectively, the most successful ETF launch of all time..But imagine global wealth managers allocate just 1% of their portfolios to bitcoin on average,&#8221; Hougan elaborates, emphasizing the scale of potential growth awaiting the cryptocurrency market. He concludes:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Think about the implications. [&#8230;] A 1% allocation across the board would mean ~$1 trillion of inflows into the space. Against this, $12 billion is barely a down payment. 1% down, 99% to go.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, BTC traded at $70,644.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-600119 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1673" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-28_09-37-39.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-28-09.09.55-A-visually-striking-and-futuristic-illustration-of-a-bitcoin-ETF-concept-encapsulating-the-idea-of-digital-wealth-transformation-and-financial-growth.jpg?fit=460%2C263" width="460" height="263" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600116</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP ETF Premium Primed For Monumental Leap: Eyes Set On $500</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/xrp-etf-premium-primed-for-monumental-leap-eyes-set-on-500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600097</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP enthusiasts are in a frenzy after prominent community figure Chad Steingraber proposed a scenario where an XRP exchange-traded fund (ETF) could trade at a staggering 100x premium. Steingraber, a seasoned game designer, laid out his thoughts in a recent post, igniting discussions about the potential trajectory of an XRP ETF, particularly in light of the ongoing push for institutional adoption of the altcoin. Related Reading: Hold Onto Your Seats: XRP Primed For 90% Rally, According To Top Analyst Targeting A $500 XRP ETF Share Price Steingraber&#8217;s speculation centers around the price at which an XRP ETF&#8217;s shares might trade. His hypothesis hinges on the crypto reaching an unprecedented price of $5 per coin. In this scenario, he theorizes that the corresponding ETF could soar to equally unprecedented heights, potentially reaching a solid $500 per share. The actual underlying asset price does NOT have to skyrocket. The fund can trade at MASSIVE Premiums. Let’s say #XRP breaks ATH @ $5, its ETF fund could literally trade at 100x premium if the institutional demand kicks in. Yes, that’s right, a $500 #XRP Institution Premium. 👍 https://t.co/bwN6cGmmZd pic.twitter.com/tHyy4fkbeK — Chad Steingraber (@ChadSteingraber) March 27, 2024 This hefty premium, according to Steingraber, would be fueled by a surge in institutional interest in the ETF. He cites the Grayscale Litecoin Trust (LTCN) as a prime example. Similar to his proposed XRP ETF, LTCN trades at a significant premium over Litecoin&#8217;s current market price. Despite Litecoin hovering around $95, investors in LTCN are currently paying a premium of over $250 per Litecoin equivalent within the trust. Can Arbitrage Opportunities Emerge? The prospect of such a high premium has sparked discussions about potential arbitrage opportunities. X user Zack, in response to Steingraber&#8217;s post, questioned whether individuals holding XRP could exploit this price disparity. Steingraber acknowledged the possibility, particularly if the issuing ETF allows for in-kind deposits, where investors can directly exchange their token for ETF shares. XRP market cap currently at $34 billion. Chart: TradingView.com However, he cautioned that in-kind deposits are still a rarity in the ETF market. While Steingraber expressed optimism about the future adoption of this practice, its absence presents a hurdle for immediate arbitrage opportunities. The XRP community has long advocated for asset managers, especially industry giant BlackRock, to launch an XRP ETF. They believe such a product would significantly bolster the value of XRP by increasing its accessibility to institutional investors. XRP up in the last seven days. Source: Coingecko A Speculative Outlook With Underlying Uncertainties It&#8217;s crucial to remember that Steingraber&#8217;s vision is entirely speculative. As of today, no asset manager has taken concrete steps towards applying for an XRP ETF. Furthermore, the justification for such a high premium rests heavily on the assumption of substantial institutional demand, a factor that remains uncertain. Related Reading: Analyst Bullish On Polkadot (DOT), Predicts $17 Price Target Before April The applicability of the Grayscale Litecoin Trust comparison also requires further scrutiny. The specific structure and features of an XRP ETF would significantly influence whether a similar premium dynamic would emerge. A Reality Check For Investors While Steingraber&#8217;s prediction has certainly captured the community&#8217;s imagination, investors are advised to approach it with a healthy dose of caution. The approval timeline for an XRP ETF hinges on the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s stance on cryptocurrency ETFs. Additionally, competition from other potential ETFs could play a role in determining the premium, if any. Featured image from Freepik, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:231">XRP enthusiasts are in a frenzy after prominent community figure Chad Steingraber proposed a scenario where an XRP exchange-traded fund (ETF) could trade at a staggering 100x premium.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:223">Steingraber, a seasoned game designer, laid out his thoughts in a recent post, igniting discussions about the potential trajectory of an XRP ETF, particularly in light of the ongoing push for institutional adoption of the altcoin.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="9:1-9:42"><strong>Targeting A $500 XRP ETF Share Price</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:324">Steingraber&#8217;s speculation centers around the price at which an XRP ETF&#8217;s shares might trade. His hypothesis hinges on the crypto reaching an unprecedented price of $5 per coin. In this scenario, he theorizes that the corresponding ETF could soar to equally unprecedented heights, potentially reaching a solid $500 per share.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The actual underlying asset price does NOT have to skyrocket. The fund can trade at MASSIVE Premiums.</p>
<p>Let’s say <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> breaks ATH @ $5, its ETF fund could literally trade at 100x premium if the institutional demand kicks in.</p>
<p>Yes, that’s right, a $500 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#XRP</a> Institution Premium. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f44d.png" alt="👍" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/bwN6cGmmZd" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/bwN6cGmmZd</a> <a href="https://t.co/tHyy4fkbeK" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/tHyy4fkbeK</a></p>
<p>— Chad Steingraber (@ChadSteingraber) <a href="https://twitter.com/ChadSteingraber/status/1772786414356197465?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 27, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:429">This hefty premium, according to Steingraber, would be fueled by a surge in institutional interest in the ETF. He cites the Grayscale Litecoin Trust (LTCN) as a prime example.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:429">Similar to his proposed XRP ETF, LTCN trades at a significant premium over Litecoin&#8217;s current market price. Despite Litecoin hovering around $95, investors in LTCN are currently paying a premium of over $250 per Litecoin equivalent within the trust.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="15:1-15:39"><strong>Can Arbitrage Opportunities Emerge?</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:394">The prospect of such a high premium has sparked discussions about potential arbitrage opportunities. X user Zack, in response to Steingraber&#8217;s post, questioned whether individuals holding XRP could exploit this price disparity. Steingraber acknowledged the possibility, particularly if the issuing ETF allows for in-kind deposits, where investors can directly exchange their token for ETF shares.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:394"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Wi5PrSI9/" width="2475" height="1163"/></p>

<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:231">However, he cautioned that in-kind deposits are still a rarity in the ETF market. While Steingraber expressed optimism about the future adoption of this practice, its absence presents a hurdle for immediate arbitrage opportunities.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:429">The XRP community has long advocated for asset managers, especially industry giant BlackRock, to launch an XRP ETF. They believe such a product would significantly <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/top-analysts-bold-prediction-xrp-set-to-skyrocket-15x/">bolster the value of XRP</a> by increasing its accessibility to institutional investors.</p>

<strong>A Speculative Outlook With Underlying Uncertainties</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="23:1-23:321">It&#8217;s crucial to remember that Steingraber&#8217;s vision is entirely speculative. As of today, no asset manager has taken concrete steps towards applying for an <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP</a> ETF. Furthermore, the justification for such a high premium rests heavily on the assumption of substantial institutional demand, a factor that remains uncertain.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="25:1-25:220">The applicability of the Grayscale Litecoin Trust comparison also requires further scrutiny. The specific structure and features of an XRP ETF would significantly influence whether a similar premium dynamic would emerge.</p>
<strong>A Reality Check For Investors</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="29:1-29:394">While Steingraber&#8217;s prediction has certainly captured the community&#8217;s imagination, investors are advised to approach it with a healthy dose of caution. The approval timeline for an XRP ETF hinges on the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s stance on cryptocurrency ETFs.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="29:1-29:394">Additionally, competition from other potential ETFs could play a role in determining the premium, if any.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="35:1-35:458"><em>Featured image from Freepik, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ed5f32.png?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600097</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Faces Uphill Task But Indicators Signal More Upsides</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-faces-uphill-task-70k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 04:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600094</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is consolidating gains above the $69,000 support zone. BTC must clear the $71,500 resistance zone to start a steady increase. Bitcoin price is still showing positive signs and facing resistance near $71,500. The price is trading above $69,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a major bullish trend line forming with support at $69,120 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair could start another increase if it clears the $71,500 resistance zone. Bitcoin Price Holds Support Bitcoin price remained in a positive zone above the $68,800 resistance zone. BTC climbed higher the $70,000 resistance zone, but the bears were active near the $71,500 level. There were more than two attempts to clear the $71,500 level but the bulls failed. There was a downside correction, and the price tested the $68,400 support. A low was formed at $68,366 and the price is now starting a decent increase. There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $71,746 swing high to the $68,366 low. Bitcoin is now trading above $69,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support at $69,120 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $70,000 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $71,746 swing high to the $68,366 low. The first major resistance could be $71,200. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com The main resistance is still near $71,500. If there is a clear move above the $71,500 resistance zone, the price could continue to gain strength. In the stated case, the price could even clear the $72,500 resistance zone in the near term. More Losses In BTC? If Bitcoin fails to rise above the $71,200 resistance zone, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $69,200 level and the trend line. The first major support is $68,400. The next support sits at $67,500. If there is a close below $67,500, the price could start a drop toward the $66,000 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $66,000 support zone in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Levels – $68,400, followed by $67,000. Major Resistance Levels – $70,000, $71,500, and $73,500.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is consolidating gains above the $69,000 support zone. BTC must clear the $71,500 resistance zone to start a steady increase.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price is still showing positive signs and facing resistance near $71,500.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $69,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a major bullish trend line forming with support at $69,120 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could start another increase if it clears the $71,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Holds Support</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained in a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-consolidates-70k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">positive zone</a> above the $68,800 resistance zone. BTC climbed higher the $70,000 resistance zone, but the bears were active near the $71,500 level.</p>
<p>There were more than two attempts to clear the $71,500 level but the bulls failed. There was a downside correction, and the price tested the $68,400 support. A low was formed at $68,366 and the price is now starting a decent increase.</p>
<p>There was a move above the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $71,746 swing high to the $68,366 low. Bitcoin is now trading above $69,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-reclaims-70k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>. There is also a major bullish trend line forming with support at $69,120 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair.</p>
<p>Immediate resistance is near the $70,000 level or the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $71,746 swing high to the $68,366 low. The first major resistance could be $71,200.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-600095" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1024" height="449" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1950 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_d7ffa4.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The main resistance is still near $71,500. If there is a clear move above the $71,500 resistance zone, the price could continue to gain strength. In the stated case, the price could even clear the $72,500 resistance zone in the near term.</p>
<h2>More Losses In BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to rise above the $71,200 resistance zone, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $69,200 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The first major support is $68,400. The next support sits at $67,500. If there is a close below $67,500, the price could start a drop toward the $66,000 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $66,000 support zone in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bearish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $68,400, followed by $67,000.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $70,000, $71,500, and $73,500.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_638895124.jpg?fit=460%2C264" width="460" height="264" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600094</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breath Of Fresh Air: Viral ‘Cardano Girls’ Video Sparks Conversation About The Project</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/breath-of-fresh-air-viral-cardano-girls-video-sparks-conversation-about-the-project/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubmar Garcia]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Girls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600067</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has received plenty of criticism over the years, whether it’s ADA’s price performance, its founder’s personality, or its community’s “beef” with Solana. This time, the project’s marketing team made the headlines after a viral video of female Cardano users became viral on social media. The ‘Cardano Girls’ video has sparked a conversation about the project’s efforts to reach a broader audience. Related Reading: Cardano (ADA) Eyes Explosive 2000% Bull Run, Targeting $12 And Quadrupling ATH A Breath Of Fresh Air In The Community The ‘Cardano Girls’ video was uploaded by Lily Brodi, a content creator and Cardano user, and went viral in hours. The video recreated a popular social media trend of people playfully listing stereotypical practices of a group of people with the phrase “We are (group). Of course, we…” The trend, recreated by millions, including famous personalities like Kim Kardashian, has reached the crypto community. Last week, a “Crypto Girls” version of the trend was uploaded on X, which prompted Brodi to make her own. Brodi’s version approached the point of view of female Cardano investors, with the opening line setting the lighthearted and playful tone: “We’re Cardano girls. Of course, we are real.” The list in the video includes how female ADA users “treat themselves with money saved on gas,” “have Charles as their phone wallpaper,” and “buy $ADA while the men create all the drama.” At the time of writing, the viral video had over 1.5 million views on X. Its massive reach resulted in the acknowledgment of Cardano’s founder, Charles Hoskinson, referred to as “Cattle Daddy” in the video. Lol, I&#39;m blushing. Thanks for all the support and love &#8212; Charles Hoskinson (@IOHK_Charles) March 25, 2024 &#8216;Cardano Girls&#8217; And Marketing Team Face Criticism The video didn’t go unnoticed by critics, who considered the video to be “cringy,” while others expressed opinions seemingly based on misogyny. Crypto influencer Peter McCormack replied to the X post stating that the video will be used “as torture at Guantanamo Bay.” However, the video appears to be well-received by the Cardano and crypto community. Brodi addressed the male detractors in an X post: after the last 24 hours, i’ve realised that a lot of men haven’t felt the warm embrace of a woman &#8212; LILY (@lilybrodi) March 26, 2024 Nonetheless, the video opened a broader conversation despite the critics. On one hand, it highlighted how the male-dominated crypto industry can be unreceptive and aggressive to women in the space. On the other hand, it pointed out a crucial issue for Cardano: its “unattractiveness.” The Need For A New Approach Brodi discussed the video’s immense impact, as it seemingly brought general interest in the project, with people reaching out to her curious about the Cardano wallet. Despite its technology and the knowledgeable people inside the community, the project doesn’t seem to attract the general user. Brodi, who creates light and informative Cardano-related content, considers that the general content offered can be “too heavy” and “overwhelming” to those who know about the industry and even more to those who don’t but want to come in. real talk #CardanoGirls &#38; cardano marketing pic.twitter.com/XePfmHiXGN &#8212; LILY (@lilybrodi) March 27, 2024 Cardano’s marketing problem, as highlighted by Brodi, has often prevented potential users from entering. She suggests that a change in the market strategy is “needed within Cardano” for broader adoption. Lighthearted, fun, and enjoyable educational content that can be easily consumable can be fundamental for broader adoption. Investors can be attracted to projects that seem easily understandable and approachable. As seen with the memecoin mania, projects can become massive, even if the long-term technology and planning aren’t developed by launch. The crypto community is undoubtedly filled with people who enjoy various content and projects. But “bringing light and fun” enjoyment is crucial to supporting adoption because, at its core, “that’s what our community is.” Related Reading: Here’s Why The Cardano Price Is Struggling Below $0.7 ADA is trading at $0.64 in the 3-day chart. Source: ADAUSDT on Trading.view.com  Featured Image from Unsplash.com, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">Cardano (ADA) has received plenty of criticism over the years, whether it’s ADA’s price performance, its founder’s personality, or its community’s “beef” with <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/cardano-founder-takes-jab-at-solana-after-major-outage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana</a>.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">This time, the project’s marketing team made the headlines after a viral video of female Cardano users became viral on social media. The ‘Cardano Girls’ video has sparked a conversation about the project’s efforts to reach a broader audience.</p>

<h2 style="font-weight: 400">A Breath Of Fresh Air In The Community</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The ‘Cardano Girls’ video was uploaded by Lily Brodi, a content creator and Cardano user, and went viral in hours. The video recreated a popular social media trend of people playfully listing stereotypical practices of a group of people with the phrase “We are (group). Of course, we…”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The trend, recreated by millions, including famous personalities like Kim Kardashian, has reached the crypto community. Last week, a “Crypto Girls” <a href="https://x.com/urbrobecc/status/1771194380348445007?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">version</a> of the trend was uploaded on X, which prompted Brodi to make her own.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">we’re cardano girls <a href="https://t.co/ebB6Qd0t2Q" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/ebB6Qd0t2Q</a></p>
<p>&mdash; LILY (@lilybrodi) <a href="https://twitter.com/lilybrodi/status/1772288881901093250?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Brodi’s version approached the point of view of female Cardano investors, with the opening line setting the lighthearted and playful tone: “We’re Cardano girls. Of course, we are real.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The list in the video includes how female ADA users “treat themselves with money saved on gas,” “have Charles as their phone wallpaper,” and “buy $ADA while the men create all the drama.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">At the time of writing, the viral video had over 1.5 million views on X. Its massive reach resulted in the acknowledgment of Cardano’s founder, Charles Hoskinson, referred to as “Cattle Daddy” in the video.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Lol, I&#39;m blushing. Thanks for all the support and love</p>
<p>&mdash; Charles Hoskinson (@IOHK_Charles) <a href="https://twitter.com/IOHK_Charles/status/1772392131648168152?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">&#8216;Cardano Girls&#8217; And Marketing Team Face Criticism</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The video didn’t go unnoticed by critics, who considered the video to be “cringy,” while others expressed opinions seemingly based on misogyny. Crypto influencer Peter McCormack <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterMcCormack/status/1772423067253276954" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">replied</a> to the X post stating that the video will be used “as torture at Guantanamo Bay.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">However, the video appears to be well-received by the Cardano and crypto community. Brodi addressed the male detractors in an X post:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">after the last 24 hours, i’ve realised that a lot of men haven’t felt the warm embrace of a woman</p>
<p>&mdash; LILY (@lilybrodi) <a href="https://twitter.com/lilybrodi/status/1772648572183339286?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Nonetheless, the video opened a broader conversation despite the critics. On one hand, it highlighted how the male-dominated crypto industry can be unreceptive and aggressive to women in the space. On the other hand, it pointed out a crucial issue for Cardano: its “unattractiveness.”</p>
The Need For A New Approach
<p style="font-weight: 400">Brodi discussed the video’s immense impact, as it seemingly brought general interest in the project, with people reaching out to her curious about the Cardano wallet. Despite its technology and the knowledgeable people inside the community, the project doesn’t seem to attract the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/cardano/cardanos-future-revealed-founder-would-love-to-be-the-taylor-swift-of-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">general user</a>.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Brodi, who creates light and informative Cardano-related content, considers that the general content offered can be “too heavy” and “overwhelming” to those who know about the industry and even more to those who don’t but want to come in.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">real talk <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CardanoGirls?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#CardanoGirls</a> &amp; cardano marketing <a href="https://t.co/XePfmHiXGN" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/XePfmHiXGN</a></p>
<p>&mdash; LILY (@lilybrodi) <a href="https://twitter.com/lilybrodi/status/1772781429618790662?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 27, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Cardano’s marketing problem, as highlighted by Brodi, has often prevented potential users from entering. She suggests that a change in the market strategy is “needed within Cardano” for broader adoption.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Lighthearted, fun, and enjoyable educational content that can be easily consumable can be fundamental for broader adoption. Investors can be attracted to projects that seem easily understandable and approachable. As seen with the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-presale-frenzy-raises-over-122m-worth-of-sol-in-a-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">memecoin mania</a>, projects can become massive, even if the long-term technology and planning aren’t developed by launch.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The crypto community is undoubtedly filled with people who enjoy various content and projects. But “bringing light and fun” enjoyment is crucial to supporting adoption because, at its core, “that’s what our community is.”</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-600070 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C433" alt="Cardano, ADA, ADAUSDT" width="860" height="433" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=1022 1022w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C433 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=360 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ADAUSDT_2024-03-27_11-41-02.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/mark-sivewright-xMjQYjGGJgk-unsplash.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600067</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ondo Finance Joins BlackRock Tokenized Fund As Inflows Surpass $160M</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ondo-finance-joins-blackrock-tokenized-fund-as-inflows-surpass-160m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 02:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock CEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock iShares Bitcoin Trust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock's iShares Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ondo Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ONDOUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ONDOUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BlackRock, one of the largest asset managers globally, has witnessed notable success with its newly launched tokenized money-market fund, BUIDL. The fund, which records shared ownership on the Ethereum (ETH) blockchain, has attracted over $160 million in just one week since its debut.  BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL Fund According to a Bloomberg report, the BlackRock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund (BUIDL) primarily invests in cash, US Treasury bills, and repurchase agreements. The fund rewards its holders with a cryptocurrency, BUIDL, valued at $1 per token.  Shareholders can transfer these tokens to other validated addresses using digital wallets approved by Securitize, BlackRock&#8217;s partner for the investment vehicle. The tokenized fund serves several key use cases, including treasury management for crypto companies, support for derivatives of Treasury bills, and acting as collateral for borrowing and trading, thus providing an alternative to stablecoins. Related Reading: Bitcoin “Liquid Inventory Ratio” Hits All-Time Low, What It Means It is worth noting that Securitize Markets, an SEC-registered alternative trading system, plays a critical role in facilitating the transfer of tokens between market participants.  While the SEC has recently increased its scrutiny of Ethereum&#8217;s native token, ETH, Securitize CEO Carlos Domingo emphasizes that the investigations should be separate from the underlying blockchain infrastructure. Domingo also highlights the battle-tested nature of the public Ethereum blockchain, which provides a &#8220;robust foundation&#8221; for tokenization activities. As previously reported by our sister website, Bitcoinist, BlackRock has emerged as an advocate for cryptocurrencies and tokenization within mainstream financial institutions. Chairman and CEO Larry Fink believes every financial asset will eventually be tokenized.  The company&#8217;s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) has already attracted more than $13 billion in inflows since its launch as an exchange-traded fund (ETF) in January. With the BUIDL fund&#8217;s launch, BlackRock continues to demonstrate its willingness to explore new digital asset solutions. Ondo Finance To Transfer $95 Million In Assets To BlackRock Ondo Finance, a platform specializing in tokenized real-world assets (RWA), has moved $95 million worth of assets to BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL fund. This strategic move enables Ondo Finance to facilitate instant settlements for its US Treasury-backed token, OUSG.  This makes Ondo Finance a major participant in the BUIDL ecosystem. According to on-chain researcher Tom Wan, it currently holds $15 million worth of BUIDL tokens, which, in addition to those above $95 million, will result in a substantial $110 million worth of BUIDL tokens.   Related Reading: Here’s Why The Cardano Price Is Struggling Below $0.7 The researcher noted that this collaboration further strengthens the tokenized US Treasury market, with the potential to reach $1 billion in value. In its announcement, the team behind the Ondo Finance platform summarized: We’re excited to see BlackRock embracing securities tokenization with the launch of BUIDL, especially its broad cooperation with ecosystem participants. Not only does this further validate our original concept of a tokenized US Treasury fund, but it also bolsters our thesis that tokenization of traditional securities on public blockchains represents the next major step in the evolution of financial markets. At the time of writing, the native token of Ondo Finance, ONDO, is trading at $0.909, exhibiting a surge of over 4% within the past 24 hours. This positive momentum adds to its impressive price uptrend of 115% recorded over the past 30 days.  Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BlackRock, one of the largest asset managers globally, has witnessed notable success with its newly launched tokenized money-market fund, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-blackrock-yield-bearing-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BUIDL</a>. The fund, which records shared ownership on the Ethereum (ETH) blockchain, has attracted over $160 million in just one week since its debut. </p>
<h2>BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL Fund</h2>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-27/blackrock-tokenized-fund-draws-160-million-in-week-since-debut" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the BlackRock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund (BUIDL) primarily invests in cash, US Treasury bills, and repurchase agreements. The fund rewards its holders with a cryptocurrency, BUIDL, valued at $1 per token. </p>
<p>Shareholders can transfer these tokens to other validated addresses using digital wallets approved by Securitize, BlackRock&#8217;s partner for the investment vehicle. The tokenized fund serves several key use cases, including <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-launches-in-brazil-etf-market-secures-4-of-total-btc-supply/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">treasury management</a> for crypto companies, support for derivatives of Treasury bills, and acting as collateral for borrowing and trading, thus providing an alternative to stablecoins.</p>

<p>It is worth noting that Securitize Markets, an SEC-registered alternative trading system, plays a critical role in facilitating the transfer of tokens between market participants. </p>
<p>While the SEC has recently increased its scrutiny of Ethereum&#8217;s native token, ETH, Securitize CEO Carlos Domingo emphasizes that the investigations should be separate from the underlying blockchain infrastructure. Domingo also highlights the battle-tested nature of the public Ethereum blockchain, which provides a &#8220;robust foundation&#8221; for tokenization activities.</p>
<p>As previously <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/blackrock-crypto-surpass-traditional-currencies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">reported </a>by our sister website, Bitcoinist, BlackRock has emerged as an advocate for cryptocurrencies and tokenization within mainstream financial institutions. Chairman and CEO Larry Fink believes every financial asset will eventually be tokenized. </p>
<p>The company&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-etf-frenzy-blackrock-smashes-expectations-with-788-million-inflows-in-one-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">iShares Bitcoin Trust</a> (IBIT) has already attracted more than $13 billion in inflows since its launch as an exchange-traded fund (ETF) in January. With the BUIDL fund&#8217;s launch, BlackRock continues to demonstrate its willingness to explore new digital asset solutions.</p>
<h2>Ondo Finance To Transfer $95 Million In Assets To BlackRock</h2>
<p>Ondo Finance, a platform specializing in tokenized real-world assets (RWA), has <a href="https://blog.ondo.finance/introducing-instant-24-7-365-subscriptions-and-redemptions-shifting-ousg-funds-into-blackrocks-buidl/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">moved</a><a href="https://blog.ondo.finance/introducing-instant-24-7-365-subscriptions-and-redemptions-shifting-ousg-funds-into-blackrocks-buidl/" rel="nofollow"> </a>$95 million worth of assets to BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL fund. This strategic move enables Ondo Finance to facilitate instant settlements for its US Treasury-backed token, OUSG. </p>
<p>This makes Ondo Finance a major participant in the BUIDL ecosystem. According to on-chain researcher Tom Wan, it currently <a href="https://x.com/tomwanhh/status/1773048655122931715?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">holds</a> $15 million worth of BUIDL tokens, which, in addition to those above $95 million, will result in a substantial $110 million worth of BUIDL tokens.  </p>

<p>The researcher noted that this collaboration further strengthens the tokenized US Treasury market, with the potential to reach $1 billion in value. In its announcement, the team behind the Ondo Finance platform summarized:</p>
<blockquote><p>We’re excited to see BlackRock embracing securities tokenization with the launch of BUIDL, especially its broad cooperation with ecosystem participants. Not only does this further validate our original concept of a tokenized US Treasury fund, but it also bolsters our thesis that tokenization of traditional securities on public blockchains represents the next major step in the evolution of financial markets.</p></blockquote>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VYM37CCU/" alt="Blackrock" width="1814" height="858"/>
<p>At the time of writing, the native token of Ondo Finance, ONDO, is trading at $0.909, exhibiting a surge of over 4% within the past 24 hours. This positive momentum adds to its impressive price uptrend of 115% recorded over the past 30 days. </p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-7-8.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600072</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>$9.5 Billion In Bitcoin Options Poised To Expire This Friday: Market Turbulence Ahead?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/9-5-billion-in-bitcoin-options-poised-to-expire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin analyst]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deribit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[open interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This Friday, the spotlight is turned to Deribit, the leading crypto derivatives exchange, as it gears up for a notable event in its trading history. Particularly, the exchange is poised to witness the expiration of over $9.5 billion in Bitcoin options open interest. For context, Open interest refers to the total number of outstanding derivative contracts, such as futures or options, that have not been settled or closed. It represents the number of contracts market participants hold at the end of each trading day.  This surge in open interest recorded by Deribit reflects increased market participation and signals heightened liquidity, marking a notable milestone in the crypto derivatives landscape. Related Reading: Bitcoin’s ‘Next Leg Higher Has Started,’ Says Analyst: Reveals $100,000 Target On The Horizon Record-Breaking Open Interest Notably, this event is significant in two ways: It underscores the growing interest in Bitcoin as an asset class and highlights the increasing “sophistication” of the cryptocurrency market. This is because Open interest can also serve as a critical indicator of market health and trader sentiment.  As such, the record levels of open interest set to expire on Deribit suggest a “vibrant” trading environment, with more investors engaging in complex financial instruments like options. According to Deribit data, the exchange is set to host one of its largest option expiries ever, with $9.5 billion worth of Bitcoin options poised for expiry at the end of the month. This figure represents a substantial portion, approximately 40%, of the exchange&#8217;s total options open interest, which stands at $26.3 billion.  The magnitude of this expiry event eclipses previous months, with January and February end-of-month expiries totaling $3.74 billion and $3.72 billion, respectively. This trend indicates a large increase in market activity and investor engagement on the platform. Implications Of The Bitcoin Expiry The upcoming expiry has notable implications for the market, especially considering the current pricing dynamics of Bitcoin. With Bitcoin&#8217;s spot price hovering below $70,000, an estimated $3.9 billion of the open interest is expected to expire &#8220;in the money,&#8221; according to Deribit analysts, presenting profitable opportunities for holders of these options contracts.  The &#8220;max pain&#8221; price, which represents the strike price at which the highest number of options would expire worthless, thereby causing the maximum financial loss to option holders, is identified at $50,000. According to the analysts, this scenario suggests that a significant number of traders are positioned to benefit from the current market conditions, potentially leading to “increased buying activity” as these options are exercised. Additionally, Deribit analysts speculate that the high level of &#8220;in-the-money expiries&#8221; could exert upward pressure on Bitcoin&#8217;s price or amplify market volatility. They added that as traders &#8220;hedge their positions&#8221; or &#8220;speculate on future price movements,&#8221; the market may witness a flurry of activity, impacting Bitcoin&#8217;s price trajectory in the short term. Related Reading: Beyond Bitcoin ETFs: ‘There Are Other Players Controlling This Market’ – Says Analyst This comes at a time when Bitcoin has experienced a slight retracement from its recent all-time high above $73,000, with the price adjusting to approximately $68,946, at the time of writing Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This Friday, the spotlight is turned to Deribit, the leading crypto derivatives exchange, as it gears up for a notable event in its trading history. Particularly, the exchange is <a href="https://metrics.deribit.com/options/BTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">poised</a> to witness the expiration of over $9.5 billion in Bitcoin options open interest.</p>
<p>For context, Open interest refers to the total number of outstanding derivative contracts, such as futures or options, that have not been settled or closed. It represents the number of contracts market participants hold at the end of each trading day. </p>
<p>This surge in open interest recorded by Deribit reflects increased market participation and signals heightened liquidity, marking a notable milestone in the crypto derivatives landscape.</p>

<h2>Record-Breaking Open Interest</h2>
<p>Notably, this event is significant in two ways: It underscores the growing interest in Bitcoin as an asset class and highlights the increasing “sophistication” of the cryptocurrency market. This is because Open interest can also serve as a critical indicator of market health and trader sentiment. </p>
<p>As such, the record levels of open interest set to expire on Deribit suggest a “vibrant” <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/beyond-bitcoin-etfs-there-are-other-players/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">trading environment</a>, with more investors engaging in complex <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-might-be-poised-for-a-double-pump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">financial instruments</a> like options.</p>
<p>According to Deribit data, the exchange is set to host one of its largest option expiries ever, with $9.5 billion worth of Bitcoin options poised for expiry at the end of the month. This figure represents a substantial portion, approximately 40%, of the exchange&#8217;s total options open interest, which stands at $26.3 billion. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-600053 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C430" alt="Bitcoin Open Interest By Expiration. " width="860" height="430" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C430 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=360 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The magnitude of this expiry event eclipses previous months, with January and February end-of-month expiries totaling $3.74 billion and $3.72 billion, respectively. This trend indicates a large increase in market activity and investor engagement on the platform.</p>
<h2>Implications Of The Bitcoin Expiry</h2>
<p>The upcoming expiry has notable implications for the market, especially considering the current pricing dynamics of Bitcoin. </p>
<p>With Bitcoin&#8217;s <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/analyst-warns-of-bitcoin-pre-halving-retrace-echoing-troubling-2020-trend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">spot price</a> hovering below $70,000, an estimated $3.9 billion of the open interest is expected to expire &#8220;in the money,&#8221; according to Deribit <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/285041/bitcoin-options-open-interest-for-march-expiry-on-deribit-hits-record-levels" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysts</a>, presenting profitable opportunities for holders of these options contracts. </p>
<p>The &#8220;max pain&#8221; price, which represents the strike price at which the highest number of options would expire worthless, thereby causing the maximum financial loss to option holders, is identified at $50,000.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-600054 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C430" alt="Bitcoin Open Interest by Strike Price. " width="860" height="430" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=2400 2400w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C430 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=360 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/deribit-metrics-2.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>According to the analysts, this scenario suggests that a significant number of traders are positioned to benefit from the current market conditions, potentially leading to “increased buying activity” as these options are exercised.</p>
<p>Additionally, Deribit analysts speculate that the high level of &#8220;in-the-money expiries&#8221; could exert upward pressure on Bitcoin&#8217;s price or amplify market volatility. They added that as traders &#8220;hedge their positions&#8221; or &#8220;speculate on future price movements,&#8221; the market may witness a flurry of activity, impacting Bitcoin&#8217;s<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-next-leg-higher-has-started-says-analyst/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> price trajectory</a> in the short term.</p>

<p>This comes at a time when Bitcoin has experienced a slight retracement from its recent all-time high above $73,000, with the price adjusting to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-rockets-past-69000-over-60k-traders-caught/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">approximately $68,946,</a> at the time of writing</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jYFoDjMa/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1496"/>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/photo-1621501011941-c8ee93618c9a.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600051</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking Records: Mantle (MNT) Soars 40% In One Day To New All-Time Highs, Next Target Revealed</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/breaking-records-mantle-mnt-soars-40-in-one-day-to-new-all-time-highs-next-target-revealed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mantle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mantle (MNT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mantle news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mantle price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MNT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MNTUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MNTUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=600058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Layer 2 (L2) blockchain Mantle (MNT) has demonstrated remarkable performance, surpassing most of the top 100 cryptocurrencies in the market. The token has surged by 40% in the past 24 hours, reaching a new all-time high (ATH) of $1.49.  Mantle Network&#8217;s Layer 2 Solution Mantle Network operates as an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)-compatible L2 scaling solution to provide a deeper understanding of the protocol. It leverages Optimistic rollups to enable fast and cost-effective transactions.  The unique aspect of Mantle lies in its modular design, which combines Optimistic rollups with a separate data availability layer. Unlike traditional blockchains, Mantle&#8217;s approach involves handling the four key blockchain functions on different layers. Related Reading: Here’s Why The Cardano Price Is Struggling Below $0.7 Mantle&#8217;s transaction execution function occurs on its EVM-compatible execution settlement layer. Blocks are generated on the L2 execution layer by Mantle&#8217;s sequencer, which then submits state root data to the Ethereum mainnet.  This architecture significantly reduces transaction costs compared to the base layer and improves network efficiency by separating the layers. Additionally, the implementation of Optimistic rollups minimizes the overall load on nodes. MNT Surges As Staking Launches One of the potential catalysts behind the recent surge in MNT can be attributed to the introduction of MNT staking, as highlighted by crypto researcher Alex Wacy.  According to Wacy, the Mantle Rewards Station plays a key role in this staking initiative, offering rewards to MNT stakers from the Mantle Ecosystem. By participating in staking, users contribute to the network&#8217;s security and operations while also being incentivized through these rewards. The staking process begins with the Ethena event, where users receive mShards tokens. These tokens have value within the Mantle decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem, allowing users to perform various decentralized finance activities within the network. These activities may include trading, investing, or interacting with various DeFi protocols and applications built on top of Mantle. In particular, mShards can be traded within the Mantle decentralized application (dApp) ecosystem, allowing users to take advantage of potential market growth options. The ability to trade these tokens increases liquidity and fosters an active ecosystem within Mantle. In addition, the researcher notes that mShard token holders will soon be able to redeem for ENA, another token associated with the Mantle Ecosystem. This redemption process adds utility and value to mShards, further increasing their appeal to token holders. The issuance of Ethena shards for Epoch 2 will end on April 1, indicating a limited-time opportunity for users to acquire these shards through staking, which may have further increased interest in the blockchain ahead of the deadline from investors looking to capitalize on this opportunity.  Bullish Prospects Examining the figures, MNT has experienced a surge in trading volume, reaching $647,118,249 in the past 24 hours, signifying a substantial 141.40% increase compared to the previous day.  Related Reading: Will Bitcoin Break $74,000 Driven By TradFi FOMO? The market capitalization of the MNT token stands at $4,157,261,742, propelling it to the 33rd position on CoinGecko&#8217;s rankings. Over the past 7 days, Mantle (MNT) has outperformed the global cryptocurrency market, which has seen a 2.30% increase, and similar cryptocurrencies within the Ethereum ecosystem have risen by 12.70%. The MNT token has retraced to the $1.27 level, marking a 2% decline in price over the past hour. Despite the temporary setback, the token&#8217;s strong momentum suggests potential trading risks and opportunities. It is worth noting that the next identified support line for the token is at the $1.080 level. If this support level fails to hold, the token&#8217;s price could drop further, potentially reaching the $1 mark. The next significant resistance level would be at $0.94.  However, if the bullish momentum continues throughout the week, the token may target the $1.60 and $1.68 levels before potentially surging towards the $2 mark. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Layer 2 (L2) blockchain Mantle (MNT) has demonstrated remarkable performance, surpassing most of the top 100 cryptocurrencies in the market. The token has surged by 40% in the past 24 hours, reaching a new all-time high (ATH) of $1.49. </p>
<h2>Mantle Network&#8217;s Layer 2 Solution</h2>
<p>Mantle Network operates as an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)-compatible L2 scaling solution to provide a deeper understanding of the protocol. It leverages Optimistic rollups to enable fast and cost-effective transactions. </p>
<p>The unique aspect of Mantle lies in its modular design, which combines Optimistic rollups with a separate data availability layer. Unlike traditional blockchains, Mantle&#8217;s approach involves handling the four key blockchain functions on different layers.</p>

<p>Mantle&#8217;s transaction execution function occurs on its EVM-compatible execution <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/100000-bitcoin-whale-accumulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">settlement layer</a>. Blocks are generated on the L2 execution layer by Mantle&#8217;s sequencer, which then submits state root data to the Ethereum mainnet. </p>
<p>This architecture significantly reduces transaction costs compared to the base layer and improves network efficiency by separating the layers. Additionally, the implementation of Optimistic rollups minimizes the overall load on nodes.</p>
<h2>MNT Surges As Staking Launches</h2>
<p>One of the potential catalysts behind the recent surge in MNT can be attributed to the introduction of MNT staking, as highlighted by crypto researcher Alex Wacy. </p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/wacy_time1/status/1773011560241184841?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">According </a>to Wacy, the Mantle Rewards Station plays a key role in this staking initiative, offering rewards to MNT stakers from the Mantle Ecosystem. By participating in staking, users contribute to the network&#8217;s security and operations while also being incentivized through these rewards.</p>
<p>The staking process begins with the Ethena event, where users receive mShards tokens. These tokens have value within the Mantle decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem, allowing users to perform various decentralized finance activities within the network. These activities may include trading, investing, or interacting with various<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ai-tokens-fetch-ai-agix-ocean-merger-surge-double-digits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> DeFi protocols</a> and applications built on top of Mantle.</p>
<p>In particular, mShards can be traded within the Mantle decentralized application (dApp) ecosystem, allowing users to take advantage of potential market growth options. The ability to trade these tokens increases liquidity and fosters an active ecosystem within Mantle.</p>
<p>In addition, the researcher notes that mShard token holders will soon be able to redeem for ENA, another token associated with the Mantle Ecosystem. This redemption process adds utility and value to mShards, further increasing their appeal to token holders.</p>
<p>The issuance of Ethena shards for Epoch 2 will end on April 1, indicating a limited-time opportunity for users to acquire these shards through <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/litecoin/litecoin-etf-rumors-fuel-10-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">staking</a>, which may have further increased interest in the blockchain ahead of the deadline from investors looking to capitalize on this opportunity. </p>
Bullish Prospects
<p>Examining the figures, MNT has experienced a surge in trading volume, reaching $647,118,249 in the past 24 hours, signifying a substantial 141.40% increase compared to the previous day. </p>

<p>The market capitalization of the MNT token stands at $4,157,261,742, propelling it to the 33rd position on CoinGecko&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/mantle" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">rankings</a>. Over the past 7 days, Mantle (MNT) has outperformed the global cryptocurrency market, which has seen a 2.30% increase, and similar cryptocurrencies within the Ethereum ecosystem have risen by 12.70%.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fWOfaEdh/" alt="Mantle" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>The MNT token has retraced to the $1.27 level, marking a 2% decline in price over the past hour. Despite the temporary setback, the token&#8217;s strong momentum suggests potential trading risks and opportunities. It is worth noting that the next identified <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-price-resume-upside-610/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">support </a>line for the token is at the $1.080 level.</p>
<p>If this support level fails to hold, the token&#8217;s price could drop further, potentially reaching the $1 mark. The next significant resistance level would be at $0.94. </p>
<p>However, if the bullish momentum continues throughout the week, the token may target the $1.60 and $1.68 levels before potentially surging towards the $2 mark.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-7-7.jpg?fit=421%2C260" width="421" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">600058</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
