<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:49:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin &#8216;Real Pump&#8217; Nears New All-Time Highs, Analyst Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-real-pump-nears-new-all-time-highs-analyst-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the ever-enigmatic digital currency, has analysts locked in a heated debate about its 2024 price trajectory. Will it soar to new heights, fueled by institutional adoption and mainstream acceptance, or will it face a reality check and revisit recent lows? Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: Can FTM Hit $2 After 20% Price Spike? Bullish Vs. Bearish Perspectives On Bitcoin The optimists, led by the prominent crypto analyst Cryptoyoddha, paint a picture of a bullish future. They point to a meticulously tracked historical chart showcasing the cyclical price movements of Bitcoin. Each cycle, Cryptoyoddha argues, follows a similar pattern: a period of accumulation followed by a parabolic surge. This analysis paves the way for the highly anticipated &#8220;Cycle IV,&#8221; which could propel Bitcoin beyond its current all-time high of $73,750 and potentially reach a staggering $150,000 or even higher. #Bitcoin The real pump will start after the halving next month. pic.twitter.com/eV5FWkzkxX — Yoddha (@CryptoYoddha) March 23, 2024 But what&#8217;s driving this bullish sentiment? Cryptoyoddha cites several factors: a surge in institutional investment, a shift towards clearer regulations for cryptocurrencies, and a growing public embrace of digital assets. These trends, coupled with the historical pattern of each cycle surpassing the previous one, paint a compelling picture for Bitcoin bulls. However, not everyone is buying into the euphoria. Michaël van de Poppe, a renowned cryptocurrency trader, injects a dose of caution with his technical analysis. Studying charts that map Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements, van de Poppe detects a potentially bearish pattern following the recent price dip. I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if #Bitcoin eventually takes the liquidity below the lows. Consolidation, low volatility. pic.twitter.com/CincO9DFjD — Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) March 23, 2024 He interprets the ongoing period of consolidation – where the price fluctuates within a narrow range – as a potential precursor to a further price drop. This drop, he suggests, could see Bitcoin revisit and even break below its recent lows. Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis focuses on the presence of &#8220;support&#8221; and &#8220;resistance&#8221; levels on his charts. These levels represent price points where historical buying and selling activity has been concentrated. If Bitcoin falls below a key support level, it could trigger a wave of panic selling, pushing the price further down. Bitcoin is now trading at $67.051. Chart: TradingView Volatility And Uncertainty The contrasting viewpoints highlight the inherent volatility of the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin&#8217;s price is constantly influenced by a complex web of factors, including unforeseen regulatory decisions, security breaches, and broader economic trends. While historical cycles can offer valuable insights, they are not crystal balls that guarantee future performance. Investors also need to be wary of placing blind faith in technical analysis. The market is not a purely mechanical system, and unpredictable events can disrupt even the most meticulously drawn charts. Related Reading: Shiba Inu Takes Over The Internet: Google Searches Climb As Global Interest Surges Despite the differing predictions, both analysts acknowledge the likelihood of significant price movement in the coming months. Cryptoyoddha&#8217;s bullish outlook hinges on a fundamental shift in the cryptocurrency landscape, while van de Poppe&#8217;s technical analysis suggests a potential short-term price correction. Ultimately, the fate of Bitcoin&#8217;s price in 2024 remains a mystery. The upcoming Bitcoin halving in April – an event that cuts the number of new Bitcoins entering circulation and has historically coincided with price increases – adds another layer of intrigue. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:263">Bitcoin, the ever-enigmatic digital currency, has analysts locked in a heated debate about its 2024 price trajectory. Will it soar to new heights, fueled by institutional adoption and mainstream acceptance, or will it face a reality check and revisit recent lows?</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:516"><strong>Bullish Vs. Bearish Perspectives On Bitcoin</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:516">The optimists, led by the prominent crypto analyst Cryptoyoddha, paint a picture of a bullish future. They point to a meticulously tracked historical chart showcasing the cyclical price movements of <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bitcoin.</a></p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:516">Each cycle, Cryptoyoddha argues, follows a similar pattern: a period of accumulation followed by a parabolic surge. This analysis paves the way for the highly anticipated &#8220;Cycle IV,&#8221; which could propel Bitcoin beyond its current all-time high of $73,750 and potentially reach a staggering $150,000 or even higher.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a></p>
<p>The real pump will start after the halving next month. <a href="https://t.co/eV5FWkzkxX" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/eV5FWkzkxX</a></p>
<p>— Yoddha (@CryptoYoddha) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoYoddha/status/1771430384401842522?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:360">But what&#8217;s driving this bullish sentiment? Cryptoyoddha cites several factors: a surge in institutional investment, a shift towards clearer regulations for cryptocurrencies, and a growing public embrace of digital assets. These trends, coupled with the historical pattern of each cycle surpassing the previous one, paint a compelling picture for Bitcoin bulls.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:537">However, not everyone is buying into the euphoria. Michaël van de Poppe, a renowned cryptocurrency trader, injects a dose of caution with his technical analysis. Studying charts that map Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements, van de Poppe detects a potentially bearish pattern following the recent price dip.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> eventually takes the liquidity below the lows.</p>
<p>Consolidation, low volatility. <a href="https://t.co/CincO9DFjD" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/CincO9DFjD</a></p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1771460957992100191?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:537">He interprets the ongoing period of consolidation – where the price fluctuates within a narrow range – as a potential precursor to a further price drop. This drop, he suggests, could see Bitcoin revisit and even break below its recent lows.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:321">Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis focuses on the presence of &#8220;support&#8221; and &#8220;resistance&#8221; levels on his charts. These levels represent price points where historical buying and selling activity has been concentrated. If Bitcoin falls below a key support level, it could trigger a wave of panic selling, pushing the price further down.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:321"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/JV1wrqsf/" width="1835" height="883" loading="lazy"/></p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="13:1-13:366"><strong>Volatility And Uncertainty</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:366">The contrasting viewpoints highlight the inherent volatility of the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin&#8217;s price is constantly influenced by a complex web of factors, including unforeseen regulatory decisions, security breaches, and broader economic trends. While historical cycles can offer valuable insights, they are not crystal balls that guarantee future performance.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:202">Investors also need to be wary of placing blind faith in technical analysis. The market is not a purely mechanical system, and unpredictable events can disrupt even the most meticulously drawn charts.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:311">Despite the differing predictions, both analysts acknowledge the likelihood of significant price movement in the coming months. Cryptoyoddha&#8217;s bullish outlook hinges on a fundamental shift in the cryptocurrency landscape, while van de Poppe&#8217;s technical analysis suggests a potential short-term price correction.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:498">Ultimately, the fate of Bitcoin&#8217;s price in 2024 remains a mystery. The upcoming Bitcoin halving in April – an event that cuts the number of new Bitcoins entering circulation and has historically coincided with price increases – adds another layer of intrigue.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:498"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_a55499.jpg?fit=460%2C345" width="460" height="345" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599499</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Macro/Crypto Summer? Don&#8217;t Miss Out, Says Expert</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/what-is-macro-crypto-summer-dont-miss-out-says-expert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liquidity Cycle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a thread on X (formerly Twitter), Raoul Pal, a renowned trading guru and the founder/CEO of Global Macro Investor and Real Vision, has illuminated the crypto community about the advent of what he terms as the &#8220;Macro/Crypto Summer.&#8221; This period, according to Pal, is not just a fleeting season but a significant phase in the financial and cryptocurrency markets, deeply rooted in the cyclical nature of the global economy. Why The Macro/Crypto Summer Matters Pal elaborates on the concept of the &#8220;Macro Summer,&#8221; explaining it as a pivotal phase in &#8220;The Everything Code&#8221; cycle, closely following the Financial Conditions Index, which historically precedes the cycle by approximately ten months. The ISM (Institute for Supply Management) index, a key indicator of economic health, often bottoms out during this period, marking the start of GDP growth. Related Reading: Buy High, Sell Low: FOMO Made This Crypto Trader Lose 6,039 SOL Pal&#8217;s thesis draws attention to the &#8220;near-perfect 3 1/2 year cyclicality&#8221; in the ISM business cycle, propelled by liquidity dynamics and the debt refinancing cycle at its core. He underscores the significance of liquidity: &#8220;And that is driven by liquidity, which bottomed at the end of 2022&#8230; macro summer and fall are all about liquidity rising and is a core part of The Everything Code thesis.&#8221; This influx of liquidity is crucial for tech stocks, which historically thrive during these phases. Yet, it&#8217;s Bitcoin and, more broadly, the cryptocurrency market that exhibit the most dramatic responses. Pal presents staggering growth figures from past Macro Summer and Fall seasons to underscore his point: Bitcoin: Saw increases of &#8220;2012/2013: +146x, 2016/2017: +30x, 2020/2021: +8x&#8230;&#8221; Ethereum: As an altcoin during the 2016/2017 and 2020/2021 cycles, it achieved &#8220;2016/2017: +1,770x, 2020/2021: +41x.&#8221; Altcoins (excluding ETH): Witnessed an aggregate market cap rise of &#8220;+24x&#8221; in the last cycle. “Wild! When we just look at Altcoins ex-ETH (we only have shorter data for the last cycle), the entire market cap rose +24x! And that includes thousands of worthless tokens that didn’t rise, so I’m not just cherry-picking winners here,” Pal remarked. DOGE, a popular meme coin, is mentioned by the expert as another prime example of the &#8220;power of Crypto Summer and Fall,&#8221; with its value experiencing significant multipliers &#8211; &#8220;2016/2017: +136x, 2020/2021: +370x” &#8211; in the aforementioned cycles. These figures underline the significant influence of macroeconomic cycles on crypto valuations, with Pal pointing out the alignment of these cycles with Bitcoin&#8217;s halving events. &#8220;Crypto summer has started and fully develops post-halving,&#8221; he states, highlighting the interconnectedness of these cycles with the broader financial landscape. Related Reading: Crypto Expert Reveals The Possibility Of Bitcoin Reaching $500,000 Notably, Pal&#8217;s analysis doesn&#8217;t stop at the past; it looks forward, suggesting that liquidity is expected to rise all the way into the end of 2025. This anticipation is rooted in a complex interplay of global financial mechanisms, including the potential for increased US money printing in response to a massive ramp-up in interest payments and changes in Fed Net Liquidity and the Treasury General Account (TGA). “Will the US join the summer party? [&#8230;] I know it seems impossible now, but the US is on the verge of a massive ramp-up in interest payments. [&#8230;] at some point – the balance sheet will stop shrinking, which is enough to unleash liquidity into the system. [&#8230;] I cannot see how they don’t massively expand liquidity, one way or another. Meanwhile, Pal predicts that it won’t be just the US injecting liquidity into the financial systems in the coming months. “I&#8217;ve no idea whether it&#8217;s China, the EU, Japan or the US that drives this or maybe a bit of all. Time will tell,” he remarked. Pal attributes his investment strategies, especially in tech and crypto, to the insights gained from The Everything Code. This approach has prepared him for the unfolding Macro Summer, with a keen eye on the altcoin market and the so-called &#8220;Banana Zone.&#8221; He concludes: But the bigger game is yet to be played out as Alt season arrives and we fully enter the Banana Zone. The Banana Zone cometh, and it is a huge wealth-generating machine. Patience will be rewarded. In the meantime, don&#8217;t fuck this up. #DFTU At press time, BTC traded at $67,003. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/RaoulGMI/status/1772039605501481191" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">thread</a> on X (formerly Twitter), Raoul Pal, a renowned trading guru and the founder/CEO of Global Macro Investor and Real Vision, has illuminated the crypto community about the advent of what he terms as the &#8220;Macro/Crypto Summer.&#8221; This period, according to Pal, is not just a fleeting season but a significant phase in the financial and cryptocurrency markets, deeply rooted in the cyclical nature of the global economy.</p>
<h2>Why The Macro/Crypto Summer Matters</h2>
<p>Pal elaborates on the concept of the &#8220;Macro Summer,&#8221; explaining it as a pivotal phase in &#8220;The Everything Code&#8221; cycle, closely following the Financial Conditions Index, which historically precedes the cycle by approximately ten months. The ISM (Institute for Supply Management) index, a key indicator of economic health, often bottoms out during this period, marking the start of GDP growth.</p>

<p>Pal&#8217;s thesis draws attention to the &#8220;near-perfect <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/where-are-we-in-this-bitcoin-cycle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">3 1/2 year cyclicality</a>&#8221; in the ISM business cycle, propelled by liquidity dynamics and the debt refinancing cycle at its core. He underscores the significance of liquidity: &#8220;And that is driven by liquidity, which bottomed at the end of 2022&#8230; macro summer and fall are all about liquidity rising and is a core part of The Everything Code thesis.&#8221;</p>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-599486 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058" alt="Macro crypto summer " width="1770" height="1058" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=1770 1770w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeI2IWXoAAWFZg.jpg?resize=1770%2C1058?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>This<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-to-over-200000-in-less-than-5-months/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> influx of liquidity</a> is crucial for tech stocks, which historically thrive during these phases. Yet, it&#8217;s Bitcoin and, more broadly, the cryptocurrency market that exhibit the most dramatic responses. Pal presents staggering growth figures from past Macro Summer and Fall seasons to underscore his point:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Bitcoin:</strong> Saw increases of &#8220;2012/2013: +146x, 2016/2017: +30x, 2020/2021: +8x&#8230;&#8221;</li>
<li><strong>Ethereum:</strong> As an altcoin during the 2016/2017 and 2020/2021 cycles, it achieved &#8220;2016/2017: +1,770x, 2020/2021: +41x.&#8221;</li>
<li><strong>Altcoins (excluding ETH):</strong> Witnessed an aggregate market cap rise of &#8220;+24x&#8221; in the last cycle.</li>
</ul>
<img decoding="async" class="wp-image-599487 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082" alt="Bitcoin summer" width="1518" height="1082" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=1518 1518w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=120 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=350 350w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJJzBWsAIQDM5-1.jpg?resize=1518%2C1082?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>“Wild! When we just look at Altcoins ex-ETH (we only have shorter data for the last cycle), the entire market cap rose +24x! And that includes thousands of worthless tokens that didn’t rise, so I’m not just cherry-picking winners here,” Pal remarked.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-599491 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823" alt="Altcoin summer" width="1413" height="823" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823?w=1413 1413w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeJnFdWoAA6z0C-1.jpg?resize=1413%2C823?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>DOGE, a popular meme coin, is mentioned by the expert as another prime example of the &#8220;power of Crypto Summer and Fall,&#8221; with its value experiencing significant multipliers &#8211; &#8220;2016/2017: +136x, 2020/2021: +370x” &#8211; in the aforementioned cycles.</p>
<p>These figures underline the significant influence of macroeconomic cycles on crypto valuations, with Pal pointing out the alignment of these cycles with <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/when-is-the-next-btc-halving-date-bitcoin-halving-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin&#8217;s halving events</a>. &#8220;Crypto summer has started and fully develops post-halving,&#8221; he states, highlighting the interconnectedness of these cycles with the broader financial landscape.</p>

<p>Notably, Pal&#8217;s analysis doesn&#8217;t stop at the past; it looks forward, suggesting that liquidity is expected to rise all the way into the end of 2025. This anticipation is rooted in a complex interplay of global financial mechanisms, including the potential for increased US money printing in response to a massive ramp-up in interest payments and changes in Fed Net Liquidity and the Treasury General Account (TGA).</p>
<p>“Will the US join the summer party? [&#8230;] I know it seems impossible now, but the US is on the verge of a massive ramp-up in interest payments. [&#8230;] at some point – the balance sheet will stop shrinking, which is enough to unleash liquidity into the system. [&#8230;] I cannot see how they don’t massively expand liquidity, one way or another.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Pal predicts that it won’t be just the US injecting liquidity into the financial systems in the coming months. “I&#8217;ve no idea whether it&#8217;s China, the EU, Japan or the US that drives this or maybe a bit of all. Time will tell,” he remarked.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-599488 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212" alt="GMI total liquidity index" width="1552" height="1212" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=1552 1552w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJeKjx2XsAA6Pgj-1.jpg?resize=1552%2C1212?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Pal attributes his investment strategies, especially in tech and crypto, to the insights gained from The Everything Code. This approach has prepared him for the unfolding Macro Summer, with a keen eye on the altcoin market and the so-called &#8220;Banana Zone.&#8221; He concludes:</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>But the bigger game is yet to be played out as Alt season arrives and we fully enter the Banana Zone. The Banana Zone cometh, and it is a huge wealth-generating machine. Patience will be rewarded. In the meantime, don&#8217;t fuck this up. #DFTU</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, BTC traded at $67,003.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-599489 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673" alt="Bitcoin price" width="3628" height="1673" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_09-33-25.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_545337184.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599478</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Takes Over The Internet: Google Searches Climb As Global Interest Surges</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-takes-over-the-internet-google-searches-climb-as-global-interest-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599456</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), the self-proclaimed &#8220;Dogecoin Killer,&#8221; is back in the spotlight with a surge in both search interest and token price. Google Trends data reveals a global increase in searches for &#8220;Shiba Inu&#8221; and related queries, indicating renewed investor optimism for the meme coin. Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: Can FTM Hit $2 After 20% Price Spike? Shiba Inu Surge Sparks Enthusiasm This increase comes after a quiet period for the memecoin. However, the past month has been nothing short of phenomenal. Search popularity reached a seven-day peak of 100 on March 16th, though it has settled at a still-healthy 48 – significantly higher than January&#8217;s levels. Phrases like &#8220;Why is Shiba Inu going up?&#8221; and &#8220;Shiba Inu All-Time High&#8221; have also seen a significant uptick, reflecting investor curiosity and potential buying interest. While the interest is global, specific regions are leading the charge. Pakistan, the Netherlands, Slovenia, Canada, and Nigeria have emerged as the top search originators for SHIB in the past week. This geographically diverse interest suggests a broad-based appeal for the meme coin. Source: Google Trends This renewed interest coincides with a remarkable price rally. SHIB&#8217;s value has skyrocketed over 180% in the past month, reaching a two-year high of $0.000045. This bullish run fueled speculation of a retest of its all-time high above $0.000088. However, the market has since witnessed a correction, bringing SHIB&#8217;s price down slightly. Despite the correction, the enthusiasm within the Shiba Inu community remains high. The long-term goal of reaching $0.01 per SHIB token continues to be a hot topic, although analysts caution it might take several years to materialize. Bitcoin is now trading at $66.780. Chart: TradingView Shibarium And Market Recovery To achieve this ambitious target, the developers are focusing on Shibarium, the project&#8217;s Layer-2 scaling solution. Shibarium aims to become a thriving smart contract hub, potentially attracting more users and driving up demand for SHIB. Experts believe several factors are contributing to the current Shiba Inu frenzy. The broader cryptocurrency market has shown signs of recovery after a recent slump, potentially boosting investor confidence in meme coins like SHIB. Additionally, ongoing developments within the Shiba Inu ecosystem, such as Shibarium and the burning initiatives to reduce the overall token supply, might be fueling investor optimism. Related Reading: Eyes On Toncoin: Speculation Rises After 40% Weekly Surge – What Comes Next? Whether SHIB can maintain its current momentum and reach its long-term price goals remains to be seen. However, the recent surge in search interest and price rally is a clear indication that the &#8220;Dogecoin Killer&#8221; is back in the game, attempting to capture the hearts (and wallets) of memecoin enthusiasts worldwide. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:286">Shiba Inu (SHIB), the self-proclaimed &#8220;Dogecoin Killer,&#8221; is back in the spotlight with a surge in both search interest and token price. <a href="https://trends.google.com/trends/explore?date=now%207-d&amp;q=shiba%20inu&amp;hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Google Trends data</a> reveals a global increase in searches for &#8220;Shiba Inu&#8221; and related queries, indicating renewed investor optimism for the meme coin.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:432"><strong>Shiba Inu Surge Sparks Enthusiasm</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:432">This increase comes after a quiet period for <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">the memecoin.</a> However, the past month has been nothing short of phenomenal. Search popularity reached a seven-day peak of 100 on March 16th, though it has settled at a still-healthy 48 – significantly higher than January&#8217;s levels. Phrases like &#8220;Why is Shiba Inu going up?&#8221; and &#8220;Shiba Inu All-Time High&#8221; have also seen a significant uptick, reflecting investor curiosity and potential buying interest.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:283">While the interest is global, specific regions are leading the charge. Pakistan, the Netherlands, Slovenia, Canada, and Nigeria have emerged as the top search originators for SHIB in the past week. This geographically diverse interest suggests a broad-based appeal for the meme coin.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:283"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-599457" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431" alt="" width="1024" height="431" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431?w=1161 1161w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31f050.png?resize=1024%2C431?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:338">This renewed interest coincides with a remarkable price rally. SHIB&#8217;s value has skyrocketed over 180% in the past month, reaching a two-year high of $0.000045. This bullish run fueled speculation of a retest of its all-time high above $0.000088. However, the market has since witnessed a correction, bringing SHIB&#8217;s price down slightly.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:472">Despite the correction, the enthusiasm within the Shiba Inu community remains high. The long-term goal of reaching $0.01 per SHIB token continues to be a hot topic, although analysts caution it might take several years to materialize.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:472"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dKY3gBRm/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="11:1-11:472"><strong>Shibarium And Market Recovery</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:472">To achieve this ambitious target, the developers are focusing on Shibarium, the project&#8217;s Layer-2 scaling solution. Shibarium aims to become a thriving smart contract hub, potentially attracting more users and driving up demand for SHIB.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:416">Experts believe several factors are contributing to the current Shiba Inu frenzy. The broader cryptocurrency market has shown signs of recovery after a recent slump, potentially boosting investor confidence in meme coins like SHIB.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:416">Additionally, ongoing developments within the Shiba Inu ecosystem, such as Shibarium and the burning initiatives to reduce the overall token supply, might be fueling investor optimism.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:317">Whether SHIB can maintain its current momentum and reach its long-term price goals remains to be seen. However, the recent surge in search interest and price rally is a clear indication that the &#8220;Dogecoin Killer&#8221; is back in the game, attempting to capture the hearts (and wallets) of memecoin enthusiasts worldwide.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:317"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_e387f6.jpg?fit=460%2C285" width="460" height="285" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599456</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Could Regain Strength If It Clears This Key Hurdle</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-strength-3580/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 04:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethbtc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599447</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ethereum price is attempting a fresh increase wave above the $3,400 zone. ETH must clear the $3,580 resistance to continue higher in the near term. Ethereum is holding gains above the $3,250 support zone. The price is trading above $3,400 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $3,400 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken). The pair could continue to rise if it settles above the $3,500 resistance zone. Ethereum Price Eyes Fresh Increase Ethereum price remained stable above the $3,250 support zone. ETH formed a base and started a fresh increase above the $3,350 resistance level, like Bitcoin. ETH climbed above the $3,400 resistance zone. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $3,587 swing high to the $3,250 low. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $3,400 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD. Ethereum is now trading above $3,400 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $3,500 level. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $3,587 swing high to the $3,250 low. Source: ETHUSD on TradingView.com The first major resistance is near the $3,550 level. The next key resistance sits at $3,580, above which the price might gain bullish momentum. In the stated case, Ether could rally toward the $3,720 level. If there is a move above the $3,720 resistance, Ethereum could even climb toward the $3,880 resistance. Any more gains might call for a test of $4,000. Another Decline In ETH? If Ethereum fails to clear the $3,500 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $3,400 level. The first major support is near the $3,250 zone. The next key support could be the $3,060 zone. A clear move below the $3,060 support might send the price toward $3,000. Any more losses might send the price toward the $2,880 level. Technical Indicators Hourly MACD – The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI &#8211; The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level. Major Support Level – $3,400 Major Resistance Level – $3,580]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Ethereum price is attempting a fresh increase wave above the $3,400 zone. ETH must clear the $3,580 resistance to continue higher in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ethereum is holding gains above the $3,250 support zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading above $3,400 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average.</li>
<li>There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $3,400 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD (data feed via Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair could continue to rise if it settles above the $3,500 resistance zone.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ethereum Price Eyes Fresh Increase</h2>
<p>Ethereum price remained stable above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-signals-uptrend-3580/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$3,250 support zone</a>. ETH formed a base and started a fresh increase above the $3,350 resistance level, like <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-upside-break-68k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>ETH climbed above the $3,400 resistance zone. There was a move above the 50% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $3,587 swing high to the $3,250 low. There was a break above a key bearish trend line with resistance at $3,400 on the hourly chart of ETH/USD.</p>
<p>Ethereum is now trading above $3,400 and the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average. On the upside, immediate resistance is near the $3,500 level. It is near the 76.4% Fib retracement level of the downward move from the $3,587 swing high to the $3,250 low.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-599449" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449" alt="Ethereum Price" width="1024" height="449" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1950 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Ethereum_a53be6.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">ETHUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>The first major resistance is near the $3,550 level. The next key resistance sits at $3,580, above which the price might gain bullish momentum. In the stated case, Ether could rally toward the $3,720 level. If there is a move above the $3,720 resistance, Ethereum could even climb toward the $3,880 resistance. Any more gains might call for a test of $4,000.</p>
<h2>Another Decline In ETH?</h2>
<p>If Ethereum fails to clear the $3,500 resistance, it could start another decline. Initial support on the downside is near the $3,400 level.</p>
<p>The first major support is near the $3,250 zone. The next key support could be the $3,060 zone. A clear move below the $3,060 support might send the price toward $3,000. Any more losses might send the price toward the $2,880 level.</p>
<p>Technical Indicators</p>
<p>Hourly MACD<strong> – </strong>The MACD for ETH/USD is gaining momentum in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI<strong> &#8211; </strong>The RSI for ETH/USD is now above the 50 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Level – $3,400</p>
<p>Major Resistance Level – $3,580</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/iStock-935533896.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599447</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Aims Key Upside Break As Dips Turn Attractive</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-upside-break-68k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aayush Jindal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 03:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xbtusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599443</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin price is again attempting an upside break above $68,000 resistance zone. BTC could rally if it clears $67,500 and $68,000 in the near term. Bitcoin price started a decent increase above the $65,000 zone. The price is trading below $65,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is a key bullish trend line forming with support at $65,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken). The pair must clear the $68,000 resistance zone to start a fresh rally. Bitcoin Price Turns Green Bitcoin price remained supported above the $64,000 resistance zone. BTC climbed higher above the $66,500 and $66,000 resistance levels. However, the bears were active near the $67,500 and $68,000 levels. A high was formed near $67,614 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $62,614 swing low to the $67,614 high. Bitcoin is now trading above $65,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average. There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support at $65,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $67,500 level. The first major resistance could be $68,000. Source: BTCUSD on TradingView.com If there is a clear move above the $68,000 resistance zone, the price could continue to gain strength. In the stated case, the price could even clear the $69,0200 resistance zone in the near term. The next key resistance sits at $70,000. Another Decline In BTC? If Bitcoin fails to rise above the $68,000 resistance zone, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $66,000 level and the trend line. The first major support is $65,200 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $62,614 swing low to the $67,614 high. The next support sits at $63,800. If there is a close below $63,800, the price could start a drop toward the $61,200 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $60,500 support zone in the near term. Technical indicators: Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone. Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 60 level. Major Support Levels – $65,900, followed by $63,800. Major Resistance Levels – $67,500, $68,000, and $69,200.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Bitcoin price is again attempting an upside break above $68,000 resistance zone. BTC could rally if it clears $67,500 and $68,000 in the near term.</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin price started a decent increase above the $65,000 zone.</li>
<li>The price is trading below $65,000 and the 100 hourly Simple moving average.</li>
<li>There is a key bullish trend line forming with support at $65,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair (data feed from Kraken).</li>
<li>The pair must clear the $68,000 resistance zone to start a fresh rally.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Turns Green</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price remained supported above the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-68k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">$64,000 resistance zone</a>. BTC climbed higher above the $66,500 and $66,000 resistance levels. However, the bears were active near the $67,500 and $68,000 levels.</p>
<p>A high was formed near $67,614 and the price is now consolidating gains. It is trading near the 23.6% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $62,614 swing low to the $67,614 high. Bitcoin is now trading above $65,000 and the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-jumps-68k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">100 hourly Simple moving average</a>.</p>
<p>There is also a key bullish trend line forming with support at $65,900 on the hourly chart of the BTC/USD pair. Immediate resistance is near the $67,500 level. The first major resistance could be $68,000.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-599445" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449" alt="Bitcoin Price" width="1024" height="449" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1950 1950w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_430436.png?resize=1024%2C449?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></a></p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD on TradingView.com</a></p>
<p>If there is a clear move above the $68,000 resistance zone, the price could continue to gain strength. In the stated case, the price could even clear the $69,0200 resistance zone in the near term. The next key resistance sits at $70,000.</p>
<h2>Another Decline In BTC?</h2>
<p>If Bitcoin fails to rise above the $68,000 resistance zone, it could start another decline. Immediate support on the downside is near the $66,000 level and the trend line.</p>
<p>The first major support is $65,200 or the 50% Fib retracement level of the upward move from the $62,614 swing low to the $67,614 high. The next support sits at $63,800. If there is a close below $63,800, the price could start a drop toward the $61,200 level. Any more losses might send the price toward the $60,500 support zone in the near term.</p>
<p>Technical indicators:</p>
<p>Hourly MACD – The MACD is now losing pace in the bullish zone.</p>
<p>Hourly RSI (Relative Strength Index) – The RSI for BTC/USD is now above the 60 level.</p>
<p>Major Support Levels – $65,900, followed by $63,800.</p>
<p>Major Resistance Levels – $67,500, $68,000, and $69,200.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shutterstock_638895124.jpg?fit=460%2C264" width="460" height="264" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599443</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin ETFs Bleed For One Week Straight &#8211; Can Price Recover To $73,000?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etfs-bleed-for-one-week-straight-can-price-recover-to-73000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 15:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599417</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last week was rough for Spot Bitcoin ETFs as they failed to attract strong inflows day after day. As a result, these Spot Bitcoin ETFs witnessed consecutive daily outflows every day last week, indicating the bullish sentiment among institutional traders might actually be waning. This seems to have been reflected in the price of Bitcoin, as the cryptocurrency fell to as low as $61,370 during the week.  Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: Can FTM Hit $2 After 20% Price Spike? Bitcoin ETFs See Sustained Outflows Investor interest in Spot bitcoin ETFs skyrocketed throughout February and early March amid Bitcoin&#8217;s bull run, pushing its price to an all-time high of $73,737. This maximum investor interest saw the ETFs setting new trading records for exchange-traded funds in the US. However, these ETFs have now set a negative record of five consecutive days of outflows to beat a four-day outflow streak set in January. According to data from BitMEX Research, these ETFs witnessed five days of consecutive outflows of $154.4 million, $326.2 million, $261.6 million, $93.1 million, and $51.6 million. At the same time, Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC set a new record for the most daily outflow. BitMEX also reveals that the world&#8217;s largest crypto asset manager saw redemptions of 9,539.7 BTC worth over $642.5 million on Monday, the largest single-day outflow in GBTC&#8217;s history. [1/4] Bitcoin ETF Flow &#8211; 22 March 2024 All data in. 5th day of net outflows. $52m total net outflow for the day. Blackrock with a record low inflow of $18.9m pic.twitter.com/63u297xh8d — BitMEX Research (@BitMEXResearch) March 23, 2024 Grayscale&#8217;s outflow wasn&#8217;t particularly surprising, considering that the fund has witnessed consistent daily outflow since its launch. The surprise came from very weak inflow into other Spot ETFs like BlackRock (IBIT) and Fidelity (FBTC), whose huge inflows have always offset outflows from GBTC.  Particularly noteworthy is the fact that Blackrock (IBIT), which has consistently been the target of the majority of inflow, established a new inflow low of $18.9 million on Friday, March 22. Fidelity, on the other hand, also saw its inflow fall to as low as $5.9 million on Monday, March 18. Bitcoin is now trading at $65.122. Chart: TradingView Can Bitcoin Price Recover? The big question now is whether Bitcoin can stage a strong recovery and reclaim its recent all-time high above $73,000. A continuation of outflows from Spot Bitcoin ETFs could further weigh on Bitcoin price.  Interestingly, the weak inflow hasn&#8217;t really related to low trading activity, as trading volume remained significant throughout the week. Data shows that the cumulative trading volume of the 10 ETFs is now at $164 billion after witnessing $22.71 billion in trading volume last week. Related Reading: Top Analyst’s Bold Prediction: XRP Set To Skyrocket 1,500% After a week of deep outflows, the coming days will be crucial in determining the next major move in the price of Bitcoin. Despite the rough week, Bitcoin still has a chance to rebound back to $73,000 or higher, especially with the approach of the next Bitcoin halving event.  Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last week was rough for Spot Bitcoin ETFs as they failed to attract strong inflows day after day. As a result, these Spot Bitcoin ETFs witnessed consecutive daily outflows every day last week, indicating the bullish sentiment among institutional traders might actually be waning. This seems to have been reflected in the price of Bitcoin, as the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-68k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">cryptocurrency fell to as low</a> as $61,370 during the week. </p>

<h2><b>Bitcoin ETFs See Sustained Outflows</b></h2>
<p>Investor interest in Spot bitcoin ETFs <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-new-ath-by-year-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">skyrocketed throughout February</a> and early March amid Bitcoin&#8217;s bull run, pushing its price to an<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/"> all-time high</a> of $73,737. </p>
<p>This maximum investor interest saw the ETFs setting new trading records for exchange-traded funds in the US. However, these ETFs have now set a negative record of five consecutive days of outflows to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-spot-etf-outflows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">beat a four-day outflow streak</a> set in January.</p>
<p>According to data from BitMEX Research, these ETFs witnessed five days of consecutive outflows of $154.4 million, $326.2 million, $261.6 million, $93.1 million, and $51.6 million. At the same time, Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC set a new record for the most daily outflow. </p>
<p>BitMEX also reveals that the world&#8217;s largest crypto asset manager saw redemptions of 9,539.7 BTC worth over $642.5 million on Monday, the largest single-day outflow in GBTC&#8217;s history.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">[1/4] Bitcoin ETF Flow &#8211; 22 March 2024</p>
<p>All data in. 5th day of net outflows. $52m total net outflow for the day. Blackrock with a record low inflow of $18.9m <a href="https://t.co/63u297xh8d" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/63u297xh8d</a></p>
<p>— BitMEX Research (@BitMEXResearch) <a href="https://twitter.com/BitMEXResearch/status/1771465855680823612?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Grayscale&#8217;s outflow wasn&#8217;t particularly surprising, considering that the fund has witnessed consistent daily outflow since its launch. The surprise came from very weak inflow into other Spot ETFs like BlackRock (IBIT) and Fidelity (FBTC), whose huge inflows have always offset outflows from GBTC. </p>
<p>Particularly noteworthy is the fact that Blackrock (IBIT), which has consistently been the target of the majority of inflow, established a new inflow low of $18.9 million on Friday, March 22. Fidelity, on the other hand, also saw its inflow fall to as low as $5.9 million on Monday, March 18.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nnxo1w7H/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<h2><b>Can Bitcoin Price Recover?</b></h2>
<p>The big question now is whether Bitcoin can stage a strong recovery and reclaim its recent all-time high above $73,000. A <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-pre-halving-btc-rally-us-fed-decision/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">continuation of outflows</a> from Spot Bitcoin ETFs could further weigh on Bitcoin price. </p>
<p>Interestingly, the weak inflow hasn&#8217;t really related to low trading activity, as trading volume remained significant throughout the week. <a href="https://www.theblock.co/data/crypto-markets/bitcoin-etf/cumulative-spot-bitcoin-etf-volumes" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data </a>shows that the cumulative trading volume of the 10 ETFs is now at $164 billion after witnessing $22.71 billion in trading volume last week.</p>

<p>After a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-long-term-holders-price-top-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">week of deep outflows</a>, the coming days will be crucial in determining the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etf-netflows-may-experience-rebound-if-this-price-is-attained-analyst-explains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">next major move</a> in the price of Bitcoin. Despite the rough week, Bitcoin still <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/buy-much-bitcoin-as-you-can/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">has a chance to rebound</a> back to $73,000 or higher, especially with the approach of the next <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-halving-result-supply-squeeze-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin halving event</a>. </p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_65933c.jpg?fit=460%2C308" width="460" height="308" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599417</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eyes On Toncoin: Speculation Rises After 40% Weekly Surge – What Comes Next?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/eyes-on-toncoin-speculation-rises-after-40-weekly-surge-what-comes-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 13:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toncoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON) has been on a hot streak, surging double digits in the past 24 hours and boasting a 40% gain in the last week. This bullish run coincides with the launch of the Ton Foundation&#8217;s Open League initiative, a program designed to incentivize user and project participation on the TON blockchain. The price currently sits at $4.96, having reached a new cycle high of $5.28 on March 23rd. This surge comes amidst a broader market downturn for major cryptocurrencies, making TON a standout performer. Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: Can FTM Hit $2 After 20% Price Spike? TON&#8217;s Open League Sparks Bullish Momentum The Open League, announced on March 20th, promises to distribute a hefty 30 million TON tokens (roughly $115 million) to participants. This sizeable reward pool has ignited excitement within the TON community, attracting new projects and users to the network. But can this momentum be sustained? Analysts are cautiously optimistic. Technical analysis paints a promising picture for TON. The Awesome Oscillator, a tool measuring market trends and momentum, displays a series of green bars, indicating a rise in bullish sentiment. Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) – a gauge of buying and selling pressure – has trended upwards, suggesting a healthy inflow of liquidity. Bitcoin is now trading at $65.083. Chart: TradingView Adding to the optimism, crypto prediction platform CoinCodex forecasts a price of $6.45 for TON by March 29th, translating to a potential 30% increase within the next five days. Toncoin&#8217;s medium-term outlook also appears strong, with a 120% gain observed in the last quarter. Source: Coingecko Toncoin: Bullish Momentum Analysis However, despite the positive indicators, cryptocurrency markets are known for their volatility. While the Open League undoubtedly injects excitement into the TON ecosystem, it&#8217;s crucial to acknowledge the possibility of a price correction. The current RSI and MFI readings could be interpreted as nearing overbought territory, potentially signaling a temporary pullback. Related Reading: Top Analyst’s Bold Prediction: XRP Set To Skyrocket 1,500% Investors should delve deeper before making any investment decisions. The broader cryptocurrency market can significantly impact TON&#8217;s price. A sustained downturn in the industry could dampen TON&#8217;s rally. Additionally, the long-term viability of TON hinges on the success of its ongoing development projects. Evaluating the roadmap and progress can provide valuable insights. Finally, staying informed about potential regulatory changes within the cryptocurrency space is crucial, as they could impact TON&#8217;s adoption and price. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:304">Toncoin (TON) has been on a hot streak, surging double digits in the past 24 hours and boasting a 40% gain in the last week. This bullish run coincides with the launch of the Ton Foundation&#8217;s Open League initiative, a program designed to incentivize user and project participation on the TON blockchain.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:201"><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">The price currently sits at $4.96</a>, having reached a new cycle high of $5.28 on March 23rd. This surge comes amidst a broader market downturn for major cryptocurrencies, making TON a standout performer.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="7:1-7:331"><strong>TON&#8217;s Open League Sparks Bullish Momentum</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:331">The Open League, announced on March 20th, promises to distribute a hefty 30 million TON tokens (roughly $115 million) to participants. This sizeable reward pool has ignited excitement within the TON community, attracting new projects and users to the network. But can this momentum be sustained? Analysts are cautiously optimistic.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:345">Technical analysis paints a promising picture for TON. The Awesome Oscillator, a tool measuring market trends and momentum, displays a series of green bars, indicating a rise in bullish sentiment.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:345">Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) – a gauge of buying and selling pressure – has trended upwards, suggesting a healthy inflow of liquidity.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:345"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/L51Hnzvc/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:276">Adding to the optimism, crypto prediction platform CoinCodex forecasts a price of $6.45 for TON by March 29th, translating to a potential 30% increase within the next five days. Toncoin&#8217;s medium-term outlook also appears strong, with a 120% gain observed in the last quarter.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:276"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-599413" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ea098e.png?resize=1024%2C341" alt="" width="1024" height="341" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ea098e.png?resize=1024%2C341?w=1033 1033w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ea098e.png?resize=1024%2C341?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ea098e.png?resize=1024%2C341?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ea098e.png?resize=1024%2C341?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ea098e.png?resize=1024%2C341?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="15:1-15:371"><strong>Toncoin: Bullish Momentum Analysis</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:371">However, despite the positive indicators, cryptocurrency markets are known for their volatility. While the Open League undoubtedly injects excitement into the TON ecosystem, it&#8217;s crucial to acknowledge the possibility of a price correction.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:371">The current RSI and MFI readings could be interpreted as nearing overbought territory, potentially signaling a temporary pullback.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:527">Investors should delve deeper before making any investment decisions. The broader cryptocurrency market can significantly impact TON&#8217;s price. A sustained downturn in the industry could dampen TON&#8217;s rally.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:527">Additionally, the long-term viability of TON hinges on the success of its ongoing development projects. Evaluating the roadmap and progress can provide valuable insights.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:527">Finally, staying informed about potential regulatory changes within the cryptocurrency space is crucial, as they could impact TON&#8217;s adoption and price.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:527"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_4f2fcc.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599404</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Addresses Add $1.6 Billion In BTC In A Single Day &#8211; Price Recovery Soon?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-addresses-add-1-6-billion-in-btc-in-a-single-day-price-recovery-soon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 10:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptoquant]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The price performance of Bitcoin over the past week has been a source of concern for the majority of the crypto community. This has pretty much been the case for other cryptocurrencies in the market, with several large-cap tokens reversing their recently-accrued profits. However, some investors are treating the recent price decline as a rare opportunity in the bull market as they continue to load their bags with assets of their choice. Specifically, the latest on-chain data shows significant buying activity amongst a certain class of investors.  25,000 BTC Flow Into Accumulation Addresses In One Day Prominent crypto pundit Ali Martinez revealed, via a post on X, that more than 25,000 BTC (valued at approximately $1.6 billion) was moved to accumulation addresses on Friday, March 22. This figure represents the highest amount transferred to these wallets in a single day so far in 2023. Related Reading: Ethereum Drops Below The 100-Day Moving Average – What’s Next? The metric of interest here is the Inflow to Accumulation Addresses on the Bitcoin blockchain. For context, a Bitcoin accumulation address refers to an address that has zero outgoing transactions and maintains a balance of at least 10 BTC. A chart showing the inflows to Bitcoin accumulation addresses &#124; Source: Ali_charts/X This classification, however, excludes digital wallets linked to centralized exchanges and miners and has less than 2 non-dust incoming transfers. Also, it doesn&#8217;t include addresses that have not seen any activity in more than seven years. The increased flow of coins into this class of wallet addresses is evidence of substantial BTC accumulation by entities who view the crypto as a long-term investment. It signals that certain big-money players are amassing Bitcoin in anticipation of potential value appreciation. What&#8217;s more, this significant acquisition by long-term investors emphasizes the increasing adoption of Bitcoin as a store of value. Meanwhile, it might be an indicator of bullish price movement in the short term.  Bitcoin Price Overview As of this writing, Bitcoin is valued at $64,636, reflecting a mere 1% price increase in the past 24 hours. This price change is somewhat negligible, considering the deep retracement of the premier cryptocurrency earlier in the week. According to data from CoinGecko, the price of BTC is down by 2.4% over the past week. Meanwhile, the market leader is currently about 13% from its record high of $73,798. Related Reading: March Sees Nearly $1 Billion In Ethereum Netflow To Centralized Exchanges – What’s Happening? However, it has been an overall positive performance for the Bitcoin price in March, having surpassed this previous all-time high of $69,000 a little over a week ago. And, with a market cap of $1.26 trillion, BTC retains its position as the largest cryptocurrency in the sector. The price of Bitcoin struggles to hold above $64,000 on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: BTCUSDT chart on TradingView Featured image from iStock, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price performance of Bitcoin over the past week has been a source of concern for the majority of the crypto community. This has pretty much been the case for other cryptocurrencies in the market, with several large-cap tokens reversing their recently-accrued profits.</p>
<p>However, some investors are treating the recent price decline as <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etf-netflows-may-experience-rebound-if-this-price-is-attained-analyst-explains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">a rare opportunity in the bull market</a> as they continue to load their bags with assets of their choice. Specifically, the latest on-chain data shows significant buying activity amongst a certain class of investors. </p>
<h2>25,000 BTC Flow Into Accumulation Addresses In One Day</h2>
<p>Prominent crypto pundit Ali Martinez revealed, via a <a href="https://x.com/ali_charts/status/1771477802707034192?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post on X</a>, that more than 25,000 BTC (valued at approximately $1.6 billion) was moved to accumulation addresses on Friday, March 22. This figure represents the highest amount transferred to these wallets in a single day so far in 2023.</p>

<p>The metric of interest here is the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/large-players-are-in-full-bitcoin-accumulation-mode-as-on-chain-activity-grows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Inflow to Accumulation Addresses</a> on the Bitcoin blockchain. For context, a Bitcoin accumulation address refers to an address that has zero outgoing transactions and maintains a balance of at least 10 BTC.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-599365 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C542" alt="Bitcoin " width="860" height="542" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=1200 1200w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C542 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJWNJQbXEAAAYT_.jpeg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p>This classification, however, excludes digital wallets linked to centralized exchanges and miners and has less than 2 non-dust incoming transfers. Also, it doesn&#8217;t include addresses that have not seen any activity in more than seven years.</p>
<p>The increased flow of coins into this class of wallet addresses is evidence of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-usdt-tether-8888-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">substantial BTC accumulation</a> by entities who view the crypto as a long-term investment. It signals that certain big-money players are amassing Bitcoin in anticipation of potential value appreciation.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s more, this significant <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-long-term-holders-price-top-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">acquisition by long-term investors</a> emphasizes the increasing adoption of Bitcoin as a store of value. Meanwhile, it might be an indicator of bullish price movement in the short term. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Overview</h2>
<p>As of this writing, Bitcoin is <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-new-ath-by-year-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">valued at $64,636</a>, reflecting a mere 1% price increase in the past 24 hours. This price change is somewhat negligible, considering the deep retracement of the premier cryptocurrency earlier in the week.</p>
<p>According to data from CoinGecko, the price of BTC is down by 2.4% over the past week. Meanwhile, the market leader is currently about 13% from its record high of $73,798.</p>

<p>However, it has been an overall positive performance for the Bitcoin price in March, having surpassed this previous all-time high of $69,000 a little over a week ago. And, with a market cap of $1.26 trillion, BTC retains its position as the largest cryptocurrency in the sector.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VrTGdW1G/" alt="Bitcoin" width="2174" height="1434"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/iStock-1326202724.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599364</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Analyst&#8217;s Bold Prediction: XRP Set To Skyrocket 1,500%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/top-analysts-bold-prediction-xrp-set-to-skyrocket-15x/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP, the native token of Ripple, is stirring up excitement in the crypto market with analysts predicting a potential short-term price explosion. However, the extent and timing of this surge remain a point of contention. In a recent analysis of the cryptocurrency market, several market analysts have expressed optimism about the short-term prospects of XRP, the digital asset associated with Ripple. These analysts believe that XRP could experience a substantial increase in price, potentially reaching new heights before the peak of the current market cycle. Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: Can FTM Hit $2 After 20% Price Spike? XRP Bold Predictions: Fact Or Folly? Capt Toblerone, a prominent crypto analyst, recently ignited the discussion with a bold claim: XRP could see a staggering 15-fold increase (1500%) before the current bull market reaches its peak. This translates to a price target of roughly $10 by July 2024, a significant leap from its current price hovering around $0.62. $XRP chart update. 3 day MACD turning bullish at the right time. 🚀🚀 pic.twitter.com/VgJAjO0Bru — CAPT. PARA8OLIC TOBLERONE (@CaptToblerone) February 16, 2024 Toblerone isn&#8217;t alone in his optimistic outlook. Analyst Jake Gagain believes a $5 price point for XRP is achievable in the near future, while crypto founder Nick envisions a more ambitious target of $10 by the cycle&#8217;s end. This bullish sentiment echoes the broader market expectation of a potential $5-$10 range for the altcoin. Total crypto market cap currently at $2.377 trillion. Chart: TradingView The underlying rationale for this bullishness hinges on XRP&#8217;s historical performance. Back in late 2017, XRP witnessed a meteoric rise, culminating in its all-time high of $3.84. Analysts like Toblerone see parallels between the current market conditions and 2017, hoping for a similar price explosion. Bullish 2025 Crypto Price Predictions. $BTC $ETH $SOL $XRP $ADA pic.twitter.com/xGQKZYRrpm — JAKE (@JakeGagain) March 21, 2024 However, a closer look reveals cracks in the bullish narrative. Toblerone&#8217;s previous prediction for Q2 2024 placed XRP within a range of $2.5-$11. With just ten days left in the quarter, achieving even the lower end of that prediction seems highly unlikely. XRP 24-hour price action. Source: Coingecko Analyzing The Divide Furthermore, the article lacks any mention of concrete factors driving the anticipated surge. While past performance offers a glimpse into possibilities, it&#8217;s not a guarantee of future results. The cryptocurrency market thrives on innovation and adoption, and without evidence of significant developments for Ripple or XRP, the predicted price surge might be wishful thinking. Related Reading: BONK Bonked: Price Crashes 30% In 7 Days – More Pain Ahead? Not all analysts share Toblerone&#8217;s enthusiasm. Some, like Dark Defender and EGRAG, propose a more conservative range of $5-$17 for XRP in the coming weeks. This more measured approach acknowledges the inherent volatility of the crypto market and avoids relying solely on historical parallels. The divided opinions highlight the importance of caution for investors considering XRP. While a price increase is certainly possible, the predicted 15x surge might be overly ambitious. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:266">XRP, the native token of Ripple, is stirring up excitement in the crypto market with analysts predicting a potential short-term price explosion. However, the extent and timing of this surge remain a point of contention.</p>
<p>In a recent analysis of the cryptocurrency market, several market analysts have expressed optimism about the short-term prospects of XRP, the digital asset associated with Ripple. These analysts believe that XRP could experience a substantial increase in price, potentially reaching new heights before the peak of the current market cycle.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:323"><strong>XRP Bold Predictions: Fact Or Folly?</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:323">Capt Toblerone, a prominent crypto analyst, recently ignited the discussion with a bold claim: XRP could see a staggering 15-fold increase (1500%) before the current bull market reaches its peak. This translates to a price target of roughly $10 by July 2024, a significant leap from its current price hovering around $0.62.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> chart update. 3 day MACD turning bullish at the right time. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/VgJAjO0Bru" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/VgJAjO0Bru</a></p>
<p>— CAPT. PARA8OLIC TOBLERONE (@CaptToblerone) <a href="https://twitter.com/CaptToblerone/status/1758464702047223859?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">February 16, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:321">Toblerone isn&#8217;t alone in his optimistic outlook. Analyst Jake Gagain believes a $5 price point for XRP is achievable in the near future, while crypto founder Nick envisions a more ambitious target of $10 by the cycle&#8217;s end. This bullish sentiment echoes the broader market expectation of a potential $5-$10 range for the altcoin.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:302"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/ZGRfWGUD/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:302">The underlying rationale for this bullishness hinges on XRP&#8217;s historical performance. Back in late 2017, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">XRP</a> witnessed a meteoric rise, culminating in its all-time high of $3.84. Analysts like Toblerone see parallels between the current market conditions and 2017, hoping for a similar price explosion.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Bullish 2025 Crypto Price Predictions. <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ETH</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SOL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SOL</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24XRP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$XRP</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ADA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$ADA</a> <a href="https://t.co/xGQKZYRrpm" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/xGQKZYRrpm</a></p>
<p>— JAKE (@JakeGagain) <a href="https://twitter.com/JakeGagain/status/1770933411915731100?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:257">However, a closer look reveals cracks in the bullish narrative. Toblerone&#8217;s previous prediction for Q2 2024 placed XRP within a range of $2.5-$11. With just ten days left in the quarter, achieving even the lower end of that prediction seems highly unlikely.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="13:1-13:376"><strong>Analyzing The Divide</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:376">Furthermore, the article lacks any mention of concrete factors driving the anticipated surge. While past performance offers a glimpse into possibilities, it&#8217;s not a guarantee of future results. The cryptocurrency market thrives on innovation and adoption, and without evidence of significant developments for Ripple or XRP, the predicted price surge might be wishful thinking.</p>



<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:292">Not all analysts share Toblerone&#8217;s enthusiasm. Some, like Dark Defender and EGRAG, propose a more conservative range of $5-$17 for XRP in the coming weeks. This more measured approach acknowledges the inherent volatility of the crypto market and avoids relying solely on historical parallels.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:452">The divided opinions highlight the importance of caution for investors considering XRP. While a price increase is certainly possible, the predicted 15x surge might be overly ambitious.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:452"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_31e9f6.jpg?fit=460%2C347" width="460" height="347" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599370</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Incoming MATIC Surge: Analyst Predicts $15 Price Target</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/incoming-matic-surge-analyst-predicts-15-price-target/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto bull run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599363</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Digital asset analyst with X handle Crypto Patel has recently shared a bullish prediction on MATIC price movement in the coming weeks. This forecast comes amidst MATIC’s poor performance in the last seven days, during which it lost 6.68% of its market value, based on data from CoinMarketCap.  The Polygon native token had been one of the best-performing assets in 2024 rising by over 76.38% between January to March. However, the altcoin has now recorded a 22.83% decline over the last two weeks, drawing much concern over its future price movement.  Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Jumps 180% In 4 Weeks: Just The Beginning? $1.20 Price Level Critical For MATIC Price Surge, Analyst Says In a post on X on March 23, Crypto Patel presented a bullish case for MATIC despite the token’s current downtrend, naming the forecast the “MATIC BULL RUN ROADMAP.” Firstly, the analyst stated that a MATIC bullish pennant was being formed. For context, the bullish pennant represents a price pattern that typically follows a string of upward movement in price (the flagpole) followed by a period of consolidation (pennant). $MATIC BULL RUN ROADMAP 🚀 1⃣ #MATIC Forming Bullish Pennant In HTF 2⃣ 2021 Bull Run: Did 100x in Last bull Market After Bull Flag Breakout 3⃣ If MATIC/USDT Break $1.20 Level in HTF then Ready for $10-$15 Target 4⃣ I am Bullish in #POLYGON for Long Run 5⃣ If Market Crash then… pic.twitter.com/FJEvGiHd4U — Crypto Patel (@CryptoPatel) March 23, 2024 A bullish pennant is characterized by converging trendlines, which indicates the continuation of the previous uptrend once the price breaks out of consolidation. Importantly, Crypto Patel emphasized that MATIC’s bullish pennant was being formed on a higher time frame (HTF), such as the weekly chart.  Following historical trends, the complete formation of the bullish pennant could result in Polygon native asset experiencing a 100x price increase in the highly anticipated crypto bull run, as observed in 2021. However, with a focus on short-term targets, Crypto Patel has stated that MATIC reaching the $1.20 price zone on the HTF could trigger a surge to a range of $10-$15, representing a potential 1500% gain on the asset’s current price.  Albeit, in the advent of an unexpected crash, the crypto analyst expects MATIC could be significantly affected but should find support around the $0.60-$0.70 price zone.  Related Reading: Buy High, Sell Low: FOMO Made This Crypto Trader Lose 6,039 SOL MATIC Price Overview At the time of writing, MATIC trades around $0.9817 with a 1.30% gain in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the token’s daily trading volume has declined by 31.82% and is valued at $291.65 million. With a market cap value of $9.7 billion, MATIC is ranked the 16th largest cryptocurrency and one of the world’s most prominent digital assets. MATIC trading at $0.9771 on the daily chart &#124; Source: MATICUSDT chart on Tradingview.com Featured image from Freepik, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital asset analyst with X handle Crypto Patel has recently shared a bullish prediction on MATIC price movement in the coming weeks. This forecast comes amidst MATIC’s poor performance in the last seven days, during which it lost 6.68% of its market value, based on<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> data from CoinMarketCap. </a></p>
<p>The Polygon native token had been one of the best-performing assets in 2024 rising by over 76.38% between January to March. However, the altcoin has now recorded a 22.83% decline <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/matic/matic-price-slumps-10-amidst-market-downturn-here-are-key-levels-to-watch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">over the last two weeks</a>, drawing much concern over its future price movement. </p>

<h2>$1.20 Price Level Critical For MATIC Price Surge, Analyst Says</h2>
<p>In a<a href="https://x.com/CryptoPatel/status/1771560468877836392?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> post on X on March 23,</a> Crypto Patel presented a bullish case for MATIC despite the token’s current downtrend, naming the forecast the “MATIC BULL RUN ROADMAP.”</p>
<p>Firstly, the analyst stated that a MATIC bullish pennant was being formed. For context, the bullish pennant represents a price pattern that typically follows a string of upward movement in price (the flagpole) followed by a period of consolidation (pennant).</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MATIC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$MATIC</a> BULL RUN ROADMAP <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>1&#x20e3; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MATIC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#MATIC</a> Forming Bullish Pennant In HTF
2&#x20e3; 2021 Bull Run: Did 100x in Last bull Market After Bull Flag Breakout
3&#x20e3; If MATIC/USDT Break $1.20 Level in HTF then Ready for $10-$15 Target
4&#x20e3; I am Bullish in <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/POLYGON?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#POLYGON</a> for Long Run
5&#x20e3; If Market Crash then… <a href="https://t.co/FJEvGiHd4U" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/FJEvGiHd4U</a></p>
<p>— Crypto Patel (@CryptoPatel) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoPatel/status/1771560468877836392?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>A bullish pennant is characterized by converging trendlines, which indicates the continuation of the previous uptrend once the price breaks out of consolidation. Importantly, Crypto Patel emphasized that MATIC’s bullish pennant was being formed on a higher time frame (HTF), such as the weekly chart. </p>
<p>Following historical trends, the complete formation of the bullish pennant could result in Polygon native asset experiencing a 100x price increase in the highly anticipated crypto bull run, as observed in 2021.</p>
<p>However, with a focus on short-term targets, Crypto Patel has stated that MATIC reaching the $1.20 price zone on the HTF could trigger a surge to a range of $10-$15, representing a potential 1500% gain on the asset’s current price.  Albeit, in the advent of an unexpected crash, the crypto analyst expects MATIC could be significantly affected but should find support around the $0.60-$0.70 price zone. </p>

<h2>MATIC Price Overview</h2>
<p style="text-align: left">At the time of writing, MATIC trades around $0.9817 with a 1.30% gain in the last 24 hours. Meanwhile, the token’s daily trading volume has declined by 31.82% and is valued at $291.65 million. With a market cap value of $9.7 billion, MATIC is ranked the 16th largest cryptocurrency and one of the world’s most prominent digital assets.</p>

<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/aID0exhR/" alt="MATIC" width="1479" height="893"/>MATIC trading at $0.9771 on the daily chart | Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/xg17RJqK/?symbol=BYBIT%3AMATICUSDT" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">MATICUSDT chart on Tradingview.com</a>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/stock-market-bull-market-trading-graph-financial-concept-market-place-stock-exchange-generative-ai_176802-3.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599363</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
