<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:44:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>AI Regulation Debate Spurs Union Attention at California Privacy Agency</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-regulation-debate-spurs-union-attention/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI in Daily Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[california]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Union]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501320</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The California Privacy Protection Agency (CPPA) has taken a significant step forward in its endeavor to regulate artificial intelligence (AI) usage, especially concerning consumer and worker data.&#160; Amidst lobbying efforts from both unions and the tech sector, the agency&#8217;s board voted 3-2 to advance rules governing the deployment of AI and the collection of personal [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The California Privacy Protection Agency (CPPA) has taken a significant step forward in its endeavor to regulate artificial intelligence (<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/study-urges-temporary-ban-on-advanced-ai/">AI</a>) usage, especially concerning consumer and worker data.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Amidst lobbying efforts from both unions and the tech sector, the agency&#8217;s board voted 3-2 to advance rules governing the deployment of AI and the collection of personal information. This development marks a crucial moment in the ongoing debate surrounding privacy, technology, and worker rights in the state.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Union advocacy for worker AI protections</h2>



<p>Labor unions in California are redoubling their efforts to influence the California Privacy Protection Agency (CPPA), seeking to establish robust safeguards around the integration of artificial intelligence (AI) in workplaces.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This renewed focus marks a significant lobbying initiative as unions confront the formidable influence of the state&#8217;s tech sector. The regulations under consideration by the CPPA are a direct response to the California Consumer Privacy Act, which extends privacy protections to employees alongside consumers.</p>



<p>The proposed regulations drafted by the CPPA encompass a wide array of AI applications in the workplace, spanning decision-making processes related to employment, housing, insurance, healthcare, and education.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Of particular significance is the provision granting individuals the right to opt out of AI-driven assessments, such as those conducted during job interviews, without fear of facing discrimination. Moreover, businesses would be obligated to disclose their utilization of AI technologies and provide transparency regarding the use of personal data for predictive purposes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Implications of enhanced worker AI rights</h2>



<p>If implemented, these regulations would represent a significant milestone in ensuring worker protection amidst the increasing integration of AI in various aspects of employment. By empowering individuals with the right to opt out of AI-based assessments and requiring businesses to be transparent about their AI usage, these regulations aim to mitigate the potential risks of algorithmic bias and discrimination in the workplace. Additionally, they underscore the evolving landscape of privacy rights in the digital age, where the intersection of technology and labor necessitates proactive regulatory measures to safeguard individual autonomy and well-being.</p>



<p>Under the proposed rules, businesses exceeding $25 million in annual revenue or processing the personal data of over 100,000 Californians would be subject to regulation. Given California&#8217;s status as a hub for AI companies, with a significant proportion of the world&#8217;s leading firms headquartered in the state, these regulations could wield substantial influence.</p>



<p>Despite progress, more than 20 labor unions and digital rights organizations have raised concerns regarding the latest iteration of the rules. They contend that amendments introduced shortly before the vote have watered down crucial provisions, potentially creating loopholes that could undermine accountability in AI usage. Specifically, changes to the definition of automated decision-making technology have drawn scrutiny, with advocates warning of potential exploitation by businesses.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Ongoing debate and future outlook</h2>



<p>The advancement of AI regulation in California has sparked robust debate, reflecting the complexities surrounding privacy protection, technological advancement, and labor rights. Business interests have weighed in, advocating for exemptions and expressing reservations about the breadth of the proposed regulations.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, proponents argue that comprehensive regulation is essential to safeguard individuals&#8217; privacy and prevent algorithmic bias and discrimination.</p>



<p>As the CPPA progresses in shaping AI regulations, stakeholders from various sectors continue to engage in dialogue and advocacy efforts. The outcome of this regulatory process will have far-reaching implications, not only for California but potentially serving as a model for AI regulation nationwide.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As discussions evolve and the regulatory landscape takes shape, the balancing act between technological innovation and privacy protection remains at the forefront of policymaking efforts in the Golden State.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_AIREGULATIONS_IN_CALIFORNIA_US_0-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_AIREGULATIONS_IN_CALIFORNIA_US_0-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Price Prediction: Will Pepe Coin Dominate Dogecoin And Shiba Inu In 2024?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/pepe-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shayan Chowdhury]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=414092</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PEPE Price Predictions 2024-2033 Meme coins are renowned in the cryptocurrency market for boosting investor morale, particularly during periods of market turbulence or stagnation. For enthusiasts of meme coins, the newly-introduced &#8220;PEPE&#8221; coin is one not to be overlooked. It has established a remarkable benchmark, experiencing an extraordinary surge of nearly 7,000% since its debut [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="wp-block-heading">PEPE Price Predictions 2024-2033</h3>



<ul>
<li><a href="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2023" data-type="internal" data-id="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2023">Pepe Price Prediction 2024 – up to $0.000002</a></li>



<li><a href="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2026" data-type="internal" data-id="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2026">Pepe Price Prediction 2027 – up to $0.000006</a></li>



<li><a href="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2029" data-type="internal" data-id="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2029">Pepe Price Prediction 2030 – up to $0.000021</a></li>



<li><a href="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2032" data-type="internal" data-id="#Pepe-Price-Prediction-2032">Pepe Price Prediction 2033 – up to $0.000064</a></li>
</ul>



<p>Meme coins are renowned in the cryptocurrency market for boosting investor morale, particularly during periods of market turbulence or stagnation. For enthusiasts of meme coins, the newly-introduced &#8220;PEPE&#8221; coin is one not to be overlooked. It has established a remarkable benchmark, experiencing an extraordinary surge of nearly 7,000% since its debut in April 2023.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Memecoins, themed after popular memes, exemplify this trend, with Pepecoin being a prime example. Pepecoin drew inspiration from the &#8220;Pepe the Frog&#8221; meme, originally featured in Matt Furie&#8217;s comic &#8220;Boy’s Club.&#8221; The initial market dynamics of Pepecoin were significantly influenced by frog-themed memes propagated by its creators and supporters on social platforms.</p>



<p>Pepecoin demonstrates how crypto communities can unite around cultural symbols, often overlooking the underlying economic fundamentals of the asset. It follows in the footsteps of dog-themed meme coins like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. Dogecoin gained prominence with backing from billionaire Elon Musk, achieving a market capitalization of $10 billion. Shiba Inu, meanwhile, boasts a market cap exceeding $5 billion. Pepecoin, by contrast, currently holds a more modest market cap of around $464 million, which is far less than its peak value of $1.5 billion in May 2023.</p>



<p>Following its remarkable bull run, the well-known meme coin Pepe has recently experienced a slowdown. However, even with this downturn, large investors are still actively acquiring PEPE. This raises an important consideration: is investing in Pepe a worthwhile decision? Can it surpass the dominance of leading meme coins, including Shiba Inu and Dogecoin?</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How Much is Pepe Coin Worth Today?</h3>



<p>The current price of Pepe today stands at $0.0000075, with a 24-hour trading volume of $45.06M. It has a current market cap of $595M and holds a market dominance of 0.04%. The PEPE price has seen a 2.8% increase in the last 24 hours.</p>



<p>Pepe Coin achieved its peak on May 5, 2023, reaching the highest price paid of $0.000004408. The record lowest price for Pepe Coin is not specified, but it hit a cycle low at $0.0000006088 following its all-time high. Conversely, the highest price Pepe Coin attained since its last cycle low was $0.051455, marking the cycle high. Talking about how many pepe coins there are, the amount is currently at 417.5 trillion, which is the current circulating supply.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe price analysis: PEPE price continues to consolidate around $0.000008</h2>



<p><strong>TL; DR Breakdown</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>PEPE price analysis shows that Pepe coin initiated a consolidation around $0.000008</li>



<li>Resistance for Pepe is present at $0.00000852</li>



<li>Support for PEPE/USDT is present at $0.00000592</li>
</ul>



<p>The PEPE price analysis for 25 March confirms that PEPE price continues to witness a tough battle among traders in validating a clear trend. However, buyers defend the $0.000006 level strongly.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Coin price analysis 1-day chart: PEPE price fails to meet buyers’ demand</h3>



<p>Analyzing the daily price chart of Pepe coin, Pepe’s price is witnessing intense selling pressure as the price attempts to break above $0.000008. Currently, PEPE price is facing a surge in selling confidence as the price struggles near Fib levels. The 24-hour volume has surged to $241 million, showing an increased interest in trading activity today. Pepe’s price is trading at $0.0000075, increasing by over 2.8% in the last 24 hours.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-26-18-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501315" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-26-18-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-26-18-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-26-18-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-26-18-1536x671.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-26-18.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The RSI-14 trend line has declined from its previous level and currently trades around the midline at level 54, hinting at a selling dominance. The SMA-14 level suggests volatility in the next few hours. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">PEPE/USDT 4-hour price chart: Bears aim for further declines</h3>



<p>The 4-hour Pepe price chart suggests that bears are increasing their domination near the immediate support line as PEPE price tumbles around resistance channels at $0.000008. However, bulls aim to gain control by holding the price above EMA20 trend line.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-44-28-1200x524.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-501317" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-44-28-1200x524.jpg 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-44-28-300x131.jpg 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-44-28-768x335.jpg 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-44-28-1536x671.jpg 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-44-28.jpg 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The BoP indicator is trading in a positive region at 0.5, showing that short-term buyers are taking a chance to accelerate an upward trend.</p>



<p>Additionally, the MACD trend line has formed bearish candles below the signal line, and the indicator aims for a negative momentum, strengthening short-position holders’ confidence.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from PEPE price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The hourly price chart confirms that Pepe attempts to drop below the immediate support line; however, bulls are eyeing a further recovery rally in the upcoming hours. If Pepe’s price successfully holds its momentum above $0.00000852, it will fuel a bullish rally to $0.00001081.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-25-54-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501318" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-25-54-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-25-54-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-25-54-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-25-54-1536x671.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PEPEUSDT_2024-03-25_13-25-54.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>If bulls fail to initiate a surge, Pepe price may drop below the immediate support line at $0.00000592, which may begin a bearish trend to $0.00000503.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is PEPE A Good Investment?</h2>



<p>Reviewing the Pepe project&#8217;s roadmap, it appears there are no specific future plans detailed, other than an anticipation that $PEPE and similar meme coins will dominate. Given this lack of clear direction, and with an already sizable community of over 500,000 Twitter followers, the project&#8217;s price growth potential may be capped.</p>



<p>However, meme coins have a reputation for offering significant returns, as their values can surge dramatically when supported by strong community movements.</p>



<p>This was evident when Pepe&#8217;s value skyrocketed by over 222% to reach a new all-time high (ATH) following its listing on the Binance exchange. A similar significant announcement in 2024 could potentially propel Pepe to surpass its previous ATH.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News&nbsp;</h2>



<p><strong>Pepe Burns $5.5 Million</strong>: In October, Pepe saw a burning of 6.9 trillion tokens. This move, which reduces the total supply, has diminished concerns about the team&#8217;s large token holdings, now worth $3.72 million. Following this, new advisors were brought on to strategize the use of the remaining tokens for partnerships and marketing. This development comes after a recent incident where several developers allegedly made unauthorized transfers of Pepe tokens.</p>



<p><strong>Pepe Rug Pull</strong>: Pepe Coin is embroiled in controversy, with claims of it being a scam emerging on social media. An anonymous developer from the team accused three members of stealing 16 trillion tokens, about 60% of the total supply, from Pepe&#8217;s multi-signature wallet and selling them on exchanges, citing internal strife and greed as the cause of the issue.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Prediction By Cryptopolitan&nbsp;</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/YmeI8He-IgyRI0M68Ip5DaFU0lKbv1Ze_a7_pAWx3hZt6dgFDAji5axgfKxneIdBlz1AyXqrYJkjKoiDnkxmVsFA7COeslbDzhSWA2TDzEuvCb45hK-MfC23ff51cxXgrmozDZ70mlZNuYWN5yHAoYY" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum ($)</td><td>Average ($)</td><td>Maximum ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>0.000002</td><td>0.000002</td><td>0.000002</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>0.000003</td><td>0.000003</td><td>0.000003</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>0.000004</td><td>0.000004</td><td>0.000004</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>0.000005</td><td>0.000006</td><td>0.000006</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>0.000008</td><td>0.000009</td><td>0.000009</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>0.000012</td><td>0.000013</td><td>0.000014</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>0.000017</td><td>0.000018</td><td>0.000021</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>0.000027</td><td>0.000027</td><td>0.000031</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>0.000037</td><td>0.000038</td><td>0.000047</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>0.000053</td><td>0.000055</td><td>0.000064</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of PEPE, in 2024 the price of Pepe is forecasted to be at around a minimum value of $0.000002. The Pepe price value can reach a maximum of $0.000002 with the average trading value of $0.000002.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>Pepe price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $0.000003 in 2025. As per our findings, the PEPE price could reach a maximum possible level of $0.000003 with the average forecast price of $0.000003.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">PEPE Price Forecast for 2026</h4>



<p>The price of Pepe is predicted to reach a minimum value of $0.000004 in 2026. The Pepe price could reach a maximum value of $0.000004 with the average trading price of $0.000004 throughout 2026.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe (PEPE) Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of PEPE, in 2027 the price of Pepe is predicted to reach at a minimum level of $0.000005. The PEPE price can reach a maximum level of $0.000006 with the average trading price of $0.000006.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>As per the forecast price and technical analysis, in 2028 the price of Pepe is predicted to reach at a minimum level of $0.000008. The PEPE price can reach a maximum level of $0.000009 with the average trading price of $0.000009.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>As per the forecast and technical analysis, in 2029 the price of Pepe is expected to reach a minimum price value of $0.000012. The PEPE price can reach a maximum price value of $0.000014 with the average value of $0.000013.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe (PEPE) Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>The price of Pepe is predicted to reach a minimum value of $0.000017 in 2030. The Pepe price could reach a maximum value of $0.000021 with the average trading price of $0.000018 throughout 2030.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Forecast 2031</h4>



<p>Pepe price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $0.000027 in 2031. As per our findings, the PEPE price could reach a maximum possible level of $0.000031 with the average forecast price of $0.000027.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe (PEPE) Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>The price of 1 Pepe is expected to reach a minimum level of $0.000037 in 2032. The PEPE price can reach a maximum level of $0.000047 with the average price of $0.000038 throughout 2032.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>The price of Pepe is predicted to reach a minimum level of $0.000053 in 2033. The Pepe price can reach a maximum level of $0.000064 with the average price of $0.000055 throughout 2033.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Prediction By Coincodex</h3>



<p>According to the current price prediction by Coincodex, the price of Pepe Coin is expected to decrease by -6.66% and reach $ 0.000001112 by January 9, 2024. Coincodex&#8217;s technical indicators suggest that the current market sentiment is Bearish, and the Fear &amp; Greed Index indicates a score of 68, denoting Greed. In the past 30 days, Pepe Coin has experienced 13/30 (43%) green days, with a price volatility of 6.17%.</p>



<p>The forecast from Coincodex advises that it is currently not an ideal time to purchase Pepe Coin. Considering the historical price trends of Pepe Coin and the BTC halving cycles, Coincodex estimates the lowest price of Pepe Coin in 2025 could be around $ 0.000001050. Furthermore, Pepe Coin&#8217;s price is anticipated to potentially reach a high of $ 0.000002611 in the next year.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Forecast By Digital Coin Price</h3>



<p>According to the forecast data analysis by Digital Coin Price, the price of PEPE is projected to surpass the level of $0.00000271 in 2025. By the end of that year, Pepe is expected to attain a minimum price of $0.00000257, with the potential to reach a maximum of $0.00000284. Furthermore, Digital Coin Price&#8217;s analysis anticipates that the price of PEPE will exceed $0.0000240 in 2033. By the conclusion of 2033, Pepe is forecasted to achieve a minimum value of $0.0000234 and could potentially reach a maximum price of $0.0000241.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Target By Changelly&nbsp;</h3>



<p>Following Changelly‘s analysis of Pepe’s historical prices, it is projected that in 2025, the minimum price of Pepe could be approximately $0.000003. The maximum PEPE price for the same year is anticipated to be around $0.000004, with an average trading price expected to be $0.000003.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Changelly’s analysts have also provided their predictions for the year 2040, indicating a potential maximum PEPE price of $0.000977. However, the price might experience a decline to around $0.000816, leading to an anticipated average trading price of $0.000858.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Coin: A Quick Overview&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The official Twitter account of PEPE coin brands it as the &#8220;most memeable memecoin ever,&#8221; playfully noting that it&#8217;s time for a change from the dog-themed meme coin era, like the once-famed Dogecoin. PEPE made its debut on April 17 with modest initial attention. It draws its theme from the Pepe the Frog meme, created by Matt Furie in 2005, which has been linked to various trends, including the alt-right movement. Despite its thematic roots, PEPE has no formal affiliation with Furie or the original cartoon character. Additional features that underscore PEPE&#8217;s memecoin status include its total supply of 420 million tokens, a nod to the 4/20 date celebrated in cannabis culture. Analysts call PEPE coin a &#8216;meme takeover.&#8217;</p>



<p>For context, Dogecoin (DOGE) required nearly four years to exceed a market capitalization of $1 billion. In stark contrast, Pepe Coin achieved this milestone within just three weeks of its introduction. Despite the significant price fluctuations of $PEPE since that time, the count of individual investors remains notably high.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The official website of Pepe Coin states that $PEPE holds no inherent value and does not promise any financial return. However, unofficially, it&#8217;s noteworthy that over a hundred thousand investors have acquired $PEPE through Binance and other major cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">PEPE’s Project Changes&nbsp;</h3>



<p>In August 2023, the Pepe Coin community was alarmed by the unexpected transfer of 16 trillion $PEPE tokens (valued at approximately $15 million USD) from the project&#8217;s multi-signature wallet to various centralized exchanges.</p>



<p>This incident, once reported in the media, led to a substantial decline in the meme coin&#8217;s value. Concerns about the future of $PEPE were voiced by community members across <a href="https://twitter.com/asxn_r/status/1694827857694924924/photo/1" data-type="link" data-id="https://twitter.com/asxn_r/status/1694827857694924924/photo/1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">social media platforms</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="1000" height="350" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Screenshot_4147.png" alt="" class="wp-image-414154" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Screenshot_4147.png 1000w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Screenshot_4147-300x105.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Screenshot_4147-768x269.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Screenshot_4147-500x175.png 500w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></figure>



<p></p>



<p>In an attempt to clarify the situation, a representative with access to the project&#8217;s official communication account provided an explanation for these mysterious transfers. This was presumably aimed at reassuring the community. Contrarily, the statement only heightened concerns.</p>



<p>The explanation revealed that disgruntled developers from the Pepe Coin team were behind the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/pepe-coins-telegram-x-accounts-compromised/">unauthorized access</a> and transfer of tokens from the multi-signature wallet, purportedly under the guise of &#8220;updating&#8221; the wallet. These developers had since parted ways with the project.</p>



<p>The individual managing the project&#8217;s communication account categorically labeled these former developers as culprits, accusing them of theft and subsequent sale of the stolen tokens.</p>



<p>Throughout September, the value of Pepe Coin continued its downward trend despite assurances that the tokens in the multi-signature wallet were secure and being managed by an individual committed to the welfare of the community and the remaining $PEPE tokens.</p>



<p>In October, a significant development was announced via the official Pepe Coin communication account. They introduced a new advisory team to lead the project. The announcement also included the news that 6.9 trillion $PEPE tokens, equivalent to about $6,000,000, had been burned, effectively reducing the total available supply of the project.</p>



<p>This action of burning tokens, combined with the news of the new advisory team, sent a positive message to investors about the ongoing development and management of the project. Consequently, these developments contributed to an increase in the price of $PEPE.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How Does Pepe Coin Work?</h2>



<p>The PEPE coin was informally created as a nod to the widely recognized internet meme &#8220;PEPE the Frog,&#8221; which became popular in the early 2000s. It lacks a structured team or a defined development roadmap.</p>



<p>Despite its absence of fundamental backing, PEPE swiftly ascended into the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, reaching the 70th position on CoinMarketCap within just two weeks of its inception. PEPE coin commenced trading on April 15, 2023, at approximately $0.000000001 per coin, and at the time of this writing, its value stands at $0.000001116 per coin.</p>



<p>The official website of the PEPE coin candidly states, &#8220;PEPE is a meme coin with no intrinsic value or expectation of financial return. There is no formal team or roadmap. The coin is completely useless and for entertainment purposes only.&#8221;</p>



<p>Contrary to this statement, PEPE was designed to leverage the meme coin craze, similar to Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, and others. Its primary distinction lies in its thematic inspiration; while Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are dog-themed, PEPE is frog-themed.</p>



<p>PEPE Coin incorporates a deflationary mechanism where a small fraction of tokens is burned with each transaction. This approach aims to create scarcity and potentially<a href="https://x.com/pepecoineth/status/1726428740845228417?s=20" data-type="link" data-id="https://x.com/pepecoineth/status/1726428740845228417?s=20" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"> enhance the value</a> of the remaining tokens over time.</p>



<p>Additionally, PEPE uses a redistribution model, where a part of each transaction is allocated among existing token holders. This strategy is intended to foster user engagement and encourage long-term investment in the coin.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Price Forecast: Price History</h2>



<p>The origins of PEPE coin remain shrouded in mystery. Unlike many other cryptocurrencies, it didn&#8217;t employ common methods like an initial coin offering (ICO), presale, or airdrop for token distribution. Instead, the coin&#8217;s emergence and popularity are solely attributed to the appeal of the &#8220;PEPE the Frog&#8221; meme among potential investors.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/orYSlsY-88lkXAebQjmmo7KQ01li5y0sNU3nVYzlFnjLFqTiX_w0lC4s5DbQFmwyGdEmoHMvR1peO3Cz19YX4G_sr3OXsFGcnLmV7GH166MayOSIEwYF6dXjhcWyD-rTQdpfvH15NuZ6s4ffZjz9ANU" alt="" /></figure>



<p>It&#8217;s important to note that there is no known connection between PEPE coin and Matt Furie, the original creator of the &#8220;PEPE the Frog&#8221; meme. The identities of PEPE coin’s creators are still undisclosed, with the only known fact being its launch around mid-April 2023.</p>



<p>Details regarding the team behind PEPE are sparse. However, despite the lack of clear information about its creators, PEPE has garnered significant attention on social media platforms like Twitter and Telegram. This visibility has rapidly cultivated a community around the meme coin.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Pepe coin quickly gained attention shortly after its discreet launch in mid-April, with its first notable activity on Etherscan recorded on April 18.</p>



<p>The coin&#8217;s value surged dramatically right from the start, jumping from $0.00000006036 to $0.0000004002 within the first three days, a remarkable 563% increase. This rapid growth sparked discussions about Pepe&#8217;s potential as a top meme coin.</p>



<p>Following a brief period of price correction and stabilization, Pepe&#8217;s value began a significant ascent on April 30, soaring 214% in just two days to reach a new all-time high. This surge was attributed by Binance to large-scale buying by major investors.</p>



<p>Pepe&#8217;s momentum continued, with the meme coin achieving a staggering market capitalization of $1.8 billion and an all-time high price of $0.000004354. This peak coincided with Binance&#8217;s announcement on May 5 that it would list Pepe.</p>



<p>However, this upward trend was short-lived, as early investors quickly began taking profits, leading to a downward price trend. After reaching its all-time high, the volatility of Pepe significantly decreased, with both buying and selling pressures appearing to diminish.</p>



<p>The token experienced a significant sell-off on August 24th and 25th, 2023, losing nearly 27% of its value. According to a statement on Pepe’s official communication channel, this drop was due to a malicious team member who misappropriated and sold funds from the Pepe multi-signature wallet.</p>



<p>On October 19th, in tandem with Bitcoin&#8217;s late-2023 rally, Pepe also experienced a resurgence. The coin burned 1.6% of its total supply, totalling 6.9 trillion tokens. This action helped Pepe break out of its long-standing downward trend, climbing 104% in eight days and surpassing the $0.000001 mark again. Since then, the coin has been trading relatively steadily, yet to retest the crucial support level of $0.000001.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More On Pepe Coin&nbsp;</h2>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pepe Coin Vs. Pepe 2.0</h4>



<p>Pepecoin (PEPE) witnessed an exceptional surge in the meme cryptocurrency market, recording an increase of over 35,000% within its first three months.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The token&#8217;s viability hinged mostly on speculation within social media circles, suggesting that a touch of real-world application might have been beneficial. The launch of a derivative platform, PEPE 2.0, which shared the limelight with the original $PEPE, resulted in a shift in investor interest. While Pepecoin ($PEPE) experienced its first-ever four-day consecutive loss, PEPE 2.0 saw a price increase over the same weekend.</p>



<p>PEPE 2.0 emerged in June as a spin-off from the original Pepecoin (PEPE) platform, about three months after $PEPE&#8217;s debut. It was created by some $PEPE investors aiming to replicate the initial success of $PEPE, but with improvements to address perceived shortcomings of the original token. The launch of PEPE 2.0 attracted significant investor attention, leading to a roughly 1,000% increase in its value within ten days, seemingly at the expense of the original Pepecoin (PEPE).</p>



<p>In contrast to Pepecoin (PEPE), PEPE 2.0 incorporates a 1% transaction tax intended to fund development initiatives for the platform. According to official statements, PEPE 2.0 is designed to incentivize token holders and foster a sustainable ecosystem. The developers have also renounced the smart contract address, demonstrating their commitment to the platform&#8217;s security and integrity.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What Influences The Price Of Pepe?</h2>



<p>Several key factors contributed to Pepe&#8217;s significant price surge, and they could continue to influence its value in the future. Here are the main ones:</p>



<ol>
<li>Exchange Listings: Pepe&#8217;s value soared following its listing on the Binance exchange. It&#8217;s now traded on various top-tier exchanges. A potential listing on another high-profile exchange like Coinbase could lead to another price hike.</li>



<li>Meme Coin Narratives: Pepe spearheaded the recent meme coin trend. Its rise in value triggered similar increases in other new meme coins. In future phases of meme-coin popularity, Pepe could experience further surges.</li>



<li>Bitcoin Halving Impact: The Bitcoin Halving, a scheduled event every four years that halves the creation of new Bitcoin, often initiates a bull market. The next Halving in April 2024 could positively impact Pepe&#8217;s price both before and after the event.</li>



<li>Future Developments: To reach valuations like Dogecoin or Shiba Inu, Pepe needs to offer more utility to its users. Announcements about Pepe&#8217;s future development could greatly affect its market value.</li>
</ol>



<p>On the flip side, if Pepe continues to function solely as a meme coin without added utility, it might struggle to sustain demand, potentially leading to a decline in its price over time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Best Place To Buy PEPE&nbsp;</h2>



<p>Since its 2023 release, Pepe has been featured on several leading crypto exchanges, with Binance being a notable inclusion. Binance distinguishes itself with its competitive fee structure, diverse features, and a range of payment options.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re interested in joining the trend and investing in PEPE coin, here are the steps to purchase it through cryptocurrency exchanges where it&#8217;s available:</p>



<ol>
<li>Account Creation and Verification: Register for an account on the exchange&#8217;s website or app. Complete the identity verification process.</li>



<li>Existing Account Login: If you already have an account on the exchange, simply log in using your existing credentials.</li>



<li>Buying Crypto: Navigate to the “Buy Crypto” section on the exchange&#8217;s website. This will display the available options in your region. At this point, you might consider purchasing a stablecoin first, which can then be traded for PEPE.</li>



<li>Payment Method: Complete the purchase of PEPE using your preferred payment method, such as a bank credit or debit card, bank deposit, or a peer-to-peer (P2P) service.</li>



<li>Storing PEPE: Once you have purchased PEPE, you have the option to store it in your personal cryptocurrency wallet or keep it in your account on the exchange.&nbsp;</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is the Pepe Hype Over?</h2>



<p>Pepe, a meme coin with a dedicated community, has seen its hype diminish recently as investors shift their focus to utility tokens. However, market trends are often cyclical, with liquidity fluctuating between different types of investments.</p>



<p>Aware of these trends, the meme coin sector anticipates future developments like exchange listings and ecosystem enhancements, potentially increasing Pepe&#8217;s value and sparking long-term interest.</p>



<p>Remarkably, Pepe soared to a $1.8 billion market cap during its peak but now sits at $477 million despite lacking inherent utility. This speculative nature renders it a high-risk investment.</p>



<p>The rapid growth of Pepe Coin has led to the emergence of numerous variants, attracting investors who are either seeking alternatives or hoping to capitalize on these new coins early, much like they did with Pepe.</p>



<p>Considering these dynamics, it&#8217;s premature to declare the end of Pepe&#8217;s popularity. In the next bull market, Pepe might align with broader market trends and possibly enhance its value through strategic updates.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The frog-themed meme coin PEPE, rapidly gaining popularity in the cryptocurrency market, has been a boon for its early adopters, offering substantial profits. It has even surpassed established meme coins like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, attracting a mix of criticism and a strong fanbase. This surge is evident in its increasing holder base, trading volume, and social media footprint, leading to speculation about its future growth.</p>



<p>However, PEPE&#8217;s foundation lacks solidity and intrinsic value, traits typical of meme coins, casting doubt on the longevity of its current success. Its future, like that of other meme coins, remains highly speculative in the volatile crypto market.</p>



<p>Historically, the crypto industry has seen a few &#8220;rags-to-riches&#8221; stories with cultural phenomena like meme coins. Only a couple, namely DOGE and SHIB, have maintained their value in bear markets and performed well as investments. PEpeCoin may be emerging as the third notable example in this trend, but it&#8217;s too early to predict the long-term viability of meme coins.</p>



<p>For meme coins like PepeCoin to be considered a stable asset class, they must endure through various Bitcoin cycles, achieve significant milestones, such as reaching a $1 trillion market cap, and form substantial, culture-driven ecosystems within the crypto world. Until such achievements are realized, meme coins, including PEPE, remain on the speculative fringe of the crypto ecosystem.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/pepe-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/pepe-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Navigating Generative AI Investments: A Strategic Guide for Board Members</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/navigating-generative-ai-guide-for-board/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501312</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the fast-evolving landscape of technological innovation, Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) stands out as a pivotal force reshaping industries worldwide. As companies grapple with decisions regarding GenAI investments, board members find themselves at the forefront of strategic deliberations. Here&#8217;s a concise yet comprehensive guide outlining key considerations for board members navigating GenAI investments. Seizing a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the fast-evolving landscape of technological innovation, Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) stands out as a pivotal force reshaping industries worldwide. As companies grapple with decisions regarding GenAI investments, board members find themselves at the forefront of strategic deliberations. Here&#8217;s a concise yet comprehensive guide outlining key considerations for board members navigating GenAI investments.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Seizing a competitive advantage with GenAI</h2>



<p>In today&#8217;s cutthroat business environment, gaining a competitive edge is paramount. GenAI offers a gateway to innovation and growth, positioning companies ahead of rivals. Despite initial apprehensions, the burgeoning GenAI market is projected to burgeon into a $1.3 billion industry by 2032, as per Bloomberg forecasts. Embracing GenAI isn&#8217;t just an option but a strategic imperative to stay abreast of industry trends and maintain relevance in dynamic markets.</p>



<p>The integration of GenAI tools across various sectors promises to revolutionize productivity. Businesses anticipate a substantial uptick in overall efficiency, with GenAI poised to streamline tasks ranging from content creation to data analysis. Notably, studies indicate significant productivity spikes, with sectors like customer support witnessing a notable 14% surge. By equipping employees with GenAI-powered solutions, companies can redirect human capital towards high-impact projects, maximizing organizational output.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Fostering innovation in GenAI ecosystems</h2>



<p>Innovation lies at the heart of GenAI integration. Companies must proactively cultivate environments conducive to GenAI-driven creativity and ingenuity. Executives recognize the need for robust resources to meet evolving GenAI innovation expectations. Instituting novel workflows and roles geared towards optimizing GenAI utilization is crucial. By championing a culture of experimentation and adaptability, organizations can harness GenAI&#8217;s transformative potential to drive sustainable growth.</p>



<p>As companies contemplate GenAI investments, assessing Return on Investment (ROI) remains paramount. While CFOs prioritize cost reduction, it&#8217;s essential to acknowledge the substantial operational expenses associated with GenAI implementation. Estimates suggest costs exceeding $76 billion by 2028, signaling the magnitude of financial commitments involved. Balancing expenditure with anticipated gains in productivity and efficiency underscores the need for prudent financial planning and strategic foresight.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Prioritizing visibility and governance in GenAI adoption</h2>



<p>Maintaining transparency and governance in GenAI utilization emerges as a critical imperative. With the proliferation of Shadow AI – unregulated GenAI usage – companies face heightened risks concerning data security and compliance. Robust monitoring mechanisms are indispensable to track internal GenAI usage effectively. Additionally, investing in employee education and training on GenAI tools is essential to foster responsible usage and mitigate potential risks associated with unauthorized utilization.</p>



<p>The transformative potential of Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) is undeniable, presenting both opportunities and challenges for organizations worldwide. As board members navigate the complex terrain of GenAI investments, strategic foresight, and decisive action are paramount. By seizing competitive advantages, boosting productivity, fostering innovation, evaluating ROI diligently, and prioritizing visibility and governance, companies can chart a course toward sustainable growth and success in the era of GenAI.</p>



<p>In a rapidly evolving technological landscape, board members must remain agile and forward-thinking, leveraging GenAI investments to drive organizational excellence and unlock new avenues of value creation. With careful deliberation and strategic acumen, companies can harness the power of GenAI to propel themselves toward a future defined by innovation, efficiency, and competitive advantage.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Navigating_Generative_AI_Investments_A_Strategic_Guide_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Navigating_Generative_AI_Investments_A_Strategic_Guide_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Dell Sells Shares as Dell Technologies&#8217; Stock Surges</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/michael-dell-shares-as-dell-technologies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Michael Dell, the founder and chief executive of Dell Technologies, has initiated a substantial sale of shares within his namesake computer company, marking his first divestiture in nearly three years. Dell, 59, has been steadily offloading shares since March 6, amounting to more than four million shares with an estimated value of $465 million. Despite [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Michael Dell, the founder and chief executive of Dell Technologies, has initiated a substantial sale of shares within his namesake computer company, marking his first divestiture in nearly three years.</p>



<p>Dell, 59, has been steadily offloading shares since March 6, amounting to more than four million shares with an estimated value of $465 million. Despite these transactions, Dell still retains half ownership of the Texas-based company, a significant portion of his $99.7 billion fortune.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Record high shares</h2>



<p>Dell&#8217;s decision to sell comes as Dell Technologies&#8217; stock continues its upward trajectory, hitting record highs. The surge in stock value follows the company&#8217;s robust financial performance, driven particularly by heightened demand for technology-supporting artificial intelligence applications.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Michael Dell joins a growing cadre of tech billionaires, including Mark Zuckerberg of Meta Platforms, Jeff Bezos of Amazon, and Peter Thiel of PayPal, who have been strategically divesting stakes in their respective companies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Sam Bankman-fried&#8217;s legal battle</h2>



<p>Meanwhile, Sam Bankman-Fried, the erstwhile billionaire and founder of the now-bankrupt FTX cryptocurrency exchange, is embroiled in a legal battle. Convicted of stealing $8 billion from FTX customers, Bankman-Fried&#8217;s successor, John Ray has labeled him &#8220;delusional&#8221; for suggesting customers may recover funds. Bankman-Fried faces sentencing on March 28, with prosecutors seeking a lengthy prison term.</p>



<p>Adam Neumann, the former CEO of WeWork, is making waves in Miami with his real estate start-up, Flow. The company plans to invest $300 million in downtown developments, including rental apartments and retail spaces. Neumann&#8217;s foray into Miami comes amid his exploration of a joint bid for WeWork, the company he previously helmed.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Joe Lewis&#8217;s insider trading plea</h2>



<p>British billionaire Joe Lewis, founder of Tavistock Group, has pleaded guilty to insider trading charges. At 87, Lewis&#8217;s legal team argues for probation over prison time, citing his age and cooperation with prosecutors. He awaits sentencing on April 4.</p>



<p>As Michael Dell cashes in on Dell Technologies&#8217; soaring stock, Sam Bankman-Fried faces the repercussions of his involvement in the FTX scandal. Meanwhile, Adam Neumann&#8217;s ambitious Miami venture and Joe Lewis&#8217;s legal battle highlight the diverse trajectories of the world&#8217;s super-wealthy.</p>



<p>With these developments, the ever-evolving landscape of billionaire fortunes continues to captivate observers worldwide. By adhering to a straightforward style and providing concise updates on each subject, this article ensures readers stay informed without unnecessary verbosity or repetition.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Dell_Sells_Shares_as_Dell_Technologies_Stock_Surges_1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Dell_Sells_Shares_as_Dell_Technologies_Stock_Surges_1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aussies Skeptical as Generative AI Hype Fails to Convince Workforce</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/aussies-skeptical-generative-ai-hype-fails/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI in Daily Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Generative AI hype]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501304</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amidst the generative AI hype sweeping through boardrooms and digital forums alike, a surprising skepticism lingers among the Australian workforce. Despite bold claims heralding a new era of transformative technologies, many Australians remain unconvinced about the tangible impact of generative AI on their professional lives.&#160; As businesses grapple with the challenges of digital transformation, a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Amidst the generative AI hype sweeping through boardrooms and digital forums alike, a surprising skepticism lingers among the Australian workforce. Despite bold claims heralding a new era of transformative technologies, many Australians remain unconvinced about the tangible impact of generative AI on their professional lives.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As businesses grapple with the challenges of digital transformation, a collaborative study by RMIT Online and Deloitte Access Economics has unveiled a concerning trend: a significant gap in understanding and readiness for the adoption of generative AI, raising questions about the nation&#8217;s preparedness for the future world of work.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Generative AI hype and it&#8217;s relevance in the workplace</h2>



<p>The growing demand for digital skills, including proficiency in generative AI, underscores the pressing need for workforce upskilling. Deloitte and the Australian Computer Society (ACS) projects a staggering shortage of 1.3 million digital skills by 2030, highlighting the urgency for businesses and individuals to adapt. However, despite acknowledging the impending integration of generative AI into various job roles, a significant portion of employees confess to never having utilized this technology in their current positions. This discrepancy between awareness and application underscores a fundamental challenge in bridging the gap between technological potential and practical implementation within the workforce.</p>



<p>As businesses grapple with the imperative to embrace digital transformation, the reluctance to invest in generative AI training becomes increasingly apparent. Despite its potential to revolutionize learning and development through personalized content creation, many employers have yet to introduce comprehensive training initiatives. This hesitancy reflects a broader skepticism or unawareness surrounding the benefits and practical applications of generative AI, even as industries brace for profound changes driven by technological innovation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Generative AI&#8217;s impact on skill demand and industry transformation</h2>



<p>The economic landscape of Australia stands poised for substantial shifts as generative AI reshapes industries and job roles. With sectors such as financial services, ICT, media, professional services, education, and wholesale trade expected to undergo transformative changes, the demand for digital skills is more pronounced than ever before. While coding has long been hailed as a critical skill, the emergence of no-code generative AI tools is democratizing access to programming capabilities, emphasizing the importance of both technical and soft skills in the modern workforce.</p>



<p>Looking ahead, generative AI is forecasted to create new job roles centered around AI model management and data analytics, necessitating specialized skills and expertise. As businesses race to harness the potential of AI technologies, the challenge lies in closing the gap between skill demand and workforce readiness, ensuring that individuals possess the requisite capabilities to thrive in an increasingly digitized economy.</p>



<p>As Australia navigates the complex terrain of digital transformation, the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/generative-ai-hype-genuine-game-changer/" data-type="post" data-id="368808">generative AI hype</a> presents both opportunities and challenges for businesses and the workforce alike. The discrepancy between enthusiasm for learning about AI and actual investment in training initiatives raises critical questions about the nation&#8217;s readiness to embrace emerging technologies. In light of these findings, how can Australian businesses and policymakers bridge the gap between generative AI&#8217;s potential and its practical implementation, ensuring that the workforce is equipped with the skills needed to succeed in the digital age?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ed1a72e6-d42d-47f4-a4d6-bf32ca9aae82.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ed1a72e6-d42d-47f4-a4d6-bf32ca9aae82.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Majority of Korean Firms Penalize AI-Crafted Resumes</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/korean-firms-penalize-ai-crafted-resumes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI in Daily Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501302</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AI-Crafted a recent Labor Ministry and the Korea Employment Information Service survey has shed light on a concerning trend in South Korea&#8217;s job market. According to the report, a significant proportion of large companies in the country are actively disadvantaging applicants who utilize artificial intelligence (AI) services to craft their resumes, with 65.4% of respondents [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>AI-Crafted a recent Labor Ministry and the Korea Employment Information Service survey has shed light on a concerning trend in South Korea&#8217;s job market. According to the report, a significant proportion of large companies in the country are actively disadvantaging applicants who utilize artificial intelligence (AI) services to craft their resumes, with 65.4% of respondents indicating negative consequences for such submissions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Survey highlights industry response</h2>



<p>The survey, based on responses from human resource managers at the nation&#8217;s top 500 companies by sales, unveiled that 65.4% of respondents expressed disapproval of AI-assisted resumes. Of these, 42.4% stated they would downgrade their evaluation, while 23.2% admitted they would outright reject such applications. The prevailing sentiment among these firms was that AI-generated resumes lacked originality and creativity, thereby hindering the applicant&#8217;s chances.</p>



<p>Despite the widespread negative perception of AI-crafted resumes, the survey also revealed a significant gap in companies&#8217; ability to detect their usage. A staggering 73% of firms admitted to not having systems in place to determine whether a resume was AI-assisted. Only a minority, comprising 18.7% of respondents, outsourced the task of identifying AI-written resumes to third-party agencies. Meanwhile, a mere 8.3% of companies boasted internal mechanisms to filter out such submissions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Implications for job seekers</h2>



<p>The findings of this survey carry significant implications for job seekers in South Korea, particularly those considering the use of AI services for resume writing. With a majority of companies expressing disfavor toward AI-assisted resumes, applicants may find themselves at a disadvantage in the competitive job market. The lack of mechanisms for detecting AI involvement further complicates the situation, leaving many applicants vulnerable to potential discrimination based on resume composition.</p>



<p>As the use of AI in various aspects of recruitment continues to evolve, stakeholders in South Korea&#8217;s job market may need to revisit their attitudes and practices concerning AI-crafted resumes. While concerns regarding originality and creativity are valid, overlooking qualified candidates solely based on resume composition could result in missed opportunities for both employers and applicants. Additionally, the absence of effective mechanisms for detecting AI involvement underscores the need for further research and development in this area.</p>



<p>The survey&#8217;s findings underscore a prevalent bias against AI-crafted resumes among South Korean firms, with a majority expressing disapproval of such submissions. However, the lack of mechanisms to detect AI involvement highlights a significant practice gap. Moving forward, stakeholders must consider the implications of their attitudes toward AI-assisted resumes and work toward fostering a fair and inclusive recruitment process that prioritizes merit and qualifications above all else.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Majority_of_Korean_Firms_Penalize_AICrafted_Resumes_2.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Majority_of_Korean_Firms_Penalize_AICrafted_Resumes_2.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI&#8217;s Health Disinformation &#8211; What Measures Are Needed to Combat It?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ais-health-disinformation-measures-needed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI's health disinformation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501297</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a digital era where information spreads like wildfire, addressing the challenge of AI&#8217;s health disinformation, particularly in healthcare domains, has emerged as a paramount concern. A recent study published in the British Medical Journal sheds light on the pressing issue of AI&#8217;s role in propagating health disinformation.&#160; Conducted by a team of researchers, the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a digital era where information spreads like wildfire, addressing the challenge of AI&#8217;s health disinformation, particularly in healthcare domains, has emerged as a paramount concern. A recent study published in the British Medical Journal sheds light on the pressing issue of AI&#8217;s role in propagating health disinformation.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Conducted by a team of researchers, the study delved into the effectiveness of current safeguards employed by large language models (LLMs) and the transparency of artificial intelligence (AI) developers in mitigating the proliferation of health misinformation. The findings underscore the imperative for stronger safeguards and enhanced transparency to counter the growing threat posed by AI&#8217;s health misinformation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AI&#8217;s health disinformation &#8211; Exploring safeguards and transparency</h2>



<p>Amid the promising applications of LLMs in healthcare, concerns loom large over their potential to generate and disseminate health misinformation. The study, encompassing a rigorous analysis, evaluated prominent LLMs&#8217; efficacy in preventing the generation of health disinformation. Notably, LLMs like GPT-4, PaLM 2, and Llama 2 exhibited susceptibility to generating false narratives regarding critical health topics such as sunscreen causing skin cancer and the alkaline diet curing cancer. This revelation underscores the urgent need for robust safeguards to curb the dissemination of misleading health information that could potentially pose significant public health risks.</p>



<p>Also, the study delved into the transparency of AI developers in addressing safeguard vulnerabilities and mitigating risks associated with health misinformation. Despite efforts to engage developers and notify them of observed health disinformation outputs, the response varied significantly.&nbsp;</p>



<p>While some developers acknowledged receipt and engaged in subsequent actions, others lacked transparency, evident from the absence of public logs, detection tools, or detailed patching mechanisms. Such inconsistencies underscore the challenges in fostering transparency and accountability within the AI landscape, necessitating concerted efforts towards regulatory interventions and enhanced auditing processes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Assessing vulnerabilities and urging action</h2>



<p>A comprehensive sensitivity analysis undertaken as a pivotal component of the study unveiled a spectrum of capacities among Language Models (LLMs) in fabricating health-related misinformation across a multitude of scenarios. While certain models demonstrated remarkable adaptability in concocting deceptive narratives, others consistently demonstrated reluctance, thereby underscoring disparities in the execution of protective measures. Nevertheless, the effectiveness of the study was impeded by the absence of thorough transparency and receptiveness from developers of Artificial Intelligence (AI), thus underscoring the pressing necessity for immediate intervention.</p>



<p>The study underscores the critical imperative for stronger safeguards and enhanced transparency in combating AI&#8217;s health misinformation challenge. As AI continues to permeate various facets of healthcare, unified regulations, robust auditing mechanisms, and proactive monitoring are indispensable in mitigating the risks posed by health disinformation. The findings call for concerted efforts from public health authorities, policymakers, and AI developers to collaboratively address these challenges and forge a path towards a more trustworthy and reliable <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/train-elevate-ai-safety-in-healthcare/" data-type="post" data-id="485588">AI-driven healthcare</a> landscape. Given the urgency of the situation, one might wonder: How can stakeholders across the healthcare spectrum collaborate to foster greater transparency and accountability in addressing the pervasive issue of AI-driven health misinformation?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/82e6d5da-ae24-41fe-8aa3-f14b02d253d0-2.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/82e6d5da-ae24-41fe-8aa3-f14b02d253d0-2.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Price Prediction 2024-2033: Is MATIC Going Past $10 Soon?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/polygon-price-prediction/</link>
					<comments>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/polygon-price-prediction/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shayan Chowdhury]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=115640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon Price Prediction 2024-2033 How much is MATIC worth? Today, the price of Polygon (MATIC) stands at $1.02, experiencing a 24-hour trading volume of $133 million. The cryptocurrency has a market capitalization of $5.8 billion and accounts for 0.41% of the market dominance. Over the past 24 hours, MATIC’s price has increased by 3.4%. Currently, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2024">Polygon Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; up to <strong>$1.8</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2027">Polygon Price Prediction 2027 &#8211; up to <strong>$4.27</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2030">Polygon Price Prediction 2030 &#8211; up to <strong>$12.35</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2033">Polygon Price Prediction 2033 &#8211; up to <strong>$35.66</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is MATIC worth?</h4>



<p>Today, the price of Polygon (MATIC) stands at $1.02, experiencing a 24-hour trading volume of $133 million. The cryptocurrency has a market capitalization of $5.8 billion and accounts for 0.41% of the market dominance. Over the past 24 hours, MATIC’s price has increased by 3.4%. Currently, 8.01 billion MATIC tokens are in circulation, out of a maximum supply of 10 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC price analysis: MATIC price attempts to break above the consolidation of $1</h2>



<ul>
<li>MATIC price analysis shows a consolidation around the $1 mark</li>



<li>Resistance for MATIC is present at $1.09</li>



<li>Support for MATIC/USD is present at $0.92</li>
</ul>



<p>The MATIC price analysis for 25 March confirms that MATIC is facing a strong battle around the $1 mark as it continues to struggle around that level. However, bulls aim for an immediate surge.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC price analysis 1-day chart: Polygon struggles to meet buyers’ demand</h3>



<p>Analyzing the daily price chart of Polygon, MATIC’s price witnessed a bearish rally after bulls were unsuccessful in pushing the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/altcoin/">altcoin</a> above immediate Fib levels. Over the last 24 hours, MATIC price has been consolidating around the $1 mark as both traders fail to validate a clear trend. The 24-hour volume declined to $55 million, showing a decreased interest in trading activity today. MATIC price is currently trading at $1.02, increasing by over 3.4% in the last 24 hours.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-01-18-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501293" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-01-18-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-01-18-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-01-18-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-01-18-1536x671.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-01-18.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The RSI-14 trend line has declined from its previous level and currently hovers around 47-level, showing that bulls are slowly losing the momentum of the price. The SMA-14 level suggests upward volatility in the next few hours.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC/USD 4-hour price chart: Bulls aim for a surge above EMA trend lines</h3>



<p>The 4-hour MATIC price chart suggests MATIC price continues to experience bearish activity around EMA lines, creating a negative sentiment on the price chart. As the price continues to face resistance near immediate Fib level, bulls are aiming to prevent further declines by sending the price above EMA20.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-21-38-1200x524.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-501294" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-21-38-1200x524.jpg 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-21-38-300x131.jpg 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-21-38-768x335.jpg 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-21-38-1536x670.jpg 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_12-21-38.jpg 1815w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The BoP indicator is trading in a bearish region at 0.02, hinting that sellers are trying to build pressure near resistance levels and boost a downward correction.</p>



<p>However, the MACD trend line has formed green candles above the signal line and the indicator aims for a positive momentum, strengthening bullish positions.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from MATIC price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The hourly price chart confirms bears are making efforts to prevent the MATIC price from an immediate surge. However, if MATIC price successfully breaks above $1.09, it may surge higher and touch the resistance at $1.28.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_11-55-20-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501295" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_11-55-20-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_11-55-20-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_11-55-20-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_11-55-20-1536x670.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-25_11-55-20.png 1815w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>If bulls cannot initiate a surge, MATIC price may drop below the immediate support line at $0.92, resulting in a correction to $0.69.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News/Opinions on MATIC</h2>



<p><strong>Outage</strong>: Polygon&#8217;s zkEVM is down due to a sequencer issue, affecting only this layer-2 Ethereum scaling solution. Other chains using Polygon&#8217;s CDK remain unaffected, the company informed its two million X followers.</p>



<p><strong>Controversy: </strong>The Polygon ecosystem has faced recent controversies, with the latest focusing on the Polygon Foundation. Accusations suggest it misused and sold off large amounts of MATIC, impacting holders.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ Polygon allocation problems and suspicious flows to exchanges.<br><br>Let&#39;s look at a very large project and explore how the allocations were not done in line with the publicly stated plan. And show some, um, suspicious flows to an exchange.<br><br>This has been part of our demo for quite…</p>&mdash; ChainArgos (@ChainArgos) <a href="https://twitter.com/ChainArgos/status/1746737284924440724?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 15, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p><strong>Partnership:</strong> Fox Corporation has introduced the Verify platform, a blockchain-based system for companies to monitor their content&#8217;s online usage. Developed in collaboration with Polygon Labs, this platform aims to track the origin and history of media used by AI firms.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Prediction By Cryptopolitan&nbsp;</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/Mll4H9Xucb-mkwui8j3CxTWOcMvXUxqKTp1qBNfZMTvyD2rUV0SWepYODjJo_CZRdMljGudpwx9MpugI9Nb2Kwp_FLI7cO3NIoODD0hDP8JnSP0KuzPUs_9-wuk07OWqfHO4YO3FbXv7w1AGahUWkhE" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum ($)</td><td>Average ($)</td><td>Maximum ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>1.08</td><td>1.11</td><td>1.8</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>1.62</td><td>1.67</td><td>2.41</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>2.43</td><td>2.52</td><td>2.80</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>3.42</td><td>3.52</td><td>4.27</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>4.98</td><td>5.16</td><td>6.00</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>7.02</td><td>7.28</td><td>8.47</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>10.39</td><td>10.68</td><td>12.35</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>14.65</td><td>15.08</td><td>17.85</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>21.09</td><td>21.70</td><td>25.73</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>29.83</td><td>30.91</td><td>35.66</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>The price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum value of $1.08 in 2024. The Polygon price could reach a maximum value of $1.8 with the average trading price of $1.11 throughout 2024.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>The price of 1 Polygon is expected to reach a minimum level of $1.62 in 2025. The MATIC price can reach a maximum level of $2.41 with the average price of $1.67 throughout 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC Price Forecast for 2026</h4>



<p>Polygon price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $2.43 in 2026. As per our findings, the MATIC price could reach a maximum possible level of $2.80 with the average forecast price of $2.52.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>As per the forecast and technical analysis, in 2027 the price of Polygon is expected to reach a minimum price value of $3.42. The MATIC price can reach a maximum price value of $4.27 with the average value of $3.52.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>As per the forecast price and technical analysis, in 2028 the price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum level of $4.98. The MATIC price can reach a maximum level of $6.00 with the average trading price of $5.16.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Polygon price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $7.02 in 2029. As per our findings, the MATIC price could reach a maximum possible level of $8.47 with the average forecast price of $7.28.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>The price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum value of $10.39 in 2030. The Polygon price could reach a maximum value of $12.35 with the average trading price of $10.68 throughout 2030.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Forecast 2031</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of MATIC, in 2031 the price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum level of $14.65. The MATIC price can reach a maximum level of $17.85 with the average trading price of $15.08.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>The price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum level of $21.09 in 2032. The Polygon price can reach a maximum level of $25.73 with the average price of $21.70 throughout 2032.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of MATIC, in 2033 the price of Polygon is forecasted to be at around a minimum value of $29.83. The Polygon price value can reach a maximum of $35.66 with the average trading value of $30.91.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction By Coincodex</h3>



<p>According to Coincodex&#8217;s current Polygon price prediction, Polygon&#8217;s price is expected to increase by 14.63%, reaching $1.159450 by March 10, 2024. Coincodex&#8217;s technical indicators suggest that the market sentiment is currently Bullish, with the Fear &amp; Greed Index indicating a score of 90 (Extreme Greed).</p>



<p>Over the past 30 days, Polygon has seen 17 out of 30 (57%) days of price increase, with a volatility of 10.05%. Based on Coincodex&#8217;s forecast, this period is considered an opportune time to invest in Polygon. Further analysis of Polygon&#8217;s historical price trends and the impact of Bitcoin halving cycles leads to a prediction of a yearly low for Polygon at $1.011490 in 2025, while its price could soar to as high as $3.66 in the following year.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Forecast By Digital Coin Price</h3>



<p>According to projections from Digital Coin Price, analysts and experts anticipate that by 2026, MATIC will commence the year with a value of $3.01 and fluctuate around $3.60. This projection suggests a significant increase from the previous year, marking a considerable growth for Polygon.</p>



<p>Looking ahead to 2033, Litecoin is expected to attempt reaching a low of $1,558.64. Efforts might be made to achieve a maximum and ascend to the next premium tier of $1,614.05, with an average forecast price set at $1,605.31. There is potential for Litecoin to surpass its previous high and advance to a new level. While there&#8217;s optimism for progress to its subsequent stage, it&#8217;s also acknowledged that there could be a downturn.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction By CryptoPredictions.com</h3>



<p>According to CryptoPredictions.com’s Polygon prediction, Polygon is forecasted to begin April 2024 with a value of $1.280 and close the month at $1.542. Throughout April, the highest predicted price for MATIC is $1.827, while the lowest anticipated price stands at $1.242.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Overview</h2>



<p>Polygon serves as a multi-layered protocol suite aimed at resolving the scalability challenges associated with the Ethereum network. By operating a separate but compatible blockchain, Polygon efficiently processes transactions before syncing them back to the main Ethereum chain. This method alleviates the strain on the Ethereum network, enabling faster transaction speeds and reducing costs to a fraction of a cent.</p>



<p>Previously known as Matic Network, Polygon offers a user-friendly framework that allows both new and existing blockchain projects to operate on the Ethereum platform without worrying about scalability constraints.</p>



<p>With Polygon, users can seamlessly engage with decentralized applications (DApps) without concerns over network bottlenecks. The company is led by CEO Jaynti Kanani, who co-founded the project with Sandeep Nailwal, the Chief Operating Officer, and Anurag Arjun, the Chief Product Officer. The team initially launched the project as Matic Network in 2017.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price History</h2>



<p>According to Polygon&#8217;s plan, all Matic coins will be released by December 2022, which is good news for long-term investors because it guarantees significant future gains.</p>



<p>Since its inception in 2017, Matic tokens have had an incredible run that has withstood the test of unforgiving crypto market turmoil that usually ends up wiping out invalid tokens.</p>



<p>Despite the prevailing bearish trend currently experienced in the crypto market, experts are convinced by Matic’s crypto price prognosis and price forecast data that indicate an overall bullish trend for the long-term investment horizon.</p>



<p>Based on Coingecko&#8217;s data, Polygon has recorded impressive gains since its launch back in 2017. The crypto token has recorded incredible gains of up to 44157.6%, and the rally is expected to continue in the following years.</p>



<p>Matic recorded its all-time low price of $0.003143 in May 2019 during the famous bearish run. However, since then, the coin has continued to make significant gains until May 2021, when it recorded a new all-time high price of $2.62. It seems then that May is the month of Polygon, after all.</p>



<p>Polygon&#8217;s price has been on the rise since it hit a high of $1 at the end of July, and experts are predicting that as Polygon&#8217;s network continues to grow with new partnerships and adoption, the value of its token could go even higher. In August, Polygon&#8217;s price hovered around the $0.80 mark, but many believe that this is just the beginning of this promising project.</p>



<p>Recently, in November, Polygon saw a significant surge after the bullish news that the social media giant Meta is teaming up with the blockchain to deliver its journey into the world of Web3 and NFTs.</p>



<p>Stephane Kasriel, head of commerce and financial technologies at Meta, revealed that Instagram businesses will soon be able to create and sell their own NFTs (non-fungible tokens). This service would first launch on the Polygon blockchain before expanding to others, including Solana. MATIC rocketed after this news and hit a high of $1.29 on 7 November.&nbsp; After peaking and later announcing multiple partnerships, including an NFT marketplace deal with Nike, MATIC eventually fell below the $1 barrier.</p>



<p>Just this past year, Polygon (@0xPolygon) has rolled out some incredible features on Twitter. From the launch of a new Token List service to mobile burning capabilities for MATIC tokens, they have allowed users to interact with MATIC in an efficient and secure manner. This means you can now access the MATIC burn console through your mobile wallet with a simplified interface that is easy to use.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" width="1114" height="404" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241.png" alt="Screenshot 1241" class="wp-image-179749" style="width:1016px;height:368px" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241.png 1114w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-300x109.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-768x279.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-24x9.png 24w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-36x13.png 36w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-48x17.png 48w" sizes="(max-width: 1114px) 100vw, 1114px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on Polygon (MATIC)</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What&#8217;s Polygon (MATIC)?</h3>



<p>Polygon is the leading platform for Ethereum scaling and infrastructure development. Its growing suite of products offers developers easy access to all major scaling and infrastructure solutions: L2 solutions, sidechains, hybrid solutions, stand-alone and enterprise chains, data availability solutions, and more. Polygon’s scaling solutions have widespread adoption with 3000+ applications hosted, 1B+ total transactions processed, ~100M+ unique user addresses, and $5B+ in assets secured.</p>



<p>Mina Protocol&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://polygon.technology/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Polygon</a>&nbsp;are working towards implementing support for Mina on Polygon PoS. This bridge will enable developers building applications on Polygon to leverage privacy and verifiability via Mina’s zero knowledge-SNARK-based protocol.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Use Cases</h3>



<p>Ethereum-based Polygon hopes to solve fundamental issues the Ethereum blockchain faces, such as interoperability and scalability. It is the first project on the Ethereum blockchain to launch an adequately structured tool that addresses the Ethereum scaling problem. Consequently, many have termed Polygon as an<strong> Ethereum scaling solution.</strong></p>



<p>Rather than running on its own blockchain, MATIC tokens are traded on the&nbsp;Ethereum&nbsp;blockchain. That’s because&nbsp;Polygon&nbsp;was developed to help scale Ethereum through side chains.&nbsp;MATIC allows you to stake on the Ethereum&nbsp;<a href="https://www.gobankingrates.com/investing/crypto/what-is-blockchain-technology/?utm_campaign=1177634&amp;utm_source=nasdaq.com&amp;utm_content=5&amp;utm_medium=rss" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">blockchain</a>&nbsp;and pay for currency transactions. This has helped reduce the high transaction costs inherent in the Ethereum blockchain, helping promote widespread adoption.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Another thing, Ethereum is home to several <strong>DeFi projects</strong> like the Polygon, formerly known as the Matic network. Since the Matic network has brought numerous functionalities to the entire Ethereum blockchain, several developers have taken an interest in the project, which has, in turn, led to steady growth of Matic price. </p>



<p>Major cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, etc., witnessed a slump on the 1st week of June, and yet, the value of Polygon(MATIC) rose nearly 35% in the same period. Investors saw Polygon (MATIC) as the next big thing, and in a short period, it surged past other cryptos to rank among the <a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/cryptocurrency/heres-how-india-based-polygonmatic-outperformed-other-major-cryptos/articleshow/83329658.cms" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">top 15 biggest cryptos</a> globally. Polygon successfully converts the limited Ethereum blockchain into an open blockchain network usable by many. In essence, it makes Ethereum steady as the internet of blockchains.</p>



<p>In turn, Polygon (Matic) project benefits immensely from the already-established Ethereum blockchain in several ways. Firstly, every blockchain project needs a secure security infrastructure; the Matic network benefits from Ethereum&#8217;s array of qualities, such as an active and vibrant community, established security systems, and transparency.</p>



<p>Within the Polygon network, transactions are settled using the Matic coin. Matic price has risen over the years, sparking interest from cryptocurrency enthusiasts. Polygon technology has improved efficiency within the Ethereum blockchain. Today, Polygon boasts of handling up to 65,000 transactions per second on its single sidechain. Similarly, it has averaged an impressive block confirmation time of two seconds per transaction.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Pros and cons of investing in Polygon (Matic)</h3>



<p>Polygon, formerly Matic network, has been considered a stable investment by crypto enthusiasts. Anyone interested in Ethereum and its bundle of projects likely has an affinity for Matic.</p>



<p>It is a well-structured organization with clear goals of extending the scalability of the Ethereum blockchain and making cryptocurrency more accessible to the public. If the project continues to push forward strides, its success is inevitable, and consequently, Matic holders will benefit significantly.</p>



<p>Investing is a full-time activity that requires individuals to analyze potential risks and returns before committing. However, within the crypto world, numerous uncertainties shape the prices of crypto coins. Therefore, even for a seasoned professional, it is challenging to make precise predictions on the price of a coin based on historical price actions alone.</p>



<p>However, for an individual to earn impressive returns on their investments, they must take risks. Here, we&#8217;ll discuss some of the benefits of investing in the Polygon ecosystem.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pros of investing in Matic</h4>



<p>Since Matic is a scaling solution on the Ethereum blockchain, it is difficult to foresee its downfall. Therefore, most forecasts are convinced that Polygon will be in existence for years to come. So what are some of the pros of investing in this token?</p>



<ul>
<li>It provides new scaling solutions to the Ethereum ecosystem, ensuring a bright future and allowing investors to make long-term investments.</li>



<li>Since 67% of the tokens are already in circulation, and the maximum supply is expected to be realized by December 2022, the coin offers immense growth potential in 2022 and beyond, allowing investors to reap more profits.</li>



<li>Matic allows for the interconnection of blockchain networks, a scaling solution that assures investors of Matic&#8217;s future performance.</li>



<li>Polygon is supported by a strong community of developers that ensures the project performs well and consequently maintains and increases Matic&#8217;s price level.</li>
</ul>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Cons of investing in Matic</h4>



<p>It is indeed public knowledge that investments always come with a degree of risk. Investing in Matic may result in losses if careful considerations of the involved risks aren&#8217;t well conducted. Below are some possible shortcomings of investment in Matic.</p>



<ul>
<li>Recently, the Polygon network was hacked, and the perpetrators made away with millions worth of Matic tokens. The hacking was a huge red flag for investors since it indicates that the network isn&#8217;t as secure as it should be.</li>



<li>Price volatility. Every cryptocurrency experiences volatility; however, when dealing, sometimes crypto coins experience extreme price drops that may hurt an individual&#8217;s portfolio. Since Matic already competes with Avalance, Polkadot, and Cosmos, it is unclear who will win the race. Therefore, for a long time horizon, investors should keep tabs and know when to exit.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="Conclusion">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Despite the short-term volatility, Polygon&#8217;s investors remain confident that it can reach double digits in no time. For instance, Lark Davis (@TheCryptoLark) confidently tweeted about his MATIC holdings expecting it to hit $10 soon.</p>



<p>Polygon has been actively forging relationships with various companies in the crypto space and staying abreast of current blockchain technology trends. Here are some recent updates, as announced by Polygon:</p>



<ul>
<li>The Polygon Mainnet is now live in Alpha and Beta versions.</li>



<li>Support for deposits and withdrawals of all Ethereum-based assets</li>



<li>Support of ERC721 to ERC20, ERC20 to ERC20, and ERC721 to ERC721 transactions enabled</li>



<li>Increasing the number and capabilities of Proof-of-Stake validators</li>



<li>Offering the API and SDK toolkit for dApp infrastructure development</li>



<li>Supernets, a new blockchain network, is ready to skyrocket with Polygon&#8217;s $100 million investment toward businesses taking advantage of its powerful technology.</li>
</ul>



<p>With partnerships and increased adoption, MATIC prices are expected to continue to surge. If investors and traders can take advantage of these bullish signs, they could enjoy significant profits. However, it is important to keep in mind that the cryptocurrency space is highly volatile and risky so always do your own research before investing.</p>



<p>There are many factors influencing the future of MATIC coin, from global economic conditions to the level of adoption of cryptocurrencies. The partnership with Meta and the latest breakout on the platform appear to be positive indicators for the coin&#8217;s future price, according to predictions from algorithm-based forecasting sites.</p>



<p>Overall, scaling solutions like Polygon are expected to gain momentum as network congestion on the Ethereum blockchain remains an issue. Polygon&#8217;s multi-layer technology allows it to authenticate transactions in a matter of seconds while still uploading them to the Ethereum blockchain, combining scalability and security. </p>



<p>Polygon&#8217;s powerful Dapp architecture makes it simple to build new apps on-chain and port current Ethereum projects. However, MATIC is projected to continue <strong>dipping by a few cents before beginning another price increase soon. Before making any investment decisions, do your </strong>research.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/polygon-price-prediction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-MATIC-_1140x570.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-MATIC-_1140x570.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Price Prediction for 2024 &#8211; 2033: Will APT Token Hold Bullish Hopes?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/aptos-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Koome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=295350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aptos Price Prediction 2024-2033 As we venture into 2024 to 2033, the period is critical for Aptos as it strives to establish itself as a significant blockchain platform. The rapidly changing market dynamics, technological advancements, and evolving adoption trends will undoubtedly shape Aptos’s path. Against this backdrop, investors and stakeholders are keen to gain insights [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/aptos-price-prediction/#aptos-price-prediction-2024"><u>Aptos Price Prediction 2024</u></a> – up to $19.10</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/aptos-price-prediction/#aptos-price-prediction-2027"><u>Aptos Price Prediction 2027</u></a> – up to $58.16</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/aptos-price-prediction/#aptos-price-prediction-2030"><u>Aptos Price Prediction 2030</u></a> – up to $187.41</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/aptos-price-prediction/#aptos-price-prediction-2033"><u>Aptos Price Prediction 2033</u></a> – up to $588.36</li>
</ul>



<p>As we venture into 2024 to 2033, the period is critical for Aptos as it strives to establish itself as a significant <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> platform. The rapidly changing market dynamics, technological advancements, and evolving adoption trends will undoubtedly shape Aptos’s path. Against this backdrop, investors and stakeholders are keen to gain insights into Aptos’s potential price movements and discern the factors that might influence its growth.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is the APT token worth?</h4>



<p>The current Aptos price is $16.23, with a 24-hour trading volume of $301 million. Aptos is down 0.66% in the last 24 hours. The current market cap ranking is #22, with a live market cap of $6.43 billion. It has a circulating supply of 396,250,668 coins.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">APTOS price analysis</h2>



<p>TL; DR Breakdown</p>



<ul>
<li>APT’s bullish trend started in October 2023.</li>



<li>It is up 72.40% in the last 30 days.</li>
</ul>



<p>A massive token unlock by Aptos released a staggering 24.84 million APT tokens, constituting 6.29% of the total circulating supply of APT tokens in March. Another similar unlock is incoming in April. The impact of such large-scale token unlocks on the crypto market remains a concern and interest.</p>



<p>APT started recovering in October 2023. It is up 35.55% from the last 12 months and 72.40% from the previous 30 days.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">APT price analysis 1-day chart</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/zVUyVxsWzfmpGVMU8mKF-r2RgM5gU7y16nmhnLKf7ybZLs6CDpjmfcv8pyYbX-f8GqpO32395YwWQowpvAHwm1-vfZso25ALzV_Qkxp_-qM0LPvjDDLagQ4aj5wawJAJ3LDpHUNGUnnHiWsHDYmVJoI" alt="" /></figure>



<p>The MACD indicator shows the coin registered positive momentum with a significant pump last week, pushing the coin above $16. The RSI is within the 30-70 neutral zone, which indicates the price is trending neutral, with the price being able to keep RSI in the last two months.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">APT/ USD 4-hour price chart: APT momentum slows</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/BtS50-nPt3aMFCoM7ck9meqtzHuEyY-gyB5seBQrm6LZVImUxkTHStKMEIxThI-0vANzxNZesVRuOSHEFRT0fHv-T_BqYeUy3MlEySukmvbE6R_SEoKsAimNRVJBPPgLN2HihPEgYl1ZMIum8u5eFIY" alt="" /></figure>



<p>The 4-hour chart highlights the APT price movement this month. The coin registers negative momentum, with its RSI at 56.25.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from APT price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The analysis shows that APT is in a bull run. The coin should move higher in the short term, considering the momentum.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News</h2>



<p>Google Cloud&#8217;s recent partnership with Aptos Labs to integrate gaming into the web3 landscape through the support of &#8220;Aptos GameStack&#8221; signifies a notable advancement in blockchain technology within video games. This collaboration enhances gaming experiences by incorporating Google Cloud&#8217;s analytics, AI, and machine learning technologies into Aptos&#8217; blockchain framework, making web3 technologies more accessible to mainstream gaming. The initiative could substantially influence the web3 gaming sector, which has already seen a surge in value beyond $30 billion, driven by investor interest in high-risk opportunities. This partnership and the development of Aptos GameStack, featuring advanced integration tools for developers, are poised to boost the price of APT by aligning with the growing enthusiasm and investment in the web3 gaming space.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is Aptos a good Investment?</h2>



<p>The Aptos <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> promises you all the infrastructure you need to build your next big idea. Aptos is gaining momentum in crypto, boasting over 1.6 million active monthly users and 427 million plus transactions. The Aptos token is central to the activity, with more applications in games, NFTs, and apps built on the Aptos blockchain. Most retailers consider it a great investment. Our Cryptopolitan Price Prediction section will show how the coin will gain value in years to come.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2024 -2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/xvGJ3wgXlRUzCaAbAP2icruibmVUMq5C2sLnaB-yoMiutA7OILo-DXcaXzgciJZkMJIoOQFyyyc493iFy7D_2zK5c4mtgzd5_OidsvnEsQdvUlXxIDfqYeRMRwYdDMv_qFL95uYha8T23ZQ7tDTRpKE" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum ($)</td><td>Average ($)</td><td>Maximum ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>$16.03</td><td>$16.63</td><td>$19.10</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>$22.13</td><td>$22.80</td><td>$27.82</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>$32.96</td><td>$34.10</td><td>$38.47</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>$51.32</td><td>$53.03</td><td>$58.16</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>$74.93</td><td>$77.05</td><td>$90.48</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>$107.02</td><td>$110.88</td><td>$128.55</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>$156.66</td><td>$161.09</td><td>$187.41</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>$234.54</td><td>$240.98</td><td>$270.46</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>$338.10</td><td>$350.15</td><td>$397.84</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>$506.29</td><td>$523.79</td><td>$588.36</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to our Aptos APT price prediction for 2024, we expect a minimum price of $16.03 and an average price of $16.63. However, if Aptos growth trajectory persists, we predict its value could reach as high as $19.10 at its peak.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>According to our Aptos APT price prediction for 2025, the minimum price of APT will be $22.13, while the average price will be around $22.80. There is potential for significant growth in the value of Aptos APT during this period, with the token possibly reaching a maximum price of $27.82 by the end of 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">APTOS Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>According to the price prediction for 2026, we expect the minimum price of the coin to be $32.96 and an average predicted value of $34.10. We expect APT’s price to surge to a maximum level of $38.47 by 2026.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>Our Aptos price prediction 2027 is a minimum price value of $51.32, with an average trading price of $53.03. Based on the Aptos APT price prediction for 2027, the price could reach a maximum of $58.16 during the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Based on our APTOS APT price prediction for 2028, the APT token is anticipated to experience a bullish trend with a predicted floor price of $74.93 and an average trading value of $77.05. The highest possible price for 2028 is estimated to reach $90.48.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our Aptos APT price prediction for 2029 suggests that the minimum price level could be $107.02. The APT token will experience significant growth, with a maximum potential price value of $128.55 and an average projected value of $110.88.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>Aptos’s price prediction for 2030, the cryptocurrency’s value may drop to a low of $156.66 by year-end. However, we expect the average trading price to be $161.09 and the maximum estimated price to reach as high as $187.41.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>Based on our Aptos APT price prediction for 2031, the minimum price of APT will be approximately $234.54, while the average price will be around $240.98. The maximum estimated value for APT in 2031 will reach $270.46.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>According to our Aptos APT price prediction for 2032, the APT coin will increase steadily. However, the minimum price of the coin will be $338.10. The average trading price is estimated at $350.15, indicating steady growth. The maximum estimated price of Aptos for 2032 is $397.84, showing a potential surge in price.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>In our 2033 Aptos APT price prediction, we anticipate a minimum trading price of $506.29 and an average value of $523.79 for the token. Aptos APT will experience a surge in value and reach a maximum price of $588.36.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Predictions by Walletinvestor</h3>



<p>Wallet Investor uses technical analysis to provide the Apt price forecast. According to the platform’s price prediction, Aptos’ past performance index rating is C; it adds that APT would make a bad one-year investment. The expected average price in 2025 will be $11.297. Aptos’s return on investment (ROI) will be -8.844% in 2025; in 2026, it will be -10.217%; in 2027, it will be -12.910%.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Predictions by CryptoPredictions</h3>



<p>The site scans a coin’s exchange rates and other historical market data and uses these data to provide Aptos price forecast. In 2024, APT will trade at an average price of $10.676 in June and $12.333 in December. In 2026, APT will sell at an average price of $17.683 in January and $21.903 in December.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price Predictions by Digitalcoinprice</h3>



<p>APTOS will be on a bullish trend from 2024 to 2033; the maximum value of APT for the entire duration will be $240.48. In 2025, it will trade at a mean price of $30.96. It will reach a maximum price of $32.21 and a minimum of $26.73. In 2027, it will trade at a mean price of $54.64. It will reach a maximum price of $56.39 and a minimum of $47.85. In 2033, it will trade at a mean price of $238.06. It will reach a minimum of $233.11.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Predictions By Industry Experts</h3>



<p>An analysis by ‘<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/"><u>Binance</u></a>,’ the world’s largest crypto exchange by trading volumes, indicates that it will trade at $13.02 in 2025, $14.35 in 2027, and $16.62 in 2030.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>MARKET CAP</td><td>CIRCULATING SUPPLY</td><td>ALL-TIME LOW</td><td>ALL-TIME HIGH</td><td>POPULARITY</td></tr><tr><td>$4.66 billion</td><td>368,220,999</td><td>$3.09</td><td>$19.90</td><td>#26</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>Layer-one protocols such as <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u>Ethereum</u></a>, Solana, BNB Smart Chain, and Avalanche have been hot topics in crypto. The astronomical rise of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) exposed the limitations of many blockchains struggling to handle mainstream adoption.</p>



<p>Before <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u>Ethereum</u></a>’s transition to Proof-of-Stake, network congestion and sky-high transaction fees were prevalent. This led to the belief that only whales could participate in multiple <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u>DeFi</u></a> initiatives on the platform.</p>



<p>Though touted as a high-throughput chain capable of processing thousands of transactions per second (TPS), Solana faced its challenges, with multiple outages rendering the network unusable.</p>



<p>A new player emerged to solve these issues: the Aptos <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u>Blockchain</u></a>. Dubbed by many as “the Solana Killer,” Aptos is a “scalable, safe, reliable, and upgradable” network that has been in development for over three years. Aptos aims at revolutionize the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> space, offering a seamless and robust platform for users and developers alike.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Aptos Price History</h2>



<p>Aptos raised $200 million in March 2022 in a seed round led by the venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz. Other crypto heavyweights like Multicoin Capital and Tiger Global participated in the funding round. In July of the same year, the startup raised another $150 million in a Series A round led by Jump Crypto and Sam Bankman-Fried’s FTX Ventures.</p>



<p>Two months later, <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/markets?ref=16863683" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a> Labs invested an undisclosed amount in Aptos, bringing its valuation to $4 billion. The blockchain launched its mainnet on 12 October 2022.</p>



<p>APT, the blockchain’s native token, marked its all-time low on December 30, 2022. A month later, tables turned as it peaked at an all-time high of $19.90 on January 30, 2023. On that day, Aptos pumped by over 25% in 24 hours, likely due to the blockchain’s non-fungible token market. Collections such as Aptos Monkeys and Aptomingos have attracted more users. APT was bearish in Q1 2023. On 6th June, APT fell below its initial listing price and extended the losses in the preceding months. In October, it started correcting, rising as high as $8.47 in November. In 2024, it broke above the $10 mark.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/wMVyrm2FVI6c8CpPoAPjoVRgm8VKq54n2M5LUtL-4Y6tAXgJzyKYblc_emLsyul6YAiOTIvGKfsU7CpBr_PHdNdFiCMSQy2INBwPsQZE2X1fJlrdR0qvZOvYSuB7ubMtzWyecJt-QQ0-kSiU27z1d1Q" alt="" /></figure>



<p>Source: <u>h<a href="//coinstats.app/coins/aptos/">ttps://coinstats.app/coins/aptos/</a></u></p>



<p></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on the Aptos Network</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Is Aptos Blockchain?</h3>



<p>Aptos, an innovative layer1 blockchain, is built upon the Move programming language and can be considered the successor to Meta’s now-defunct Diem blockchain project.</p>



<p>Centered on scalability, reliability, safety, and upgradeability, Aptos aims to bring ground-breaking concepts to the layer one space, featuring novel consensus mechanisms, performance optimization, system security, and smart contract designs.</p>



<p>With a vision to recreate the cloud infrastructure that powers web2 in a decentralized manner, Aptos strives to establish a comprehensive blockchain solution that paves the way for rapid mainstream adoption of web3. Concurrently, the project is committed to accelerating a dApp ecosystem that addresses real-world challenges.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Founders Behind Aptos Ecosystem&nbsp;</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/sVfgcD9x_oJQroCqjk6-FpbzGm6bK1hz5No4qxlpZkKB6QG7EVBA85c2vG3PMOIsyydZfFTG79UUuywn-pfW1gYjmHladx9xllAZlgIC-DO3LPCpqANOibJzhcqChGRL2FLldHDJB4ZzYXI-yXhWOK0" alt="image 580" /></figure>



<p>Aptos was brought to life by Aptos Labs, a company co-founded by Mo Shaikh (CEO) and Avery Ching (CTO). Shaikh and Ching are former Meta employees with years of experience under their belts as senior developers and engineers in the blockchain industry.</p>



<p>Aptos Labs boasts a diverse and experienced team of skilled designers, engineers, researchers, and strategists working together to drive the project forward.</p>



<p>A significant factor contributing to the buzz surrounding the Aptos crypto project is its intriguing history. While Aptos is an independent blockchain with its unique vision and technology, it has roots in Meta’s discontinued Diem blockchain initiative. A substantial portion of the Aptos team was directly involved in Diem’s creation, design, and development, adding to the project’s interesting narrative.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How Does the Aptos Blockchain Work?</h3>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">PoS with advanced BFT consensus</h4>



<p>Aptos is a robust proof-of-stake (PoS) blockchain that employs a sophisticated Byzantine Fault Tolerance (BFT) consensus mechanism, working with a group of validators responsible for receiving, processing, and validating transactions.</p>



<p>Holders of APT tokens can stake their tokens with validators, which grants each validator a consensus voting weight proportional to the number of tokens staked in their custody. Validators can then utilize their voting weight to actively participate in the consensus process and governance of the blockchain.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Light and full node clients</h4>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/AFB3fJaqZUVxcibLq5e3ToqhNANimL_vJZBIK4Vmu2dDxMPjbt-em5Vm0u9Cy9Mrob5gnF6PjISrFYZ05His8_14pihLTLK6Bg9hItqWkC3R8cL8TQ8wCBD83fC8rLZFbd8wIIZHXkG9dwRNb6n7_Rg" alt="image 577" /></figure>



<p>Aptos categorizes its clients into two distinct groups — full node and light clients.</p>



<p>Full node clients maintain a complete copy of the Aptos transaction ledger, while light clients store a streamlined version. Both types of clients communicate with validators to inquire about the ledger’s history and current state before submitting transactions to be appended.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Move programming language</h4>



<p>Aptos’ whitepaper states that it employs the Move programming language’s object model to depict the state of its ledger. Move, a relatively new programmable platform for blockchains, smart contracts, and other applications, was initially developed for Facebook (now Meta) for its discontinued crypto/blockchain projects, Libra and Diem.</p>



<p>The Aptos team asserts that Move’s advanced smart contract language is ideal for facilitating swift and secure transactions. Move simplifies the auditing and analysis of the blockchain and smart contracts that utilize it.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Parallel transaction processing</h4>



<p>The Aptos blockchain supports parallel transaction processing, essential for achieving high scalability and throughput. By optimizing a multi-threaded, in-memory parallel engine using BlockSTM, it can deliver over 160,000 non-trivial Move transactions per second.</p>



<p>The underlying infrastructure is designed for complex atomic transactions, ensuring transaction viability protection. Each transaction is fully completed or doesn’t occur at all. This approach enables secure peer-to-peer trustless transactions with no intermediary.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">The Aptos Token (APT)</h3>



<p>The Aptos token (APT) is the native cryptocurrency within the Aptos ecosystem. At one point, the project faced controversy when it planned to launch the Aptos token without providing any public information—no details on total supply, distribution, or even a general roadmap. However, after receiving backlash from the community, the Aptos team made amends and shared most of the necessary details through a blog post.</p>



<p>The Mainnet officially launched on October 12, 2022, with an initial token supply of 1 billion. APT features eight digits of precision, and each minimal unit is called an Octa.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>Since its inception, Aptos appears to have successfully integrated various projects. This is a promising development, as it expands the ecosystem’s reach and potential for growth.</p>



<p>With its current trajectory and sub-second transaction times, the Aptos crypto project holds the potential to surpass many of its rivals in the long run, provided it continues on this path. However, it is advised to research and conduct good investment advice before investing in the volatile crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/82ESfrV4J6w" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/82ESfrV4J6w" />
			<media:title type="plain">APTOS (apt) Price Prediction for the Bull Market in 2024/2025</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[APTOS (apt) Price Prediction for the Bull Market in 2024/2025  APTOS (apt) Crypto Price, APTOS (apt) Technical analysis and APTOS (apt)  Price Predictionapt,...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Solidity-2.png" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Solidity-2.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Solidity-2.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prediction 2024-2033: Will Bitcoin Bulls Rally?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bitcoin-price-forecast/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shayan Chowdhury]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=84135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BTC Price Predictions 2024-2033 How much is Bitcoin (BTC) worth? Today, the price of Bitcoin stands at $67,474, with a trading volume over the past 24 hours reaching $24 billion. Its market capitalization is $1.3 trillion, and it currently commands 54% of the market share. Over the last 24 hours, the BTC price has experienced [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BTC Price Predictions 2024-2033</h3>



<ul>
<li><a href="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2023" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2023">B</a><a href="#Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-2024" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2023">itcoin Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; up to <strong>$71,373.32</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-2027" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2026">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2027 &#8211; up to <strong>$2,13,504.58</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-2029" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2029">Bitcoin Price Prediction 20</a><a href="#Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-2030" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2029">30 </a><a href="#Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-2029" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2029">&#8211; up to <strong>$5,90,158.57</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-2033" data-type="internal" data-id="#Bitcoin-(BTC)-Price-Prediction-2032">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2033- up to <strong>$17,07,069.67</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How much is Bitcoin (BTC) worth?</h3>



<p>Today, the price of Bitcoin stands at $67,474, with a trading volume over the past 24 hours reaching $24 billion. Its market capitalization is $1.3 trillion, and it currently commands 54% of the market share. Over the last 24 hours, the BTC price has experienced a 4.9% increase. As for its circulating supply, 19.46 million BTC are in circulation out of a maximum possible supply of 21 million BTC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin price analysis: BTC price surges toward $68K but faces bearish pressure</h2>



<p><strong>TL; DR Breakdown</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>BTC price analysis shows that Bitcoin faced a bullish pattern as the price surged toward $68K</li>



<li>Resistance for BTC is present at $69,116</li>



<li>Support for BTC/USD is present at $65,639</li>
</ul>



<p>The BTC price analysis for 25 March confirms that bulls sparked a solid buying pressure as BTC price plunged sellers’ confidence by heading toward the $67K mark. However, BTC price prepares for a short-term correction in the coming hours.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BTC price analysis 1-day chart: Bitcoin price charges toward $68K</h3>



<p>Analyzing the daily price chart of Bitcoin, BTC’s price is witnessing a robust buying pressure as the price continued to surge above immediate Fib channels and headed toward the $68K level. However, the price is facing a bearish slowdown near that level. The 24-hour volume has surged to $14.6 million, showing an increased interest in trading activity today. BTC price is currently trading at $67,474, increasing by over 4.9% in the last 24 hours.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-09-41-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501288" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-09-41-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-09-41-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-09-41-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-09-41-1536x670.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-09-41.png 1815w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The RSI-14 trend line has declined from its previous level and currently trades near the midline at level 53, hinting that a correction is on the edge. The SMA-14 level suggests volatility in the next few hours.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BTC/USD 4-hour price chart: Bears aim for a correction below moving averages</h3>



<p>The 4-hour Bitcoin price chart suggests that bears are strengthening their position as they are aiming to send the price below the Fib lines. However, bulls are holding buying confidence and are aiming to defend a decline by holding the price above the EMA20 trend line.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-31-50-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501289" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-31-50-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-31-50-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-31-50-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-31-50-1536x670.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_11-31-50.png 1815w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The BoP indicator is trading in a negative region at 0.02, showing that short-term sellers are taking a chance to accelerate a downward trend.</p>



<p>However, the MACD trend line has formed bullish candles above the signal line and the indicator aims for a positive momentum, strengthening long-position holders’ confidence.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from BTC price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The hourly price chart confirms that Bitcoin attempts to drop below the immediate support line; however, bulls are eyeing for further recovery rally in the upcoming hours. If BTC’s price successfully holds its momentum above $69,116, it will fuel a bullish rally to $73,870.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="524" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_10-58-01-1200x524.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501290" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_10-58-01-1200x524.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_10-58-01-300x131.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_10-58-01-768x335.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_10-58-01-1536x671.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-25_10-58-01.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>If bulls fail to initiate a surge, BTC price may drop below the immediate support line at $65,639, which may begin a bearish trend to $62,446.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is Bitcoin A Good Investment? </h2>



<p>Bitcoin has historically presented the opportunity for significant returns due to its decentralized nature. Bitcoin also holds the potential to act as an asset that does not correlate with the broader market trends, akin to gold. This characteristic suggests that it could move independently of other assets such as stocks. Additionally, the recent launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs has made it a good investment option with bright market potential. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent BTC News/Opinions</h2>



<p><strong>Spot ETF Outflow</strong>: ETFs linked to Bitcoin saw $742 million withdrawn in three days, reflecting a shift from its peak demand. Despite this, they&#8217;ve attracted $11.4 billion since launch, with the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust reporting $13.3 billion in outflows.</p>



<p><strong>Morgan Stanley In Bitcoin ETF</strong>: Morgan Stanley is evaluating the possibility of offering spot bitcoin ETFs on its brokerage platform, following the SEC&#8217;s approval of these products. This move by one of Wall Street&#8217;s largest broker-dealers aims to meet growing client interest in cryptocurrencies and could lead to a significant increase in investments once major financial platforms begin offering these ETFs.</p>



<p><strong>SEC Approves Spot Bitcoin ETF:</strong> U.S. authorities have given the green light to Bitcoin ETFs, significantly expanding the reach of the 15-year-old digital currency. The Securities and Exchange Commission announced on Wednesday that it has validated essential documents from market operators aiming to list these innovative offerings. Trading of these ETFs is set to commence on Thursday.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Predictions By Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/g7QaPDZZsWoeLW0xvkXOKUYA31jvMNZa40h4ZGxzpMbxQZbdzzz9OUqJ84owCBC1OqrELSMnMUNcxckvYDDRU7uIKAeWyTpISWEVghDtCcXTOpWnEEAyTdmduhgAvhin49BM9kneQbQQB_AzGdYaTc8" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum ($)</td><td>Average ($)</td><td>Maximum ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>58,828.51</td><td>60,990.40</td><td>71,373.32</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>83,023.53</td><td>86,073.05</td><td>1,04,164.06</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>1,23,227.79</td><td>1,27,531.44</td><td>1,45,360.74</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>1,70,141.77</td><td>1,76,518.34</td><td>2,13,504.58</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>2,42,028.31</td><td>2,49,089.04</td><td>2,91,244.07</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>3,39,040.77</td><td>3,51,495.22</td><td>4,16,401.30</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>4,77,127.53</td><td>4,91,187.34</td><td>5,90,158.57</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>6,68,566.27</td><td>6,93,125.64</td><td>8,14,116.30</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>10,02,294.49</td><td>10,36,950.77</td><td>11,69,615.41</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>13,66,048.54</td><td>14,07,526.57</td><td>17,07,069.67</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>In 2024, the expected minimum price of 1 Bitcoin is $58,828.51. The maximum price level could be $71,373.32, with an average price of $60,990.40 throughout the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>For 2025, Bitcoin&#8217;s price is anticipated to reach a minimum of $83,023.53. It may peak at $104,164.06, with the average price hovering around $86,073.05 during the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BTC Price Forecast for 2026</h4>



<p>According to forecasts and technical analysis, Bitcoin&#8217;s price in 2026 might start at a minimum of $123,227.79. The peak price could be $145,360.74, with an average value of $127,531.44.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>In 2027, the lowest forecasted price for Bitcoin is $170,141.77. The peak price might reach $213,504.58, with an average price expected to be $176,518.34.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>The 2028 forecast for Bitcoin&#8217;s price suggests a minimum value of $242,028.31. It could reach a maximum of $291,244.07, averaging around $249,089.04 throughout the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Based on extensive technical analysis, the 2029 prediction for Bitcoin&#8217;s price is a minimum of $339,040.77. The maximum price might be $416,401.30, with an average of $351,495.22.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>In 2030, Bitcoin&#8217;s price is expected to be at least $477,127.53. The maximum price could reach $590,158.57, with an average value of $491,187.34.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Forecast 2031</h4>



<p>For 2031, the forecast suggests Bitcoin&#8217;s price might start at a minimum of $668,566.27. It could rise to a maximum of $814,116.30, with an average price of $693,125.64.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price in 2032 is predicted to reach a minimum of $1,002,294.49. The maximum value could be $1,169,615.41, with the year&#8217;s average price at $1,036,950.77.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>In 2033, Bitcoin is expected to have a minimum price of $1,366,048.54. The maximum price could reach $1,707,069.67, with an average trading price of $1,407,526.57.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction By Coincodex</h3>



<p>According to Coincodex&#8217;s current Bitcoin price prediction, the cryptocurrency is forecasted to experience a 2.39% increase, reaching $63,591 by March 7, 2024. Their technical indicators suggest a Bullish sentiment, while the Fear &amp; Greed Index stands at 80, indicating Extreme Greed. Bitcoin has seen 21 out of 30 green days, with a 10.67% price volatility over the past month.</p>



<p>Coincodex suggests that it&#8217;s a favorable time to buy Bitcoin based on their forecast. Considering historical price movements and BTC halving cycles, the yearly low Bitcoin price prediction for 2025 is estimated at $62,727. Moreover, Coincodex predicts that Bitcoin could surge as high as $156,066 next year.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction By Digital Coin Price</h3>



<p>According to Digital Coin Price&#8217;s analysis, there exists a possibility for Bitcoin to surpass the $159,174.21 threshold and assert dominance in the market by the conclusion of 2025. They estimate the lowest Bitcoin price to fluctuate between $133,177.56 to $159,174.21, with the most probable price stabilizing around $145,388.73 by the end of 2025.</p>



<p>Despite the volatility in Bitcoin&#8217;s value and the controversies surrounding its environmental impact, billionaire venture capitalist Tim Draper maintains his forecast that Bitcoin will reach $159,174.21 by the end of 2025 or early 2026.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Price Prediction By CryptoPredictions.com</h3>



<p>According to CryptoPredictions.com, Bitcoin is forecasted to commence April 2024 at $43,346.766 and conclude the month at $42,409.797 amid the bitcoin halving event. Throughout April, the highest projected BTC price stands at $59,352.028, while the lowest is anticipated to be $40,359.379.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BTC Price Overview</h2>



<p>The price of Bitcoin had experienced notable peaks and troughs in its value. Despite this volatility, the unique nature of the Bitcoin network and its limited supply of coins has attracted the attention of investors and traders worldwide. The blockchain technology underlying Bitcoin enables secure and transparent transactions without the need for intermediaries, making it an attractive alternative to traditional financial systems.</p>



<p>In recent years, Bitcoin has trended upwards, with significant increases in value occurring in 2017 and 2021. This growth has been driven by a variety of factors, including increased adoption and acceptance of Bitcoin as a form of payment, as well as speculation by investors and traders. Today, Bitcoin is trading at +56654654.6% above its all-time low in July 2010.</p>



<p>While the future of Bitcoin&#8217;s price remains uncertain, many experts predict that the trend towards increased adoption and acceptance of digital currencies will continue to drive demand for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BTC Price history</h2>



<p>Bitcoin’s (BTC) price again reached an all-time high in 2021, as values exceeded over 65,000 USD in November 2021. That particular price hike was connected to the launch of a Bitcoin ETF in the United States, whilst others in 2021 were due to events involving Tesla and Coinbase, respectively.</p>



<p>Tesla’s announcement in March 2021 that it had acquired 1.5 billion U.S. dollars worth of the digital coin fueled mass interest.&nbsp; The market was noticeably different by the end of 2022, however, with Bitcoin prices reaching roughly $17194.91 as of January 10, 2023, after another crypto exchange, FTX, filed for bankruptcy.</p>



<p>Large BTC holders – ‘whales’ – are said to make up two percent of anonymous ownership accounts, and own approx 92 percent of BTC. As most people who use cryptocurrency-related services worldwide are retail clients rather than institutional investors, Bitcoin prices are difficult to measure, as movements from one large whale already have a significant impact on this market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on Bitcoin</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is Bitcoin?</h3>



<p>Launched in 2009, Bitcoin is a decentralized digital currency powered by blockchain technology. Satoshi Nakamoto created the coin to overcome the shortcomings of government-issued currencies without requiring a controlling authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin (BTC) was created out of the need for a cryptography-based e-payment system rather than the conventional trust-based system. Cryptocurrency acts as a store of value and a payment method for any transaction process in the crypto space. It is often dubbed &#8220;digital gold.&#8221;</p>



<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s current cryptography is based on an impenetrable algorithm (SHA-256) designed by the United States National Security Agency (NSA) in 2016, after the collapse of the SHA-1 algorithm. This algorithm makes it impossible to crack the Bitcoin network.</p>



<p>Since the launch of Bitcoin in 2009, its value has risen dramatically, from less than 0.01 USD in May 2010 to over 67,000 USD in November 2021. Bitcoin is expected to attain newer feats in the coming years as more institutional investors and traders continue to turn to cryptocurrency.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Influences Bitcoin&#8217;s Price?</h3>



<p>The world&#8217;s premier cryptocurrency, Bitcoin, has recently taken a substantial hit, dipping below the $25.5K threshold and reaching its lowest value in three months. This downward trend follows a lawsuit initiated by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, and its founder and CEO, Changpeng Zhao (CZ).</p>



<p>The news of this legal dispute sparked a swift wave of Bitcoin selling, causing a ripple effect across the majority of other cryptocurrencies. The market strain has escalated as the SEC has expanded its legal pursuits to encompass Coinbase, another key contender in the cryptocurrency exchange market.</p>



<p>Crypto experts posit that if Bitcoin can hold its resistance level at $26,000, we might see a bounce back in the coming months. However, if this level is breached, Bitcoin could potentially tumble to its lowest ever value of $20,000.</p>



<p>Yet, the experts also caution that the current rise in interest rates and a more stringent monetary policy might hinder Bitcoin from making a significant recovery in the near term.</p>



<p>Despite these hurdles, the year 2023 holds promise for Bitcoin advocates who see it as a &#8220;digital safe-haven&#8221; or &#8220;virtual gold&#8221;. These enthusiasts are confident that Bitcoin can offer investors a substantial hedge or attractive yields during periods of market instability.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Challenges</h3>



<p>Despite its success, Bitcoin has faced several criticisms, especially its energy-hungry mining system. According to an energy consumption tracker developed by the University of Cambridge, Bitcoin mining was estimated to consume 100 TWh per year, about one-third of the UK&#8217;s total energy consumption in 2016.</p>



<p>In addition, BTC&#8217;s criminality potential has positioned it for more scrutiny, as it has facilitated numerous dark web dealings, such as acquiring illegal weapons, money laundering, etc.</p>



<p>The most significant and long-standing challenge of Bitcoin is scalability. Bitcoin&#8217;s underlying technology limits its performance in terms of transaction completion timeframe, with an insufficient capacity of 3-7 TPS. As more transactions are initiated on the network, processing delays will surface. Several proposals have been put forward to nip this concern in the bud, but a favorable long-term fix remains unclear.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How do you buy and sell Bitcoin?</h3>



<p>You can buy and sell Bitcoin through cryptocurrency exchanges or peer-to-peer platforms. To purchase Bitcoin, you typically need to create an account with a cryptocurrency exchange, fund your account, and place an order to buy Bitcoin.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is Bitcoin&#8217;s role in the broader financial system?</h3>



<p>Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are seen by some as a disruptive force that could challenge traditional financial systems and provide greater financial freedom and autonomy for users.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Where to store Bitcoin?</h3>



<p>The best ways to store Bitcoin include hardware wallets, paper wallets, and software wallets. Hardware wallets are considered the most secure, as they store private keys offline and require physical confirmation of transactions. Paper wallets, which involve printing out private keys and keeping them in a secure location, are also considered secure but require careful handling. Software wallets, which run on computers or mobile devices, are a great option, but more vulnerable to hacking and malware attacks.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What drives the value of BTC?</h3>



<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s value is determined by supply and demand factors, such as market sentiment, adoption rates, regulatory changes, and investor speculation. Bitcoin&#8217;s decentralized nature, scarcity, and high-security features also contribute to its value in the market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>As the crypto market leader, Bitcoin cryptocurrency is one digital asset with massive potential for mainstream adoption. Several businesses already accept Bitcoin as an alternative to fiat currencies, with the latest club member being the Spanish company Telefonica. The telecommunication giant recently partnered with crypto exchanges Bit2Me to enable settlements in Bitcoin, among other cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>According to our BTC price forecast, Bitcoin’s long-term prospects are looking good, with several possibilities of future price appreciation. Our expectations are also backed by Bitcoin price history. Bitcoin could be a significant portfolio addition for many BTC investors in years to come. However, before you buy Bitcoin or any other cryptocurrency, do remember to conduct your own research, taking into account all risks involved.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/p7n-qA-uPp8" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/p7n-qA-uPp8" />
			<media:title type="plain">Bitcoin BTC Price News Today - Technical Analysis and Elliott Wave Analysis and Price Prediction!</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[Trade on Bybit:Receive an up to $30,000 bonus (see terms on Bybit)https://partner.bybit.com/b/MCOBitcoin BTC Price News Today - Technical Analysis and Elliot...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/bitcoin-btc-price-news-today-tec.jpg" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Bitcoin-V1_featured-image_1140x815.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Bitcoin-V1_featured-image_1140x815.png"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
