<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:52:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How Will the EU&#8217;s AI Legislation Influence the Fashion Industry?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/eu-ai-legislation-influence-fashion-industry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI Legislation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Europe&#8217;s strides in AI legislation have reached a historic milestone as the European Parliament greenlights the AI Act, setting a global precedent for comprehensive regulation in artificial intelligence development and use. This landmark legislation not only shapes the future of technology within the European Union but also holds significant implications for various sectors, including the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Europe&#8217;s strides in AI legislation have reached a historic milestone as the European Parliament greenlights the AI Act, setting a global precedent for comprehensive regulation in artificial intelligence development and use. This landmark legislation not only shapes the future of technology within the European Union but also holds significant implications for various sectors, including the fashion industry.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The AI Act&#8217;s impact on Fashion industry &#8211; Regulatory framework and compliance</h2>



<p>The AI Act&#8217;s passage introduces a robust regulatory framework that categorizes AI systems based on risk levels, thereby guiding their development and usage. High-risk applications such as biometric surveillance and predictive policing face outright bans, reflecting a commitment to safeguarding individual rights and privacy. For fashion brands leveraging AI in personalized recommendations or styling advice, compliance entails transparent communication regarding AI utilization and the labeling of AI-generated content.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to James Brown, a partner at Haynes Boone UK, brands must implement rigorous risk assessments and mitigation strategies to ensure adherence to regulatory standards, especially concerning employment-related AI applications like CV-sorting systems. Also, this regulatory framework encourages the adoption of ethical AI practices, fostering consumer trust and long-term brand loyalty.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Transparency and bias mitigation</h2>



<p>Beyond regulatory compliance, the AI Act mandates transparency in AI model development, necessitating the disclosure of training data to regulators. This requirement extends to fashion brands utilizing AI for trend analysis or personalization, compelling them to divulge the datasets informing their predictive algorithms.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Agatha Liu, a partner at law firm Duane Morris, emphasizes the need for fashion brands to adopt a customer-centric approach, prioritizing transparency and providing consumers with comprehensive insights into AI-driven processes. The Act&#8217;s focus on eradicating bias underscores the importance of inclusive AI models within the fashion industry.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Dominique Leipzig, a privacy and cyber partner at Mayer Brown, advocates for collaborative efforts between brands and tech providers to embed inclusivity and fairness into AI tools. This collaborative approach, she asserts, enables brands to proactively address biases and align AI practices with ethical standards. As brands embrace transparency and bias mitigation measures, they pave the way for more equitable and socially responsible AI-driven fashion solutions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Fashion&#8217;s journey with EU&#8217;s AI legislation</h2>



<p>As Europe pioneers a new era of AI governance, fashion brands are compelled to navigate evolving regulatory landscapes and embrace responsible AI adoption. The AI Act&#8217;s emphasis on transparency, bias mitigation, and collaboration with technology providers signals a paradigm shift in industry practices. Looking ahead, the question arises: How will fashion brands leverage this legislative momentum to cultivate ethical AI ecosystems and drive industry-wide innovation?&nbsp;</p>



<p>As stakeholders across the fashion ecosystem embark on this transformative journey, the convergence of regulatory compliance and <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/concerns-ai-driven-political-microtargeting/" data-type="post" data-id="484164">ethical AI practices</a> promises to redefine the future of fashion technology. Through proactive engagement with regulatory requirements and ethical considerations, fashion brands have the opportunity to not only comply with the AI Act but also lead the industry towards sustainable and inclusive AI-driven innovations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/e5674275-e2bc-4f55-912a-fd078470e7ff.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/e5674275-e2bc-4f55-912a-fd078470e7ff.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Profitability Of The Graph (GRT) Soars As Near Protocol (NEAR) Expands; Algotech (ALGT) Presale Sees Buying Frenzy</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/profitability-of-the-graph-grt-soars-as-near-protocol-near-expands-algotech-algt-presale-sees-buying-frenzy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sathya Rani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Rejuvenating all the market bulls, Algotech’s (ALGT) presale has set several success records. The new project has entered the market with an irresistible uniqueness and attraction. Therefore, its presale has sold over 53 million ALGT tokens in just a matter of days. This article will focus on The Graph (GRT), Near Protocol (NEAR), and Algotech [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Rejuvenating all the market bulls, Algotech’s (ALGT) presale has set several success records. The new project has entered the market with an irresistible uniqueness and attraction. Therefore, its presale has sold over 53 million ALGT tokens in just a matter of days. This article will focus on The Graph (GRT), Near Protocol (NEAR), and Algotech (ALGT) to help you make the best investment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Graph (GRT) Investors Are In The Money</h2>



<p><a href="https://thegraph.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">The Graph (GRT)</a> has been moving upward for the past many weeks. Consequently, the market value of The Graph (GRT) has risen by 142% on the monthly chart. At the time of writing, The Graph (GRT) is trading at <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/the-graph/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$0.40</a>.</p>



<p>Subsequently, the profitability of The Graph (GRT) has also surged. The data from IntoTheBlock shows more than 66% of The Graph (GRT) investors are now in the money. These considerable gains have boosted the positive sentiments among The Graph (GRT) community.</p>



<p>Besides, whales have also increased their holdings in The Graph (GRT). The data shows over 84% of The Graph (GRT) circulation is controlled by large holders.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Near Protocol (NEAR) Collaborates With Stacks</h2>



<p><a href="https://near.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Near Protocol (NEAR)</a> is taking steps to capitalize on the positive sentiments around Bitcoin. In the latest event, the Near Protocol (NEAR) has joined the Stacks network as a Signer. Under this collaboration, Near Protocol (NEAR) will facilitate the growth of “a new economy on top of Bitcoin.”</p>



<p>Near Protocol (NEAR) will enhance the security of the Stacks network, the leading Bitcoin Layer-2 solution. As a Signer, Near Protocol (NEAR) will be responsible for validating blocks and processing transactions.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, Near Protocol (NEAR) has experienced a 42% price surge in the last week. Currently, Near Protocol (NEAR) is changing hands at <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/near-protocol/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$6.08</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Algotech (ALGT) Presale Surpasses Expectations</h2>



<p>Are you deep into trading, <a href="https://algotech.trade?utm_source=cryptopolitan&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=1503" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Algotech (ALGT)</a> is here to help you fly high. It is a new crypto trading platform that supports advanced algorithms. Notably, algo trading offers several benefits such as extremely high speed and cost efficiency. Subsequently, the share of algorithms in the global trading industry has surged to around 70%.</p>



<p>Algotech (ALGT) will use disruptive technologies like artificial intelligence and machine learning. It will analyze real-time market data to notify about profitable trade strategies, and growing digital assets. Whether you like short-term positions or long-term trades, Algotech (ALGT) will help you gain big in all situations.</p>



<p>Besides, you can modify your positions at any time to exploit all dynamic conditions of the market. Moreover, Algotech (ALGT) will offer complete transparency. The project’s smart contract is audited, and the team is KYC-verified.</p>



<p>The platform also supports social trading. Users will be able to share their strategies with others, as well as copy the trades of other profitable traders. Early Algotech (ALGT) investors will win several additional benefits. They can win the latest iPhones and VIP tickets for the Blockchain Life 2024 event in giveaways.</p>



<p>Moreover, an Algotech <a href="https://algotech.trade?utm_source=cryptopolitan&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=1503" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">(ALGT</a>) token’s price surged by 50% in the recently concluded stage 1 of the token presale. Hence, the demand for stage 2 presale has soared, with a token currently costing $0.06. However, the tokens’ value is likely to jump by 275% during the presale phase. Interestingly, there is a 15% bonus on any deposit if you lock ALGT tokens now.</p>



<p>Learn more:</p>



<p><a href="https://algotech.trade?utm_source=cryptopolitan&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=1503" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Visit Algotech Presale</strong></a></p>



<p><a href="https://linktr.ee/algotech.trade" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Join the Algotech Community</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Untitled-2-5.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Untitled-2-5.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Predicts AI Superiority by 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/elon-musk-predicts-ai-superiority-by-2025/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Innovators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Renowned entrepreneur Elon Musk has stirred discussions with his bold prediction that artificial intelligence (AI) will surpass human intelligence by 2025. Musk&#8217;s assertion, made during a podcast interview, has sparked debate about the potential implications of advancing AI technology. Elon Musk predicted in a provocative statement that has reignited discussions around the future of artificial [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Renowned entrepreneur Elon Musk has stirred discussions with his bold prediction that artificial intelligence (AI) will surpass human intelligence by 2025. Musk&#8217;s assertion, made during a podcast interview, has sparked debate about the potential implications of advancing AI technology.</p>



<p>Elon Musk predicted in a provocative statement that has reignited discussions around the future of artificial intelligence (AI). The tech billionaire&#8217;s comments came during a recent interview on the Joe Rogan Experience podcast.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AI supremacy in four years?</h2>



<p>&#8220;AI will be vastly smarter than humans and amplify its lead at an astonishing rate,&#8221; Musk declared, projecting AI could match human intelligence next year and leave humanity&#8217;s collective wit in the dust by 2029. His bold forecast aligns with past projections from futurist Ray Kurzweil, who envisioned the pivotal AI &#8220;singularity&#8221; by the end of this decade.</p>



<p>While ambitious timelines for transformative AI have sparked skepticism in the past, Musk&#8217;s stature as one of the world&#8217;s most influential tech visionaries immediately amplified the proclamation&#8217;s significance. Observers pondered the potential seismic shifts to employment, education, and society at large should his prediction prove accurate.</p>



<p>Musk did not mince words about AI&#8217;s perceived threat to human labor, warning entire industries could see the mass obsolescence of traditional job roles. &#8220;There will be a redistribution of intelligence that is vastly smarter than any human,&#8221; he stated bluntly, envisioning an era where dominance belongs to &#8220;whatever is smarter.&#8221;</p>



<p>The SpaceX founder&#8217;s track record of successfully disrupting multiple industries, from electronic payments to space exploration, added weight to his controversial outlook on AI&#8217;s trajectory.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">A polarizing prediction</h2>



<p>Reaction was swift, with AI experts and ethicists weighing in to scrutinize Musk&#8217;s claims. While some considered the timeline realistic if arguably conservative, others dismissed it as sensationalism from a skilled self-promoter. Polarized camps quickly formed in analyzing the prediction&#8217;s credibility and its implications.</p>



<p>As the AI debate rages on, Musk&#8217;s bombshell statements ensure the technology&#8217;s future will remain squarely in the spotlight leading up to his purported singularity in 2025. Whether dream or nightmare, he compelled the world to consider an AI-dominated reality may be just around the corner.</p>



<p>Elon Musk&#8217;s remarks underscore the profound impact that AI could have on society in the coming years. He views AI as a potentially disruptive force, capable of rendering traditional job roles obsolete. Musk envisions a future where AI technology surpasses human abilities, leading to fundamental shifts in labor markets and societal structures.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Elon_Musk_Predicts_AI_Superiority_by_2025_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Elon_Musk_Predicts_AI_Superiority_by_2025_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink&#8217;s CCIP revenue jumps 180% amid growing adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/chainlinks-ccip-revenue-180-growing-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CCIP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chainlink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484907</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink&#8217;s Cross Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP) has experienced a substantial revenue increase of 180% over the past two months, demonstrating a significant uptick in its adoption. According to data from Dune Analytics, CCIP&#8217;s fee revenue jumped from around $61,000 in January to more than $171,000 in the first half of March. This growth brought the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Chainlink&#8217;s Cross Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP) has experienced a substantial revenue increase of 180% over the past two months, demonstrating a significant uptick in its adoption. According to data from Dune Analytics, CCIP&#8217;s fee revenue jumped from around $61,000 in January to more than $171,000 in the first half of March. This growth brought the total cumulative revenue of the protocol, launched in July 2023, to $377,724.</p>



<p>The CCIP has been designed to allow smart contracts to securely access data from any external API or system, facilitating seamless data connectivity between blockchains and off-chain systems. This protocol operates through Chainlink&#8217;s decentralized oracle network, aiming to enhance interoperability across the blockchain ecosystem.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1200" height="348" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-7.48.31-AM-1200x348.png" alt="" class="wp-image-484913" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-7.48.31-AM-1200x348.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-7.48.31-AM-300x87.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-7.48.31-AM-768x222.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-7.48.31-AM-1536x445.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-7.48.31-AM.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Network fees in CCIP \ Source: Dune Analytics </em></figcaption></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Key Contributors and Revenue Sources</h2>



<p>Ethereum&#8217;s layer-2 protocol, Arbitrum, has been identified as the largest contributor to CCIP network fees, accounting for 28% of the total, closely followed by Base, which contributes 24%. These platforms highlight the protocol&#8217;s integral role in supporting transactions across different blockchain environments. Chainlink community ambassador, known as &#8220;ChainLinkGod,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/ChainLinkGod/status/1767053780376584237" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">explained that</a> the fees generated through CCIP cover the gas costs associated with completing transactions on the destination chain as well as the premium paid to CCIP service providers.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Strategic Integrations and Partnerships</h2>



<p>The recent surge in CCIP&#8217;s adoption and revenue has been partly driven by a series of strategic integrations and partnerships. Notable collaborations include those with the Metis layer-2 network, auditing platform Code4rena, stablecoin issuer Circle, and South Korea&#8217;s major game developer, Wemade. Additionally, a significant partnership was forged with SWIFT in 2022 to undertake a proof-of-concept project for token transfers.</p>



<p>Chainlink&#8217;s revenue streams extend beyond CCIP, with the network earning from node operator fees, a portion of LINK staking, network revenue share, and enterprise products. Its total cumulative revenue stands at $373 million, with the majority originating from Oracle feeds. The LINK token experienced a notable price increase, reaching its highest level in over two years at $21.71 on March 11, reflecting the protocol&#8217;s growing value and adoption within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-11-10.38.53-Design-an-uplifting-and-visually-stunning-image-that-captures-Bitcoins-latest-milestone-surpassing-the-71000-mark-without-using-text.-Picture-a-g.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-11-10.38.53-Design-an-uplifting-and-visually-stunning-image-that-captures-Bitcoins-latest-milestone-surpassing-the-71000-mark-without-using-text.-Picture-a-g.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin mining difficulty hits all-time high as BTC price tumbles</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-hits-all-time-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On March 14, the cryptocurrency market watched as Bitcoin mining difficulty skyrocketed to an unprecedented 83.95 trillion hashes. This shows that miners are getting more and more competitive as they try to solve the hard puzzles that keep the Bitcoin network running. And guess what? This happened right when Bitcoin&#8217;s price decided to play its [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>On March 14, the cryptocurrency market watched as Bitcoin mining difficulty skyrocketed to an unprecedented 83.95 trillion hashes. This shows that miners are getting more and more competitive as they try to solve the hard puzzles that keep the Bitcoin network running. And guess what? This happened right when Bitcoin&#8217;s price decided to play its own game of snakes and ladders, soaring to an all-time high before taking a nosedive that has got investors feeling not-so-peachy right now.<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-btc-mining-difficulty-reaches-new-historical-high-halving-looms" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Never-ending Battle of Hashes and Cash</h2>



<p>Let&#8217;s be for real. Mining Bitcoin has never been for the weak. It&#8217;s a battle of wits, energy, and who has the most advanced piece of machinery on the block. So the recent surge to 83.95 trillion hashes from February&#8217;s 79.35 trillion is a clear sign that the arena is getting crowded. More miners jumping into the fray means higher difficulty levels. Why? Cause the Bitcoin protocol is designed to adjust the puzzle&#8217;s difficulty to ensure that the time it takes to mine one block remains consistent at about 10 minutes, regardless of how many people are on it.</p>



<p>This adjustment isn&#8217;t arbitrary. On the contrary, it&#8217;s a meticulously calculated shift that ensures the network&#8217;s security and functionality, adjusting at a rate of 613.94 exahashes per second, a slight but still kind of huge increase from the last cycle&#8217;s 602.14 EH/s.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Price Fluctuations: The Rollercoaster You Didn&#8217;t Sign Up For</h2>



<p>Now, let&#8217;s talk about the elephant in the room—the price of Bitcoin. The cryptocurrency has been on such a fascinating rollercoaster lately, reaching dizzying heights of $73,835, only to take a tumble down to $68,551 as of press time. This volatility is nothing new to us, but it sure is a reminder of the unpredictable nature of investing in cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>But it&#8217;s not just Bitcoin that&#8217;s feeling the heat. The altcoin market, too, has been a mirror reflecting Bitcoin&#8217;s volatile dance. <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethereums-dencun-upgrade-goes-live/" data-type="post" data-id="484040">Ethereum</a>, Solana, and BNB, among others, reached new records only to face sharp retracements. This domino effect led to nearly 200,000 traders being liquidated in a 24-hour frenzy.</p>



<p>The fallout from these price movements is more than just numbers on a screen. It&#8217;s a clear indication of the high-risk, high-reward nature of cryptocurrency investment. The recent dip to $68,500, a level not seen in a week, and the subsequent red ink across the altcoin market, is just another proof of the volatility that defines this market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.57.03-Design-an-image-that-vividly-captures-the-contrast-between-Bitcoins-mining-difficulty-reaching-an-all-time-high-and-the-simultaneous-tumble-in-BTC-pr.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.57.03-Design-an-image-that-vividly-captures-the-contrast-between-Bitcoins-mining-difficulty-reaching-an-all-time-high-and-the-simultaneous-tumble-in-BTC-pr.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investors Highlight 11 Promising AI Startups in Europe</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/11-promising-ai-startups-in-europe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Innovators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Leading investors in the AI space have identified 11 promising startups in Europe, signaling a growing interest in innovative AI technologies. These startups span various countries and sectors, offering unique solutions to revolutionize industries and address emerging challenges. Investors from renowned firms such as Speedinvest, Runa Capital, Apex Ventures, and Octopus Ventures have unveiled their [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Leading investors in the AI space have identified 11 promising startups in Europe, signaling a growing interest in innovative AI technologies. These startups span various countries and sectors, offering unique solutions to revolutionize industries and address emerging challenges.</p>



<p>Investors from renowned firms such as Speedinvest, Runa Capital, Apex Ventures, and Octopus Ventures have unveiled their top picks for AI startups in Europe. These startups represent the forefront of AI innovation, leveraging advanced technologies to tackle complex problems across diverse domains.</p>



<p>The selected startups offer diverse solutions, from symbolic AI frameworks to neuromorphic processors and cybersecurity for AI. Each startup brings its unique approach to harnessing AI&#8217;s potential, addressing critical needs in areas such as data processing, edge computing, and cybersecurity. As the AI revolution gains momentum, these companies are poised to reshape various industries and unlock unprecedented possibilities.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The AI Vanguard</h2>



<p>Europe&#8217;s AI ecosystem is brimming with promising startups, each offering unique solutions that push the boundaries of what was once considered impossible. From cutting-edge chip design to advanced AI security and novel software creation tools, these companies are redefining the future of technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Revolutionizing Computing Power</h2>



<p>At the forefront of this AI renaissance are startups like Innatera from the Netherlands and GEMESYS from Germany. Innatera&#8217;s neuromorphic processors mimic the brain&#8217;s mechanisms for processing sensory data, optimizing power and latency for edge applications. GEMESYS, on the other hand, is pioneering analog AI chips tailored for edge computing, drawing inspiration from the human brain&#8217;s processing capabilities.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Enhancing AI acceleration</h2>



<p>Companies like Lumai and Fractile in the UK are tackling the growing demand for AI compute capacity within data centers. Lumai leverages 3D optical computing to enable energy-efficient and scalable AI deployment, while Fractile takes a ground-up approach to accelerated computing, optimizing transformer models for maximum speed.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Securing AI systems</h2>



<p>As AI systems become more prevalent, ensuring their security is paramount. Mindgard, a UK-based startup, specializes in cybersecurity for AI, offering automated security and rapid threat response for generative AI and large language models (LLMs). Meanwhile, Invariant Lab from Switzerland is building a novel platform for secured AI agents, ensuring their actions comply with data privacy policies and security protocols.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AI for software creation</h2>



<p>Revolutionizing the software development process, Cogna, a London-based startup, is developing an AI-driven &#8220;software factory&#8221; that empowers non-technical experts to articulate challenges, explore solutions, and rapidly create custom software through program synthesis.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Causal AI and symbolic reasoning</h2>



<p>Extensity.ai from Austria and Causa from the UK are pioneering causal AI and symbolic reasoning approaches. Extensity.ai combines deep learning and generative AI with human-like &#8220;common sense&#8221; for autonomous systems, while Causa provides a solution for accurate outcome prediction, personalized recommendations, and optimal decision-making.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Enhancing AI performance</h2>



<p>Innovators like Synthara from Switzerland and Nebuly from Italy are tackling performance bottlenecks in AI systems. Synthara offers chip makers the ability to seamlessly integrate in-memory computing, boosting performance by 50-fold without disrupting existing architectures. Nebuly, on the other hand, is building user analytics for LLMs, enabling enterprises to better understand how users interact with these models.</p>



<p>These startups have caught the attention of prominent investors, who see immense potential in their groundbreaking technologies. Firms like Speedinvest, Octopus Ventures, Apex Ventures, and Runa Capital have identified these companies as ones to watch, recognizing their ability to shape the future of AI.</p>



<p>As the AI revolution unfolds, Europe&#8217;s trailblazing startups are poised to lead the way, pushing the boundaries of what is possible and unlocking new realms of innovation across various sectors.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Investors_Highlight_11_Promising_AI_Startups_in_Europe_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Investors_Highlight_11_Promising_AI_Startups_in_Europe_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Reserve is likely not going to cut interest rates this year</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/federal-reserve-not-gonna-cut-rates-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rate cuts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The recent data of the U.S. economy has put the brakes on any fantasies about the Federal Reserve cutting interest rates anytime soon. With the latest figures on inflation heating up and unemployment claims cooling down more than anticipated, it looks like the Fed&#8217;s big chair might just stay put, keeping the interest rates at [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The recent data of the U.S. economy has put the brakes on any fantasies about the Federal Reserve cutting interest rates anytime soon. With the latest figures on inflation heating up and unemployment claims cooling down more than anticipated, it looks like the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/federal-reserve-grapples-with-endurance-test/" data-type="post" data-id="483486">Fed&#8217;s</a> big chair might just stay put, keeping the interest rates at their two-decade high. And let&#8217;s not forget, while some pockets of the economy seem to be taking a nap, particularly consumer spending, the overall message given by the latest stats is one of a weirdly-strong economy that&#8217;s not ready for a bedtime story about rate cuts. And probably won&#8217;t be for quite some time.<a href="https://archive.is/BT2IF" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Economic Indicators Playing Hard to Get</h3>



<p>Let&#8217;s dive a bit deeper into this economic soup. Prices that producers charge have gone beyond what our economists expected in February, and the line for jobless benefits got shorter, suggesting fewer people are getting laid off. Earlier, data had already shown that prices for the rest of us, the consumers, also climbed up a bit faster than your morning jog last month. Now, if that&#8217;s not enough to keep the Federal Reserve&#8217;s hands tied, I don&#8217;t know what is.</p>



<p>The Fed have been pretty clear about their game plan. They&#8217;re not about to make borrowing cheaper until they&#8217;re really, really sure that prices aren&#8217;t going to keep jumping up and that everyone who wants a job can get one. And from the looks of it, they&#8217;re nowhere near convinced.</p>



<p>Sure, we saw a bit of a lag in how freely people are opening their wallets at stores, but that&#8217;s just one piece of the puzzle. When it comes to making the call on interest rates, the Fed&#8217;s eyes are glued on inflation and employment numbers. And right now, those numbers are telling them to stay the course, keep rates where they are, and not even think about touching that rate-cut button for a while longer.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">A Closer Look at the Crystal Ball</h3>



<p>Now, let me sprinkle a little context on this. Inflation, that sneaky thief that slowly empties your wallet without you noticing, had started to chill out over the past year, thanks in part to cheaper goods and power. But like any good plot twist, recent reports suggest this calm might be the quiet before a massive storm. Prices for things we buy regularly have started to increase again.</p>



<p>And it&#8217;s not just about paying more for last year&#8217;s fashion or second-hand cars; energy costs have also jumped back into the ring, pushing overall price increases above what analysts had guessed. This is the kind of stuff that keeps Federal Reserve officials up at night, wondering if they need to keep interest rates high to prevent prices from spiraling out of control.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, when it comes to jobs and unemployment, it turns out fewer people have been signing up for unemployment benefits than we thought. This is good news because it means the job market is strong, but it&#8217;s also another reason for the Fed to keep a tight grip on interest rates.</p>



<p>Economists are now pushing back their forecasts for when the Fed might start cutting rates. Some say not until mid-summer, others think even later. The takeaway here? Don&#8217;t hold your breath for cheaper loans or mortgages anytime soon, guys.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.56.58-Visualize-the-concept-that-the-Federal-Reserve-is-unlikely-to-cut-interest-rates-this-year-without-using-text.-Imagine-a-scene-that-symbolizes-steadf.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.56.58-Visualize-the-concept-that-the-Federal-Reserve-is-unlikely-to-cut-interest-rates-this-year-without-using-text.-Imagine-a-scene-that-symbolizes-steadf.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU Adopts Landmark AI Legislation, Impacts Tech Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/eu-ai-legislation-impacts-tech-companies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484920</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The European Parliament has approved the groundbreaking AI Act, marking a significant milestone in global AI regulation. This comprehensive law aims to mitigate potential risks associated with artificial intelligence while setting strict standards for its deployment. However, it also poses challenges for tech giants eyeing the lucrative EU market. Under the AI Act, stringent regulations [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The European Parliament has approved the groundbreaking AI Act, marking a significant milestone in global AI regulation. This comprehensive law aims to mitigate potential risks associated with artificial intelligence while setting strict standards for its deployment. However, it also poses challenges for tech giants eyeing the lucrative EU market.</p>



<p>Under the AI Act, stringent regulations are imposed on AI systems deemed to pose higher risks to society. Technologies involving biometric data processing and facial recognition databases, among others, will face prohibitive measures to safeguard fundamental rights. Sectors like infrastructure, healthcare, and law enforcement will be subject to rigorous requirements to ensure accountability and transparency in AI deployment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Tech companies to show transparency and compliance mandates</h2>



<p>The legislation mandates transparency from producers of AI systems, particularly in areas such as generative AI tools and chatbots. Companies must disclose the materials used to train their models and adhere to EU copyright laws. Furthermore, the Act addresses concerns regarding manipulated media content, requiring clear labeling of artificial or manipulated images, audio, or video content (deepfakes).</p>



<p>While lauded for its forward-thinking approach to AI governance, the AI Act poses challenges for tech companies, particularly those from the US and China, seeking entry into the EU market. Compliance with the Act&#8217;s standards and requirements will necessitate significant investments in research and development, potentially affecting the competitiveness of these companies in Europe. The legislation&#8217;s enforcement is expected to commence in 2025, following final reviews and approval from the European Council.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Chinese observers&#8217; perspective</h2>



<p>Chinese observers acknowledge the Act&#8217;s efforts to address AI risks but express concerns regarding its impact on market access for Chinese tech companies. The EU&#8217;s ambition to assert itself as a global leader in AI governance may create hurdles for Chinese firms looking to expand into Europe. Despite China&#8217;s own regulatory efforts in AI governance, the Act presents new challenges for Chinese companies operating in the European market.</p>



<p>The adoption of the AI Act signifies the EU&#8217;s proactive approach to regulating AI technologies, positioning itself as a standard-setter in global AI governance. However, the Act&#8217;s implications extend beyond Europe, affecting key players in the AI industry worldwide. Both Chinese and US companies will need to navigate higher market access thresholds, potentially reshaping the competitive landscape in Europe&#8217;s AI market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_EU_Adopts_Landmark_AI_Legislation_Impacts_Tech_Compani_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_EU_Adopts_Landmark_AI_Legislation_Impacts_Tech_Compani_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Low-income U.S. consumers continue to suffer despite it all</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/low-income-us-consumers-continue-to-suffer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the economy parades around in its fancy clothes, boasting of growth and employment numbers that would make any economist impressed, the situation remains stark for low-income U.S. consumers. They&#8217;re stuck in the mud, trying to pull themselves out by the bootstraps that have long been worn thin by inflation and interest rates that show [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>While the economy parades around in its fancy clothes, boasting of growth and employment numbers that would make any economist impressed, the situation remains stark for low-income U.S. consumers. They&#8217;re stuck in the mud, trying to pull themselves out by the bootstraps that have long been worn thin by inflation and interest rates that show absolutely no mercy. It&#8217;s a situation that doesn&#8217;t quite fit the prosperity claimed by mainstream numbers, where it seems like the sun shines equally on everyone.<a href="https://archive.is/56S7f#selection-2267.0-2270.0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<p>Ian Borden of McDonald&#8217;s said something instriguing at a recent industry conference that highlights the grim reality facing those at the lower end of the income ladder. With Covid savings depleted and the cost of eating at home rising, many are left with no choice but to tighten their belts a notch further. This is causing problems in sectors like fast food, which anticipates a downturn in foot traffic as a direct consequence. It&#8217;s a wake-up call that Borden says sent McDonald&#8217;s shares tumbling, but really, should we be surprised? The signs have always been there, in booming stock markets and employment stats that boast a less than four percent unemployment rate.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Invisible Divide</h2>



<p>Scratch beneath the surface, and the divide becomes glaringly obvious. The New York Fed&#8217;s auto loan delinquency rates offer a window into the struggles of younger borrowers, who find themselves in financial hot water at rates reminiscent of the great financial crisis. It&#8217;s kind of weird for an economy that&#8217;s supposedly firing on all cylinders. My question here is &#8211; why aren&#8217;t more companies being vocal about this discrepancy? Is it perhaps because the loudest voices in the room are those at the upper end of the income spectrum, comfortably shielded from the realities of those less fortunate?</p>



<p>This disparity is the reality for companies catering to the budget-conscious consumer. Stocks in consumer staples have barely moved, lagging behind the market as they struggle with the triple threat of rising bond yields, a shift away from defensive stocks, and the simple fact that their primary customer base is quite literally in a financial crisis. And the worst part is this is unlikely to ease up if interest rates continue their upward trajectory, because of an economy that just refuses to cool down.</p>



<p>The banking sector offers another lens through which to view this unbalanced growth. A look at the long-term trends in U.S. banking assets reveals a striking consolidation of power among the top banks, with JPMorgan Chase at the top. This shift towards greater concentration of assets among the biggest players speaks volumes about the underlying dynamics of the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/us-core-inflation-how-we-doing-over-there/" data-type="post" data-id="482405">U.S. economy</a> over the past two decades. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">A Tale of Two Economies</h2>



<p>What we&#8217;re witnessing is a tale of two economies: one bathed in the glow of prosperity and the other shrouded in financial hardships. The fake resilience of the U.S. economy masks the struggles of those who find themselves on the wrong side of the prosperity divide.</p>



<p>The dominance of institutions like JPMorgan Chase is a painful reminder that the benefits of economic growth are not distributed equally. As interest rates rise and the economic environment changes, the pressure on low-income consumers is likely to increase.</p>



<p>Behind every statistic, every stock ticker, and every corporate earnings report, there is the average people trying to make ends meet. The challenges they face may not always make headlines or shake the stock market, but they are the true measure of our economic health. Without addressing the needs of low-income U.S. consumers, Biden&#8217;s proud claim of economic success remains incomplete, a glossy cover over a story that&#8217;s far from over.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.56.53-Design-a-more-subdued-and-reflective-image-that-captures-the-challenges-faced-by-low-income-U.S.-consumers-without-using-text.-Envision-a-simpler-sce.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.56.53-Design-a-more-subdued-and-reflective-image-that-captures-the-challenges-faced-by-low-income-U.S.-consumers-without-using-text.-Envision-a-simpler-sce.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Craig Wright is NOT Satoshi Nakamoto &#8211; Is anyone surprised?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/craig-wright-is-not-satoshi-nakamoto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Craig Wright]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[satoshi nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=484881</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Well, well, well, if it isn&#8217;t what we&#8217;ve all always known. Craig Wright is NOT Satoshi Nakamoto. It&#8217;s been legally declared. Slicing through the thick fog of claims and counterclaims like a hot knife through butter, UK Judge James Mellor has delivered a ruling that essentially throws cold water on Wright&#8217;s long-standing assertion. His annoying [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Well, well, well, if it isn&#8217;t what we&#8217;ve all always known. Craig Wright is NOT Satoshi Nakamoto. It&#8217;s been legally declared. Slicing through the thick fog of claims and counterclaims like a hot knife through butter, UK Judge James Mellor has delivered a ruling that essentially throws cold water on Wright&#8217;s long-standing assertion. His annoying crusade to be recognized as the father of Bitcoin is finally coming to an end. And I, for one, couldn&#8217;t be more excited about it. This came after the Crypto Open Patent Alliance (COPA) took Wright to court, tired of his claims and seeking a legal muzzle to keep him from further proclaiming himself as Nakamoto over and over again.<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/craig-wright-not-satoshi-nakamoto" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Battle Lines Were Drawn</h2>



<p>The showdown reached its climax on March 12 in London, where the legal teams locked horns over the truth of Wright&#8217;s identity as Satoshi. COPA, a coalition formed by the who&#8217;s who of the crypto industry, including giants like <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/coinbase-appeals-sec-rulemaking-denial/" data-type="post" data-id="482908">Coinbase</a>, Block, and Meta, was there to defend the integrity of the crypto community. They were on a mission to challenge Wright&#8217;s claims and to secure the open, collaborative spirit of cryptocurrency innovation.</p>



<p>Wright&#8217;s approach to proving his identity was as ridiculous as it was bogus. Accusations of extensive document forgery have been thrown his way, showing a man willing to craft an elaborate historical narrative, complete with fabricated evidence, to back his claim that no one was going to believe anyway. Did he even think that all the way through? I wonder.</p>



<p>Despite the mounting skepticism, Wright shamelessly dug his heels in, offering an olive branch in the form of an out-of-court settlement on January 24. COPA, however, was not in a forgiving mood, choosing instead to let the courts decide. Their opinion was that the truth of Wright&#8217;s claim needed to be scrutinized under the legal microscope, not settled in quiet corners.</p>



<p>The COPA alliance is no minor league player. Founded in 2020 with the ambitious goal of tearing down the patent walls stifling crypto innovation, its ranks are filled with 33 of the crypto industry&#8217;s most influential entities.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">A Web of Legal Wrangles</h2>



<p>Wright&#8217;s legal entanglements extend beyond the courtroom drama with COPA. In another ridiculously bold move, he sued 13 of Bitcoin&#8217;s core developers and several cornerstone companies within the crypto industry, alleging copyright infringement over the Bitcoin white paper and the digital architecture of the Bitcoin blockchain itself. My mans literally declared war on the very principles of open-source development that underpins the cryptocurrency movement. And he never stood a chance.</p>



<p>The response from the Bitcoin Legal Defense Fund was swift and scathing, condemning Wright&#8217;s actions as part of a bigger pattern of sinister litigation designed to intimidate and exhaust those dedicated to Bitcoin&#8217;s development.</p>



<p>In a twist of irony though, Wright&#8217;s claim to the Bitcoin white paper and code came to a head with a court injunction aimed at preventing further copyright claims on his part. The Bitcoin white paper, a legendary piece document that has achieved almost mythic status, falls under an MIT open-source license, emphasizing the ethos of free use and modification that is antithetical to Wright&#8217;s actions.</p>



<p>As this chapter closes with Judge Mellor&#8217;s ruling, the crypto community is left to ponder the implications of this legal battle. The fight over Nakamoto&#8217;s true identity may have been settled in court for now, but the larger war over the soul of cryptocurrency innovation rages on. Wright&#8217;s assertions and the subsequent legal battle now leads us to the question: how do we balance the drive for individual recognition with the need for communal progress and transparency?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.56.50-Design-an-image-that-humorously-captures-the-general-lack-of-surprise-at-the-revelation-that-Craig-Wright-is-not-Satoshi-Nakamoto-the-mysterious-crea.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-15-04.56.50-Design-an-image-that-humorously-captures-the-general-lack-of-surprise-at-the-revelation-that-Craig-Wright-is-not-Satoshi-Nakamoto-the-mysterious-crea.webp"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
