<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
            <rss version = "2.0"
                xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
                xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
                xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
                xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
                xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
                xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
                <channel>
                    <title>News &#8211; Finance Magnates | Financial and business news</title>
<atom:link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//</link>
<description></description>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:44:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<language>en-US</language>
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<generator></generator>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[FM Group to Exhibit at Upcoming iFX EXPO LATAM 2024]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//fm-events/fm-group-to-exhibit-at-upcoming-ifx-expo-latam-2024/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//fm-events/fm-group-to-exhibit-at-upcoming-ifx-expo-latam-2024/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:20:09 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jeff Patterson]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[FM-Events]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//fm-events/fm-group-to-exhibit-at-upcoming-ifx-expo-latam-2024</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNormal">iFX EXPO LATAM 2024 will be taking place in nearly two weeks on April 9-11 in Mexico City. As one of the most anticipated events of the year in LATAM, the expo looks to bridge the B2B and B2C space. Finance Magnates Group will be making its presence felt as an exhibitor and will be available throughout the event at Booth 84.</p><p>The expo will be attracting many different types of attendees, ranging from online traders to leading brokers, IBs, affiliates, service providers, and more. This includes a global audience that is expected to reach upwards of 3.5k participants and 1.6k companies, across a total 120 countries. </p><p>Interested clients and parties are encouraged to reach out to <a href="mailto:sales@financemagnates.com">sales@financemagnates.com</a> and arrange a meeting with Finance Magnates ahead of the event. Janet Pinto, Senior Relationship Manager at FM will be on site for the three-day event.</p><p class="MsoNormal text-align-start">Network and Engage in LATAM’s Biggest Event </p><p class="MsoNormal">iFX EXPO LATAM 2024 is poised to play a central role in connecting not only businesses but every element of the retail trading industry. This includes the most trusted brokers, leading service, and technology providers, IBs, affiliates, and much more.</p><p class="MsoNormal">All participants can expect ample opportunities to forge partnerships, promote new business, and establish lasting connections. Nowhere else in LATAM will industry professionals have the chance to collaborate and network directly with so much talent, experts, specialists, providers, and peers.</p><p class="MsoNormal">Finance Magnates Group will be available to speak with each of these parties, providing a wide range of marketing and content services for clients. As the leading authority for news and content, the company is strategically placed to amplify branding, authority, and exposure. </p><p class="MsoNormal text-align-start">Head on over to Booth 84 during the event and see what Finance Magnates can do for your business!</p>

This article was written by Jeff Patterson at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[XTB Introduces Social Trading, Focusing on Investor Engagement]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/xtb-introduces-social-trading-focusing-on-investor-engagement/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/xtb-introduces-social-trading-focusing-on-investor-engagement/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:57:42 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damian Chmiel]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Brokers]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/xtb-introduces-social-trading-focusing-on-investor-engagement</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Continuing
with the roadmap announced at the beginning of 2024, XTB is introducing another
new service to its offering, this time based on social trading. As part of the XTB Social product, users can follow the most successful
investors, review their own statistics and portfolio composition, and receive
personalized notifications about transactions.</p><p>In a conversation with Finance Magnates, XTB admitted that it was looking for a solution that would "meet expectations in the context of social features" and, at the same time, "allow users to follow other people's investments."</p><p>XTB Launches Social
Trading Feature, Enabling Investors to Follow Top Performers</p><p>The launch
of XTB Social marks another milestone in <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/xtb-to-launch-social-trading-and-bond-offering-in-2024-product-roadmap/">the company's product developments this
year</a>. In recent weeks, XTB's clients gained the ability to <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/e/exchange/" class="terms__secondary-term" id="b5da6e64-2afe-421d-9b81-16404b7d59d6">exchange</a> currencies
between their investment accounts. </p><p>Now, the
investment app has been enriched with social features allowing customers to follow the best investors, check their investment statistics, and share
user profiles with friends. The company also promised to introduce bond trading
this year.</p><p>"Social
aims to fill a gap that we perceive in the financial market," Omar
Arnaout, the CEO of XTB, emphasized the growing popularity of user
engagement-based social features.</p><p>XTB Social enables users to follow top investors and friends investing with
the broker, providing insights into their portfolio composition, transaction
history, and investment statistics. At present, the new service will only be available in Poland, with plans to expand to other markets soon.</p><p>The leaderboard ranking is based on an
algorithm that considers portfolio profitability relative to risk and
other criteria, such as diversification, concentration, and risk levels. The
service further allows users to receive notifications about transactions made by
the investors they follow.</p><p>"Social
is a service that will help our clients develop their own investment
strategies," added Arnaout.</p><p>Social
trading will be another addition to XTB's offering after the company started to
more heavily <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/exclusive-xtb-introduces-etf-based-investment-plans-to-lure-passive-investors/">promote passive investments</a>, including ETFs. To this end, a month
ago, it entered into a partnership with <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/xtb-and-10-trillion-giant-blackrock-partner-up-to-promote-etf-investing/">BlackRock, the $10 trillion giant of
the fund market</a>.</p><p>It Won't Be Copy Trading</p><p>Finance
Magnates spoke with
XTB representatives about the details of the new offering. As the press
spokesman admitted, XTB Social will have nothing to do with copy trading, and
there are currently no plans for the service to evolve in that direction.</p><p>"When
we tested Social before its launch, it turned out that users were most eager to
follow their own statistics as well as the results and transactions of their
friends," XTB explained. This means that beta testers preferred to focus
on the results of friends and personal acquaintances rather than more
experienced investors.</p><p>XTB has
long "resisted" introducing social trading, unlike its competitors.
However, as it explains, it wanted to create a solution based on "original
ideas and its own technology." Furthermore, the fintech promises that XTB Social will be a completely different service from the
social trading tools offered by, for example, eToro, the leader in this branch
of <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/r/retail-trading/" class="terms__main-term" id="2d172307-15c6-4278-a100-fcbb8d9c19c9">retail trading</a>. </p><p>"We
focus exclusively on the social aspect," the XTB spokesman summarized in a
conversation with Finance Magnates.</p><p>Back in
January, XTB released preliminary financial results for 2023, which the company
confirmed this week. The report highlighted <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/xtbs-revenue-rises-10-yoy-with-active-clients-doubling-in-number/">a surge of 51% in the number of active
clients</a> to 311,971 and a net profit of PLN 791.3 million.</p>

This article was written by Damian Chmiel at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Vantage Updates Trading App to Become "Premier Destination" for Indices CFDs]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/vantage-updates-trading-app-to-become-premier-destination-for-indices-cfds/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/vantage-updates-trading-app-to-become-premier-destination-for-indices-cfds/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:49:55 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damian Chmiel]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Brokers]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/vantage-updates-trading-app-to-become-premier-destination-for-indices-cfds</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The Retail
FX/CFD broker Vantage announced today (Thursday) an update to its website and
trading application, which is intended to provide users with "greater
transparency" and "cost savings."</p><p>According
to the broker's representatives, Vantage wants to become the first choice for
retail investors interested in trading index contracts for difference (CFDs).</p><p>Vantage Changes Website
and Application</p><p>As
indicated by Vantage's press release, this move is a direct consequence of
<a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/vantage-revamps-cfds-offering-targets-asian-indices-for-2024/">introducing new stock index CFDs </a>to the brokerage’s offering in January. The
update of the website and trading application is aimed at better adapting to
investors interested in index trading.</p><p>With them
in mind, the broker has prepared additional educational materials, a more
transparent pricing comparison with competitors' offers, and better visibility
of spreads.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Explore over 25 global tradable indices with Vantage's all-in-one trading app, right at your fingertips! 🖐️ 💰 Download the app and trade indices like a pro today: <a href="https://t.co/VaqNm4ixgh">https://t.co/VaqNm4ixgh</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VantageApp?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VantageApp</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AllInOneApp?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AllInOneApp</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/IndexTrading?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#IndexTrading</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FinancialMarkets?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FinancialMarkets</a> <a href="https://t.co/snG6PqwCvR">pic.twitter.com/snG6PqwCvR</a></p>— Vantage (@vantagemkts) <a href="https://twitter.com/vantagemkts/status/1749688417728819438?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 23, 2024</a></blockquote><p>"Our
latest developments reflect our dedication to becoming the premier destination
for Indices CFD trading, providing clients with the edge they need in today's
dynamic markets," commented Marc Despallieres, the Chief Strategy and Trading
Officer at Vantage.</p><p>Additionally,
Vantage's mobile application has been enhanced with new, more advanced charting
tools. It's worth
mentioning that Vantage updated its website <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/vantage-revamps-website-in-new-year-new-look-move/">once in 2024 in a "New year, new look" move</a>, focusing on greater optimization for mobile devices. At the same time, Vantage Academy was introduced, serving
as the company's educational center.</p><p>Vantage Bets on Motorsport</p><p>Vantage's
product lineup emphasizes indices, yet its marketing efforts predominantly
highlight motorsport despite football's broad popularity among brokers. In
February, the company announced its decision to <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/motorsport-not-just-football-this-broker-bets-on-racing-for-the-third-consecutive-year/">extend its sponsorship of the
NEOM McLaren Extreme E racing team</a> for a third consecutive year. This team
competes in the off-road electric SUV racing circuit, which aims to highlight
sustainability initiatives.</p><p>The
partnership, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/brokers/vantage-becomes-sponsor-of-mclaren-racings-extreme-e-team/">initiated in 2022</a> between the UK-based Vantage and the NEOM
McLaren team, is built around a mutual dedication to innovation. </p><p>While the
norm among brokers has largely been to leverage football for promotional
activities, there's a growing trend toward engaging with motorsports. This
shift traces back to twelve years ago when XTB took the pioneering step <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/brokers/xtb-is-on-a-roll-interview-with-ceo-jakub-zablocki/">of
sponsoring an F1 team</a>. </p><p>Following
in these footsteps, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/robomarkets-sponsors-bmw-m-motorsport-for-dtm-2023-season/">RoboMarkets entered the arena</a> by sponsoring the BMW M
Motorsport team in the DTM 2023 Season, underscoring a broadening approach to
sports sponsorship within the trading industry.</p>

This article was written by Damian Chmiel at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Indonesia Implements Sandbox for Crypto Firms Ahead of OJK Oversight]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/indonesia-implements-sandbox-for-crypto-firms-ahead-of-ojk-oversight/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/indonesia-implements-sandbox-for-crypto-firms-ahead-of-ojk-oversight/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:45:15 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tareq Sikder]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[CryptoCurrency]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/indonesia-implements-sandbox-for-crypto-firms-ahead-of-ojk-oversight</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>To reshape the landscape of the cryptocurrency industry in
Indonesia, the Financial Services Authority (OJK) has announced that crypto
firms will be subject to evaluation in a regulatory sandbox before they can
obtain licenses to operate. This development comes as part of the transition of
regulatory oversight from the commodities and futures trading regulator,
Bappebti, to OJK, scheduled to take place in January 2025.</p><p>New Measure to Enhance Crypto Sector Security</p><p>Under the new regulatory framework, firms offering crypto
services in Indonesia will be required to undergo evaluation within the
regulatory sandbox. Failure to comply with this prerequisite will result in
such firms being deemed to operate illegally within the country.</p><p>A regulatory <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/s/sandbox/" class="terms__main-term" id="044130ee-16bf-4d90-b373-b634d8335cfb">sandbox</a> functions as a controlled environment
where innovative financial products and services can be tested to ensure their
safety and reliability. It provides a platform for trial runs, allowing
regulators to assess the potential risks and benefits associated with new
offerings, thereby enhancing security and responsible management within the
financial sector.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Indonesian regulator <a href="https://twitter.com/ojkindonesia?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ojkindonesia</a> says crypto products will have to be evaluated in a sandbox environment before being licensed once it takes over supervision in January 2025, <a href="https://twitter.com/shoennax?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Shoennax</a> reports.<a href="https://t.co/jGCLiLGAYT">https://t.co/jGCLiLGAYT</a></p>— CoinDesk (@CoinDesk) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinDesk/status/1773271820323492337?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 28, 2024</a></blockquote><p>Crypto Assets Set to Move from Commodities to Financial Instruments</p><p>The impending shift of regulatory supervision from Bappebti
to OJK marks a significant transition for the crypto industry in<a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/indonesia/" target="_blank" rel="follow"> Indonesia</a>.
Currently classified as commodities, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="follow">crypto </a>assets fall under the purview of
Bappebti. However, with OJK taking over supervision, it is anticipated that
crypto assets will be reclassified as financial instruments.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Indonesia's Financial Services Authority to Regulate Crypto Industry in 2025 with Evaluation in Regulatory SandboxIndonesia's Financial Services Authority (OJK) will take over regulation of the crypto industry from the commodities agency Bappebti. Crypto firms must undergo…</p>— DexBot (@dexbot) <a href="https://twitter.com/dexbot/status/1773276038782693412?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 28, 2024</a></blockquote><p>"This aligns with our spirit at OJK, particularly in
consumer protection and education," Hasan Fawzi, the regulator's Head of
Supervision for financial technology, digital financial assets and crypto, said
at a media briefing. "We expect our regulatory mechanisms to directly
impact the prevention of fraudulent investments."</p>

This article was written by Tareq Sikder at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[DED Trends on Twitter After Memecoin Snapshot Announcement]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:13:59 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[FM Contributors]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Thought Leadership]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/ded-trends-on-twitter-after-memecoin-snapshot-announcement</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNormal">Polkadot-backed community coin #DED, made it to the trending charts on X, demonstrating community’s engagement and interest behind the memecoin. The project has sparked a new-found excitement in the Polkadot ecosystem, seeing over 20,000 await their airdrop in the $DED telegram channel (https://t.me/dedbird). </p><p class="MsoNormal">With the token’s snapshot debuting early last week, the team hopes $DED signifies a second coming for the Polkadot ecosystem and fresh liquidity.</p><p class="MsoNormal">With partnerships and support from top projects on the network such as Talisman Wallet, Nova wallet, SubWallet and others, $DED is showcasing how powerful and committed the Polkadot community can be.</p><p class="MsoNormal">DED has also launched the biggest Zealy campaign the network has seen, with a total prize pool of over $30,000 in DOT and big crypto personalities have also jumped in on the action. YouTuber DataDash noted in part of his latest video that this could “Put Polkadot back in centre stage”, with others such as Ash Crypto, DubzyXBT and Crypto Banter piling into the action.</p><p class="MsoNormal text-align-start">The Dot is DED Mission Recap</p><p class="MsoNormal">DOT is $DED was initiated by the community with the purpose of creating the first memecoin on DOT. The community felt that if they worked together they could bring excitement which would onboard a larger community to Polkadot. Figuring out how to do it was the hard part, but after seeing how $BONK acted as a catalyst for the Solana ($SOL), the answer was right in front of the team.</p><p class="MsoNormal">There are now over 1 million DOT holders, and an estimated 100,000 of them have stuck it out to support the DED launch. Now the Snapshot has been taken, DOT is DED will await its airdrop.</p><p class="MsoNormal text-align-start">For the latest updates and community activity Join the $DED Telegram channel and follow on X.</p>

This article was written by FM Contributors at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Capital Markets Elite Group’s UK Losses Deepen despite Revenue Rise]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/capital-markets-elite-groups-uk-losses-deepen-despite-revenue-rise/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/capital-markets-elite-groups-uk-losses-deepen-despite-revenue-rise/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 08:40:57 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arnab Shome]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Brokers]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/capital-markets-elite-groups-uk-losses-deepen-despite-revenue-rise</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The United Kingdom-registered entity of Capital Markets Elite Group, a broker specializing in forex and contracts for differences, released its financials for the last fiscal year as it generated an annual turnover of £449,772.</p><p dir="ltr">A Loss Making Broker</p><p dir="ltr">The figure for the fiscal year, which ended on 31 May 2023, was reported following a year when it recorded a turnover of £27,786. After considering £311,364 in cost of sales, the brokerage operator's latest gross profit amounted to £138,408.</p><p dir="ltr">However, the administrative expense of the UK-registered company exceeded £1.03 million, compared to £560,534 in the previous year. The costs also pushed the company towards an operating loss of £895,807, deepening it from a loss of £495,991 in the previous year.</p><p dir="ltr">The net loss of the broker from its UK operations for the year totaled £892,630, while this figure was at a loss of £448,282 in the previous year.</p><p dir="ltr">A Multi-Regulated Broker</p><p dir="ltr">Apart from its operations in the United Kingdom, the broker brand also operates with another entity licensed in the <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/cayman-islands/">Cayman Islands</a>, which is owned by a holding company registered in Saint Lucia.</p><p dir="ltr">“The firm continues in business using its existing financial service regulated permissions. The firm offers brokerage and execution services for both equities and derivative products. The firm’s focus to date has been to the equity markets targeting mainly <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/simplicity-beats-complex-design-how-to-build-a-retail-trading-solution/">retail clients based in the UK and Europe</a>,” the latest Companies House filing stated. However, it is not clear how the brokerage has any other licenses from any <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/european-union/">European Union</a> member to operate within the bloc. </p><p dir="ltr">The latest filing added that the client onboarding program of the UK entity added close to 1,000 new accounts in the last fiscal year, and about half of them have “progressed to funding.” It further highlighted that the client demographic is predominantly “retail.”</p>

This article was written by Arnab Shome at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Crypto Miner Sells Data Center for $6.1M as Its Shares Plunge 55% in 2024]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-miner-sells-data-center-for-61m-as-its-shares-plunge-55-in-2024/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-miner-sells-data-center-for-61m-as-its-shares-plunge-55-in-2024/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 08:33:29 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damian Chmiel]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[CryptoCurrency]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-miner-sells-data-center-for-61m-as-its-shares-plunge-55-in-2024</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Although
Bitcoin (BTC) has already gained nearly 70% in 2024, shares of Argo Blockchain,
a cryptocurrency mining company publicly listed in London and the USA, are
scraping the bottom, falling 55%.</p><p>The
company's solution to some of its problems and shareholder discontent is selling its data center in Mirabel, Canada. The company's London branch (LSE: <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/argo/" target="_blank" rel="follow">ARB</a>) announced the finalization of this move on Thursday. At the
same time, the miner issued over 460,000 new ordinary shares.</p><p>Argo Blockchain Closes
Sale of Mirabel Data Center, Reduces Debt by $12.4M</p><p>The plan to sell a data center in the Quebec region was first announced <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/argo-crypto-miner-chops-galaxy-debt-by-60-in-61m-deal/">almost two months ago</a>. The transaction, which yielded a total consideration of $6.1 million, has
enabled the company to reduce its debt and streamline its operations significantly.</p><p>The net
proceeds from the sale were used to repay the Mirabel Facility's outstanding
mortgage of $1.4 million, with the remainder being allocated to repay <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/mike-novogratzs-galaxy-saves-bitcoin-miner-argo-from-bankruptcy/">debt owed
to Galaxy Digital Holdings, Ltd. </a></p><p>As of 28
March 2024, Argo's debt balance with Galaxy is $12.8 million,
representing a reduction of 63% from the original balance of $35 million.</p><p>"The
Company continues to execute on its strategy of strengthening the balance sheet
and reducing non-mining operating expenses. The Company reduced its debt by
$12.4 million in Q1 2024,” Thomas Chippas, the Chief Executive Officer at Argo,
<a href="https://www.londonstockexchange.com/news-article/ARB/closing-on-sale-of-mirabel-tvr/16398972">commented on the transaction</a>.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ARB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ARB</a> ARGO BLOCKCHAIN Closing on sale of Mirabel data centre for a total consideration of $6.1m</p>— The Dude (@Redpanda73) <a href="https://twitter.com/Redpanda73/status/1773256366074786293?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 28, 2024</a></blockquote><p>In addition
to the debt reduction, Argo has relocated and deployed mining machines from the Mirabel Facility to its facility in Baie Comeau,
Quebec. This consolidation is expected to reduce the company's non-mining
operating expenses by $0.7 million per year, allowing for more efficient use of
the facility and onsite team. Argo
Blockchain also announced the issuance of 460,477 new ordinary shares.</p><p>Bitcoin Winter Hits Argo</p><p>As
mentioned at the very beginning, the price of <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/b/bitcoin/" class="terms__main-term" id="261088a9-0f41-4202-a73c-31f75ba6bd93">Bitcoin</a> is dynamically growing in
2024. Initially, Argo Blockchain's shares rose along with it, but
weaker-than-expected <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-winter-hits-argo-a-look-into-its-sluggish-start-in-2024/">BTC production in the first months of the year</a> caused
shareholders to lose confidence in the company. As a result, the cryptocurrency
spring in the broad market turned into an extended winter for the digital asset
miner.</p><p>In the
meantime, Argo <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/b/blockchain/" class="terms__secondary-term" id="be18ed01-45fc-4044-b447-06802a10dbcd">Blockchain</a> underwent significant changes in its management
ranks. <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/argo-blockchain-excels-in-bitcoin-production-announces-coo-exit/">Seif El-Bakly </a>stepped down as Chief Operating Officer after serving as
interim Chief Executive Officer from February to November 2023.</p><p>Whether we look at Argo's shares listed in London or the USA, the charts
show the same picture: a decline of about 55% since the beginning of the year.</p><p>At the same time, Marathon Digital Holdings, the largest publicly traded cryptocurrency miner, is losing only 6%, and Phoenix Group is gaining around 2%.</p>

This article was written by Damian Chmiel at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Dirty Truth of Clean Investments: ASIC Triumphs in Historic Greenwashing Case]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/dirty-truth-of-clean-investments-asic-triumphs-in-historic-greenwashing-case/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/dirty-truth-of-clean-investments-asic-triumphs-in-historic-greenwashing-case/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 08:10:50 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damian Chmiel]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/dirty-truth-of-clean-investments-asic-triumphs-in-historic-greenwashing-case</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In a
resounding win for the Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC),
the Federal Court has determined that Vanguard Investments Australia
contravened the ASIC rules by making misleading representations about the environmental,
social, and governance (ESG) exclusionary screens used in its Vanguard
Ethically Conscious Global </p><p>The ruling
is an important turning point for ASIC in its ongoing efforts to combat
greenwashing in the financial services industry.</p><p>ASIC Secures Victory in
First Civil Penalty Action Targeting Misleading ESG Claims</p><p>During a March
hearing, Vanguard admitted to engaging in conduct that was liable to mislead
the public and making false or misleading representations. Justice O'Bryan
subsequently found that Vanguard had contravened the <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/a/asic/" class="terms__main-term" id="dfb41d67-b79e-4b09-b365-1f341b85a51b">ASIC</a> Act on numerous
occasions in relation to its Vanguard Ethically Conscious Global Aggregate Bond
Index Fund.</p><p>The
misleading claims were made in various communications, including product
disclosure statements, a media release, website statements, a YouTube
interview, and an online presentation at a Fund Manager Event. </p><p>“By
Vanguard’s own admission, it misled investors on a number of its claims,” said the
ASIC Deputy Chairwoman, Sarah Court. This is another important step in a case
<a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/institutional-forex/asic-pursues-vanguard-australia-in-greenwashing-lawsuit/">that began in July last year</a>.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Federal Court has found Vanguard Investments Australia made misleading claims about certain <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ESG?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ESG</a> exclusionary screens applied to investments in an index fund <a href="https://t.co/IbCKhbRxLt">https://t.co/IbCKhbRxLt</a> <a href="https://t.co/miMqmPc9t8">pic.twitter.com/miMqmPc9t8</a></p>— ASIC Media (@asicmedia) <a href="https://twitter.com/asicmedia/status/1773210932233019544?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 28, 2024</a></blockquote><p>Vanguard
had asserted that the fund's underlying index excluded companies with
significant business activities in industries such as fossil fuels. However,
the company has now acknowledged that a substantial proportion of the
securities in the index and the fund were not properly screened against the
relevant ESG criteria.</p><p>"As
ASIC's first greenwashing court outcome, the case shows our commitment to
taking on misleading marketing and greenwashing claims made by companies in the
financial services industry,” Court added.” It sends a strong message to
companies making sustainable investment claims that they need to reflect the
true position."</p><p>The court
will consider the appropriate penalty for Vanguard's conduct at a further
hearing scheduled for 1 August 2024. As of 26 February 2021, the Vanguard
Ethically Conscious Global Aggregate Bond Index Fund had over $1 billion in
assets under management.</p><p>It Is Cool to Be Green</p><p>Greenwashing
is when a company tries to make itself look more environmentally friendly than
it really is through misleading marketing and unsubstantiated claims. The term
combines "green" (meaning environmentally sound) and
"whitewashing" (meaning to gloss over wrongdoing).</p><p>In essence,
greenwashing is a deceptive advertising gimmick intended to mislead consumers
who prefer to buy goods and services from companies that care about the
environment. The company might make false or exaggerated claims about the
sustainability of its products, practices or brand image.</p><p>ASIC, by
the end of 2022, had established 12 new "Enforcement priorities,"
among which <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/asic-heralds-12-enforcement-priorities-for-2023-including-crypto/">combating greenwashing was included</a>. The first case against
Vanguard demonstrates its effectiveness in addressing this issue. </p><p>The topic
of greenwashing and ESG investing <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/institutional-forex/esg-investing-beyond-greenwashing-perspectives-from-fmls23/">was also discussed</a> at the Finance Magnates
London Summit 2023.</p><p>Evdokia
Pitsillidou, the Partner, Risk, and <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/c/compliance/" class="terms__secondary-term" id="569f58ee-534c-44f0-a7cd-f55b0f9a2b2a">Compliance</a> Director at SALVUS FUND, in a
conversation with Matt Bullivant, the Director of Sustainability and ESG
Strategy at OakNorth, and P.Faisal Islam, the CEO of Complytek.ai, explored the
current status of ESG investing and its future implications.</p>

This article was written by Damian Chmiel at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Breaking: Prop Trading Firm the Funded Trader "Pauses All Operations"]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/breaking-prop-trading-firm-the-funded-trader-pauses-all-operations/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/breaking-prop-trading-firm-the-funded-trader-pauses-all-operations/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 06:07:06 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arnab Shome]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Brokers]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/breaking-prop-trading-firm-the-funded-trader-pauses-all-operations</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Funded Trader, a prop trading firm that recently faced an array of complaints for payout denials, has “temporarily paused all operations” with promises of a relaunch.</p><p dir="ltr">“Over the coming week, we will follow up with specifics as we work to resume operations,” a notice on the prop trading firm’s website noted with a countdown timer of 21 days. However, it did not clarify if the timer is for its relaunch.</p><p dir="ltr">Relaunch Promised, but When?</p><p dir="ltr">Angelo Ciaramello, the Chief Executive Officer of The Funded Trader, noted in an announcement: “In pausing our operations, we will be relaunching the brand but with a slightly different look and feel.”</p><p dir="ltr">“Over the coming week, we will post updates on what this will look like and how this decision affects everyone involved… The relaunch of TFT is coming, and earning your trust will be difficult, but we know what it takes.”</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I wanted to address you all personally. You have been the lifeblood of TFT. You have fought in battle with me day in and day out for years. You have participated in one of the greatest movements in history and have delivered to me what I dreamed of, this community. Being in the…</p>— The Funded Trader (@thefundedtrader) <a href="https://twitter.com/thefundedtrader/status/1773212708235546660?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 28, 2024</a></blockquote><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The company further noted that it will put out a plan for existing customers in the coming weeks. Despite the assurance of the relaunch, pausing the entire operation for a relaunch looks odd.</p><p dir="ltr">The Company Faces a Wave of Complaints</p><p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/the-funded-trader/">The Funded Trader</a>, with over 80,000 accounts, is a part of Easton Consulting Technologies LLC, which operates a number of other prop trading platforms. In the past few weeks, the customers of the prop trading platform took to social media, especially Trustpilot, to complaints about abrupt payout denials and unresponsive customer support.</p><p dir="ltr">However, Ciaramello called the complaints "propaganda" against the firm. Subsequently, the prop trading firm confirmed that it suspended all payouts because of a “<a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/prop-trading-firm-the-funded-trader-cites-internal-audit-to-suspend-payouts/">self-imposed internal audit.</a>”</p><p dir="ltr">During a live broadcast on YouTube, Ciaramello presented a graphic suggesting that in the first two months of 2024, TFT paid out over $17 million to clients while blocking withdrawals of just over $2 million during the same period.</p><p dir="ltr">“The payments were rejected due to KYC, due to any type of fraud, credit card fraud and any prohibited trading strategies,” the CEO said during the live broadcast. However, he <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/traders-rage-as-prop-firm-the-funded-trader-delays-payouts-for-up-to-a-month/">continued to face backlash on social media</a>.</p>

This article was written by Arnab Shome at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Robinhood Launches Credit Card to Diversify Offerings beyond Trading]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/robinhood-launches-credit-card-to-diversify-offerings-beyond-trading/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/robinhood-launches-credit-card-to-diversify-offerings-beyond-trading/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/robinhood-launches-credit-card-to-diversify-offerings-beyond-trading</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Robinhood has introduced a credit card tailored for
its premium customers. This move aims to solidify the firm's presence
in the personal finance sector while onboarding more users to subscribe to its
premium services. </p><p>Dubbed Robinhood Gold Card, the new offering charges no annual or foreign
transaction fees to provide users with a cost-effective payment solution.
According to Robinhood's website, cardholders can receive up to 3% cash back on
purchases, along with 5% cash back on bookings made through Robinhood's travel
portal. </p><p>Diversifying Offerings</p><p>The launch of the <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="follow">Robinhood</a> Gold Card marks a
significant step in the company's endeavor to diversify its product range and
reduce reliance on market-sensitive trading revenue, Reuters reported. With the launch of the Robinhood Gold Card, the
online trading app based in California is broadening its range of financial products.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Forged in fire. Cast in solid gold. Limited edition. Claim your spot on the waitlist for the Robinhood Gold Card. Terms and subscription fee apply. <a href="https://t.co/iQ03uMuWiH">https://t.co/iQ03uMuWiH</a> <a href="https://t.co/axjKnhd1Xz">pic.twitter.com/axjKnhd1Xz</a></p>— Robinhood (@RobinhoodApp) <a href="https://twitter.com/RobinhoodApp/status/1772994595405607055?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 27, 2024</a></blockquote><p>The introduction of the Robinhood Gold Card presents a
compelling proposition for the platform's existing Gold members. With no annual
fee and lucrative cash-back rewards, the card aims to incentivize users to
maintain their premium membership. </p><p>Additionally, users gain access to perks, such
as the ability to create virtual cards, add family members, and track spending
through a dedicated app. By leveraging its extensive user base, Robinhood plans
to enhance loyalty programs in the financial services industry.</p><p>Strategic Acquisitions </p><p>Robinhood entered the credit
card market after acquiring the fintech startup firm X1 Inc. for $95 million
last year, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/" target="_blank" rel="follow">Finance Magnates</a> reported. As part of the <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/fintech/p2p/robinhood-to-acquire-credit-card-firm-x1-for-95m/" target="_blank" rel="follow">acquisition</a> deal, Robinhood welcomed the Co-Founders of X1, Deepak Rao and Siddharth Batra. The executives were tasked with overseeing Robinhood's newly acquired credit card business.</p><p>Robinhood's February 2024 report highlighted impressive milestones. The firm's funded customers reached 23.6 million by the end of the month, representing a substantial increase of approximately 130,000 from the previous month. </p><p>
Besides that, assets under custody experienced a remarkable upswing, soaring to nearly $119 billion. This marked a substantial upsurge of 59% from the previous year. In the fourth quarter of 2023, Robinhood posted a net revenue of $471 million, representing an increase of 24% year-over-year. </p>

This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Coinbase Faces Regulatory Heat as Judge Allows SEC's Lawsuit to Proceed]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-faces-regulatory-heat-as-judge-allows-secs-lawsuit-to-proceed/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-faces-regulatory-heat-as-judge-allows-secs-lawsuit-to-proceed/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:14:08 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[CryptoCurrency]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinbase-faces-regulatory-heat-as-judge-allows-secs-lawsuit-to-proceed</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>A federal judge in Manhattan has allowed the US
Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to proceed with a lawsuit against
Coinbase. While the court dismissed one of the regulator's claims, this latest decision paves the way for a potentially lengthy legal battle. The ruling marks a significant development in the ongoing regulatory scrutiny facing digital assets firms, Reuters reported.</p><p>The US District Judge Katherine Failla partly
granted Coinbase's motion to dismiss the <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/us-sec/" target="_blank" rel="follow">SEC</a>'s lawsuit, which accused the
company of violating securities regulations. Despite this partial win, the ruling largely aligns
with the SEC's approach to regulating cryptocurrency, echoing previous
decisions in favor of the regulator.</p><p>Coinbase's Legal Arguments</p><p><a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="follow">Coinbase</a>'s Chief Legal Officer, Paul Grewal, expressed
the exchange's preparedness for the ruling and reiterated its commitment to
contesting the SEC's claims. Despite this setback, Coinbase has expressed optimism
in its legal arguments and plans to prove its position in court.</p><p>The SEC's lawsuit against Coinbase, initiated in June,
alleges that the <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/e/exchange/" class="terms__main-term" id="b5da6e64-2afe-421d-9b81-16404b7d59d6">exchange</a> facilitated the trading of several crypto tokens that
should have been registered as securities. Additionally, the SEC claims that Coinbase operated
unlawfully as a national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency
without proper registration.</p><p>Judge Failla's ruling allowed most aspects of the
lawsuit to proceed, except for the SEC's claims that Coinbase acted as an
unregistered broker through its wallet application. This legal confrontation
marks a pivotal moment in the SEC's efforts to apply traditional securities
laws to the rapidly evolving digital asset sector.</p><p>Implications for the Crypto Market</p><p>Central to the legal dispute is the interpretation of
what constitutes security in the context of crypto assets. The SEC
has relied on established legal precedents, including a US Supreme Court
ruling, to determine whether certain crypto assets should be considered securities.</p><p>However, Coinbase has contended that, unlike traditional
securities, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/c/cryptocurrencies/" class="terms__secondary-term" id="b091101e-6e02-4b36-aa0e-7c972dfdd6ed">cryptocurrencies</a> do not meet the criteria of deriving returns
solely from the efforts of others. Judge Failla's decision favored the SEC's argument,
suggesting that some digital assets listed on Coinbase could indeed be
classified as securities.</p><p>Last year, the SEC <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/sec-rejects-coinbases-call-for-crypto-specific-regulations-citing-existing-laws/" target="_blank" rel="follow">declined Coinbase Global's petition</a> for
specific regulations in the digital asset sector. Despite Coinbase's plea for
these rules, citing inadequacies in current securities laws, the SEC's Chair, Gary Gensler, mentioned that the existing regulations are sufficient. He emphasized the applicability of the current laws to crypto markets.</p><p>In a letter to Coinbase's Chief Legal Officer, Gensler
claimed that the current regulations are suitable for the crypto industry.
Gensler stressed the adaptability of existing laws, citing the Supreme Court's
Howey test, which has been effectively used to evaluate crypto assets in
federal courts.</p>

This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[XCAD Announces Multiple Governments’ Backing for New Initiative to Expand Web3 Education]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/xcad-announces-multiple-governments-backing-for-new-initiative-to-expand-web3-education/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/xcad-announces-multiple-governments-backing-for-new-initiative-to-expand-web3-education/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:25:27 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[FM Contributors]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Thought Leadership]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/xcad-announces-multiple-governments-backing-for-new-initiative-to-expand-web3-education</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>XCAD Network - a tokenisation platform for YouTubers to connect and reward their viewers with crypto tokens - today announced it has signed MOUs (Memorandum of Understanding) with multiple governments to expand incentivised Web3 education to millions of people across the globe.</p><p>By securing the support of several governments, XCAD aims to bridge the gap between Web2 and Web3, and enable more people to partake in the Web3 Space. XCAD Network has announced the first government agreement, which is with Pakistan. Under this partnership, XCAD will distribute and incentivise the consumption of educational media among Pakistani citizens. </p><p>Education is the first step in bringing new people into the Web3 space. As part of the MOUs, XCAD Network will work with governments to launch pilot campaigns to educate their citizens on Web3. These campaigns will be joint campaigns launched by governments and the XCAD team alongside select content creators from that country's jurisdiction. </p><p>Users will have to download the XCAD Network application to watch interactive educational content on various Web3 topics. Upon completing the modules and consuming content, users are rewarded with tokens.</p><p>Blockchain, cryptocurrency and the Web3 world will be the key focus areas. However, governments can also focus education on other subjects, such as financial literacy. </p><p>Oliver Bell, the Chief Executive Officer of XCAD Network, commented, “Working directly with Government entities is incredibly exciting for the XCAD project and the Web3 Space as a whole. What we're doing aligns with the government's vision towards digitisation and global blockchain adoption” </p><p>Another way that XCAD plans to work with Government entities, is by leveraging the XCAD platform to boost travel and tourism engagement in their country. They want to partner with creators and citizens to create engaging educational content around tourism in their country. Those who consume the content are then rewarded.</p><p>XCAD Network has already onboarded some of the biggest YouTubers in the world to issue creator tokens on its platform. However, getting governments involved gives the project more credibility. This allows XCAD Network to attract even bigger names to issue creator tokens, stay on top of regulatory requirements and drive more users to the XCAD platform.</p><p>About XCAD Network</p><p>XCAD Network (https://xcadnetwork.com/) allows YouTube creators to launch personalised tokens and generate dedicated economies around their loyal fan-base It also offers new upstart creators a way to earn tokens and generate income even before the creator generates traction on YouTube itself.</p><p>In addition to helping generate new revenue, XCAD Network fosters deeper engagement through gamification and rewards. Fans benefit monetarily from the growth of their favourite creators, thus strengthening the bonds between creators and their followers.</p><p>The platform is backed by famous YouTubers such as KSI and Mr Beast, and is home to 100+ celebrity influencers globally with a combined audience of over 800M.</p><p class="text-align-start">The XCAD ecosystem consists of DEXs, a governance portal, a browser plugin with Youtube integration, cross-chain bridges, staking pools, and creator swap, which lets users exchange creator tokens.</p>

This article was written by FM Contributors at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[European Banks Grapple with SEPA Instant Payment Deadline: 58% Deem Unrealistic]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/european-banks-grapple-with-sepa-instant-payment-deadline-58-deem-unrealistic/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/european-banks-grapple-with-sepa-instant-payment-deadline-58-deem-unrealistic/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:08 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[FinTech]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/european-banks-grapple-with-sepa-instant-payment-deadline-58-deem-unrealistic</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The majority of European banks are facing a
difficult situation regarding the timelines  for implementing the Single European Payments Area (SEPA) instant payments set by the EU. A report by RedCompass Labs revealed that 58% of 200 senior payment
professionals surveyed find the timelines unrealistic.</p><p>Embracing Instant Payments </p><p>According to the survey, there is looming uncertainty over the readiness of
banks to facilitate <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/sepa/" target="_blank" rel="follow">SEPA</a> instant payments. One of the key findings of the
research is that European banks are underestimating the volume of payments they
need to process per second. </p><p>Instant payments accelerate the movement of money
between businesses and individuals. While the average target is between 101 and 300
payments per second, experts suggest that aiming for at least 1,000 <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/p/payments/" class="terms__main-term" id="f1d2a713-da14-4a6b-8fcd-e8f360d07f45">payments</a>
per second is imperative, considering the magnitude of bulk payment files.</p><p>The transition towards SEPA instant payments is hindered by the challenges faced by the European banks. The top five hurdles include adapting
customers' channels, implementing the provisions for <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/k/know-your-customer-kyc/" target="_blank" rel="follow">KYC</a> and sanctions screening, scaling
throughput, creating value-added offerings, and ensuring 24/7 availability.</p><p>Tom Hewson, the Partner and CEO at RedCompass Labs,
mentioned: "Europe
is taking a leap forward with new legislation that will make around-the-clock
instant payments the new normal. This is an exciting development, but the deadlines
are tight. Banks, already extremely stretched delivering the migration to ISO 20022,
must be able to send and receive instant payments by the end of 2025. That’s a
big ask."</p><p>Benefits of Instant Payments</p><p>Despite these challenges, there's a silver lining for
European banks. A significant 77% of the respondents in the survey believe that the benefits of instant payments
outweigh the costs. Moreover, there's a growing demand for instant payment
products and services, with 89% of respondents acknowledging this trend.</p><p>The adoption of new rules for instant <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/euro/" target="_blank" rel="follow">Euro</a> transfers
by MEPs marks a significant milestone in Europe's journey towards instant
payments. The legislation aims to promote SEPA integration, strengthen the
Euro's international role, and reduce reliance on foreign payment schemes.</p><p>Hewson added: "As a bank, your internal systems
must be ready to handle the increased volume and speed of transactions. In the
past, we talked about hundreds of transactions per second for bank-to-bank
systems. Currently, it is multiples of thousands per second. You will need to cover
downtime and system outages while recording and synchronizing data accurately,
in real-time, across various parts of the payment system for it to be reliable."</p>

This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA["Card Payments No Longer the Default Choice”: Study Predicts 19% Decline in 4 Years]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/card-payments-no-longer-the-default-choice-predicts-19-plummet-in-4-years/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/card-payments-no-longer-the-default-choice-predicts-19-plummet-in-4-years/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:40:05 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tareq Sikder]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/card-payments-no-longer-the-default-choice-predicts-19-plummet-in-4-years</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Boku, a global network for localized payment solutions, has
collaborated with Juniper Research to release the '2024 Global Ecommerce
Report: The Changing World of Payments'. The report offers an examination of
consumer payment preferences and behaviors across the globe, highlighting a
notable trend towards local payment methods in ecommerce transactions.</p><p>Local Payment Methods Outpace Traditional Cards </p><p>Based on a survey of 10,500 consumers and data analysis from
37 major markets, the report has indicated a decline in the market share of
traditional card payments alongside an increase in the use of local payment
methods for online purchases globally. Key findings include the rapid growth of
Account to Account (A2A) payments, such as PIX in Brazil, UPI in India, and
iDEAL in the Netherlands, emerging as the fastest-growing payment method within
ecommerce.</p><p>According to the report's global findings, traditional card
payments are expected to decrease to 19% of transaction value by 2028, down
from 31% in 2023. Conversely, local payment methods are projected to constitute
58% of ecommerce transaction values by 2028, an increase from 47% in 2023, marking the
first time they surpass traditional card payments in transaction value.
Additionally, it is estimated that 37% of individuals globally will actively
utilize local payment methods by 2028.</p><p>Instant A2A Payments and Wallets to Dominate by 2028</p><p>Instant A2A and non-card-linked wallets are forecasted to
account for over 50% of ecommerce transaction value globally by 2028, with
instant A2A payments anticipated to more than double, constituting 18% of all
ecommerce transactions by volume by 2028, up from 8% in 2023.</p><p>Stuart Neal, the CEO of Boku said: “Our research shows the
way the world transacts online is changing fast, and that change is being
driven in the main by a consumer preference for convenient, seamless payment
methods like digital wallets, direct carrier billing and Account to Account transfers.
Merchants now realise that the key to their future global growth and success
lies in their ability to offer consumers more payment choice.” </p><p>“At Boku, we’re excited to provide the world’s largest
merchants with access to our global network of localised payment solutions so
their customers can more easily pay for the things they love, the way they want
- no matter where they are in the world.” </p><p>The report emphasizes the significance of <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/payment/">payment</a> choice for
consumers worldwide, particularly among mobile-first generations, who
prioritize the convenience and seamlessness of digital wallets, direct carrier
billing, and instant A2A payments. This shift in consumer behavior is shaping
the present and potentially paving the way for adoption by older demographics.</p><p>From Mobile Money to A2A Payments, Insights from Africa
to Asia</p><p>Regionally, the report provides insights into specific
markets. In Africa &amp; <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/middle-east/" target="_blank" rel="follow">Middle East</a>, local payments and mobile money services
like M-PESA and MoMo have seen success, necessitating highly localized payment
strategies. Similarly, in Asia Pacific, while card payments remain significant,
local payment methods are rapidly gaining traction. </p><p>Europe anticipates a decline in card payments with
substantial growth in A2A payments, while the Far East &amp; China continue to
prefer mobile wallets. LATAM and North America also exhibit shifting payment
preferences, while the Indian Subcontinent sees a significant shift towards
local payment methods, particularly A2A payments, driven by successful
initiatives like UPI in India.</p><p>Nick Maynard, the VP of <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/f/fintech/" class="terms__main-term" id="891edcf3-475e-45f3-a8b8-3ba2e7d37339">Fintech</a> Market Research, at Juniper
Research said: “Our research for this report from Boku highlights that against
a backdrop of continued strong growth in ecommerce, the global card schemes
(credit, debit and card-linked wallets) continue to lose share to regional and
local payment methods. This is a trend seen at an aggregate global level but
also repeated in every region across the world."</p>

This article was written by Tareq Sikder at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[A Truce in the Swipe War: How Visa and Mastercard Settlements Could Reshape Payments]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/a-truce-in-the-swipe-war-how-visa-and-mastercard-settlements-could-reshape-payments/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/a-truce-in-the-swipe-war-how-visa-and-mastercard-settlements-could-reshape-payments/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro Ferreira]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/a-truce-in-the-swipe-war-how-visa-and-mastercard-settlements-could-reshape-payments</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>For nearly two decades, a simmering battle raged between
the titans of the payments industry - Visa and Mastercard - and the merchants
who rely on them. The bone of contention? Swipe fees, the invisible tax levied
on every credit card transaction. </p><p>Finally, a white flag has been raised. <a href="https://investor.visa.com/news/news-details/2024/Visa-Agrees-to-Landmark-Settlement-with-U.S.-Merchants-Reducing-Rates-and-Guaranteeing-No-Increases-for-at-Least-Five-Years/default.aspx">Visa</a>
and <a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/press/2024/march/mastercard-commits-to-lowering-u-s-interchange-for-small-businesses-and-broader-merchant-community/">Mastercard</a>
reached settlements with U.S. merchants, promising reduced fees and a period of
stability. But what does <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/fintech/visa-strikes-deal-with-us-merchants-to-cap-interchange-rates-for-five-years/">this
truce</a> mean for the future of payments? </p><p>A Boon for Small Businesses?</p><p>The settlements are a clear win for merchants, particularly
the lifeblood of the American economy - small businesses. Lower fees translate
to increased profit margins, potentially allowing them to invest in growth or
even lower prices for consumers. </p><p>Additionally, the cap on interchange rates for at least
five years provides much-needed predictability, enabling businesses to plan
their finances more effectively.</p><p>A Shift in the Power Dynamic?</p><p>Visa and Mastercard moves signal a shift in the power
dynamic within the payments ecosystem. Historically, both companies held the
upper hand, dictating fees and wielding control over how transactions are
processed. </p><p>This new landscape, however, empowers merchants, granting
them greater flexibility. Notably, the ability to steer customers towards
preferred payment methods, potentially debit cards with lower fees, could seriously disrupt the status quo.</p><p>In fact, given that these settlements weaken Visa and
Mastercard’s position, merchants now have more leverage to negotiate lower
interchange fees with both networks. Consequently, this could lead to increased
pressure on interchange rates, with merchants, particularly large retailers,
pushing for steeper reductions. Additionally, issuers might differentiate
interchange rates based on a merchant's risk profile, potentially offering lower
fees to those with lower fraud rates or a history of on-time payments.</p><p>A Domino Effect on Consumer Prices or on
Interchange Revenue?</p><p>A central question remains: will these fee reductions
translate into lower prices for consumers? The answer, like most things in
economics, is nuanced. While merchants might be incentivized to pass on some
savings, the impact could be muted. Retailers might choose to absorb the cost
to maintain competitiveness, or they might invest the savings in other areas like
employee wages or marketing. Ultimately, it might just be a little too soon to
predict the effect on consumer prices as it will depend on market forces and
individual business decisions.</p><p>On the flipside, lower interchange fees might also translate
to a significant drop in revenue for issuing banks. To compensate, they might just
increase cardholder fees, focusing on premium rewards programs with higher
annual fees and richer benefits to maintain profitability. Visa and Mastercard
might also adjust network rules or introduce new fees to generate additional
revenue streams, meaning it's still too early to tell.</p><p>Innovation on the Horizon?</p><p>The settlements could inadvertently spark a wave of
innovation in the payments space. With a more level playing field, new players
might emerge, offering alternative payment solutions with lower fees and
advanced functionalities. Additionally, competition between Visa and Mastercard
to retain merchants could lead to further advancements in security, fraud
prevention, and payment processing efficiency.</p><p>A Long Game with Uncertain Outcomes</p><p>It's important to remember that the settlements are just
the first move in a long game. The ultimate impact will depend on court
approval, implementation details, and how merchants and consumers adapt to the
new paradigm. Additionally, the settlements only address the U.S. market,
leaving the global payments scene ripe for further disruption.</p><p>A Thorn in the Side of Traditional Networks</p><p>While Visa and Mastercard’s moves might seem to suggest a
solidified landscape, on the periphery lurks a potential game-changer:
cryptocurrency. Crypto payments have been gaining traction in recent years,
offering an alternative with potentially lower fees and faster settlement
times. While the settlements provide stability in the traditional card network,
they could also inadvertently fuel the growth of crypto payments.</p><p>It is undeniable that cryptocurrencies boast inherent cost
advantages and by eliminating the need for intermediaries like Visa and
Mastercard, crypto transactions could undercut interchange fees altogether.
This cost advantage could incentivize merchants, particularly those operating
in high-volume, low-margin sectors, to embrace crypto payments.</p><p>Moreover, the transparency and immutability of blockchain
technology, the backbone of cryptocurrencies, has the potential to disrupt the
current system. Unlike traditional card networks, blockchain transactions
provide a clear record of fees associated with each payment. This transparency
could empower merchants to negotiate fairer fees with established players or
fully embrace decentralized finance solutions.</p><p>The Takeaway: A Reshaped Payments Landscape</p><p>The <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/mastercard-visa-reach-30-bln-settlement-over-credit-card-fees-2024-03-26/">Visa
and Mastercard settlements</a> mark a turning point in the payments industry.
While the full impact remains to be seen, one thing is certain: the days of
merchants silently absorbing swipe fees are over. This newfound parity has the
potential to benefit businesses, spur innovation, and reshape the way we pay
for goods and services. As the dust settles on this long-standing dispute, one
can't help but feel a sense of anticipation for the next chapter in the
evolution of payments.</p>

This article was written by Pedro Ferreira at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Let's Not Write the Eulogy for Cash Just Yet]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/lets-not-write-the-eulogy-for-cash-just-yet/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/lets-not-write-the-eulogy-for-cash-just-yet/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro Ferreira]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Payments]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//fintech/payments/lets-not-write-the-eulogy-for-cash-just-yet</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Central Bank Digital Currencies, or CBDCs, are the new
hotness. Governments and financial institutions are singing their praises like some
sort of digital barbershop quartet, promising a future of seamless, frictionless
transactions and a marvelous financial utopia built upon a foundation of ones
and zeroes. But hold onto your wallets because in our eagerness to
dive headfirst into the digital pool, we might just be overlooking the seriously
unassuming greenback (or whatever your local paper currency may be) chilling in
our back pockets.</p><p>Power Outages Mean (No) Business</p><p>The recent payment processing outages in the UK, where <a href="https://www.euronews.com/business/2024/03/15/mcdonalds-system-outages-reported-in-europe-and-worldwide">retail
giants like McDonald's</a> and <a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/tech/down-tesco-greggs-sainsburys-mcdonalds-shops-offline-not-working-b2515841.html">Tesco</a>
were forced to temporarily become cash-only establishments, serve as a harsh
wake-up call.</p><p>Well, as it turns out, <a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2024/03/21/review-launched-sainsburys-greggs-hit-payment-problems/">digital systems aren't exactly
flawless</a>. A software glitch, a cyberattack with ill intent, or even a seemingly
harmless update can bring our meticulously crafted cashless world screeching to
a halt. And, suddenly, just like that, that cup of coffee you desperately crave
becomes an unattainable luxury.</p><p>Sure, CBDCs promise a lot. Faster transactions, wider
financial inclusion, and let's not forget, the ever-watchful eye of the
government. Cash, on the other hand, offers a crucial layer of anonymity and
resilience that CBDCs might struggle to match. Need to grab that perfect
birthday present without your significant other getting a notification about
your extravagant spending? Cash is your wingman. Facing a tech meltdown that
brings the entire payment network to its knees? Cash keeps the wheels of
commerce – and your ability to buy that cup of coffee –  turning.</p><p>Embracing progress seems to be a necessity
these days. But progress shouldn't come at the expense of individual freedom
and redundancy. </p><p>CBDCs can definitely be a part of the financial equation,
but let's not write the eulogy for cash just yet. It's the OG of currencies,
and it's not going anywhere anytime soon.</p><p>Think about it: a world where CBDCs reign supreme. Every
transaction meticulously tracked, every penny monitored. It might sound
efficient on the surface, but it also nudges us closer to a panopticonic
society where every purchase becomes a data point. Cash, on the other hand,
offers a breath of fresh air – a realm of transactions free from prying eyes.</p><p>In fact, when it comes to CBDCs, the way a
government treats cash can be a real canary in the coal mine, revealing its
authoritarian tendencies.</p><p>In nations where individual liberty reigns supreme, the
idea of a cashless society is likely to meet significant resistance. People
value their financial privacy, and the ability to make purchases without a
watchful eye is a cornerstone of a free society. Cash transactions are like
whispers in the financial marketplace – untraceable and anonymous. CBDCs, on
the other hand, could be akin to shouting every purchase from the rooftops,
with governments potentially privy to every cup of coffee you buy.</p><p>This shouldn’t come as a surprise or sound like some
dystopian fantasy. Authoritarian regimes around the world are drooling at the
potential of CBDCs as it's a recipe for <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/fintech/payments/cash-with-an-expiration-date-how-cbdcs-could-borrow-a-radical-idea/">a society where every purchase becomes
a data point used to control and manipulate the populace</a>. Cash, in this
scenario, becomes a symbol of rebellion, a tiny act of defiance against an
all-encompassing digital eye.</p><p>The recent pushback against cashless mandates in places <a href="https://www.flsenate.gov/Session/Bill/2024/106/BillText/Filed/HTML">like
Florida</a>, a state known for its championing of individual liberty, is a
refreshing sign.  </p><p>Here, lawmakers are actively considering legislation that
would require businesses to accept cash. This stands in stark contrast to the
eagerness with which some authoritarian leaning governments are <a href="https://au.finance.yahoo.com/news/cashless-fear-as-date-australia-will-ditch-physical-money-is-revealed-043638197.html">rushing towards a
cashless future</a>.</p><p>The truth is, CBDCs do not and should not have
to be an all-or-nothing proposition.</p><p>We can embrace the potential benefits of digital currencies
while still safeguarding the irreplaceable value of cash. Cash is a safety net
in case of technological glitches, a way to ensure financial inclusion for
those without access to digital payment systems, and a vital tool for
protecting our financial privacy. </p><p>So, the next time you're tempted to ditch your bills for a
fancy CBDC pilot program, remember the power you hold in your hand. Cash might
not be the sole inhabitant of the future financial landscape, but it's a vital
part of our present. It offers a safety net and a sliver of privacy in an
increasingly digital world. Let's embrace the future with open arms, but let's
not forget the wisdom of the past – sometimes, the simplest solutions are the
most robust.</p>

This article was written by Pedro Ferreira at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[KuCoin Faces $1 Billion Crypto Exodus amid US Charges, Assets Plummet 20%]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/kucoin-faces-1-billion-crypto-exodus-amid-us-charges-assets-plummet-20/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/kucoin-faces-1-billion-crypto-exodus-amid-us-charges-assets-plummet-20/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 15:20:48 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tareq Sikder]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[CryptoCurrency]]></category>
<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/kucoin-faces-1-billion-crypto-exodus-amid-us-charges-assets-plummet-20</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>KuCoin witnessed a staggering $1 billion in crypto
withdrawals within 24 hours, coupled with a decline of 20% in assets under
management, following charges levied against the platform by US
authorities. Data analysis from Nansen and Arkham Intelligence has revealed the
extent of the withdrawal surge and the subsequent depletion of assets.</p><p>KuCoin Bleeds $1.083B in Crypto Exodus</p><p>Data provided by Nansen and Arkham Intelligence hasindicated
that KuCoin encountered an unprecedented outflow of approximately $1.083
billion across Ethereum Virtual Machine-compatible chains, dwarfing the
meagre inflows of $144 million during the same period. Notably, net outflows on
the Ethereum network alone amounted to $840 million, as reported by Nansen.</p><p>"This is more than a 15% drop in assets held by the
exchange," Nansen noted in a statement today (Wednesday), highlighting the
substantial impact of the withdrawal wave.</p><p>Arkham Intelligence's <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/b/blockchain/" class="terms__secondary-term" id="be18ed01-45fc-4044-b447-06802a10dbcd">blockchain</a> data corroborated the
significant decline in crypto assets held by KuCoin-tagged addresses,
plummeting from $6 billion to $4.8 billion within a day. Despite potential
price fluctuations, the decrease primarily stems from users withdrawing their
assets from the platform in response to the unfolding legal challenges.</p><p>Investor Concerns Mount as Exchange Responds to Alleged Charges</p><p>The surge in withdrawals coincided with US federal
prosecutors charging <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/kucoin/" target="_blank" rel="follow">KuCoin</a> and two of its founders with violating anti-money
laundering laws. A Homeland Security Investigations Special Agent characterized
the exchange as "an alleged multibillion-dollar criminal conspiracy,"
exacerbating concerns among investors.</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">XRP Dump Ahead? Will Ripple Survive? Should You Withdraw Your Funds From KuCoin? | MetaLawMan <a href="https://t.co/WOj1xLaCIl">https://t.co/WOj1xLaCIl</a></p>— The Wolf Of All Streets (@scottmelker) <a href="https://twitter.com/scottmelker/status/1772972512311447805?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 27, 2024</a></blockquote><p>While some users reported delays in withdrawal processing,
blockchain data revealed that outgoing transactions from KuCoin were eventually
executed. These delays were likely attributed to the high volume of withdrawal
requests accumulated during the tumultuous period.</p><p>Responding to mounting apprehensions, KuCoin reassured users
of the platform's stability and the safety of their assets in a social media
statement. The <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/e/exchange/" class="terms__main-term" id="b5da6e64-2afe-421d-9b81-16404b7d59d6">exchange</a> emphasized that it is "operating well,"
despite the challenging circumstances.</p>

This article was written by Tareq Sikder at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[UF AWARDS LATAM 2024 – Vote for This Year’s Winners]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/uf-awards-latam-2024-vote-for-this-years-winners/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/uf-awards-latam-2024-vote-for-this-years-winners/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 14:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[FM Contributors]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Thought Leadership]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//thought-leadership/uf-awards-latam-2024-vote-for-this-years-winners</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNormal">Voting for the most <a href="https://uf-awards.com/latam2024/">prestigious accolades of the year</a>, the UF AWARDS LATAM 2024, is now underway! The excitement continues today with live voting after a highly successful Nominations Round, which short listed the best brokers, B2B players, and fintech brands in the industry. The hype surrounding these awards could not be higher, with so much on the line for the most sought-after honours.</p><p class="MsoNormal">The UF AWARDS have no equal in the industry, bestowing unique titles to the most innovative and best performing brands in Latin America (LATAM). This year’s awards provide the best chance for leading companies to gain not only validation, but premier brand recognition and authority on the continent.</p><p class="MsoNormal">Make Your Voice Heard Today and Cast Your Vote for UF AWARDS LATAM 2024!</p><p class="MsoNormal">The past few weeks have seen a massive flow of support for the UF AWARDS LATAM 2024, with record participation in the Nominations Round. The next stage kicks off today and will continue until April 3, allowing participants the chance to cast their vote from a list of marquee brands.</p><p class="MsoNormal">This includes prominent and leading forex brands as well as affiliates, IBs, service providers, fintechs and more. Looking to see your brand reign supreme and establish itself as a true leader? Don’t miss out on your chance to make history and make your voice heard by voting today.</p><p class="MsoNormal">As a quick reminder, only registered participants can cast their vote for the awards. If you’re not yet a registered UF AWARDS LATAM 2024 member, you can do so by simply filling out the registration form <a href="https://uf-awards.com/latam2024/" target="_blank">here</a>. Users can log in and select from a short list of nominated brands for each category and vote.</p><p class="MsoNormal">This year’s UF AWARDS LATAM 2024 feature some prominent titles with no two awards being the same. Each of these represents a huge achievement for any company and reflects the best opportunity to make a splash among industry peers. Only the most innovative and deserving brands can lay claim to these coveted awards. The below list includes some of this year’s most competitive titles:</p><p class="MsoNormal">B2C Awards</p><ul><li>BEST BROKER – LATAM</li><li>MOST TRUSTED BROKER – LATAM</li><li>MOST TRANSPARENT BROKER – LATAM</li><li>BEST CFD BROKER – LATAM</li><li>BEST IB/AFFILIATE PROGRAMME - LATAM</li></ul><p class="MsoNormal">B2B Awards</p><ul><li>BEST TRADING PLATFORM – LATAM</li><li>BEST BRIDGE PROVIDER – LATAM</li><li>BEST TECHNOLOGY PROVIDER – LATAM</li><li>BEST CRM SOFTWARE PROVIDER – LATAM</li><li>BEST CFD LIQUIDITY PROVIDER – LATAM</li></ul><p class="MsoNormal">Explore the full list of awards <a href="https://uf-awards.com/latam2024/">here</a>.</p><p class="MsoNormal">Which Brands Will Establish Themselves as Elite?</p><p class="MsoNormal">The UF AWARDS are only given to the top performing B2C and B2B brands for their pioneering achievements, innovation, and significant contributions in the online trading and fintech space. Perhaps most importantly, these awards help showcase the true brand leaders and authorities, providing both traders and businesses with an industry benchmark of the best companies to trade and do business with. </p><p class="MsoNormal">These honours are part of the upcoming iFX EXPO LATAM 2024, held at World Trade Center Mexico City. The final Awards Ceremony will take place on April 10, concluding the first day of the iFX EXPO LATAM 2024. For over a decade, the iFX EXPO has become a tradition, establishing itself as the world’s leading online trading expo. This highly anticipated event series has helped bridge the B2B and B2C space, bringing together professionals and brands in online trading, fintech and financial services across Europe, Asia, the Middle East, and LATAM.</p><p class="MsoNormal">Brought to you by Ultimate Fintech, the UF AWARDS LATAM 2024 will help separate the elite brands from the rest of the industry. With so much visibility on the line in LATAM, the stakes could not be higher for these awards. As the most prestigious titles of 2024 await their distinguished winners, make sure not to be on the sidelines and <a href="https://latam2024.ifxexpo.com/en">vote for this year’s winners</a>!</p>

This article was written by FM Contributors at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Exclusive: HYCM Europe Renounces CIF License, to Cease Accepting Clients in the EU]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/exclusive-hycm-europe-renounces-cif-license-to-cease-accepting-clients-in-the-eu/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/exclusive-hycm-europe-renounces-cif-license-to-cease-accepting-clients-in-the-eu/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 14:31:20 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jared Kirui]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/exclusive-hycm-europe-renounces-cif-license-to-cease-accepting-clients-in-the-eu</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Finance Magnates has learned that the forex and CFD
trading platform HYCM (Europe) is voluntarily renouncing its CIF License. In a
statement published on its website, the company mentioned that it will no longer
accept new clients or open new accounts for individuals based in the EU. </p><p>Additionally, HYCM Europe is in the process of
terminating services for all existing clients in the region. However, the company will ensure that users are informed about
how they can access their funds. The firm has not
provided specific details regarding the reasons for this decision.</p><p>Terminating Services in the EU </p><p>HYCM Europe wrote: "We would like to inform you
that <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/hycm/" target="_blank" rel="follow">HYCM</a> (Europe) Limited (the Company) hereby notifies you that it is in the
process of voluntarily renouncing its CIF License with authorization number
259/14." </p><p>"Therefore, the Company will no longer accept any
new EU-based clients and/or the opening of any new EU-based accounts while it
is in the process of terminating all its existing EU-based clients and
informing them about the procedure that should be followed for their fund's
return."</p><p>The brokerage firm has directed clients seeking clarification to compliance@hycm.com and those with complaints to send their
emails to complaints@hycm.com. <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/" target="_blank" rel="follow">Finance Magnates</a> contacted HYCM for comments and will update this article once we get their feedback.</p><p>Meanwhile, the Cyprus Securities and Exchange
Commission indicated on its website that HYCM Europe is under examination for voluntary renunciation
of its authorization.</p><p>HYCM's Financial Performance</p><p>Last year, HYCM Capital Markets (UK) Limited <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/hycm-uk-sees-2022-profit-drop-despite-revenue-growth/" target="_blank" rel="follow">released its financial performance</a> for the fiscal year ending December 31, 2022. Despite
experiencing a notable surge in revenue, the company faced a decline in
profitability compared to the previous year. </p><p>The company's turnover soared to over £1.88 million,
marking a substantial increase of 14% from the preceding year. This
surge in revenue was attributed to various factors, including a significant
boost from 'other operating income' sources, which skyrocketed to £697,335 from £5,464 in the previous fiscal year. </p><p>However, amidst this growth in revenue, HYCM UK
encountered a significant rise in administrative expenses, which surpassed
£2.57 million. This represents a substantial increase of 43% compared to the previous
year.</p><p>Despite the uptick in revenue and supplementary
income, HYCM UK's operating profit for the year amounted to a modest £13,088,
significantly lower than the £198,050 recorded in the preceding fiscal period.
The company attributed this decline to the surge in administrative
expenses. </p>

This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Clone Scams are the Top Threat to Retail Traders: Survey]]></title>
<link>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/most-traders-lose-money-to-clone-brokers-than-other-online-scams-survey/</link>
<comments>https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/most-traders-lose-money-to-clone-brokers-than-other-online-scams-survey/#respond</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arnab Shome]]></dc:creator>
<dc:creator><![CDATA[www.financemagnates.com]]></dc:creator>
<category><![CDATA[Retail FX]]></category>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.financemagnates.com//forex/most-traders-lose-money-to-clone-brokers-than-other-online-scams-survey</guid>
<description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">As much as 38 percent of traders who lost funds mostly encountered clone brokers and signal providers, as compared to any other type of scam, a joint survey by Finance Magnates and FXStreet found. A total of 631 traders participated in the survey, sharing their experiences with online scams.</p><p dir="ltr">Want to influence the survey results? <a href="https://fxstreet1.typeform.com/to/lfSpVpPY" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">You can still participate here</a>.</p><p dir="ltr">Clones Top When It Comes to Victims Losing Funds</p><p dir="ltr">Following the clones of legitimate platforms, investment and Ponzi schemes were next in line to successfully trap victims, as about 35 percent of the traders who lost funds encountered such scams. When it comes to <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/p/phishing/" class="terms__main-term" id="ab3b6971-b22e-40d3-9c34-9e4b3b557786">phishing</a> emails or messages, 19.4 percent of the traders who lost funds encountered such scams, while the figure is 8 percent for fake news.</p><p dir="ltr">Clones of legitimate brokers and signal providers are also rampant. Regulators around the world are actively issuing warnings against such clones. Many regulators even cautioned against the impersonation of their official website and officials, as scammers were trying to extort money. Most recently, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/fma-warns-against-crypto-exchange-clone-and-unlicensed-firm-in-latest-alert/">New Zealand's financial market regulator flagged a crypto exchange clone</a>. </p><p dir="ltr">Clones are so rampant that one or the other regulator flag them almost every day. Even <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/dukascopy-bank-issues-another-warning-over-fraudulent-clone-website/">brokers individually issued warnings</a> against their impersonators. </p><p dir="ltr">Earlier, Finance Magnates reported that <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/cysec-and-fca-are-aware-of-rife-investor-fraud-on-social-media-stopping-it-is-harder/">many clones of legitimate brokers and signal providers are targeting traders on Telegram</a>. Although companies are trying to take these clones down by reporting them, it's almost impossible to take complete control of them.</p><p dir="ltr">On the other hand, <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/tag/ponzi-scheme/">Ponzi schemes</a> generally trap investors by promising significant and guaranteed returns and then paying off the old investors with the capital inflow from the new investors. Such schemes were rampant in all asset classes, including <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/terms/c/cryptocurrencies/" class="terms__secondary-term" id="b091101e-6e02-4b36-aa0e-7c972dfdd6ed">cryptocurrencies</a>. Official records show that Australians reported AU$3.1 billion loss to scams in 2022, out of which AU$1.5 billion was lost to investment scams.</p><p dir="ltr">Telegram Is a Hotbed for Fraud</p><p dir="ltr">Telegram and WhatsApp were the two forms of social media that <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/telegram-whatsapp-lead-on-the-number-of-traders-who-lose-money-to-scams-survey/">topped the number of fraud victims who lost funds</a> as 60 percent of the victims of on these platforms endured financial losses. For Facebook and Instagram, it was 56 percent and 52 percent, respectively.</p><p dir="ltr">“Although we have not yet taken direct action against Telegram, we recognize that fake or scam brokerage platforms and clones of regulated entities put investors at risk, and we are taking action in other ways to protect investors," a CySEC representative told Finance Magnates earlier.</p><p dir="ltr">“We do this by using sophisticated social media monitoring tools that identify aggressive marketing tactics in real-time and capture suspicious activity. When our investigations lead us to blacklist a fake website, we report the case to the police electronic crime unit.”</p><p dir="ltr">Among the respondents of the survey, 17.5 percent of the ones who fell victim to investment and Ponzi schemes did not lose any funds. For clone brokers and signal providers, this figure is at 20.7 percent. Further, 29 percent of the victims of fake news did not lose funds, while 28 percent of the victims of phishing emails or messages avoided losing funds.</p><p dir="ltr">Interestingly, the survey found that <a href="https://www.financemagnates.com/forex/facebook-outpaces-telegram-when-it-comes-to-financial-frauds-survey/">more traders on Facebook are being targeted by scams</a> when compared to other platforms like Telegram or WhatsApp.</p>

This article was written by Arnab Shome at www.financemagnates.com.]]></description>
</item>
</channel></rss>