<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 14:52:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Grayscale Submits Revised Application For Ethereum Spot ETF &#8211; What&#8217;s New?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/ethereum-news/grayscale-submits-revised-application-for-ethereum-spot-etf-whats-new/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Spot ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Asset management firm Grayscale Investments has updated its application for an Ethereum spot ETF (exchange-traded fund) with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Ethereum Spot ETF Case Just As Solid As Bitcoin’s, Grayscale Argues According to a recent post on X by Craig Salm, Grayscale’s chief legal officer, the asset management firm has revised its 19b-4 form for an Ether spot ETF. Salm claimed that this move was “important” in an effort for Grayscale to list and trade shares of its Ether Trust on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) Arca. The chief legal officer stated in his post that investors “want and deserve access” to Ethereum via a spot exchange-traded product, likening the situation to the Bitcoin ETF story. “We believe the case is just as strong as it was for spot Bitcoin ETFs,” Salm said. Related Reading: Behind The Scenes Of Shiba Inu 12% Plunge: What On-Chain Analysis Tells Us The asset manager is amongst the numerous firms looking to issue the first Ethereum spot ETF in the United States, having filed an application with the SEC on October 10, 2023. However, these ETF applications have faced delays multiple times, with the most recent coming against BlackRock’s filing on March 4, 2024. As a result, the likelihood of the SEC approving an Ethereum spot ETF has taken a nosedive in recent weeks. Once-optimistic Bloomberg ETF expert Balchunas even revealed in his latest analysis that the ETH funds now have only a 35% chance of approval. SEC Chairman Faces Pressure Over Crypto Approval Two US senators of the Democrat party, Sens. Laphonza Butler of California and Jack Reed of Rhode Island, have urged the SEC chairman to avoid approving crypto investment products. In a letter dated March 11, the lawmakers, who are also members of the Senate Banking Committee, asked the Commission to limit future crypto ETF applications. Following the approval of 11 Bitcoin spot ETFs in January, the attention of the crypto public has somewhat turned to whether the SEC will do the same for the Ethereum versions. However, this latest letter from the senate seems to further hurt the chances of an ETH ETF approval. Related Reading: Altcoins Fall: Will Ethereum And Solana Bulls Surpass Expectations? A part of the letter read: Retail investors would face enormous risks from ETPs referencing thinly traded cryptocurrencies or cryptocurrencies whose prices are especially susceptible to pump-and-dump or other fraudulent schemes,&#8221; they said. &#8220;The Commission is under no obligation to approve such products, and given the risk, it should not do so. As of this writing, the price of the Ethereum token stands at $3,731, reflecting a 1.2% increase in the past day. Ethereum price on a deep correction on the daily timeframe &#124; Source: ETHUSDT chart on TradingView Featured image from The Economic Times, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-spot-etf-grayscale-outflows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Asset management firm Grayscale</a> Investments has updated its application for an Ethereum spot ETF (exchange-traded fund) with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2 class="p1"><strong>Ethereum Spot ETF Case Just As Solid As Bitcoin’s, Grayscale Argues</strong></h2>
<p class="p1">According to a recent post on X by Craig Salm, Grayscale’s chief legal officer, the asset management firm has <a href="https://www.nyse.com/publicdocs/nyse/markets/nyse-arca/rule-filings/filings/2024/SR-NYSEArca-2023-70_Am._1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revised its 19b-4 form</a> for an Ether spot ETF. Salm claimed that this move was “important” in an effort for Grayscale to list and trade shares of its Ether Trust on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) Arca.</p>
<p class="p1">The chief legal officer <a href="https://x.com/CraigSalm/status/1768750794021511218?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated in his post</a> that investors “want and deserve access” to Ethereum via a spot exchange-traded product, likening the situation to the Bitcoin ETF story. “We believe the case is just as strong as it was for spot Bitcoin ETFs,” Salm said.</p>

<p class="p1">The asset manager is amongst the numerous firms <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/approval-denial-ethereum-etf-sell-the-news-event/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">looking to issue the first Ethereum spot ETF</a> in the United States, having filed an application with the SEC on October 10, 2023. However, these ETF applications have faced delays multiple times, with the most recent coming against BlackRock’s filing on March 4, 2024.</p>
<p class="p1">As a result, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-etfs-approval-odds-drop-to-35/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">the likelihood</a> of the SEC approving an Ethereum spot ETF has taken a nosedive in recent weeks. Once-optimistic Bloomberg ETF expert Balchunas even revealed in his latest analysis that the ETH funds now have only a 35% chance of approval.</p>












<h2><strong>SEC Chairman Faces Pressure Over Crypto Approval</strong></h2>













<p class="p1">Two US senators of the Democrat party, Sens. Laphonza Butler of California and Jack Reed of Rhode Island, have urged the SEC chairman to avoid approving crypto investment products. In a letter dated March 11, the lawmakers, who are also members of the Senate Banking Committee, asked the Commission to limit future crypto ETF applications.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The success of the BTC spot products clearly ruffling some feathers on the Hill. <a href="https://twitter.com/SenatorJackReed?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@SenatorJackReed</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/Senlaphonza?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@Senlaphonza</a> write to the <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@SECGov</a> urging:-no further ETPs for other tokens-make life difficult (i.e. examinations/reviews) for brokers and advisers that recommend BTC ETPs <a href="https://t.co/enxdumC02N" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/enxdumC02N</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Alexander Grieve (@AlexanderGrieve) <a href="https://twitter.com/AlexanderGrieve/status/1768373756169261076?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 14, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p class="p1">Following the approval of 11 Bitcoin spot ETFs in January, the attention of the crypto public has somewhat turned to whether the SEC will do the same for the Ethereum versions. However, this latest letter from the senate seems to further <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-etfs-approval-outlook-fades-ahead-may-23/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">hurt the chances of an ETH ETF approval</a>.</p>

<p class="p1">A part of the letter read:</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p1">Retail investors would face enormous risks from ETPs referencing thinly traded cryptocurrencies or cryptocurrencies whose prices are especially susceptible to pump-and-dump or other fraudulent schemes,&#8221; they said. &#8220;The Commission is under no obligation to approve such products, and given the risk, it should not do so.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p1">As of this writing, the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-takes-hit-3680/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">price of the Ethereum</a> token stands at $3,731, reflecting a 1.2% increase in the past day.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Zu1Rz9LH/" alt="Grayscale" width="2174" height="1434" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/the-crypto-world-cant-wait-for-the-merge.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598136</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Records Massive 80% Surge In Trading Volume &#8211; Can Price Reach A New ATH?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/all/xrp-records-massive-80-surge-in-trading-volume-can-price-reach-a-new-ath/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[network activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[XRP continues to show strength despite largely underperforming during the ongoing bull market. Interestingly, the crypto witnessed a surge in activity last week, with trading volume surging in tandem. Particularly, the trading volume saw an increase of over 80% recently.  However, the boost in activity and trading volume has not necessarily translated into continuous price growth, as XRP is currently on a 13% percent correction from the $0.74 price level on Monday. Related Reading: Sell Sign Ignites Speculation: Solana Fate Hangs In The Balance? XRP Trading Volume Surges, But Will Price Follow? XRP witnessed a surge earlier in the week which saw it breaking out of a 6-year-long symmetrical triangle, prompting analysts to anticipate a continued price surge. During this period, the crypto witnessed a surge in trading volume from whales in particular, with large bouts of XRP leaving crypto exchanges. This bullish sentiment allowed XRP to cross over $0.74 for the first time in eight months, albeit for a short moment. This surge in price was short-lived, as XRP fell as low as $0.6 in the days after. However, a recent 80% surge in on-chain activity and trading volume has led to the price of XRP increasing by 4.45% in the past 24 hours and 2.2% in a seven-day timeframe. Volume spikes of this magnitude often occur before a price rally, therefore, this massive spike in volume has the XRP community speculating that a strong price rally could be on the horizon. Total crypto market cap currently at $2.5 trillion. Chart: TradingView Current Price Action: Can XRP Reach A New All-Time High? At the time of writing, XRP is trading at $0.6398. The crypto&#8217;s journey to a new all-time high is definitely not going to be an easy one, as it is now down by 83% from its current all-time high of $3.84.  However, current market dynamics and various predictions from many crypto analysts indicate that the crypto might go on a surge of great magnitude in the near future. One of these is a prediction from analyst Jaydee, who noted that XRP&#8217;s recent breakout from the six-year trendline mentioned earlier could lead to a surge to $3 from the current price level. The major resistance level to watch is $0.74. XRP tested this level a few days ago but failed to close above it. If bullish momentum continues and volume stays strong, XRP could break through $0.74 decisively in the new week. If it does, the next resistance levels are at $0.82 and $1.5.  Related Reading: Crypto Carnage: Over $800 Million Wiped Out In Market Plunge One of the few factors that could contribute to a strong price increase is regulatory clarity regarding XRP&#8217;s status, which could boost confidence from institutional investors. Notably, XRP&#8217;s non-security status seems to be gaining ground. The European Corporate Governance Institute (ECGI) recently published a research paper acknowledging this non-security status. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP continues to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-break-bull-pattern/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">show strength</a> despite largely underperforming during the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ongoing bull market</a>. Interestingly, the crypto witnessed a surge in activity last week, with trading volume surging in tandem. Particularly, the trading volume saw an increase of over 80% recently. </p>
<p>However, the boost in activity and trading volume has not necessarily translated into continuous price growth, as XRP is currently on a 13% percent correction from the $0.74 price level on Monday.</p>

<h2><b>XRP Trading Volume Surges, But Will Price Follow?</b></h2>
<p>XRP witnessed a surge earlier in the week which saw it breaking out of a 6-year-long symmetrical triangle, prompting analysts to anticipate a continued price surge. </p>
<p>During this period, the crypto witnessed a surge in trading volume from whales in particular, with large bouts of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/94-million-xrp-exits-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">XRP leaving crypto exchanges</a>.</p>
<p>This bullish sentiment allowed XRP to cross over $0.74 for the first time in eight months, albeit for a short moment. This surge in price was short-lived, as XRP fell as low as $0.6 in the days after.</p>
<p>However, a recent 80% surge in on-chain activity and trading volume has led to the price of XRP increasing by 4.45% in the past 24 hours and 2.2% in a seven-day timeframe. </p>
<p>Volume spikes of this magnitude often occur before a price rally, therefore, this massive spike in volume has the XRP community speculating that a strong price rally could be on the horizon.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7pDB2vOg/" width="1835" height="883" loading="lazy"/></p>

<h2><b>Current Price Action: Can XRP Reach A New All-Time High?</b></h2>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP is trading at $0.6398. The crypto&#8217;s journey to a new all-time high is definitely <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/xrp-on-the-brink-bullish-pattern-or-profit-taking-retreat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">not going to be an easy one</a>, as it is now down by 83% from its current all-time high of $3.84. </p>
<p>However, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-rocket-2300-to-14-6/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">current market dynamics</a> and various <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-to-skyrockets-to-1-33-amidst-april-rally-analysts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">predictions from many crypto analysts</a> indicate that the crypto might go on a surge of great magnitude in the near future. </p>
<p>One of these is a prediction from <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/symmetrical-30000-xrp-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analyst Jaydee</a>, who <a href="https://x.com/jaydee_757/status/1751468373756858664?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">noted </a>that XRP&#8217;s recent breakout from the six-year trendline mentioned earlier could lead to a surge to $3 from the current price level.</p>
<p>The major resistance level to watch is $0.74. XRP tested this level a few days ago but failed to close above it. If bullish momentum continues and volume stays strong, XRP could break through $0.74 decisively in the new week. If it does, the next resistance <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-prediction-rally-0-85/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">levels are at $0.82</a> and $1.5. </p>

<p>One of the few factors that could contribute to a strong price increase is <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-scores-win-endorsed-as-non-security-status/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">regulatory clarity</a> regarding XRP&#8217;s status, which could boost confidence from institutional investors. </p>
<p>Notably, XRP&#8217;s non-security status seems <a href="https://t.co/uJ0bDpKfJE" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">to be gaining ground</a>. The European Corporate Governance Institute (ECGI) recently published a <a href="https://www.ecgi.global/sites/default/files/working_papers/documents/corporategovernancemeetsdataandtechnology.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">research paper</a> acknowledging this non-security status.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_517559.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598186</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Carnage: Over $800 Million Wiped Out In Market Plunge</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-carnage-over-800-million-wiped-out-in-market-plunge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598167</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The recent market plunge has sent shockwaves through the crypto industry, resulting in hundreds of millions in dollars being wiped out in a matter of hours. The price of Bitcoin has retreated violently to a weekly low of $67,500 after a few days of showing remarkable advances and setting new all-time highs. The altcoins have experienced a significant decline as well, resulting in nearly 200,000 traders making liquidations during the last 24 hours. The weekend brought a tremor to the cryptocurrency market, with a sudden price correction causing short-term panic and hundreds of millions in liquidated positions. However, despite the wobble, analysts are divided on whether this signifies a broader market shift or a mere blip on the bullish radar. Crypto Long Squeeze Triggers Liquidations Over a 24-hour period ending Friday, March 15th, the global cryptocurrency market capitalization shed a cool 6%. This triggered a wave of automated liquidations, particularly for investors holding leveraged long positions – essentially large bets on rising prices. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Brace For Impact As Difficulty Reaches Unprecedented Levels According to Coinglass, a crypto data analysis platform, over $800 million worth of long positions were liquidated across the market. Bitcoin itself bore the brunt of the selling pressure, dipping as low as $67,000 – its lowest point in over a week. Liquidation heatmap in the 24-hour timeframe. Source: Coinglass The pain wasn&#8217;t evenly distributed. Over one third of the liquidations, a total of $660 million, came from long positions on Bitcoin. Altcoin Bloodbath Follows Bitcoin&#8217;s Lead The tremors weren&#8217;t confined to Bitcoin. The correction spilled over to the altcoin market, with popular tokens like Cardano, Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, and XRP all experiencing significant price drops. This, in turn, triggered further liquidations for long positions held on these altcoins. XRP traders alone saw over $10 million liquidated, with nearly $11 million coming from long positions. Total crypto market cap is currently at $2.5 trillion. Chart: TradingView Crypto Market Fights Back: Buying The Dip Despite the week&#8217;s fright, the overall sentiment in the crypto market remains surprisingly bullish. This is primarily fueled by the swift buying activity observed at key support levels as prices dipped. Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s most sought-after crypto asset, for example, has already staged a partial recovery, bouncing back to a little over $69,000 at the time of writing. Similar rebounds have been observed across several altcoins, suggesting that investors might be viewing this as a buying opportunity. Related Reading: Sell Sign Ignites Speculation: Solana Fate Hangs In The Balance? This correction can be seen as a healthy market reset after a strong rally, some analysts say. While some leveraged positions got burned, the fact that investors are stepping in to buy the dip indicates continued confidence in the long-term potential of cryptocurrencies. A Continued Balancing Act The weekend&#8217;s events serve as a microcosm of the ongoing struggle within the crypto market. On one hand, there&#8217;s a growing sense of institutional adoption and mainstream acceptance, fueling a bullish sentiment. On the other, the inherent volatility of crypto assets continues to pose a challenge, with sudden price swings capable of inflicting significant losses on unsuspecting investors. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recent market plunge has sent shockwaves through the crypto industry, resulting in hundreds of millions in dollars being wiped out in a matter of hours.</p>
<p>The price of<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Bitcoin</a> has retreated violently to a weekly low of $67,500 after a few days of showing remarkable advances and setting new all-time highs.</p>
<p>The altcoins have experienced a significant decline as well, resulting in nearly 200,000 traders making liquidations during the last 24 hours.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:300">The weekend brought a tremor to the cryptocurrency market, with a sudden price correction causing short-term panic and hundreds of millions in liquidated positions.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:300">However, despite the wobble, analysts are divided on whether this signifies a broader market shift or a mere blip on the bullish radar.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:45"><strong>Crypto Long Squeeze Triggers Liquidations</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:523">Over a 24-hour period ending Friday, March 15th, the global cryptocurrency market capitalization shed a cool 6%. This triggered a wave of automated liquidations, particularly for investors holding leveraged long positions – essentially large bets on rising prices.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:523">According to Coinglass, a crypto data analysis platform,<a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> over $800 million worth of long positions were liquidated</a> across the market. Bitcoin itself bore the brunt of the selling pressure, dipping as low as $67,000 – its lowest point in over a week.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:328">The pain wasn&#8217;t evenly distributed. Over one third of the liquidations, a total of $660 million, came from long positions on Bitcoin.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="11:1-11:44"><strong>Altcoin Bloodbath Follows Bitcoin&#8217;s Lead</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:389">The tremors weren&#8217;t confined to Bitcoin. The correction spilled over to the altcoin market, with popular tokens like Cardano, Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, and XRP all experiencing significant price drops.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:389">This, in turn, triggered further liquidations for long positions held on these altcoins. XRP traders alone saw over $10 million liquidated, with nearly $11 million coming from long positions.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:389"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Un3Ttg2O/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<strong>Crypto Market Fights Back: Buying The Dip</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:455">Despite the week&#8217;s fright, the overall sentiment in the crypto market remains surprisingly bullish. This is primarily fueled by the swift buying activity observed at key support levels as prices dipped.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:455">Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s most sought-after crypto asset, for example, has already staged a partial recovery, bouncing back to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">a little over $69,000</a> at the time of writing.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:455">Similar rebounds have been observed across several altcoins, suggesting that investors might be viewing this as a buying opportunity.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:290">This correction can be seen as a healthy market reset after a strong rally, some analysts say. While some leveraged positions got burned, the fact that investors are stepping in to buy the dip indicates continued confidence in the long-term potential of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<strong>A Continued Balancing Act</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="23:1-23:394">The weekend&#8217;s events serve as a microcosm of the ongoing struggle within the crypto market. On one hand, there&#8217;s a growing sense of institutional adoption and mainstream acceptance, fueling a bullish sentiment.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="23:1-23:394">On the other, the inherent volatility of crypto assets continues to pose a challenge, with sudden price swings capable of inflicting significant losses on unsuspecting investors.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="23:1-23:394"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_bb2a2c.jpg?fit=460%2C305" width="460" height="305" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598167</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Expects Bitcoin Price Correction To Persist, Targets $57,000 Support</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/analyst-expects-bitcoin-price-correction-to-persist-targets-57000-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Corrrection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michaal van de Poppe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has drawn much attention in the last few weeks, with a stunning price surge leading to a new all-time high of $73,750. Largely defined as the pre-halving rally, BTC&#8217;s bolstering gains have been followed by significant price correction, with the crypto market leader trading as low as $65,630 on March 15.  While the cryptocurrency may have picked up some minor gains in the last 12 hours as it attempts a market recovery, popular analyst Michaël van de Poppe has released a disturbing prediction that indicates Bitcoin price correction may be far from over. Related Reading: Behind The Scenes Of Shiba Inu 12% Plunge: What On-Chain Analysis Tells Us Bitcoin May Have Peaked Pre-Halving, Analyst Says In a Friday post on X, van de Poppe shared a market forecast that Bitcoin could fall as low as $57,000, thus prolonging its current correction phase. The analyst began by highlighting that BTC still retained a valid bearish divergence which occurs when the price of an asset forms higher highs while the corresponding indicator forms lower highs. It usually indicates that the driving force behind a certain trend is attenuated with a reversal now on the horizon. #Bitcoin remains to have a valid bearish divergence. This is confirmed by the lower timeframe, lower highs, and clear rejection at $70.5K. For this correction, I&#8217;d be targeting $57-61K, and, likely, we&#8217;ll have peaked pre-halving. Altcoin summer is on the horizon. pic.twitter.com/bGmnHcVDnz — Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) March 15, 2024 In the case of Bitcoin, the bearish divergence indicates the coin’s recent rally may be exhausted and is now likely to produce major negative price movements. Van de Poppe stated this theory was confirmed by BTC’s latest rejection at the $70,000 zone during its attempted market rebound.  The prominent crypto analyst predicts Bitcoin to soon resume its price correction, falling to a price range of $57,000 to $61,000. If these speculations prove true, it could also indicate that in similar fashion, the BTC market may attain its highest value prior to the Bitcoin halving.  For context, the Bitcoin Halving is historically preceded by a price rally followed by a significant price retrace ranging from 20% to 40%. With the next Halving event set for April 2024, van de Poppe believes that further retracement by Bitcoin could stamp the end of the pre-halving rally. Related Reading: Key Trend Driving Altcoin Market Toward $425 Billion: Analyst BTC Price Overview According to data from CoinMarketCap, Bitcoin is currently trading at $69,027 with a 0.17% and 1.26% in the last hour and day, respectively. In tandem, the token’s daily trading volume is up by 1.20% and is valued at $69.58 million. BTC trading at $69,259 on the weekly chart &#124; Source: BTCUSD chart on Tradingview.com Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has drawn much attention in the last few weeks, with a stunning price surge leading to a new <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-whale-217-million-profit-btc-73000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">all-time high of $73,750.</a> Largely defined as the pre-halving rally, BTC&#8217;s bolstering gains have been followed by <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-suffers-crash-to-65000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">significant price correction,</a> with the crypto market leader trading as low as $65,630 on March 15. </p>
<p>While the cryptocurrency may have picked up some minor gains in the last 12 hours as it attempts a market recovery, popular analyst Michaël van de Poppe has released a disturbing prediction that indicates Bitcoin price correction may be far from over.
</p>
Related Reading: <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/behind-the-scenes-of-shiba-inu-12-plunge-what-on-chain-analysis-tells-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Behind The Scenes Of Shiba Inu 12% Plunge: What On-Chain Analysis Tells Us</a>

<h2>Bitcoin May Have Peaked Pre-Halving, Analyst Says</h2>
<p>In a<a href="https://x.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1768737010087231899?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> Friday post on X</a>, van de Poppe shared a market forecast that Bitcoin could fall as low as $57,000, thus prolonging its current correction phase. The analyst began by highlighting that BTC still retained a valid bearish divergence which occurs when the price of an asset forms higher highs while the corresponding indicator forms lower highs. It usually indicates that the driving force behind a certain trend is attenuated with a reversal now on the horizon.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> remains to have a valid bearish divergence.</p>
<p>This is confirmed by the lower timeframe, lower highs, and clear rejection at $70.5K.</p>
<p>For this correction, I&#8217;d be targeting $57-61K, and, likely, we&#8217;ll have peaked pre-halving.</p>
<p>Altcoin summer is on the horizon. <a href="https://t.co/bGmnHcVDnz" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/bGmnHcVDnz</a></p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1768737010087231899?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 15, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>In the case of Bitcoin, the bearish divergence indicates the coin’s recent rally may be exhausted and is now likely to produce major negative price movements. Van de Poppe stated this theory was confirmed by BTC’s latest rejection at the $70,000 zone during its attempted market rebound. </p>
<p>The prominent crypto analyst predicts Bitcoin to soon resume its price correction, falling to a price range of $57,000 to $61,000. If these speculations prove true, it could also indicate that in similar fashion, the BTC market may attain its highest value prior to the Bitcoin halving. </p>
<p>For context, the Bitcoin Halving is historically preceded by a price rally followed by a significant price retrace ranging from 20% to 40%. With the next Halving event set for April 2024, van de Poppe believes that further retracement by Bitcoin could stamp the end of the pre-halving rally.
</p>

<h2>BTC Price Overview</h2>
<p style="text-align: left">According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">data from CoinMarketCap,</a> Bitcoin is currently trading at $69,027 with a 0.17% and 1.26% in the last hour and day, respectively. In tandem, the token’s daily trading volume is up by 1.20% and is valued at $69.58 million.</p>

<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rZKtI6Id/" alt="Bitcoin" width="1479" height="893"/>BTC trading at $69,259 on the weekly chart | Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/xg17RJqK/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">BTCUSD chart on Tradingview.com</a>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/pexels-pixabay-315788-scaled-1.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598137</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sell Sign Ignites Speculation: Solana Fate Hangs In The Balance?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/sell-sign-ignites-speculation-solana-fate-hangs-in-the-balance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Solana (SOL), the high-speed blockchain darling, has entered a tug-of-war between technical indicators flashing red and a market sentiment surging with exuberance. This paradox leaves investors wondering: is a price correction imminent, or is Solana poised for a major breakout? Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Brace For Impact As Difficulty Reaches Unprecedented Levels Solana Faces Technical Headwinds Technical analysts are raising red flags. Ali Martinez, a prominent analyst, identified a sell signal on Solana&#8217;s daily chart using the TD Sequential indicator. This indicator has a haunting history with SOL, preceding price drops of 17% to 28% in the past. Based on this historical data, Martinez predicts a potential retracement, suggesting Solana could dip as low as $127. This technical analysis injects a dose of realism into the market, reminding investors of the inherent volatility of cryptocurrencies. The TD Sequential presents a sell signal on the #Solana daily chart! Since December 2023, every time this indicator suggested selling, the price of $SOL dropped by 17% to 28%. A similar outlook could see #SOL retrace to $152 or even $127. pic.twitter.com/3JbXdabK3v — Ali (@ali_charts) March 14, 2024 Solana Defies Pressure With Bullish Momentum However, dismissing Solana based solely on technicals would be a mistake. In a surprising turn of events, Solana is currently defying the sell signal. As of this writing, SOL is trading at a robust $190, boasting a significant 24-hour trading volume and a market capitalization exceeding $79 billion. Solana price action. Chart: TradingView More importantly, the price has been on a tear, surging nearly 50% in the past month and a remarkable 24% in the last week. This bullish momentum throws a wrench into the technical analysis, highlighting the unpredictable nature of market sentiment in the crypto sphere. Solana: On Optimism And Caution Looking ahead, the battle between technical indicators and market sentiment is set to continue. Bullish forecasts paint a rosy picture. Changelly, a popular crypto exchange, predicts a 12% increase for SOL by mid-March. Related Reading: Solana’s Biggest Memecoin Gains Over $680,000 In 3 Days As Investors Bet On Its Popularity This aligns with the overwhelmingly bullish market sentiment, with technical indicators showing a 77% positive outlook and the Fear &#38; Greed Index hovering at an &#8220;extreme greed&#8221; score of 81. Crypto experts are joining the chorus of optimism, projecting an average SOL price of $237 for March, with a potential return on investment exceeding 80%. Buckle Up For A Bumpy Ride Meanwhile, the bitcoin market saw total liquidations of more than $230 million in the last day. Of this, liquidations from long positions totaled around $148 million, while those from short positions totaling about $82 million. Of them, Solana (SOL) had to deal with liquidations of close to $8 million in the same period. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:283">Solana (SOL), the high-speed blockchain darling, has entered a tug-of-war between technical indicators flashing red and a market sentiment surging with exuberance. This paradox leaves investors wondering: is a price correction imminent, or is Solana poised for a major breakout?</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:37"><strong>Solana Faces Technical Headwinds</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:552">Technical analysts are raising red flags. Ali Martinez, a prominent analyst, identified a sell signal on Solana&#8217;s daily chart using the TD Sequential indicator. This indicator has a haunting history with SOL, preceding price drops of 17% to 28% in the past.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:552">Based on this historical data, Martinez predicts a potential retracement, suggesting <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Solana</a> could dip as low as $127. This technical analysis injects a dose of realism into the market, reminding investors of the inherent volatility of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The TD Sequential presents a sell signal on the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Solana?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Solana</a> daily chart!</p>
<p>Since December 2023, every time this indicator suggested selling, the price of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SOL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SOL</a> dropped by 17% to 28%. A similar outlook could see <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SOL?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#SOL</a> retrace to $152 or even $127. <a href="https://t.co/3JbXdabK3v" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/3JbXdabK3v</a></p>
<p>— Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1768213412947845581?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 14, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<h2 data-sourcepos="9:1-9:48"><strong>Solana Defies Pressure With Bullish Momentum</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:574">However, dismissing Solana based solely on technicals would be a mistake. In a surprising turn of events, Solana is currently defying the sell signal. As of this writing, SOL is <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">trading at a robust $190</a>, boasting a significant 24-hour trading volume and a market capitalization exceeding $79 billion.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:574"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Vh3swaOE/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:574">More importantly, the price has been on a tear, surging nearly 50% in the past month and a remarkable 24% in the last week. This bullish momentum throws a wrench into the technical analysis, highlighting the unpredictable nature of market sentiment in the crypto sphere.</p>
<strong>Solana: On Optimism And Caution</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:568">Looking ahead, the battle between technical indicators and market sentiment is set to continue. Bullish forecasts paint a rosy picture. Changelly, a popular crypto exchange, predicts a 12% increase for SOL by mid-March.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:568">This aligns with the overwhelmingly bullish market sentiment, with technical indicators showing a 77% positive outlook and the Fear &amp; Greed Index hovering at an &#8220;extreme greed&#8221; score of 81. Crypto experts are joining the chorus of optimism, projecting an average SOL price of $237 for March, with a potential return on investment exceeding 80%.</p>
<strong>Buckle Up For A Bumpy Ride</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:567">Meanwhile, the bitcoin market saw total liquidations of more than $230 million in the last day. Of this, liquidations from long positions totaled around $148 million, while those from short positions totaling about $82 million. Of them, Solana (SOL) had to deal with liquidations of close to $8 million in the same period.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:567"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_d241ce.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598040</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Post-Halving Pressure: Marathon Digital Anticipates Bitcoin Break-Even Price Of $43,000</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/post-halving-pressure-marathon-digital-anticipates-bitcoin-break-even-price-of-43000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin chart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin technical analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[latest bitcoin news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin (BTC) market has been on a wild ride recently, hitting a new all-time high (ATH) before experiencing notable volatility that resulted in an 8% drop to the $65,500 level on Friday.  Meanwhile, Marathon Digital, one of the largest US-based Bitcoin mining companies, is preparing to acquire more power infrastructure and streamline operations to meet the challenges posed by a reduction in revenue due to the upcoming April halving event.  Bitcoin Miners Brace For Post-Halving Shakeout According to a Bloomberg report, Marathon Digital plans to acquire additional power infrastructure and expand its mining capacity to keep costs low and maintain profitability.  By optimizing operations and scaling up, Marathon aims to mitigate the impact of the impending revenue drop and secure wider margins in the post-halving landscape. Related Reading: Solana’s Biggest Memecoin Gains Over $680,000 In 3 Days As Investors Bet On Its Popularity Marathon Digital recently announced an agreement to purchase a 200-megawatt data center in Garden City, Texas, for over $87 million. This acquisition marks the company&#8217;s second major investment in power infrastructure after it acquired multiple sites for $179 million earlier this year.  By increasing its ownership of mining capacity infrastructure to 53%, up from a meager 3% in the previous year, Marathon is positioning itself for greater operational efficiency and cost-effectiveness, Bloomberg notes.  However, post-halving, the Bitcoin mining industry is expected to undergo significant changes, with some miners facing profitability challenges and potential exits.  Profitability Crisis Looms Marathon Digital&#8217;s CEO, Fred Thiel, highlights the impact of revenue reduction, estimating that the industry&#8217;s average break-even point will rise from around $23,000 per Bitcoin to approximately $43,000. Thiel stated: Post halving, there will be some miners to lose profitability, maybe challenged, or maybe looking for an exit as their revenues will drop because of the Bitcoin rewarded will drop. The simple math is, if the industry average break-even point was around $23,000 per Bitcoin, it will now go up to around $43,000. It is worth noting that this does not necessarily mean that Bitcoin&#8217;s price will fall to $43,000 from its current trading price of $69,300. The breakeven price refers to the price at which miners like Marathon Digital can cover their operating costs and achieve profitability. It is not directly correlated to the market price of Bitcoin. Related Reading: Crypto Pundit Says God Candle Is Imminent For This Solana-Based Meme Coin As of the time of writing, BTC is trading at $69,300 and is on the verge of reclaiming the significant milestone of $70,000. The cryptocurrency experienced a notable spike in volatility during the early hours of Friday&#8217;s trading session but has since recovered, mitigating its losses from 8% down to 2.5%. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin (BTC) market has been on a wild ride recently, hitting a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">new all-time high </a>(ATH) before experiencing notable volatility that resulted in an 8% drop to the $65,500 level on Friday. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Marathon Digital, one of the largest US-based Bitcoin mining companies, is preparing to acquire more power infrastructure and streamline operations to meet the challenges posed by a reduction in revenue due to the upcoming April<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/grayscale-next-bitcoin-halving-different/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> halving event</a>. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miners Brace For Post-Halving Shakeout</h2>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-15/bitcoin-miner-marathon-mara-plans-to-make-purchases-to-offset-reward-halving" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, Marathon Digital plans to acquire additional power infrastructure and expand its mining capacity to keep costs low and maintain profitability. </p>
<p>By optimizing operations and scaling up, Marathon aims to mitigate the impact of the impending revenue drop and secure wider margins in the post-halving landscape.</p>

<p>Marathon Digital recently announced an agreement to purchase a 200-megawatt data center in Garden City, Texas, for over $87 million. This acquisition marks the company&#8217;s second major investment in power infrastructure after it acquired multiple sites for $179 million earlier this year. </p>
<p>By increasing its ownership of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-halving-prep-analyst-outlines-key-points-ahead-of-event/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">mining capacity</a> infrastructure to 53%, up from a meager 3% in the previous year, Marathon is positioning itself for greater operational efficiency and cost-effectiveness, Bloomberg notes. </p>
<p>However, post-halving, the Bitcoin mining industry is expected to undergo significant changes, with some miners facing profitability challenges and potential exits. </p>
<h2>Profitability Crisis Looms</h2>
<p>Marathon Digital&#8217;s CEO, Fred Thiel, highlights the impact of revenue reduction, estimating that the industry&#8217;s average break-even point will rise from around $23,000 per Bitcoin to approximately $43,000. Thiel stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>Post halving, there will be some miners to lose profitability, maybe challenged, or maybe looking for an exit as their revenues will drop because of the Bitcoin rewarded will drop. The simple math is, if the industry average break-even point was around $23,000 per Bitcoin, it will now go up to around $43,000.</p></blockquote>
<p>It is worth noting that this does not necessarily mean that Bitcoin&#8217;s price will fall to $43,000 from its current trading price of $69,300. The<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/anticipation-peaks-as-bitcoin-halving-countdown-drops-below-100-days-will-prices-skyrocket/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> breakeven price</a> refers to the price at which miners like Marathon Digital can cover their operating costs and achieve profitability. It is not directly correlated to the market price of Bitcoin.</p>

<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1c7xh35O/" alt="Bitcoin " width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of the time of writing, BTC is trading at $69,300 and is on the verge of reclaiming the significant milestone of $70,000. The cryptocurrency experienced a notable spike in volatility during the early hours of Friday&#8217;s trading session but has since recovered, mitigating its losses from 8% down to 2.5%.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-6-3.jpg?fit=390%2C260" width="390" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598125</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Surge Alert: Bitcoin&#8217;s Futures Basis Climbs To New Heights, What This Means For BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/surge-alert-bitcoin-futures-basis-climbs-to-new-heights/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598098</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s futures market is showcasing signs that have historically signalled bullish sentiment. Analysts are turning their attention to the Bitcoin futures basis—a metric representing the differential between the futures price of Bitcoin and its spot price. Recent data has revealed that this basis has escalated to unprecedented levels since Bitcoin&#8217;s all-time high of $69,000 in November 2021. Related Reading: Bitcoin’s 2024 Forecast: Analyst Predicts $60,000 Surge Before Halving And New ATH By Q4 Bullish Indications From Bitcoin Futures Deribit&#8217;s Chief Commercial Officer, Luuk Strijers, has highlighted the current state of the Bitcoin futures basis, which ranges between 18% to 25% annually, a rate reminiscent of the market conditions in 2021. According to Strijers&#8217;s comment, this elevated basis is not just a number but a lucrative opportunity for derivatives traders. By engaging in trades that involve buying Bitcoin in the spot market and simultaneously selling futures contracts at a premium, traders can secure a &#8220;dollar gain&#8221; that will materialize at the contract&#8217;s expiry, irrespective of Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility. Strijers further noted that this strategy is particularly appealing in the current climate, fueled by the influx of new investments following the approval of Bitcoin ETFs and anticipation surrounding the Bitcoin halving event. The significance of the heightened futures basis extends beyond the mechanics of derivatives trading. It further reflects broader market optimism, &#8220;bolstered&#8221; by recent regulatory approvals and macroeconomic factors influencing cryptocurrency. The disparity between Bitcoin&#8217;s spot and futures prices suggests a confident market outlook, propelled by the anticipation of continued investment inflows and the impact of the upcoming Bitcoin halving. Such conditions create a fertile ground for Bitcoin&#8217;s value to surge, as historical precedents have often linked bullish futures basis rates with periods of substantial price appreciation. Market Sentiment And Halving Cycles While Bitcoin&#8217;s current market performance exhibits a bearish trajectory, with a 3.9% dip bringing its price to $68,203, market analysts advise against interpreting this as a negative signal. Rekt Capital, a respected figure in crypto analysis, views the recent price correction as a &#8220;positive adjustment&#8221; preceding the much-anticipated Bitcoin halving in April. Halving events, which reduce the block reward for miners, thus slowing the rate of new Bitcoin entering circulation, have traditionally catalyzed significant price rallies due to the resulting supply constraints. Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis parallels current market movements and historical patterns observed in previous halving cycles. Related Reading: The $69,000 Bitcoin Question: Expert Forecasts When Price Will Breakout According to the analyst, despite the swift pace of these cycles, they exhibit a consistent sequence of a pre-halving rally followed by a retracement phase—both of which align with Bitcoin&#8217;s current trajectory. This cyclical perspective suggests that the recent dip is merely a temporary setback, setting the stage for the next bullish phase post-halving. #BTC Though there are signs of BTC experiencing an Accelerated Cycle&#8230; History still continues to repeat, nonetheless$BTC broke out into a &#8220;Pre-Halving Rally&#8221; right on schedule And now, #Bitcoin is transitioning into its &#8220;Pre-Halving Retrace&#8221; right on schedule#Crypto https://t.co/Egqxs9ritl pic.twitter.com/lj0IdQtBEE — Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) March 15, 2024 Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s futures market is showcasing signs that have historically signalled bullish sentiment. Analysts are turning their attention to the Bitcoin <a href="https://metrics.deribit.com/futures/BTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">futures basis</a>—a metric representing the differential between the futures price of Bitcoin and its spot price.</p>
<p>Recent data has revealed that this basis has escalated to unprecedented levels since Bitcoin&#8217;s <a href="http://The $69,000 Bitcoin Question: Expert Forecasts When Price Will Breakout" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">all-time high of $69,000</a> in November 2021.</p>

<h2>Bullish Indications From Bitcoin Futures</h2>
<p>Deribit&#8217;s Chief Commercial Officer, Luuk Strijers, has <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/282761/bitcoin-futures-basis-is-a-bullish-indicator-for-the-market-analyst-says" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> the current state of the Bitcoin futures basis, which ranges between 18% to 25% annually, a rate reminiscent of the market conditions in 2021.</p>
<p>According to Strijers&#8217;s comment, this elevated basis is not just a number but a lucrative opportunity for derivatives traders.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-598103 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C464" alt="Bitcoin Futures Premium Above The Index Price." width="860" height="464" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=2286 2286w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C464 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>By engaging in trades that involve buying Bitcoin in the spot market and simultaneously selling futures contracts at a premium, traders can secure a &#8220;dollar gain&#8221; that will materialize at the contract&#8217;s expiry, irrespective of Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility.</p>
<p>Strijers further noted that this strategy is particularly appealing in the current climate, fueled by the influx of new investments following the approval of Bitcoin ETFs and anticipation surrounding the Bitcoin halving event.</p>
<p>The significance of the heightened futures basis extends beyond the mechanics of derivatives trading. It further reflects broader market optimism, &#8220;bolstered&#8221; by recent regulatory approvals and macroeconomic factors influencing cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The disparity between Bitcoin&#8217;s spot and futures prices suggests a confident market outlook, propelled by the anticipation of continued investment inflows and the impact of the upcoming Bitcoin halving.</p>
<p>Such conditions create a fertile ground for Bitcoin&#8217;s value to surge, as historical precedents have often linked bullish futures basis rates with periods of<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/historical-data-signals-bitcoins-imminent-25-plunge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> substantial price appreciation</a>.</p>
<h2>Market Sentiment And Halving Cycles</h2>
<p>While Bitcoin&#8217;s current <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-2024-forecast-analyst-predicts-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market performance</a> exhibits a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-suffers-crash-to-65000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish trajectory</a>, with a 3.9% dip bringing its price to $68,203, market analysts advise against interpreting this as a negative signal. Rekt Capital, a respected figure in crypto analysis, <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1768592730928685149?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">views</a> the recent price correction as a &#8220;positive adjustment&#8221; preceding the much-anticipated Bitcoin halving in April.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FLvIeQAC/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<p>Halving events, which reduce the block reward for miners, thus slowing the rate of new Bitcoin entering circulation, have traditionally catalyzed significant price rallies due to the resulting supply constraints.</p>
<p>Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis parallels <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-crash-failed-1-billion-hedge-fund-trade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">current market movements</a> and historical patterns observed in previous halving cycles.</p>

<p>According to the analyst, despite the swift pace of these cycles, they exhibit a consistent sequence of a pre-halving rally followed by a retracement phase—both of which align with Bitcoin&#8217;s current trajectory. This cyclical perspective suggests that the recent dip is merely a temporary setback, setting the stage for the next bullish phase post-halving.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#BTC</a></p>
<p>Though there are signs of BTC experiencing an Accelerated Cycle&#8230;</p>
<p>History still continues to repeat, nonetheless<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$BTC</a> broke out into a &#8220;Pre-Halving Rally&#8221; right on schedule</p>
<p>And now, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> is transitioning into its &#8220;Pre-Halving Retrace&#8221; right on schedule<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://t.co/Egqxs9ritl" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">https://t.co/Egqxs9ritl</a> <a href="https://t.co/lj0IdQtBEE" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pic.twitter.com/lj0IdQtBEE</a></p>
<p>— Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1768592730928685149?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 15, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin.jpeg?fit=460%2C329" width="460" height="329" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598098</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>United States Dominates Global Crypto Market With Massive $9.3 Billion In Profits</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/united-states-dominates-global-crypto-market-with-massive-9-3-billion-in-profits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto market analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto market news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market Recovery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market Sentiment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market update]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[total crypto market cap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent report by market intelligence firm Chainalysis, it has been revealed that global crypto gains in 2023 amounted to a staggering $37.6 billion. This profit surge reflects improved asset prices and market sentiment compared to 2022.  Although this figure falls short of the $159.7 billion gains witnessed during the 2021 bull market, it signifies a significant recovery from the estimated losses of $127.1 billion experienced in 2022. Sharp Surge In Crypto Gains The report suggests that despite similar growth rates in crypto asset prices in 2021 and 2023, the total gains for the latter year were lower. According to Chainalysis, this discrepancy could potentially be attributed to investors&#8217; decreased inclination to convert their crypto assets into cash.  The analysis further suggests that investors in 2023 seem to have anticipated further price increases, as crypto asset prices did not exceed previous all-time highs (ATHs) during the year, unlike in 2021. Related Reading: Altcoins Fall: Will Ethereum And Solana Bulls Surpass Expectations? Cryptocurrency gains remained relatively consistent throughout 2023, except for two consecutive months of losses in August and September, as seen in the image above. However, gains surged sharply thereafter, with November and December eclipsing all previous months. United States Leads Leading the pack in cryptocurrency gains was the United States, with an estimated $9.36 billion in profits in 2023. The United Kingdom secured the second position with an estimated $1.39 billion in crypto gains.  Notably, several upper and lower-middle-income countries, particularly in Asia, such as Vietnam, China, Indonesia, and India, achieved significant gains, each surpassing $1 billion and ranking within the top six countries worldwide.  Chainalysis had previously observed strong cryptocurrency adoption in these income categories, particularly in &#8220;lower-middle-income&#8221; countries, which demonstrated resilience even during the recent bear market. The gains estimates indicate that investors in these countries have reaped substantial benefits from embracing the asset class. Related Reading: Crypto Pundit Says God Candle Is Imminent For This Solana-Based Meme Coin Ultimately, the Chainalysis report suggests that the positive trends observed in 2023 have carried over into 2024, with prominent cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) hitting all-time highs of $73,700 following the approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and increased institutional adoption.  If these trends persist, the firm believes that it is conceivable that gains in 2024 will align more closely with those witnessed in 2021.  As of this writing, the total crypto market cap valuation stands at $2.5 trillion, a sharp drop of over 4% in the last 24 hours alone, and down from Thursday&#8217;s two-year high of $2.7 trillion. Bitcoin, on the other hand, is trading at $68,400 after dropping as low as $65,500 but has quickly regained its current trading price, limiting losses to 4% over the past 24 hours. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent report by market intelligence firm Chainalysis, it has been revealed that global crypto gains in 2023 amounted to a staggering $37.6 billion. This profit surge reflects improved asset prices and market sentiment compared to 2022. </p>
<p>Although this figure falls short of the $159.7 billion gains witnessed during the 2021 bull market, it signifies a significant recovery from the estimated losses of $127.1 billion experienced in 2022.</p>
<h2>Sharp Surge In Crypto Gains</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.chainalysis.com/blog/cryptocurrency-gains-by-country-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>suggests that despite similar growth rates in crypto asset prices in 2021 and 2023, the total gains for the latter year were lower. According to Chainalysis, this discrepancy could potentially be attributed to investors&#8217; decreased inclination to convert their crypto assets into cash. </p>
<p>The analysis further suggests that investors in 2023 seem to have anticipated further price increases, as crypto asset prices did not exceed previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">all-time highs</a> (ATHs) during the year, unlike in 2021.
</p>

<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-598123" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=829&#038;resize=829%2C346" alt="Crypto " width="829" height="346" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=829&#038;resize=829%2C346 829w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 829px) 100vw, 829px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Cryptocurrency gains remained relatively consistent throughout 2023, except for two consecutive <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-crash-failed-1-billion-hedge-fund-trade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">months of losses</a> in August and September, as seen in the image above. However, gains surged sharply thereafter, with November and December eclipsing all previous months.</p>
<h2>United States Leads</h2>
<p>Leading the pack in cryptocurrency gains was the United States, with an estimated $9.36 billion in profits in 2023. The United Kingdom secured the second position with an estimated $1.39 billion in crypto gains. </p>
<p>Notably, several upper and lower-middle-income countries, particularly in Asia, such as Vietnam, China, Indonesia, and India, achieved significant gains, each surpassing $1 billion and ranking within the top six countries worldwide. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-598122" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=761&#038;resize=761%2C232" alt="Crypto" width="761" height="232" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=761&#038;resize=761%2C232 761w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 761px) 100vw, 761px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Chainalysis had previously observed strong cryptocurrency adoption in these income categories, particularly in &#8220;lower-middle-income&#8221; countries, which demonstrated resilience even during the recent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/altcoins-fall-ethereum-solana-surpass-expectations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bear market</a>. The gains estimates indicate that investors in these countries have reaped substantial benefits from embracing the asset class.</p>



<p>Ultimately, the Chainalysis report suggests that the positive trends observed in 2023 have carried over into 2024, with prominent cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) hitting all-time highs of $73,700 following the approval of Bitcoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-suffers-crash-to-65000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange-traded funds</a> (ETFs) and increased institutional adoption. </p>
<p>If these trends persist, the firm believes that it is conceivable that gains in 2024 will align more closely with those witnessed in 2021. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tplik6SJ/" alt="Crypto" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of this writing, the total crypto market cap valuation stands at $2.5 trillion, a sharp drop of over 4% in the last 24 hours alone, and down from Thursday&#8217;s two-year high of $2.7 trillion. Bitcoin, on the other hand, is trading at $68,400 after dropping as low as $65,500 but has quickly regained its current trading price, limiting losses to 4% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-6-2.jpg?fit=390%2C260" width="390" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598120</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin FOMO: Over 533,330 Addresses Bought Above $70,180</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-fomo-533330-addresses-bought-70180/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin addresses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cost-Basis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin FOMO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests more than 533,330 addresses FOMO&#8217;d into Bitcoin above $70,180. Following the latest plunge, these investors would all be in losses. Over 500K Bitcoin Addresses Have A Cost Basis Between $70,180 &#38; $71,340 As pointed out by analyst Ali in a post on X, many investors have bought at the recently high price levels. Below is the chart shared by the analyst that shows how the distribution of the BTC supply looks right now across the various price ranges. How the BTC cost basis distribution looks like for the price ranges near the current one &#124; Source: @ali_charts on X The data is from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, which has used on-chain data to determine the average acquisition price for any given address based on when its coins moved into its balance. Related Reading: Bitcoin To $53,200? Why History Says It’s Possible In the chart, the size of the dots represents the amount of coins that have their cost basis inside the corresponding range. It would appear that the $64,743 and $66,700 range is below the current price that hosts the cost basis of a significant amount of addresses. More particularly, 382,000 addresses acquired 275,450 BTC at these levels. As the Bitcoin spot price is currently trading above this range, all these investors would naturally be carrying some profits. Generally, investors are sensitive to retests of their cost basis, as such retests can potentially flip their profit-loss status. For holders who were in profit before the retest, the dip may appear as an opportunity to buy more. The emerging reaction can be significant when many hands share their cost basis inside the same narrow range. If this retest occurs from above, the asset could feel some support as these investors rush to accumulate more. Since the $64,743 to $66,700 range is dense with investors and is situated below the current spot price of the cryptocurrency, it could act as a major support center. &#8220;Monitoring this level closely is crucial, as losing it could shift the focus to the next significant demand zone between $60,760 and $62,790, safeguarded by 797,500 addresses with over 298,000 BTC,&#8221; notes Ali. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Brace For Impact As Difficulty Reaches Unprecedented Levels In terms of the levels above, the $70,180 to $71,340 range particularly stands out, as 533,330 addresses bought a total of almost 433,000 BTC. A lot of these new buyers would be those FOMO&#8217;ing into the asset after seeing it explore new all-time highs. This large block, however, may serve as a point of resistance for the cryptocurrency. These fresh hands might sell just as quickly as they bought in when a retest of their cost basis happens since they may be willing to just exit at their break-even, fearing more drops in the near future. BTC Price Bitcoin has seen a sharp correction during the past day, following which its spot price is now trading around the $67,900 level. BTC made a brief visit under the $66,000 level during this correction &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, IntoTheBlock.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data suggests more than 533,330 addresses FOMO&#8217;d into Bitcoin above $70,180. Following the latest plunge, these investors would all be in losses.</p>
<h2>Over 500K Bitcoin Addresses Have A Cost Basis Between $70,180 &amp; $71,340</h2>
<p>As pointed out by analyst Ali in a <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1768575782778028153" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, many investors have bought at the recently high price levels. Below is the chart shared by the analyst that shows how the distribution of the BTC supply looks right now across the various price ranges.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GIs8XsjX0AAfL-s?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Cost Basis" width="2552" height="860"/></p>

<p>The data is from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, which has used on-chain data to determine the average acquisition price for any given address based on when its coins moved into its balance.</p>

<p>In the chart, the size of the dots represents the amount of coins that have their cost basis inside the corresponding range. It would appear that the $64,743 and $66,700 range is below the current price that hosts the cost basis of a significant amount of addresses.</p>
<p>More particularly, 382,000 addresses acquired 275,450 BTC at these levels. As the Bitcoin spot price is currently trading above this range, all these investors would naturally be carrying some <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/95-bitcoin-now-profit-could-signal-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">profits</a>.</p>
<p>Generally, investors are sensitive to retests of their cost basis, as such retests can potentially flip their profit-loss status. For holders who were in profit before the retest, the dip may appear as an opportunity to buy more.</p>
<p>The emerging reaction can be significant when many hands share their cost basis inside the same narrow range. If this retest occurs from above, the asset could feel some <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-takes-hit-3680/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">support</a> as these investors rush to accumulate more.</p>
<p>Since the $64,743 to $66,700 range is dense with investors and is situated below the current spot price of the cryptocurrency, it could act as a major support center.</p>
<p>&#8220;Monitoring this level closely is crucial, as losing it could shift the focus to the next significant demand zone between $60,760 and $62,790, safeguarded by 797,500 addresses with over 298,000 BTC,&#8221; notes Ali.</p>

<p>In terms of the levels above, the $70,180 to $71,340 range particularly stands out, as 533,330 addresses bought a total of almost 433,000 BTC. A lot of these new buyers would be those FOMO&#8217;ing into the asset after seeing it explore new all-time highs.</p>
<p>This large block, however, may serve as a point of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-large-resistance-wall-ahead-level-watch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">resistance</a> for the cryptocurrency. These fresh hands might sell just as quickly as they bought in when a retest of their cost basis happens since they may be willing to just exit at their break-even, fearing more drops in the near future.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has seen a sharp correction during the past day, following which its spot price is now trading around the $67,900 level.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dua2dSs7/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kanchanara-OqEPgkdX3RA-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598099</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind The Scenes Of Shiba Inu 12% Plunge: What On-Chain Analysis Tells Us</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/behind-the-scenes-of-shiba-inu-12-plunge-what-on-chain-analysis-tells-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), a popular memecoin, has experienced a notable decline. It dropped nearly 20% over the past week and continued a 13% fall in just the past 24 hours. This downturn occurs amid a broader bearish trend across the crypto landscape. However, detailed on-chain analysis has uncovered specific factors contributing to SHIB&#8217;s sharp decline. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Optimistic About A Shiba Inu Short-Term Surge To $0.000066 Whale Movements And Market Influence Insights from IntoTheBlock have shed light on large transaction activities, often indicative of &#8220;whale&#8221; movements, which have seen a general decrease since March 5, further compounding the downward pressure on SHIB&#8217;s price. The role of speculative trading in influencing SHIB&#8217;s market performance has also become increasingly apparent. Data pointing to the holding time of transacted coins suggests a shift towards short-term trading strategies among investors, possibly in pursuit of quick profits. Such behaviors are underscored by a significant reduction in the average holding period of coins, from four weeks to just two months as of mid-March, accompanied by a transaction volume of 2.12 trillion SHIB. This trend towards speculative trading has been a key driver behind the memecoin&#8217;s recent price movements, reflecting the broader dynamics within the cryptocurrency market. The decrease in large transactions involving Shiba Inu signifies dwindling confidence among whales, whose actions can profoundly impact market direction. The observed decline in whale activities aligns with a broader caution in the crypto market, where investors reevaluate their positions amid shifting market conditions. Shiba Inu Bright Horizon Despite the current downturn, Shiba Inu remains a focal point within the altcoin sector, buoyed by optimistic predictions from crypto analysts. Related Reading: Crypto Expert Says Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, PEPE, Others Are About To Explode Michaël van de Poppe, a well-regarded figure in the crypto analysis community, has recently posited that altcoins,  are set for significant rallies, potentially positioning Shiba Inu for a notable rebound as the market stabilizes. &#160; There&#8217;s still around 40-60% market capitalization to gain for the #Altcoins. That&#8217;s going to be a fun ride for the altcoins in the coming period. pic.twitter.com/qT0FRU4qpY — Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) March 7, 2024 This sentiment is echoed by Shiba Inu&#8217;s co-founder, Shytoshi Kusama, who has expressed confidence in SHIB&#8217;s ability to lead in the next bull market, citing the project&#8217;s comprehensive plans, community support, and execution as key differentiators. No. The community with the strongest tech, vision, plan, supporters, partners, and execution will. #SHIB But if you wanted some impressions why not say hi? https://t.co/jc6qJ11GJ6 — Shytoshi Kusama™ (@ShytoshiKusama) March 6, 2024 Regardless, SHIB has continued its bearish trajectory, with a market price now sitting at $0.00002916 at the time of writing. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), a popular memecoin, has <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=all&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">experienced</a> a notable decline. It dropped nearly 20% over the past week and continued a 13% fall in just the past 24 hours. This downturn occurs amid a broader bearish trend across the crypto landscape.</p>
<p>However, detailed on-chain analysis has uncovered specific factors contributing to SHIB&#8217;s sharp decline.</p>

<h2>Whale Movements And Market Influence</h2>
<p>Insights from IntoTheBlock have shed light on large transaction activities, often indicative of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whale-1-25-trillion-shib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">&#8220;whale&#8221; movements,</a> which have seen a general decrease since March 5, further compounding the downward pressure on SHIB&#8217;s price.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/u.today/sites/default/files/inline-images/15032024%200000.PNG?resize=1627%2C461&#038;ssl=1" alt="Decline whale activities." width="1627" height="461"  data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The role of speculative trading in influencing <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-optimistic-about-a-shiba-inu-short-term-surge-to-0-000066/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB&#8217;s market performance</a> has also become increasingly apparent. Data pointing to the holding time of transacted coins suggests a shift towards short-term trading strategies among investors, possibly in pursuit of quick profits.</p>
<p>Such behaviors are underscored by a significant reduction in the average holding period of coins, from four weeks to just two months as of mid-March, accompanied by a transaction volume of 2.12 trillion SHIB.</p>
<p>This trend towards speculative trading has been a key driver behind the memecoin&#8217;s recent price movements, reflecting the broader dynamics within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>The decrease in large transactions involving Shiba Inu signifies dwindling confidence among whales, whose actions can profoundly impact <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-skyrockets-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market direction</a>.</p>
<p>The observed decline in whale activities aligns with a broader caution in the crypto market, where investors reevaluate their positions amid shifting market conditions.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VlYn5wEd/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<h2>Shiba Inu Bright Horizon</h2>
<p>Despite the current downturn, Shiba Inu remains a focal point within the altcoin sector, buoyed by optimistic predictions from crypto analysts.</p>

<p>Michaël van de Poppe, a well-regarded figure in the crypto analysis community, has recently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/dogecoin-shiba-inu-pepe-explode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">posited that altcoins,  are set for significant rallies</a>, potentially positioning Shiba Inu for a notable rebound as the market stabilizes.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">There&#8217;s still around 40-60% market capitalization to gain for the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Altcoins</a>.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s going to be a fun ride for the altcoins in the coming period. <a href="https://t.co/qT0FRU4qpY" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/qT0FRU4qpY</a></p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1765728607010234712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 7, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This sentiment is echoed by Shiba Inu&#8217;s co-founder, Shytoshi Kusama, who has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-dev-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">expressed confidence in SHIB&#8217;s ability</a> to lead in the next bull market, citing the project&#8217;s comprehensive plans, community support, and execution as key differentiators.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">No. The community with the strongest tech, vision, plan, supporters, partners, and execution will. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#SHIB</a> But if you wanted some impressions why not say hi? <a href="https://t.co/jc6qJ11GJ6" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">https://t.co/jc6qJ11GJ6</a></p>
<p>— Shytoshi Kusama<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@ShytoshiKusama) <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/status/1765358580985675904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Regardless, SHIB has continued its bearish trajectory, with a market price now sitting at $0.00002916 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SHIB-Shibarium.jpg?fit=350%2C250" width="350" height="250" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598080</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
