<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033: Time to Buy AVAX?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Koome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=127387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033 Here’s a thought: The value of an AVAX token is tied to the usefulness of the Avalanche platform. If people want to use the Avalanche platform, AVAX tokens rise in value. Conversely, the AVAX token won’t be as useful for an investment portfolio if the platform becomes obsolete or unpopular. Do [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2024"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2024</u></a> – up to $67.77</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2027"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2027</u></a>– up to $208.30</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2030"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2030</u></a> – up to $681.32</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2033"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2033</u></a> – up to $2,098.00</li>
</ul>



<p>Here’s a thought: The value of an AVAX token is tied to the usefulness of the Avalanche platform. If people want to use the Avalanche platform, AVAX tokens rise in value. Conversely, the AVAX token won’t be as useful for an investment portfolio if the platform becomes obsolete or unpopular.</p>



<p>Do you think Avalanche will still be a viable cryptocurrency in 2024 and beyond now that we know more about it? Let’s study the charts in this AVAX price analysis and AVAX price prediction.</p>



<p>Is it time to buy the dip? While some platforms suggest Avalanche can reach $166.17 by 2027, Cryptopolitan estimates AVAX to hit a maximum of $1,465.95 at best in 2033.&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is AVAX worth?</h4>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<p>The current price of Avalanche is $58.21, with a 24-hour trading volume of $936 million. Avalanche is up 3.50% in the last 24 hours. The current Market cap ranking is #10, with a live market cap of $21.98 billion. It has a circulating supply of 377,416,536 AVAX coins and a maximum supply of 715,748,719 AVAX coins.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche price analysis</h2>



<p>TL; DR Breakdown:</p>



<ul>
<li>AVAX is one of the best-performing mega-cap altcoins.</li>



<li>The coin also achieved a new one-year high of $61.27.</li>
</ul>



<p>AVAX’s recovery in the last quarter of 2023 pushed it to the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization. The coin also achieved a new one-year high of $61.27.</p>



<p>It has risen 239.45% in the last 12 months and 57.57% over the previous 30 days. The recent run helped it recoup all of 2023’s losses.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">AVAX price analysis 1-day chart</h3>



<p>The charts show that the AVAX price rose this year, creating multiple bullish daily candlesticks.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/Sqhk28DUD4HUkhMU5GxeEZ7UJdHs1Sbsbchcs-8seQ0ZaoGGkXVXPgKEW92QIxgdGHxzlnQsDCWaKyfIen-wcJoDIrn-gggQnQBeROkBCASqFOx9xlzB-0oeitUuOMFsGQ-ajr2p0CuV6VscF2ff8ps" alt="" /></figure>



<p>The RSI is a momentum indicator that evaluates whether a market is overbought or oversold and whether to accumulate or sell an asset.</p>



<p>Readings above 50 and an upward trend suggest that bulls have an advantage, while readings below 50 indicate the opposite. The coin is in neutral territory without divergence. AVAX registered positive momentum for the better part of March.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">AVAX/USD 4-hour price chart</h3>



<p>The coin registers positive momentum in this time frame, contributing to the recent price stagation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/RO-VWFSlfjyZtlj-lpPunIRoQLGoMHEry3dOJsK0CIc4-BW-fASbOCtcQVIlJLByKdndQz9N8gESaaKO5dTVxFkFzhhCpKnm4iIdGvoCwst0LCTX_E64gyEDCmnzTjw38cRUUe9qG3hMVR9g3PElN9o" alt="" /></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from AVAX price analysis next?</h3>



<p>AVAX’s recent correction pushed the coin below $60. The coin should remain rangebound in the short term.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is AVAX a Good Investment?</h2>



<p>Avalanche promises to outperform the second-largest <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> by market capitalization, <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u>Ethereum</u></a>. The coin already made it to the top 10 list and is among the best-performing mega-altcoins this year. The AVAX token acts as the basic accounting unit on the Avalanche network. Our CP Price Prediction section will show how the coin will gain value in years to come.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News</h2>



<p>Ava Labs’ introduction of the Vryx for the Avalanche (AVAX) blockchain is pivotal when the coin strives to maintain its #9 market cap position. Scheduled for the second quarter of 2024, this update targets the critical challenge of scaling blockchains for higher transaction volumes without sacrificing security or decentralization. Vryx is set to achieve an impressive 100,000 transactions per second (TPS) by employing a novel approach named Decoupled State Machine Replication (DSMR). Unlike traditional methods where transactions and verification are intertwined, DSMR separates these processes, allowing for faster and more efficient transaction handling. This upgrade will be initially tested on the HyperSDK testnet. While DSMR promises increased throughput, it also raises concerns about the potential spread of invalid transactions, which could congest the network. To mitigate this, Vryx will ensure only transactions that pay fees are circulated, maintaining the network’s efficiency. This advancement, if successful, could significantly enhance Avalanche’s capabilities and influence in the blockchain sector.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/XUipI_wDgIpMiGwstbLPsDuXCy8cumN20fXpzNpYReb2aWXhbPXDFt9XQpE4XoBQohdQ8hjE6Phb7WB8GHGcYHPsIsXoskOzRAXRsSivAYxE79bHyj6Xgae9a0PTG7dQ2PSYbtHx1va4HL6KjaxWP2Q" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum Price $</td><td>Average Price $</td><td>Maximum Price $</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>$56.28</td><td>$58.01</td><td>$67.77</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>$83.62</td><td>$85.95</td><td>$95.17</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>$120.22</td><td>$123.66</td><td>$143.31</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>$178.80</td><td>$184.98</td><td>$208.30</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>$269.31</td><td>$276.71</td><td>$319.85</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>$384.30</td><td>$398.13</td><td>$459.77</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>$562.57</td><td>$578.50</td><td>$681.32</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>$803.57</td><td>$832.50</td><td>$986.86</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>$1,200.00</td><td>$1,233.00</td><td>$1,401.00</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>$1,696.00</td><td>$1,757.00</td><td>$2,098.00</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2024, we expect a minimum price of $56.28&nbsp; and an average price of $58.01. However, If Avalanche AVAX’s growth trajectory persists, we predict its value could reach as high as $67.77 at its peak.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2025, the minimum price of AVAX will be $83.62, while the average price will be around $85.95. There is potential for significant growth in the value of Avalanche AVAX during this period, with the token possibly reaching a maximum price of $95.17 by the end of 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>Avalanche’s price prediction for 2026 will be a minimum price of $120.22 and an average predicted value of $123.66. We expect AVAX’s price to surge to a maximum of $143.31 by 2026.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>Our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2027 is a minimum value of $178.80 with an average trading price of $184.98. Based on the Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2027, the price could reach a maximum of $208.30 during the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Based on our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2028, the AVAX token is anticipated to experience a bullish trend with a predicted floor price of $269.31 and an average trading value of $276.71. The highest possible price for 2028 is estimated to reach $319.85, reflecting a significant increase in the token’s valuation.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2029 suggests that the minimum price level could be $384.30. The AVAX token will experience significant growth, with a maximum potential price value of $459.77 and an average projected value of $398.13.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2030, the cryptocurrency’s value may drop to a low of $562.57 by year-end. However, we expect the average trading price to be $578.50 and the maximum estimated price to reach as high as $681.32.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>Based on our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2031, the minimum price of AVAX will be approximately $803.57, while the average price will be around $832.50. The maximum estimated value for AVAX in 2031 will reach $986.86.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>In our 2033 Avalanche AVAX price prediction, we anticipate a minimum trading price of $1200 and an average value of $1233 for the token. We expect Avalanche AVAX to experience a surge in value and reach a maximum price of $1401.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2032, the AVAX coin will rise steadily. However, the minimum price of the coin will be $1696. The average trading price is estimated at $1757, indicating steady growth. The maximum estimated price for 2032 is $2098, showing a potential surge in price.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Predictions by Walletinvestor</h3>



<p>Wallet Investor uses technical analysis to provide the AVAX price forecast. The platform indicates Avalanche’s past performance index rating as C; it adds that AVAX would make an ‘good’ one-year investment. The expected average price in 2025 will be $50.017. Avalanche’s return on investment (ROI) will be 14.9% in 2025. In 2026, the ROI will be 32%; in 2027, it will be 48.6%; in 2028, it will be 65.8%. According to the analysis, the Avalanche price is bearish over the entire period.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Predictions by CryptoPredictions</h3>



<p>The site scans a coin’s exchange prices and other historical crypto market data and analyzes it to provide an Avalanche price forecast.</p>



<p>In 2025, the Avalanche cost will be $43.031 in June and $47.498 in December. In 2027, AVAX will sell at an average price of $58.049 in January and $66.631 in December.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Predictions by Digitalcoinprice</h3>



<p>Avalanche will be on a bullish trend from 2024 to 2033; the minimum and maximum prices AVAX for the entire duration will be $37.93 and $834.53, respectively. In 2025, it will trade at a mean price of $106.67. It will reach a maximum price of $111.20 and a minimum of $92.06. In 2027, it will trade at a mean price of $186.15. It will reach a maximum price of $189.26 and a minimum of $165.17. In 2033, it will trade at a mean price of $824.40. It will reach a minimum of $805.21.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Predictions By Industry Experts</h3>



<p>Avalanche forecast by<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/markets?ref=16863683" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><u> Binance</u></a>, the world’s largest exchange by trading volume, indicates a bullish price projection; AVAX will average at $45.64 in 2025, $50.32 in 2027, and $58.25 in 2030.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>MARKET CAP</td><td>CIRCULATING SUPPLY</td><td>POPULARITY</td><td>ALL-TIME LOW</td><td>ALL-TIME HIGH</td></tr><tr><td>$16.288 Billion</td><td>377,259,824</td><td>#11</td><td>$2.79</td><td>$146.22</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>Avalanche began as a protocol for solving for consensus in a network of unreliable machines, where failures may be crash-fault or Byzantine. The protocol’s fundamentals were first shared on the InterPlanetary File System (IPFS) in May 2018 by a pseudonymous group of enthusiasts named “Team Rocket.”</p>



<p>Researchers from Cornell University led by Emin Gün Sirer and doctoral students Maofan “Ted” Yin and Kevin Sekniqi later developed Avalanche. Following the research stage, a startup technology company was founded to develop a blockchain network that met finance industry requirements. In March 2020, the AVA codebase (Developer Accelerator Program or AVA DAP) for the Avalanche consensus protocol became publicly available as open-source software.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AVAX Price History</h2>



<p>In September 2020, Avalanche issued its native token, Avax. On Dec 31, 2020, the coin hit an All Time Low at $2.7888.</p>



<p>In September 2021, the Ava Labs Foundation received a $230 million investment from a Polychain and Three Arrows Capital group by purchasing the AVAX cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>In November 2021, following an agreement with Deloitte to improve U.S. disaster relief funding, the Avalanche blockchain moved into the top 10 cryptocurrencies in capitalization. At that time, AVAX achieved its All-Time High at $146.22.</p>



<p>In August 2022, whistleblower “Crypto Leaks” published a report accusing Ava Labs of secret deals with a law firm aimed at legally destabilizing Avalanche’s competitors. Ava Labs CEO Emin Gün Sirer denies any dirty deal with Roche Freedmen law firm.</p>



<p>In 2023, AVAX maintained a bullish trend between January and May, after which bears overwhelmed the market. It resumed the positive momentum in October, rising to $49.96. It corrected to $40 in 2024.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/GVN9pOxcZFNZa66ZMCdGsWX-_enz-EJ0-_wYOC4tBIOPuCJ7ez7r4N4WP7Cu5IT3rGq23xjUwBUZcdXjO8JCMPuA_OHvGXB7N852mzBuJB31OOgSUyau3t4zlezAeNXs2RQZ4kfrb12uHlgI7oEb-gQ" alt="" /></figure>



<p>Source:<a href="https://coinstats.app/coins/avalanche-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2024"><u>https://coinstats.app/coins/avalanche-2/</u></a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on Avalanche/ AVAX:</h2>



<p>The platform is fast, low-cost, and eco-friendly. Avalanche is fully compatible with<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u> Ethereum</u></a> assets, apps, and tools with faster speeds, higher throughput, and lower fees. Applications include</p>



<ul>
<li>Asset Issuance,</li>



<li>Borrowing and lending,</li>



<li>Automated Market Makers (AMMs),</li>



<li>Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs).</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is Avalanche &amp; AVAX?</h3>



<p>Ava Labs believes in the Avalanche protocol’s objective to construct a strong, safe, and power-efficient cryptocurrency network for apps (“dApps”), unique payment primitives, and new interconnecting blockchains. The Avax protocol is developing a new tokenized economy via its revolutionary technological approach, which includes seamless physical &amp; virtual asset trade, modular payment application primitives and derivative products, Web 3.0 private data and social apps, and much more.</p>



<p>Avalanche is one of the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u> blockchain</u></a> sector’s fastest smart contracts cryptocurrency networks. The network’s high number of PoS validators ensures efficiency. Furthermore, the Avalanche network is a lightning-fast, low-fee, and environmentally friendly platform. Again, any smart contract-based application might surpass its rivals on Avalanche.</p>



<p>Avalanche’s mainnet went live on September 21, 2021, and ever since, the platform has secured multiple projects, over $23.63 million of AVAX fees burnt, about 1,200 other block-offering validators, and over 958,000 community members on X.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What makes Avalanche the best smart contracts platform?</h3>



<ul>
<li>The Web’s Next Generation</li>
</ul>



<p>Avalanche and other cryptocurrency networks are next-generation web app platforms. The web is constantly changing. Web 1.0 PC networks linked us to the web and access to information and electronic online commerce payments. Web 2.0 mobile-first social networks linked us to internet communities, while algorithms enhanced our data user experience. Web 3.0 cryptocurrency networks are trustless community-based protocols such as Avalanche, which offers consumers back control over their information and privacy via natively incorporated<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u> DeFi</u></a> apps.</p>



<ul>
<li>The third age of cryptocurrency innovation:</li>
</ul>



<p>Earlier cryptocurrency networks allowed for worldwide, decentralized virtual money. The 2nd wave of platforms expanded on this foundational technology to enable the construction of programmable dApps, enabling<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u> DeFi</u></a> devices, NFTs, and other revenue-generating applications. These systems, however, have serviced a restricted range of use cases because of high-cost implications for transactions and slow transaction speeds. The third generation of cryptocurrency networks intends to accommodate a wider variety of decentralized Apps on less expensive and quicker blockchains, ushering in a multi-chain future with many ecosystems competing on speed, safety, and customization.</p>



<ul>
<li>Innovative technological architecture</li>
</ul>



<p>Avalanche uses revolutionary consensus means and a one-of-a-kind feature to provide a quick and scalable solution. Avalanche is a proof-of-stake (“PoS”) network that leverages probabilistic agreement to protect payments while maintaining performance and scalability. Avalanche’s distinctive multi-chain design makes it a blockchain platform, with several “subnets” supporting varied customer demands. This primary feature essential operations native to distinct subnets to interoperate effortlessly, without performance deterioration seen in networks when all activity is piled onto a single chain.</p>



<ul>
<li>Reliable network fulfillment</li>
</ul>



<p>Base-layer decentralized network technology protocols to host various applications and develop a robust digital economy must provide an optimum balance of decentralization, safety, and scalability while charging cheap transaction costs. Avalanche’s main net provides a transaction resolution layer that is highly competitive with the top PoS and PoW cryptocurrency systems in various criteria.</p>



<ul>
<li>Early uptake is encouraging.</li>
</ul>



<p>The capabilities of Avalanche have made it appropriate for many 3rd developers who are quickly launching new<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u> DeFi</u></a> solutions on the Avax C-Chain. Decentralized exchanges, liquidity mining, loans, synthetic assets, and other services are available via dApps. Consequently, the network has seen a significant increase in assets, apps, and bespoke execution on subnets targeted to corporations and bodies introduced briefly since the main net went online. This increased use has resulted in a continuous increase in transaction fee income to the network, supporting the tokens’ economic worth. Remember, the Avalanche blockchain was meant to help dApp developers deploy products on active subnets, just like the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u> Ethereum</u></a> virtual machine.</p>



<ul>
<li>Risks and uncertainty:</li>
</ul>



<p>Failing to implement its product plan, delayed system governance rollout, declining developer cravings, dApps not acquiring significant demand, rival cryptocurrency networks gaining share, user and transaction cost implication income do not materialize, crypto volatility, and regulatory concerns.</p>



<p>Avalanche provides a new form of consensus and flexibility that other Layer 1.0 protocols do not offer. While the system is still in its early stages, its degree of acceptance indicates that blockchain developers are aware of its potential and expect Avalanche to achieve its vision of a scalable and extensible digital world more than other blockchains.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Features</h3>



<p>The Platform Chain (P-Chain), the Exchange Chain (X-Chain), and the Contract Chain are all incorporated into Avalanche (C-Chain). All three blockchains are authenticated and secured by Avalanche’s fundamental network.</p>



<ul>
<li>The P-Chain is a network of interconnected nodes (Platform Chain).</li>
</ul>



<p>Avalanche’s metadata blockchain, which controls authenticators and custom subnets, is known as the P-Chain. Validators stake AVAX on the P-Chain to defend the network.</p>



<ul>
<li>The X-Chain is a network of interconnected computers.</li>
</ul>



<p>The X-Chain is Avalanche’s default asset blockchain, allowing asset building and trading. This Avalanche blockchain is designed for transactions requiring high throughput and quick completion (for dApps, use the C-Chain).</p>



<ul>
<li>The C-Chain is a series of links in a chain (Contract Chain).</li>
</ul>



<p>The C-Chain is Avalanche’s default smart contract blockchain, letting developers create<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u> Ethereum</u></a>-compatible programs and assets at lower prices and quicker transactions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The future of Avalanche (AVAX) holds both promise and uncertainty as it continues to establish its position in the blockchain industry. With its focus on scalability, fast transaction processing, and unique features like decentralized governance and fee structures, Avalanche has gained attention as a potential competitor to established platforms like Ethereum.</p>



<p>Looking ahead, the price prediction for AVAX from 2024 to 2033, investment advice, and your research may present a range of possibilities. While it is challenging to accurately forecast the exact trajectory of any cryptocurrency from the current Avalanche price, several factors contribute to its potential growth. These include its expanding ecosystem, increasing adoption of the Avalanche platform, and advancements in technology that improve transaction speeds and scalability.</p>



<p>Additionally, broader market trends, regulatory developments, and investor sentiment toward cryptocurrencies will influence AVAX’s performance. As the blockchain industry continues to evolve, competition among platforms intensifies, and market dynamics shift, it is crucial to consider both the opportunities and risks associated with AVAX. Remember to conduct own research if you intend to invest.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TmA7L1zhYlA" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TmA7L1zhYlA" />
			<media:title type="plain">AVAX A +8674% IS COMING?? - AVALANCHE PRICE PREDICTION 2023 &amp; ANALYSES</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX A +8674% IS COMING?? - AVALANCHE PRICE PREDICTION 2023 &amp; ANALYSESWarning : The Indications that have been revealed in this video are unique and only for...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/avax-a-8674-is-coming-avalanche-.jpg" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-AVAX-_1140x570.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-AVAX-_1140x570.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033: Will APE Break $3 Resistance?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Koome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 08:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=189466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033 The NFT industry has been booming for the past few years and is not stopping anytime soon. The NFT project Bored Ape Yacht Club has been one of the most successful in the blockchain industry. However, recent statistics indicate that the project is losing its momentum. Various APE price highlights unfold [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033</h3>



<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2024">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024</a> – up to $3.65</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2027">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2027</a> – up to $10.80</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2030">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2030</a> – up to $33.46</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2033">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2033</a> – up to $97.86</li>
</ul>



<p>The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/"> NFT</a> industry has been booming for the past few years and is not stopping anytime soon. The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/"> NFT</a> project Bored Ape Yacht Club has been one of the most successful in the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"> blockchain</a> industry. However, recent statistics indicate that the project is losing its momentum. Various APE price highlights unfold in this ApeCoin Price Prediction.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How much is ApeCoin (APE) worth?</h3>



<p></p>



<p>The current ApeCoin price is $2.12, with a 24-hour trading volume of $69 million. ApeCoin is up 4.90% in the last 24 hours. The current Market capitalization ranking is #90, with a live Apecoin market cap of $1.279 billion. It has a circulating supply of 604,895,833 APE coins and a maximum supply of 1,000,000,000 APE coins.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin price analysis</h2>



<p>TL; DR Breakdown</p>



<ul>
<li>APE is down 49.08% in the last 12 months and up 6.32% over the previous 30 days.</li>



<li>This week, it broke above the $2 resistance.</li>
</ul>



<p>In 2023, APE’s decline accelerated in June, forcing it to trade below $2 multiple times. Positive market sentiment helped it hit the $1.434 mark in October; it continued rising this year, reaching a high of $2.5.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">APE price analysis 1-day chart</h3>



<p>APE turned bullish in October 2023. It is down 49.08% in the last 12 months and up 6.32% over the previous 30 days.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/GFRSJu9efbRe4JAOJj18n8hndWQAqcpGlMH44lYXH86P2GvTx9WOe-0Tdh8uM4vgrICnY1818J5pJjtQPjNBW7eHM3NsOdJLtAO_lLwRdAbqIufBwYPVigZDdEVpYbcnXXejIu8hxqO4YWKzd__9YC4" alt="" /></figure>



<p>APE registers negative momentum this week amidst high volatility. Currently, the RSI is within the 30-70 neutral zone, which indicates the price is trending neutral.</p>



<p>There is a bullish divergence within the last four candles, a sign of price reversal from current areas.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">APE/USD 4-hour price chart</h3>



<p>The 4-hour chart highlights ApeCoin’s movement and ‘choppiness’ through 2024.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/TwSQCO36VU7JrHc8c7L8bQ2-poT3F2gz7yS_TV5DYLJHhjX4H_Zn6wUL-8pyLegO2TN32iYJppXrmmLNIe-QsYY1e70KUiMkLBn7GigsHrdQjr6_SMsTVVkWOxyETiT7BWxdgfFN76besY0TdzwzJ1A" alt="" /></figure>



<p>The MACD indicator shows the coin registers positive momentum.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from APE price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The positive price growth momentum on the charts give a clear advantage to the bulls. It should trade higher in the short term.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is ApeCoin a Good Investment?</h2>



<p>ApeCoin is a payment-ready cryptocurrency with a design that is identical to any other Web3 coin. Since ApeCoin is a widely used ERC-20 token, most retailers consider it acceptable.</p>



<p>Additionally, the coin is already being used as <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/">NFT</a> rewards; holders with the BAYC can immediately cash in their free APE. Our CP Price Prediction section will show how the coin will gain value in years to come.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News</h2>



<p>Yuga Labs, a leading force in the NFT industry, has expanded its portfolio by acquiring Proof, known for its Moonbirds collection, further cementing its status as a dominant player. Yuga Labs CEO Daniel Alegre expressed enthusiasm for integrating Proof into the Yuga ecosystem, highlighting the move to enhance art, culture, and community engagement on the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/">blockchain</a>. Although the financial details of the acquisition were not disclosed, the union is notable, considering Moonbirds’ once-celebrated status and its potential collaboration with Yuga Labs’ Otherside metaverse project. This strategic acquisition may positively influence the price of APE, Yuga Labs’ associated cryptocurrency, by boosting overall brand value, expanding the community, and integrating Moonbirds’ assets into high-profile projects like Otherside. However, the impact on APE’s price will also depend on broader NFT market trends, which have seen fluctuations in trading volumes compared to the peaks in previous years.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/tZvi0RaiNLekUymcaKH52f3ukKxVchId7FYbwR6aCT7z2-qC-jfwKf0kwrGIxKJr8giGKOmgZ7WKYO8qM2VBIwSE7U1Y9A9zQklCXEukCsZac2SpfnSosXZz0R-K9Oj0hY6sNbUf762A7eTCl-84Tyg" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum Price $</td><td>Average Price $</td><td>Maximum Price $</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>$3.12</td><td>$3.21</td><td>$3.65</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>$4.54</td><td>$4.66</td><td>$5.36</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>$6.22</td><td>$6.45</td><td>$7.63</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>$9.12</td><td>$9.38</td><td>$10.80</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>$13.03</td><td>$13.50</td><td>$15.87</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>$19.51</td><td>$20.19</td><td>$22.79</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>$26.93</td><td>$27.94</td><td>$33.46</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>$38.70</td><td>$39.81</td><td>$46.57</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>$55.14</td><td>$56.73</td><td>$66.30</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>$82.60</td><td>$84.87</td><td>$97.86</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2024, we expect a minimum price of $3.12 and an average price of $3.21. However, if ApeCoin APE’s growth trajectory persists, we predict its value could reach as high as $3.65 at its peak.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2025, the minimum price of APE will be $4.54, while the average price will be around $4.66. There is potential for significant growth in the value of ApeCoin APE during this period, with the token possibly reaching a maximum price of $5.36 by the end of 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>According to price prediction for 2026, we expect the minimum price of the coin to be $6.22 and an average predicted value of $6.45. We expect APE’s price to surge to a maximum of $7.63 by 2026.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>Our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2027 is a minimum value of $9.12 with an average trading price of $9.38. Based on the ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2027, the price could reach a maximum of $10.80 during the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Based on our ApeCoin APE price predictions for 2028, the APE token is anticipated to experience a bullish trend with a predicted floor price of $13.03 and an average trading value of $13.50. The highest possible price for 2028 is estimated to reach $15.87, reflecting a significant increase in the token’s valuation.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2029 suggests that the minimum price level could be $19.51. The APE token will experience significant growth, with a maximum potential price value of $22.79 and an average projected value of $20.19.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2030, the cryptocurrency’s value may drop to a low of $26.93 by year-end. However, we expect the average trading price to be $27.94 and the maximum estimated price to reach as high as $33.46.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>Based on our ApeCoin price prediction for 2031, the minimum price of APE will be approximately $38.70, while the average price will be around $39.81. The maximum estimated value for APE in 2031 will reach $46.57.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin price prediction for 2032, the APE coin will rise steadily. However, the minimum price of the coin will be $55.14. The average trading price is estimated at $56.73, indicating steady growth. The maximum estimated price for 2032 is $66.30, showing a potential surge in price.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>In our 2033 ApeCoin price prediction, we anticipate a minimum trading price of $82.60 and an average value of $84.87 for the token. With several scheduled ecosystem upgrades, we expect ApeCoin APE to experience a surge in value and reach a maximum price of $97.86.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Predictions by WalletInvestor</h3>



<p>Wallet Investor uses technical analysis to provide a detailed Apecoin price forecast. The platform indicates. ApeCoin’s past performance index rating of C and adds that APE would make a bad one-year investment. The expected average price in 2025 is $0.2080. ApeCoin’s return on investment (ROI) will be -91.00% in 2025. In 2026, the ROI will be -91.22%; in 2027, it will be -88.67%; in 2028, it will be -86.47%. According to the analysis, the ApeCoin price is bearish over the entire period.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Predictions by CryptoPredictions</h3>



<p>The site scans a coin’s exchange prices and other historical market data and analyses it to provide APE coin price prediction.</p>



<p>In 2024, APE will trade at an average price of $2.621 in June and $2.314 in December. In 2026, APE will sell at an average price of $3.215 in January and $3.848 in December.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Predictions by Digitalcoin Price</h3>



<p>ApeCoin will be on a bullish trend from 2024 to 2033; the maximum value of APE for the entire duration will be $45.59. In 2025, it will trade at a mean price of $5.61. It will reach a maximum price of $6.07 and a minimum of $5.03. In 2027, it will trade at a mean price of $10.56. It will reach a maximum price of $10.69 and a minimum of $8.99. In 2033, it will trade at a mean price of $45.10. It will reach a minimum of $43.84.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Predictions By Industry Experts</h3>



<p>ApeCoin price predictions by <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/">Binance</a>, the world’s largest exchange by trading volume, indicate a bullish price projection; APE will average at $2.446577 in 2025, $2.697351 in 2027, and $3.122521 in 2030.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>MARKETCAP</td><td>CIRCULATING SUPPLY</td><td>ALL-TIME LOW</td><td>POPULARITY</td><td>ALL-TIME HIGH</td></tr><tr><td>$1.418 billion</td><td>604,895,833</td><td>$1.00</td><td>#75</td><td>$39.40</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price History</h2>



<p>When Yuga Labs debuted the Bored Ape and Mutant Ape <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/">NFT</a> collections, they became the most popular NFT brand. Yuga Labs founded<a href="https://apecoin.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Apecoin</a> to power the entire operation of their apps and services offered for them to be improved. APE price fell to a low of $6.48 within an hour, and it remained in a sideways range between that figure and $9.35 for the rest of the afternoon. Many investors were concerned by the huge gaps in APE’s value, with several centralized exchanges claiming that ApeCoin had dropped 80% within a few hours of its launch.</p>



<p>The ApeCoin team knows the project’s high risk and price volatility but believes the long-term potential rewards justify these risks. On the minute of the airdrop,<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/"> Binance</a> recorded a high of $28 on its one-minute chart, <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2024">whileGate.io</a> recorded an incredibly large $214.</p>



<p>In late March 2022, VC powerhouse Andreessen Horowitz led a funding round of $450 million, bringing the company’s valuation to an astounding $4 billion.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Later, when Yuga Labs said it was working on an “Otherside metaverse,” there were a lot of positive developments. On 28 April, the price was $26.91, setting a new all-time high. Since then, however, it has dropped significantly.</p>



<p>The floor price of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection reached all-time lows, an 84.3% decline from its peak in 2022.&nbsp; In 2023, the coin was in a bear run until October, when it started recovering, rising from a low of $1 to a high of $1.8. The coin extended the run this year as it rose above $2.0.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/rzZR0LF0frISlaxibdUphIdH-Lf7mIB0grk-V0rGU8sjDq_4JOMmWCjC-ACPQ8XR4jeQeVSherSOTB8Oh8ntkUgRw5GCvy6o-eEFcvw7ZRs3v1I0QUVSrj2bGsqaEyAhY51it-wUPuZpGyrFfEmNDpA" alt="" /></figure>



<p>Source: <a href="https://coinstats.app/coins/apecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://coinstats.app/coins/apecoin/</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on the Apecoin Network</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is ApeCoin?</h3>



<p>ApeCoin (APE) is a digital asset that allows users to send and receive payments securely and efficiently. ApeCoin is built on<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"> blockchain</a> technology and utilizes a peer-to-peer network to facilitate transactions. APE is used in the ApeEcosystem to encourage a decentralized community that advances Web3. The cryptocurrency was created and launched by ApeCoin DAO, a decentralized autonomous organization dedicated to promoting the coin in the future years. Hosted on the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/">Ethereum</a> <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/">blockchain</a>, ApeCoin is an ERC-20 token for governance and utility.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How does ApeCoin Work?</h3>



<p>The Bored Ape Yacht Club, long renowned for its satire and humor in trading circles, was the basis for ApeCoin, a cryptocurrency named after a well-known animal. The APE token is a governance mechanism in the APE ecosystem.APE powers the community that is cryptocurrency development at the forefront of web3.</p>



<p>ApeCoin cryptocurrency holders can choose the ecosystem’s path and how the DAO spends its funds.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Many consider ApeCoin a meme token if not an excessively hyped currency. Some investors/ whales are firmly behind ApeCoin, while others believe its bubble will burst in months.</p>



<p>You can buy ApeCoin on popular exchanges like <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/">Binance</a>, Coinbase, and Kraken.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Team Behind ApeCoin</h3>



<p>The ApeCoin team comprises experienced professionals from various backgrounds. Yuga Sato leads the team. Other members of the team include Daisuke Tanaka, who is the CTO of ApeCoin, and Kenta Suzuki, who is the Head of Business Development.&nbsp;</p>



<p>A group advises the ApeCoin team of experienced individuals from the blockchain and cryptocurrency industry. These advisors include Vitalik Buterin, the founder of <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/">Ethereum</a>, and Daico Takahashi, the co-founder of OmiseGO.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Is The ApeCoin Foundation?</h3>



<p>The ApeCoin Foundation is a decentralized autonomous organization responsible for developing and adopting the ApeCoin token. It’s not like a regulator; it’s more of a foundation layer on which holders of ApeCoin in the ApeCoin DAO may build.&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Mission</h4>



<p>The Foundation’s objective is to provide decentralized and community-led governance, and it aims to become more decentralized over time. It is in charge of the ApeCoin DAO’s decisions and responsible for day-to-day management, accounting, project management, and other duties that ensure the DAO community’s ideas receive the support they require to come to reality.</p>



<p>The APE Foundation’s mission is to promote and protect the APE ecosystem fairly and inclusively. The ApeCoin Foundation’s primary objective is to utilize the Ecosystem Fund, which is governed by a multisig wallet, to pay its costs as directed by the ApeCoin DAO while providing an infrastructure for ApeCoin owners to collaborate via open and free governance procedures.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Vision</h4>



<p>ApeCoin’s vision is to create a decentralized future where everyone has an equal say. The project aspires to build a global community of ApeCoin holders who can shape the future of the APE ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The ApeCoin Foundation’s vision is to provide an infrastructure for ApeCoin owners to collaborate via open and free governance procedures.</p>



<p>ApeCoin also plans to use the APE ecosystem to create digital gaming, entertainment, and art.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The APE ecosystem has continued to draw investors who use the platform to explore opportunities its ecosystem presents, including<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"> Defi</a>, DAO, and NFTs. A quick look at the Apecoins roadmap and recent developments show compelling reasons to invest in the coin.</p>



<p>There is a lot of hype around the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFTs. With celebrity backing and connection to that project, there is potential for the price of ApeCoin to rise during another Bitcoin bull run. However, the coin has a limited utility, and community members have criticized its staking mechanics. The ApeCoin team is working hard to meet the community’s expectations and continue adding utility to the coin.</p>



<p>Given the current macroeconomic conditions plaguing all coins, the ApeCoin price prediction may reach over $3 by year’s end.</p>



<p>Overall, ApeCoin has a lot of hype and community support behind it right now, which will probably drive the price of APE. If you’re interested in investing in the token, conduct own research and follow current APE news before deciding when to buy, hold, or sell. Investing in ApeCoin is safe as a cryptocurrency but also carries volatility risks. Investing in cryptocurrencies such as ApeCoin on a regulated platform like Coinbase or eToro is also highly advisable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TWgm5CUnXow" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TWgm5CUnXow" />
			<media:title type="plain">APE Coin Realistic Price Prediction... Time To Face Reality</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[APE Coin Price prediction and analysis APE Coin Price Prediction and technical analysis#ape #apecoin #crypto #bitcoin 🔸My Fairdesk referral link ($5040 Bonu...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/ape-coin-realistic-price-predict.jpg" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cpn-2022-06-21T042531.306.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cpn-2022-06-21T042531.306.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investors call for delay in South Korea&#8217;s crypto tax implementation</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/investors-call-for-delay-south-korea-crypto-tax/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 08:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAXA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501763</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A petition has been launched in South Korea requesting the government to delay the introduction of taxes on cryptocurrency gains. The petition, submitted to the National Assembly on March 21, advocates for a two-year postponement of the tax plan, which is presently scheduled to commence in January 2025.&#160; This request stems from concerns over a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A petition has been launched in South Korea requesting the government to delay the introduction of taxes on cryptocurrency gains. The petition, submitted to the National Assembly on March 21, advocates for a two-year postponement of the tax plan, which is presently scheduled to commence in January 2025.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This request stems from concerns over a potential migration of crypto investors to overseas exchanges due to the country&#8217;s lack of readiness for such taxation. The petition has accumulated 10,888 signatures as of Tuesday afternoon in Asia, with a target of 50,000 signatures by April 20 to prompt a legislative review.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the petition calls for increased regulatory oversight of the Digital Asset Exchange Alliance (DAXA), an advisory group comprising the top five cryptocurrency exchanges in South Korea. It criticizes DAXA&#8217;s decision-making process on the support and discontinuation of certain cryptocurrencies as opaque and subject to arbitrary judgment.</p>



<p>South Korea boasts a robust cryptocurrency market, highlighted by the performance of Upbit, the leading exchange, which has processed $185 billion in trading volume in <a href="https://www.theblock.co/data/crypto-markets/spot" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">March alone</a>. This figure represents nearly 9% of the total global exchange trading volume. The fervor around cryptocurrency trading in South Korea has intensified recently, with trading volumes on local exchanges surpassing those on the country’s KOSPI stock market on certain days. Specifically, on March 11, South Korean exchanges recorded a trading volume of 11.85 trillion Korean won ($8.8 billion), exceeding the trading activity on the KOSPI, according<a href="https://www.busan.com/view/busan/view.php?code=2024031116402850911" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> to local reports</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Investors-call-for-delay-in-South-Koreas-crypto-tax-implementation-.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Investors-call-for-delay-in-South-Koreas-crypto-tax-implementation-.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto firms linked to Russia face US sanctions for evasion</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/crypto-firm-linked-to-russia-face-us-sanctios/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutuma Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 08:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto sanctions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501760</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of the Treasury&#8217;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) recently announced sanctions against 13 entities and two individuals. These sanctions target those aiding the potential evasion of sanctions on behalf of Russian nationals through cryptocurrency-related services. OFAC&#8217;s statement emphasized the role of these entities and individuals in facilitating transactions to assist other [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. Department of the Treasury&#8217;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bloxroute-reject-block-ofac-flagged-address/">OFAC</a>) recently announced sanctions against 13 entities and two individuals. These sanctions target those aiding the potential evasion of sanctions on behalf of Russian nationals through cryptocurrency-related services. OFAC&#8217;s statement emphasized the role of these entities and individuals in facilitating transactions to assist other sanctioned entities in evading U.S. sanctions.</p>



<p>Brian E. Nelson, Under Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence, highlighted Russia&#8217;s shift towards alternative payment mechanisms. This move aims to bypass U.S. sanctions and continue funding its military actions against Ukraine. Nelson affirmed the Treasury&#8217;s commitment to identifying and disrupting companies aiding sanctioned Russian financial institutions in reconnecting with the global economic system.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Russian entities boost crypto transfers to darknet</strong></h2>



<p>Blockchain analytics firm Chainalysis provided insights into the operations of the sanctioned entities. The firm noted that most of these entities and individuals are based in Russia. They are linked to Russia through the cryptocurrency services they provide. Among the sanctioned entities, Netex24 and Bitpapa were particularly noted for their transactions with OFAC-sanctioned banks, crypto exchanges, and darknet markets.</p>



<p>Chainalysis reported that Netex24 and Bitpapa have been instrumental in facilitating funds transfers to sanctioned entities over the past two years. Their transaction history showed a significant portion of outflows directed toward darknet markets and other illicit services. The research highlighted a steady increase in the value sent by these entities to sanctioned entities and darknet markets since the onset of Russia&#8217;s conflict with Ukraine.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>OFAC targets crypto for sanction evasion fight</strong></h2>



<p>The OFAC&#8217;s action <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy2204" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">against these entities</a> signals an increasing focus on combating sanctions evasion through cryptocurrency. This approach particularly targets businesses that facilitate on- and off-ramp activities for sanctioned Russian banks. Chainalysis&#8217;s findings underscore the significance of darknet markets in the transaction history of Netex24 and Bitpapa, alongside a constant flow to exchanges lacking strict know-your-customer guidelines.</p>



<p>The sanctions against these 13 entities and two individuals represent a critical step in the U.S.&#8217;s efforts to prevent sanction evasion. The Treasury&#8217;s proactive measures aim to limit Russia&#8217;s access to alternative financial networks. This strategy underscores the importance of transparency and regulation in the global cryptocurrency market to prevent misuse by sanctioned entities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-26-11.20.40-Visualize-an-abstract-concept-where-symbolic-elements-represent-the-United-States-imposing-sanctions-on-cryptocurrency-firms.-The-image-should-contain.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-26-11.20.40-Visualize-an-abstract-concept-where-symbolic-elements-represent-the-United-States-imposing-sanctions-on-cryptocurrency-firms.-The-image-should-contain.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian crypto mining sector moves towards legalization</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/russian-crypto-mining-towards-legalization/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 08:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alexander Brazhnikov]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anton Tkachev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RACIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Russian cryptocurrency industry leaders and business executives have collaborated to draft a bill aimed at legalizing crypto mining in the country.&#160; Alexander Brazhnikov, Executive Director of the Russian Association of Cryptocurrency and Blockchain (RACIB), revealed the initiative at a cryptocurrency event on March 22, according to ComNews. However, the draft seeks to formalize the framework [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Russian cryptocurrency industry leaders and business executives have collaborated to draft a bill aimed at legalizing crypto mining in the country.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Alexander Brazhnikov, Executive Director of the Russian Association of Cryptocurrency and Blockchain (RACIB), revealed the initiative at a cryptocurrency event on March 22, <a href="https://www.comnews.ru/content/232225/2024-03-25/2024-w13/1008/mayning-rossii-ischet-put-oficialnoe-pole" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">according to </a>ComNews. However, the draft seeks to formalize the framework for crypto mining activities, which are currently operating in a regulatory gray area in Russia.</p>



<p>Brazhnikov noted that after discussions with regulators, RACIB was encouraged to propose ideas for the mining bill themselves. Consequently, draft regulation proposals have been sent to the Ministry of Energy, the Ministry of Economic Development, and Rosfinmonitoring, Russia&#8217;s anti-money laundering agency. The Ministry of Finance is also expected to review the proposals.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Industry Support and Government Engagement</h2>



<p>The move comes after previous attempts to legalize the sector, with a bill failing to progress in the Duma in 2022. However, the latest efforts have garnered the support of State Duma lawmakers Anton Tkachev, Vladimir Plyakin, Grigory Shilkin, and Sardana Avksentyeva. According to the bill, over 12 million cryptocurrency wallets have been opened by Russian citizens, holding a combined total of $108 billion worth of coins.</p>



<p>The bill aims to secure an official classification for mining as a form of economic activity, which would allow for the taxation of crypto-mining operations. Additionally, it proposes the creation of an experimental legal sandbox for the centralized conversion of digital assets obtained as a result of mining, indicating interest in a state-run crypto exchange for miners and firms using crypto in cross-border trade.</p>



<p>RACIB&#8217;s efforts also include promises of investment in new multi-purpose data centers, potentially aiding government tech development plans and solidifying a safe operational future for companies in the Russian crypto mining industry.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Russian-crypto-mining-sector-moves-towards-legalization.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Russian-crypto-mining-sector-moves-towards-legalization.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE Central Bank launches Digital Dirham strategy for wholesale and retail use</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/uae-central-bank-digital-dirham-strategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cbdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBUAE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[central bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates (CBUAE) has announced the commencement of the initial phase of its central bank digital currency (CBDC) strategy, marking an important stride towards the adoption of digital currency in the region.&#160; In collaboration with R3 and G42 Cloud, the strategy aims to explore the utility of CBDC for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates (CBUAE) has announced the commencement of the initial phase of its central bank digital currency (CBDC) strategy, marking an important stride towards the adoption of digital currency in the region.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In collaboration with R3 and G42 Cloud, the strategy aims to explore the utility of CBDC for both retail and wholesale applications, ensuring a robust infrastructure and technology base for the digital dirham.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Strategic partnerships and phases</h2>



<p>The strategy&#8217;s <a href="https://www.centralbank.ae/media/q5nldmrv/cbuae-launches-the-central-bank-digital-currency-strategy-the-digital-dirham-en.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">rollout began</a> with a signing event on March 23, highlighting partnerships with R3, a key player in CBDC technology, and G42 Cloud, an entity within the AI conglomerate G42. This first phase encompasses three critical components: the launch of Project mBridge, a proof-of-concept for a CBDC bilateral bridge with India, and a proof-of-concept for domestic use. These initiatives point to the CBUAE&#8217;s commitment to addressing cross-border payment challenges, advancing financial inclusion, and transitioning towards a cashless society.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Towards a digital economy</h2>



<p>Embedded within the CBUAE’s Financial Infrastructure Transformation Programme, the CBDC strategy aims to enhance the efficiency of domestic and international payments. Also, it mandates the integration of the Digital Dirham by all UAE-licensed financial institutions by 2026. Project mBridge and Project Aber, with the Saudi Central Bank, serve as foundational projects, underscoring the CBUAE&#8217;s role as a pioneer in digital currency exploration. </p>



<p>The collaboration with R3 and G42, alongside the projected 12 to 15-month implementation period, is expected to set a clear pathway for the digital dirham&#8217;s integration into the financial ecosystem, reinforcing the UAE’s position as a forward-thinking participant in the global digital economy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/UAE-Central-Bank-launches-Digital-Dirham-strategy-for-wholesale-and-retail-use.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/UAE-Central-Bank-launches-Digital-Dirham-strategy-for-wholesale-and-retail-use.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>tymt™ &#8211; A Game Launcher Transforming Gaming Experiences</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tymt-a-game-launcher-transforming-gaming-experiences/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Corporate Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sollefteå, Sweden, December 20th, 2023, Chainwire The Gaming Landscape: An Ongoing Struggle Gaming, an essential part of global culture, connects over a billion people worldwide through entertainment, escape, and social interaction. However, within this vast realm of gaming platforms and titles, a perpetual battle for dominance, revenue, and player engagement persists. Gamers encounter numerous options [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Sollefteå, Sweden, December 20th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<h3><strong>The Gaming Landscape: An Ongoing Struggle</strong></h3>
<p>Gaming, an essential part of global culture, connects over a billion people worldwide through entertainment, escape, and social interaction. However, within this vast realm of gaming platforms and titles, a perpetual battle for dominance, revenue, and player engagement persists.</p>
<p>Gamers encounter numerous options for game launchers, from major players like Steam and Epic Games to smaller platforms like EA Origin and Good Old Games, as well as niche, open-source, and game-specific launchers.</p>
<h3><strong>Introducing tymt™: A Unified Gaming Hub</strong></h3>
<p><a href="https://tymt.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>tymt™</strong></a> presents a fresh perspective and an opportunity for harmony among games. By providing a peak environment for any game, whether traditional, MMO, blockchain-based, play-to-earn, or part of the Metaverse, <strong>tymt™</strong> aims to elevate the gaming experience to unprecedented heights.</p>
<h3><strong>Venturing into the Metaverse: A New Frontier</strong></h3>
<p>Amidst these choices emerges a new category of games known as Web3 games, offering decentralized, immersive experiences fueled by blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Web3 games encompass a diverse range of experiences leveraging blockchain technology to offer unique gameplay mechanics and reward systems:</p>
<ul>
<li>Blockchain games enable players to own in-game assets recorded on the blockchain.</li>
<li>NFT games utilize non-fungible tokens for rare or unique in-game items.</li>
<li>Play-to-earn games incentivize players with cryptocurrency rewards.</li>
<li>Play-and-earn games combine traditional gameplay with earning opportunities.</li>
<li>The Metaverse represents interconnected virtual worlds where players socialize and engage in various activities.</li>
</ul>
<p>Together, these Web3 games provide a glimpse into the future of gaming, where ownership, rewards, and immersive experiences converge.</p>
<p><strong><img decoding="async" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/xKOkTTL2r5icHhYB6OL0PTD-lxY76_tG0AlRbd3XKm0BR5y00h_1711377672id1E6pRnS7.jpeg"></strong></p>
<h3><strong>Bridging the Gap: tymt™&#8217;s Promise</strong></h3>
<p><strong>tymt™ </strong>serves as more than just a game launcher; it acts as a catalyst for unity in an industry often marked by fragmentation and competition. By integrating traditional, blockchain, Web3, and Metaverse games into a single platform,<strong> tymt™</strong> offers gamers a sanctuary for exploration, connection, and endless play.</p>
<h3><strong>Demystifying Blockchain Technology</strong></h3>
<p>Despite its potential to revolutionize gaming, blockchain technology remains obscure to many. <strong>tymt™</strong> aims to demystify this complexity by leveraging the Solar blockchain for all transactions, ensuring platform- and currency-independent gameplay.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/5VT-g-RhVHO8S-D81_dWDdbWU-pOy3NMfB9i4zJbURad1w4ydQ_1711377673a7wDnMqUXM.jpeg"></p>
<h3><strong>Empowering Users with Innovative Features</strong></h3>
<p><strong>tymt™</strong>&#8216;s versatility extends beyond game launching, offering a multi-chain cryptocurrency wallet with integrated social capabilities. By utilizing the Solar Blockchain, <strong>tymt™</strong> enhances security, transparency, and benefits for users and investors alike.</p>
<h3><strong>What Sets tymt™ Apart?</strong></h3>
<p>Unlike conventional game launchers, <strong>tymt™</strong> embraces diversity, offering seamless integration with various wallets, multiple access options, effortless crypto game purchases, extensive game libraries, and an interconnected gaming community.</p>
<ul>
<li>Seamless Integration with Custodial and Non-Custodial Wallets: Partnering with ChangeNOW ensures top-tier security and flexibility in transactions, instilling confidence as users navigate the gaming landscape.</li>
<li>Multiple Access Options: Whether logging in with a BinanceID or opting for guest access via Discord, Facebook, or Google credentials, <strong>tymt™</strong> provides users with unparalleled flexibility in connectivity.</li>
<li>Effortless Crypto Game Purchases: <strong>tymt™</strong> facilitates smooth and convenient game purchases with cryptocurrencies, streamlining transactions for gamers worldwide.</li>
<li>Access to Extensive Game Libraries: With the integration of more partners, <strong>tymt™</strong> aims to grant users access to a vast library of games, ensuring that gaming adventures are never constrained.</li>
<li>Interconnected Gaming Community: <strong>tymt™</strong> v2 transcends traditional gaming boundaries, fostering a global community where players can connect, chat, and forge friendships across supported blockchains.</li>
<li>Multi-Chain Universe: Explore a diverse multi-chain universe supported by the Solar Mobile Wallet, granting users seamless access to a range of cryptocurrencies, including SXP, BNB, ETH, BTC, SOL, MATIC, AVAX, OP, and ARB.</li>
</ul>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/7LE8Ei2uZKqFNbbN-l5NVj7GLXvGSVoIRS_AT3ZJ8JuQcKjT-o_1711377673Hs5bZAeTtB.jpeg"></p>
<p>From seamless integration with different types of wallets to effortless game purchases with cryptocurrencies,<strong> tymt™</strong> prioritizes convenience and accessibility.</p>
<p>Moreover, <strong>tymt™</strong> fosters a sense of community among gamers, enabling connections and friendships across supported blockchains. Whether you&#8217;re collaborating with fellow players or exploring new gaming worlds together, <strong>tymt™</strong> creates opportunities for social interaction and shared experiences.</p>
<h3><strong>District 53: Exploring the Metaverse</strong></h3>
<p><strong>tymt™</strong> comes equipped with a multiplayer, voxel-based metaverse game platform &#8211; District 53.</p>
<p>Based on the open-source engine of Mintetest, District 53 offers a dynamic fusion of cutting-edge technology and familiar “mine-craft-build” gameplay, offering endless possibilities for Creative or Survival adventures. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/2BHAC3Q3kWMIPutM6nnzOZwvb6jvmcTdsJKzzMCXMHk5agmC9g_1711377672G9Svk3JrZf.jpeg"></p>
<p>Unlike conventional virtual worlds, District 53 introduces players to a fully decentralized ecosystem where player-driven economies thrive and every interaction shapes the landscape. With its integration into the Solar Blockchain, District 53 empowers players with true ownership of their digital assets and fosters a community-driven ethos where innovation knows no bounds. </p>
<h3><strong>In Conclusion</strong></h3>
<p><strong>tymt™</strong> represents a paradigm shift in gaming, bridging traditional and emerging technologies while empowering users with innovative features. As gaming evolves, <strong>tymt™</strong> stands at the forefront, offering a glimpse into the future of gaming.</p>
<h3><strong>About Solar Enterprises</strong></h3>
<p><a href="https://solarenterprises.in/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Solar Enterprises</a>, funded by the Solar Blockchain Foundation, develops user-friendly, blockchain-based products, including the Solar Wallet, <strong>tymt™</strong> game launcher, and District 53 metaverse.</p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Chief Marketing Officer</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Jacek Studziński</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Solar Network/Dokdo</strong><br /></span><span><strong>jacek@dokdo.sh</strong><br /></span></p>
<p class="chainwire-disclaimer cp-box cp-box-gray"><i><strong>Disclaimer.</strong> This is a paid press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. <a href="https://cryptopolitan.com/">Cryptopolitan.com</a> is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tymt-cover-1024_1711375589vw6MpdgwkK.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/tymt-cover-1024_1711375589vw6MpdgwkK.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tiny Corp Introduces AMD and NVIDIA Powered AI Systems Starting at $15K</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tiny-corp-introduces-nvidia-ai-systems/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501738</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tiny Corp, the AI startup, has unveiled its latest offering in the form of AI systems powered by both AMD and NVIDIA, with prices kicking off at $15,000. The move comes in the wake of a tumultuous period marked by a dispute between Tiny Corp and AMD regarding GPU firmware libraries. Despite initial setbacks, Tiny [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tiny Corp, the AI startup, has unveiled its latest offering in the form of AI systems powered by both AMD and NVIDIA, with prices kicking off at $15,000. The move comes in the wake of a tumultuous period marked by a dispute between Tiny Corp and AMD regarding GPU firmware libraries. Despite initial setbacks, Tiny Corp has now expanded its offerings to include NVIDIA-powered systems alongside AMD alternatives.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">NVIDIA systems at $25K, AMD systems at $15K</h2>



<p>Following the fallout with AMD, Tiny Corp has opted to collaborate with NVIDIA, presenting a new alternative featuring six GeForce RTX 4090 GPUs. However, the adoption of NVIDIA components has led to a significant price hike, with the NVIDIA-powered system priced at $25,000, marking a $10,000 increase over its AMD counterpart. Conversely, the AMD system, equipped with Radeon RX 7900 XTX GPUs, remains available at the starting price of $15,000.</p>



<p>Tiny Corp&#8217;s pivot towards NVIDIA-powered AI systems poses challenges for AMD&#8217;s standing among AI startups. The company&#8217;s emphasis on the criticality of software resources underscores the importance of seamless integration and stability, an area where NVIDIA has historically held an edge. Despite Tiny Corp&#8217;s commitment to continue working with AMD, challenges persist, with reported instances of driver crashes and functionality issues.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Stability versus customization in the NVIDIA advantage</h2>



<p>Tiny Corp&#8217;s endorsement of NVIDIA&#8217;s GeForce-powered solution is rooted in the promise of reliability and ease of use. Citing NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang&#8217;s mantra, &#8220;It Just Works,&#8221; Tiny Corp positions NVIDIA as the go-to option for users seeking hassle-free performance out of the box. The endorsement reflects the broader sentiment within the AI community, where stability and reliability often take precedence over customization.</p>



<p>The announcement of Tiny Corp&#8217;s AMD and NVIDIA-powered AI systems has garnered significant interest from the market, with the company reporting 583 preorders to date. This surge in demand underscores the growing need for accessible AI solutions capable of handling low-to-mid workloads without the need for specialized accelerators. With shipments expected to commence in April, Tiny Corp aims to capitalize on this momentum and solidify its position in the AI hardware market.</p>



<p>Tiny Corp&#8217;s foray into AMD and NVIDIA-powered AI systems marks a pivotal moment in the company&#8217;s evolution. Despite initial setbacks with AMD, the inclusion of NVIDIA alternatives underscores Tiny Corp&#8217;s commitment to providing versatile solutions tailored to the diverse needs of its customers. While challenges persist, particularly concerning software optimization and stability, Tiny Corp remains steadfast in its pursuit of innovation. As the demand for AI solutions continues to soar, Tiny Corp&#8217;s offerings promise to reshape the landscape of AI hardware, catering to both mainstream users and enterprise clients alike.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Tiny_Corp_Introduces_AMD_and_NVIDIA_Powered_AI_Systems_1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Tiny_Corp_Introduces_AMD_and_NVIDIA_Powered_AI_Systems_1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Introduces AI-Summarized Search Results: Potential Impact on Websites</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/google-introduces-ai-impact-on-websites/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI in Daily Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google has unveiled a new feature in its search engine, introducing AI-generated summaries directly within search results. Initially an opt-in experience, Google&#8217;s Search Generative Experience (SGE) now provides AI summaries to a select group of users in the United States, regardless of their preference. This move marks a significant step in Google&#8217;s utilization of artificial [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Google has unveiled a new feature in its search engine, introducing AI-generated summaries directly within search results. Initially an opt-in experience, Google&#8217;s Search Generative Experience (SGE) now provides AI summaries to a select group of users in the United States, regardless of their preference. This move marks a significant step in Google&#8217;s utilization of artificial intelligence to enhance search functionality.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AI-summarized search results</h2>



<p>When users input complex queries or those requiring information from multiple sources, Google&#8217;s AI analyzes relevant content and generates concise summaries. These summaries, displayed prominently at the top of search results in a shaded section, aim to streamline the search process by presenting users with direct answers without the need to navigate through multiple websites.</p>



<p>For users, this innovation promises quicker access to information and potentially eliminates the need to click on individual search results. Imagine searching for a solution to a specific problem, such as &#8220;How to remove water stains from wood?&#8221; With AI-summarized results, users can obtain relevant information at a glance, enhancing efficiency and convenience in their online search experience.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Google&#8217;s experimentation and user feedback</h2>



<p>Google views this feature as an experimental endeavor, seeking feedback from a broader audience by defaulting it to select users. By observing how users interact with AI-summarized results, Google aims to gauge the technology&#8217;s effectiveness and identify areas for improvement. This approach reflects Google&#8217;s commitment to refining its search capabilities based on user behavior and preferences.</p>



<p>While AI-summarized results benefit users, they raise concerns for websites reliant on search engine optimization (SEO) traffic. If users find answers directly within the search results, website traffic may remain high, affecting revenue and audience engagement for online businesses and content creators. Google&#8217;s decision to make AI summaries default for some users underscores its confidence in AI technology and its potential to reshape online information retrieval.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Google&#8217;s assurance and industry response</h2>



<p>Google asserts that AI summaries will only appear when they offer a clear advantage over traditional search results. However, industry experts speculate on the long-term implications for website traffic and SEO strategies. This shift in user behavior underscores the need for websites to adapt and innovate in response to evolving search trends and technologies.</p>



<p>In light of Google&#8217;s AI-summarized search results, website owners may need to reassess their strategies to maintain visibility and relevance in search rankings. This may involve optimizing content for featured snippets and focusing on delivering value-added information to users beyond what AI summaries provide. Additionally, diversifying traffic sources and exploring alternative marketing channels can help mitigate the potential impact of changes in search dynamics.</p>



<p>Google&#8217;s introduction of AI-summarized search results represents a significant evolution in online information retrieval. While enhancing user experience, this innovation poses challenges for websites dependent on SEO traffic. As Google continues to refine its search capabilities and adapt to changing user behaviors, website owners must remain agile in their strategies to navigate the evolving landscape of online search and maintain their visibility and relevance in the digital realm.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Google_Introduces_AISummarized_Search_Results_Potentia_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Google_Introduces_AISummarized_Search_Results_Potentia_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UT Researchers Utilize AI to Enhance Alzheimer’s Medication Production</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ut-researchers-ai-to-enhance-medication/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glory Kaburu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hidden Gems]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[University of Texas (UT) researchers have harnessed the power of artificial intelligence (AI) to revolutionize the production of a medication crucial in treating Alzheimer’s and dementia symptoms. Their breakthrough study, published on March 7, unveils AI-driven tools designed to expedite the manufacturing process of galantamine, an essential compound derived from daffodils. AI-powered fermentation process Led [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>University of Texas (UT) researchers have harnessed the power of artificial intelligence (AI) to revolutionize the production of a medication crucial in treating Alzheimer’s and dementia symptoms. Their breakthrough study, published on March 7, unveils AI-driven tools designed to expedite the manufacturing process of galantamine, an essential compound derived from daffodils.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AI-powered fermentation process</h2>



<p>Led by Simon d’Oelsnitz, a former UT postdoctoral researcher now at Harvard Medical School, the research team aimed to streamline the laborious and yield-dependent extraction process of galantamine from daffodils. D’Oelsnitz likened the endeavor to fermenting beer, envisioning a more secure and cost-effective means of production. Leveraging AI tools and biosensors, the team embarked on engineering microbes to ferment the medication, marking a significant departure from traditional extraction methods.</p>



<p>Daniel Diaz, a UT postdoctoral scientist leading the Deep Proteins group at the Institute for Foundations of Machine Learning, spearheaded the development of MutComputeX, an AI system tailored to identify protein mutations capable of tripling the production rate of galantamine. Diaz&#8217;s innovative approach involves isolating proteins from daffodils that are responsible for synthesizing the drug and mimicking their functions in a lab setting.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Protein engineering unraveled</h2>



<p>Employing a protein engineering technique, Diaz elucidated the pivotal mutations within daffodil proteins conducive to galantamine production. Drawing parallels to a mathematical function, Diaz explained the AI-based process as akin to solving for y=f(x), wherein proteins act as independent variables (x) and galantamine production as dependent variables (y). This methodology elucidates how protein mutations catalyze galantamine synthesis, paving the way for efficient replication in laboratory settings.</p>



<p>While synthetic methods for galantamine production exist, they are prohibitively expensive. Extracting the compound from daffodils offers a more economically feasible alternative, albeit constrained by the plant&#8217;s growth cycles, exacerbated by climate change. D’Oelsnitz emphasized the urgency of their research in light of these challenges, highlighting the potential of AI-driven fermentation techniques to mitigate production constraints and address the rising demand for Alzheimer’s medications.</p>



<p>UT researchers have forged a path toward enhancing Alzheimer’s medication production through AI-driven innovation. By leveraging advanced computational methods and protein engineering techniques, they have not only streamlined galantamine production but also laid the groundwork for future advancements in bioengineering. As awareness grows surrounding the potential of AI in pharmaceutical manufacturing, the bioengineering community stands poised to capitalize on these transformative technologies.</p>



<p>With this groundbreaking study, UT researchers have not only accelerated the production of Alzheimer’s medication but also set a precedent for leveraging AI in pharmaceutical manufacturing. As the field continues to evolve, the integration of AI-driven solutions promises to revolutionize drug development and production processes, offering hope for more accessible and cost-effective treatments for neurodegenerative diseases.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_UT_Researchers_Utilize_AI_to_Enhance_Alzheimers_Medica_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_UT_Researchers_Utilize_AI_to_Enhance_Alzheimers_Medica_0.jpg"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
