<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:05:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX Presale Gains Momentum Amidst Rising Demand for Bitcoin ETFs and Surging Bitcoin Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/healix-protocols-hlx-presale-gains-momentum-amidst-rising-demand-for-bitcoin-etfs-and-surging-bitcoin-prices/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Guest User]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Corporate Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a world where innovation intersects with opportunity, Healix Protocol emerges as a beacon of transformation in the healthcare sector. As the demand for Bitcoin ETFs skyrockets amidst surging Bitcoin prices, Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX token presale gains momentum, offering investors a unique opportunity to capitalize on the bullish trends in both the cryptocurrency market and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a world where innovation intersects with opportunity, <a href="https://healixprotocol.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Healix Protocol</a> emerges as a beacon of transformation in the healthcare sector. As the demand for Bitcoin ETFs skyrockets amidst surging Bitcoin prices, Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX token presale gains momentum, offering investors a unique opportunity to capitalize on the bullish trends in both the cryptocurrency market and healthcare finance.</p>



<p><strong>Rising Demand for Bitcoin ETFs and Surging Bitcoin Prices</strong></p>



<p>The recent surge in demand for Bitcoin ETFs reflects a growing interest among institutional and retail investors alike to gain exposure to the cryptocurrency market through traditional investment vehicles. Bitcoin ETFs offer investors the convenience and familiarity of investing in cryptocurrencies within the regulated framework of traditional financial markets. Meanwhile, the surging prices of Bitcoin underscore the broader confidence in the long-term viability and potential of cryptocurrencies as a store of value and hedge against inflation. As institutional investors allocate sizable portions of their portfolios to Bitcoin and retail investors flock to the market in search of wealth-building opportunities, the bullish momentum advancing Bitcoin prices shows no signs of slowing down.</p>



<p><strong>Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX Presale: A Gateway to Healthcare Innovation</strong></p>



<p>Amidst the backdrop of rising demand for Bitcoin ETFs and surging Bitcoin prices, Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX token presale emerges as a strategic investment opportunity for investors seeking exposure to both the cryptocurrency market and the transformative potential of the healthcare sector. The HLX token presale not only offers investors the chance to capitalize on the bullish trends in the crypto market but also to support a visionary project that aims to revolutionize healthcare finance through blockchain technology.</p>



<p><strong>Why Invest in Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX Presale?</strong></p>



<p>Investing in <a href="https://healixprotocol.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Healix Protocol&#8217;s HLX presale</a> offers investors the opportunity to participate in a project that addresses real-world challenges in healthcare finance while also benefiting from the bullish trends in the cryptocurrency market. Unlike speculative tokens driven solely by market hype, the HLX token embodies a tangible solution to healthcare finance, backed by a team of experienced professionals and supported by a growing community of believers. By investing in the HLX presale, investors not only stand to gain financial rewards but also contribute to creating a more accessible, transparent, and efficient healthcare system for all.</p>



<p><strong>Capture the opportunity with Healix Protocol</strong></p>



<p>As the demand for Bitcoin ETFs surges and Bitcoin prices reach new highs, the time is ripe for investors to capitalize on the bullish trends in the cryptocurrency market while supporting innovative projects like Healix Protocol. Don&#8217;t miss out on this opportunity to be part of a transformative project that combines the best of both worlds—healthcare innovation and cryptocurrency investment. Join the HLX token presale today and embark on a journey towards a brighter future with Healix Protocol.</p>



<p>Visit Healix website: <a href="https://healixprotocol.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://healixprotocol.com/</a></p>



<p>Join <a href="https://t.me/healixprotocol" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Healix Telegram</a> channel</p>



<p>Follow <a href="https://twitter.com/healixprotocol?s=21&amp;t=WQhFDvd-ChY9CtQvop-K3w" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Healix on X</a></p>



<p>Follow <a href="https://www.instagram.com/healixprotocol/?igsh=azZieDlteWFmYTF0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Healix on Instagram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-98-1200x800-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-98-1200x800-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoin Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; 2033: Is MEME A Wise Investment?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/memecoin-price-prediction-2024-2033/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Palmer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=411686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Memecoin MEME Overview Today’s&#160; Memecoin price is $0.03779, with a 24-hour trading volume of $71,706,296. Memecoin is down 0.11% in the last 24 hours. The current CoinMarketCap ranking is 180, with a live market cap of $439,725,982. It has a circulating supply of 11,678,435,763 MEME coins and a max. Supply of 69,000,000,000 MEME coins. Memecoin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><a href="#1">Memecoin Price Prediction 2024– up to </a><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-admin/post.php?post=411686&amp;action=edit#1">$0.0371</a></li>



<li><a href="#2">Memecoin Price Prediction 2027 – up to </a><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-admin/post.php?post=411686&amp;action=edit#2">$0.1139</a></li>



<li><a href="#3">Memecoin Price Prediction 2030 – up to </a><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-admin/post.php?post=411686&amp;action=edit#3">$0.3266</a></li>



<li><a href="#4">Memecoin Price Prediction 2033 – up to $</a><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-admin/post.php?post=411686&amp;action=edit#4">0.9989</a></li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin MEME Overview</h2>



<p>Today’s&nbsp; Memecoin price is $0.03779, with a 24-hour trading volume of $71,706,296. Memecoin is down 0.11% in the last 24 hours. The current CoinMarketCap ranking is 180, with a live market cap of $439,725,982. It has a circulating supply of 11,678,435,763 MEME coins and a max. Supply of 69,000,000,000 MEME coins.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Analysis: Meme Recovers Above $0.03700 as Bulls Resist The Downtrend</h2>



<ul>
<li>Memecoin price analysis shows an uptrend.</li>



<li>MEME token price has been trading in&nbsp; a bearish trendline but has recently shown signs of a bullish revival</li>



<li>The key resistance level for MEME is $0.03938.</li>
</ul>



<p>The latest memecoin price analysis shows that the popular cryptocurrency, MEME token, has been on an uptrend recently after facing a bearish trendline for several weeks. The coin has shown signs of a bullish revival and could be set to make significant gains. Memecoin is trading at $0.03779 at the time of writing, with a market capitalization of $439 million.</p>



<p>The MEME token has been on retracement in the past few days, forming a double-bottom pattern, which could be bullish. This price action has been confirmed by bullish candlestick patterns, indicating a reversal in the current downtrend. The key resistance level for MEME is $0.03938; if this level is breached, we could see a strong uptrend toward the next resistance.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Analysis 1-day Chart: Meme Forms An Uptrend Following The Bullish Pressure</h3>



<p>The daily chart for MEME/USD shows that the bulls are staging a major comeback. The Bollinger Bands, which measure volatility in the market, have opened up, indicating a potential uptrend for the MEME token. This is further supported by significant increases in volume levels, showing renewed interest from buyers.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/VkKSPeYNWOVBINr4MWikUgdDuYbCw4huHvE7ErsjI4o0gG6U4tHaJ30zikJShrF4vZwNOUFpHlNvVj3UjRoH0yWqhxC7EvOL4Y36FE8J2-wzrIlnItjfS-dymNPoG_FKXUpvTbTe2FN9Nf4YajRF3g" alt="" /></figure>



<p>MEME/USD 1-day price chart; <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3zYjVaxU/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TradingView</a></p>



<p>The Moving Averages also indicate strong bullish momentum, with the 50-day MA crossing above the 200-day MA, forming a bullish crossover pattern. This shows that the overall trend for MEME/USD has shifted upward. The daily chart&#8217;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) also shows a positive outlook for MEME/USD. The RSI is currently at 49.70, in the neutral zone, indicating that there is still room for further gains before it reaches overbought levels.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin price analysis 4-hour chart: Bulls dominate the Meme market; more upside to follow?</h3>



<p>On the 4-hour chart, MEME/USD has formed an ascending triangle pattern. This bullish continuation pattern indicates a potential breakout towards higher levels.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/CbUnL0YwspUJX3oCW21Mo09dawcPamxl9UcBUfuzvzvsHoYY1U8TLRctyJdm-sacxIvTYfATWDg8Ev6u_wJihx2k9YGIqAT2QG_SrK_YG6LoRhkIgNvZM31nPIbtBwpJqpaZAt-7R_u3bB0odE3iiA" alt="" /></figure>



<p>MEME/USD 4-hour price chart; <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/wQfYUhzp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TradingView</a></p>



<p>The Moving Averages also indicate strong bullish momentum, with the 50-day MA crossing above the 200-day MA, forming a bullish crossover pattern. This shows that the overall trend for MEME/USD has shifted upward. The daily chart&#8217;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) also indicates a positive outlook for MEME/USD. The RSI is currently at 55.56, in the neutral zone, indicating that there is still room for further gains before it reaches overbought levels.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What To Expect From Memecoin Price&nbsp; Analysis</h3>



<p>The Memecoin price analysis shows a potential bullish revival for the Memecoin price, between $0.03747 and $0.03938. The technical indicators also support this uptrend, with bullish crossovers and ascending triangle patterns. The bulls are gaining control of MEME coin prices, making it an exciting time for investors to watch this popular cryptocurrency&#8217;s performance in the market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Memecoin Price Prediction 2024-2033 by Cryptopolitan</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="752" height="452" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/image-86.png" alt="" class="wp-image-443101" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/image-86.png 752w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/image-86-300x180.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 752px) 100vw, 752px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum</td><td>Average</td><td>Maximum&nbsp;</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>$0.0296</td><td>$0.0308</td><td>$0.0371</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>$0.0450</td><td>$0.0465</td><td>$0.0527</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>$0.0651</td><td>$0.0670</td><td>$0.0776</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>$0.0940</td><td>$0.0973</td><td>$0.1139</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>$0.1361</td><td>$0.1400</td><td>$0.1630</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>$0.1906</td><td>$0.1976</td><td>$0.2314</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>$0.2636</td><td>$0.2735</td><td>$0.3266</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>$0.3903</td><td>$0.4012</td><td>$0.4621</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>$0.5686</td><td>$0.5886</td><td>$0.6730</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>$0.8399</td><td>$0.8634</td><td>$0.9989</td></tr></tbody></table><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Memecoin price prediction</figcaption></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to the technical analysis of Memecoi prices expected in 2024, the minimum cost of MEME will be $0.0296. The maximum level that the MEME price can reach is $0.0371. The average trading price is expected around $0.0308.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>Memecoin price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $0.0450 in 2025. As per our findings, the MEME price could reach a maximum possible level of $0.0527 with the average forecast price of $0.0465.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>Based on the price fluctuations of Memecoi at the beginning of 2026, crypto experts expect the average MEME rate of $0.0670. Its minimum and maximum prices can be expected at $0.0651 and at $0.0776, respectively.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>After the analysis of the prices of Memecoin in previous years, it is assumed that in 2027, the minimum price of MEME will be around $0.0940. The maximum expected MEME price may be around $0.1139. On average, the trading price might be $0.0973 in 2027.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>As per the forecast and technical analysis, In 2028 the price of Memecoin is expected to reach at a minimum price value of $0.1361. The MEME price can reach a maximum price value of $0.1630 with the average value of $0.1400.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Based on the technical analysis by cryptocurrency experts regarding the prices of Memecoin, in 2029, MEME is expected to have the following minimum and maximum prices: about $0.1906 and $0.2314, respectively. The average expected trading cost is $0.1976.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>The price of Memecoin is predicted to reach at a minimum value of $0.1906 in 2029. The Memecoin price could reach a maximum value of $0.2314 with the average trading price of $0.1976 throughout 2029.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin (MEME) Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of MEME, In 2030 the price of Memecoin is predicted to reach at a minimum level of $0.2636. The MEME price can reach a maximum level of $0.3266 with the average trading price of $0.2735.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Forecast 2031</h4>



<p>The experts in the field of cryptocurrency have analyzed the prices of Memecoin and their fluctuations during the previous years. It is assumed that in 2031, the minimum MEME price might drop to $0.3903, while its maximum can reach $0.4621. On average, the trading cost will be around $0.4012.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin (MEME) Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>Memecoin price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $0.5686 in 2032. As per our findings, the MEME price could reach a maximum possible level of $0.6730 with the average forecast price of $0.5886.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of MEME, In 2033 the price of Memecoin is forecasted to be at around a minimum value of $0.8399. The Memecoin price value can reach a maximum of $0.9989 with the average trading value of $0.8634.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Memecoin Price Prediction by CoinCodex</strong></h3>



<p>The Memecoin price forecast by Coincodex suggests that the MEME coin will drop by -2.60% and reach $ 0.026647 by January 7, 2024. According to the technical indicators, the current sentiment is Bearish while the Fear &amp; Greed Index is showing 71 (Greed). Memecoin recorded 12/30 (40%) green days with 12.66% price volatility over the last 30 days. Based on their Memecoin forecast, it&#8217;s now a bad time to buy Memecoin.</p>



<p>Based on the historical price movements of Memecoin and the BTC halving cycles, the yearly low Memecoin price prediction for 2024 is estimated at $ 0.024312. Meanwhile, the price of Memecoin is predicted to reach as high as $ 0.038052 next year. Using the same basis, here is the Memecoin price prediction for each year until 2030.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Memecoin Price Prediction by DigitalCoinPrice</strong></h3>



<p>According to the Memecoin price predictions by Coincodex, there is an anticipated fluctuation in the value of Memecoin in the coming years. By 2025, the price is expected to oscillate between a yearly low of $0.023742 and a high of $0.040555. This trend of volatility and growth is projected to continue, with 2026 seeing potential highs of $0.092991 and 2027 with a maximum of $0.051937. </p>



<p>The predictions for subsequent years indicate a steady increase, with 2028 and 2029 experiencing highs of $0.071680 and $0.073521, respectively. By 2030 and 2031, Memecoin could reach highs of $0.132364 and $0.094669, respectively, suggesting a significant potential for growth compared to its current price, with a projected increase of up to 263.03% by 2031 if it reaches the upper price target.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What is Memecoin MEME</h2>



<p>Memecoin (MEME) token is a native cryptocurrency of the Memeland ecosystem, developed by 9GAG. Memecoin (MEME) presents an intriguing case in the cryptocurrency landscape, primarily because it openly declares having no intrinsic value or functionality and does not promise any form of financial return, profit, or dividend.</p>



<p>Despite this straightforward admission, MEME has garnered substantial attention and investment within the cryptocurrency community. This interest reflects a cultural phenomenon in the digital asset world, where community interest and the cultural significance of memes rather than traditional financial metrics or utility can drive perceived value and engagement.</p>



<p>The Memeland ecosystem, closely associated with MEME, features a series of unique PFP (Profile Picture) collections, each with its thematic focus and community value. These collections include &#8220;You the real MVP,&#8221; featuring 420 gold trophies as a token of appreciation for the community; &#8220;The Potatoz,&#8221; a set of 9,999 meme and pop culture-inspired PFPs that function as the base-level membership of Memeland; and &#8220;The Captainz,&#8221; consisting of 9,999 PFPs with traits inspired by pirates and pop culture, representing the premier-level membership.</p>



<p>These collections serve as digital collectibles and play a role in the governance of the Memeland DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization), contributing to the decision-making process and growth of the Memeland ecosystem. The Captainz, in particular, have first access to new developments, including the Memeland metaverse project, Treasure Islandz.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Price History</h2>



<p>Memecoin was launched on 28th October by the renowned internet humor platform 9GAG and has quickly become a significant player in the meme coin market. The Memecoin garnered immense popularity through a unique launch strategy involving a fire sale and strategic social media airdrops to cultivate a robust and dedicated community. This approach proved highly successful, with the fire sale raising over $11 million and selling more than 11.4 billion MEME tokens at $0.001 each, representing a 150% surge from what the team initially planned.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://images.surferseo.art/e4734bc9-a0a9-48b6-b4c9-c8dadd3f0fd0.png" alt="" /></figure>



<p>Looking at its price history since 27th October 2020, MEME saw its first price pump on the same day, reaching a high of $0.02868. The MEME token price remained above $0.0020 until 7 November, when a minor pullback occurred below the $0.0200 level. Memecoin continued trading around the $0.020 level, with minor fluctuations, until the price spiked again on 4 January, reaching an all-time high of $0.04075 on November 15th.</p>



<p>Memecoin recorded an all-time low of $0.0751 on 14 January, following a significant market correction. This dip was short-lived, and the token&#8217;s price quickly rebounded. The memecoin has been trading at around $0.0268 for the past few days.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on Memecoin Token</h2>



<p>Memecoin (MEME), post its fire sale, has witnessed remarkable developments in the crypto market, notably with its inclusion on Binance’s spot market and the Binance Launchpool. This listing and its introduction on other major exchanges like MEXC, BitMEX, and Bybit significantly boosted its visibility and trading volume.</p>



<p>Despite an initial 36% drop in price following the fire sale, MEME has shown a strong recovery, surging by 128% and experiencing a 60% increase in the last 24 hours. This growth is largely attributed to speculative interest and robust community engagement, as evidenced by its substantial social media following. Currently, Memecoin ranks as the fifth-largest meme coin globally by <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/memes/">market</a> capitalization and leads as the most-traded meme coin in daily volume.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Memecoin Tokenomics</h2>



<p>Memecoin (MEME), as per its <a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" href="https://www.memecoin.org/whitepaper">tokenomics</a>, has a total supply of 69 billion MEME tokens. The token distribution is structured in a phased manner, with the first 2.7% of the total supply, amounting to approximately 1.863 billion tokens, becoming available on October 27. Following this initial release, the remaining tokens will be gradually unlocked over eighteen months. This phased approach to token distribution is often adopted in the cryptocurrency space to manage supply and potentially stabilize the token&#8217;s market value over time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Memecoin cryptocurrency has exhibited strong potential for growth over the past month, with its price stabilizing and steadily increasing. With several price predictions by reputable sources, it is evident that Memecoin has the potential to continue its upward trajectory in the coming years, making it a promising investment opportunity for those interested in cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>If investors continue to show interest and support for this meme-based digital asset, there is a high likelihood that Memecoin will continue to grow and potentially reach new heights. However, as with any investment, it is essential to research and carefully consider all factors before making financial decisions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/DreamShaper_v7_Memecoin_MEME_Pri-2.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/DreamShaper_v7_Memecoin_MEME_Pri-2.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRPL considers a Canary Network amidst technical challenges</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/xrpl-considers-a-canary-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutuma Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The XRP Ledger (XRPL) discussions have emerged among developers concerning the establishment of a Canary Network. This initiative, spearheaded by Wietse Wind, co-founder of Xumm Wallet, seeks to introduce a reliable testing environment for the layer-1 blockchain. Wind&#8217;s proposal comes as a response to a recent incident where the launch of an Automated Market Maker [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/circle-and-xrp-ledger-community-engage-in-talks-over-potential-usdc-support/"> XRP Ledger</a> (XRPL) discussions have emerged among developers concerning the establishment of a Canary Network. This initiative, spearheaded by Wietse Wind, co-founder of Xumm Wallet, seeks to introduce a reliable testing environment for the layer-1 blockchain. Wind&#8217;s proposal comes as a response to a recent incident where the launch of an Automated Market Maker (AMM) feature on the XRPL encountered a critical bug, leading to operational disruptions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The necessity of a testing ground</strong></h2>



<p>The idea for a Canary Network underscores the importance of a dedicated space where developers can thoroughly test upgrades and products before they are implemented on the XRP Ledger mainnet. Wind argues that such a platform could prevent technical issues, like the one that affected the AMM feature, from impacting the live environment. He envisions a network that replicates the mainnet in every aspect, ensuring tests reflect real-world conditions. Additionally, the network would feature its assets, including native tokens and stablecoins, to facilitate comprehensive testing.</p>



<p>The push for a <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/kusama-the-canary-network-polkadot/">Canary Network</a> aligns the XRPL with practices adopted by other blockchain ecosystems, such as Ethereum, Flare, and Songbird. Ethereum, for example, utilizes multiple testnets, including Goerli and Sepolia, to vet major updates before they go live. This systematic approach to testing and implementation has enabled Ethereum to execute upgrades smoothly, as demonstrated by the recent success of the Dencun Upgrade. Wind&#8217;s proposal suggests a similar strategy that could mitigate risks associated with deploying new features on the XRPL.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>XRPL community anticipates an enhanced testing environment</strong></h2>



<p>A crucial aspect of the proposed Canary Network is its emphasis on decentralization. Wind believes that for the network to serve its purpose effectively, it must engage a broad spectrum of stakeholders within the XRPL ecosystem. This includes traders, developers, and other key participants who can contribute to the network&#8217;s robustness through active testing and feedback. The objective is to create a collaborative environment that enhances the security and functionality of the XRPL through collective effort.</p>



<p><br>The<a href="https://twitter.com/WietseWind/status/1771998717832278162?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> call for a Canary Network</a> by a prominent Ripple developer highlights a proactive approach to addressing technical vulnerabilities within the XRPL. By fostering a comprehensive testing environment, the initiative aims to bolster the blockchain&#8217;s resilience against potential glitches. As discussions about this proposal advance, the XRPL community anticipates the development of a platform that not only mirrors the mainnet but also enriches the ecosystem through enhanced decentralization and stakeholder involvement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/DALL·E-2023-12-09-16.09.14-A-digital-art-concept-representing-the-XRPL-XRP-Ledger-featuring-a-futuristic-abstract-design.-The-image-should-include-digital-elements-such-as-g.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/DALL·E-2023-12-09-16.09.14-A-digital-art-concept-representing-the-XRPL-XRP-Ledger-featuring-a-futuristic-abstract-design.-The-image-should-include-digital-elements-such-as-g.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are spot Bitcoin ETFs dying slowly? &#8211; What is going on?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/are-spot-bitcoin-etfs-dying-slowly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency scene is currently witnessing an unexpected twist in the tale of Bitcoin ETFs, which had once enjoyed a meteoric rise in the financial markets. Following the green light from U.S. regulators for 11 new Bitcoin ETFs in January, there was a reversal of fortune this week as we saw a significant outflow of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The cryptocurrency scene is currently witnessing an unexpected twist in the tale of Bitcoin ETFs, which had once enjoyed a meteoric rise in the financial markets. Following the green light from <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/half-of-us-in-recession-dollars-depreciation/" data-type="post" data-id="501206">U.S.</a> regulators for 11 new Bitcoin ETFs in January, there was a reversal of fortune this week as we saw a significant outflow of funds. Observers and investors alike are now on their toes, wondering if this $850 million departure is a mere hiccup or a forewarning of a deeper downturn in the world&#8217;s premier cryptocurrency.<a href="https://archive.is/LDTHl#selection-2241.0-2244.0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<p>After a bullish run that saw Bitcoin&#8217;s value soar to a record $73,000, the recent price dip has seemingly doused the flames of investor enthusiasm. This week, Bitcoin&#8217;s price took a dive to as low as $60,760, causing many to second-guess their investment strategies. James Butterfill from CoinShares pointed out, “People have looked at how much the price of bitcoin has fallen and they’ve decided to hold off, nobody wants to catch a falling knife.”</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">The Tug of War in ETF Land</h3>



<p>While BlackRock, the global leader in asset management, boasted inflows of $576 million this week, its competitors weren&#8217;t as fortunate, witnessing minimal new investments. However, Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF, which transitioned from a trust in January, is facing a stiff headwind due to its higher management fees, leading to sustained withdrawals. Ilan Solot of Marex chimed in, saying, “We’re approaching a dead zone for these ETF products where the initial frenzy of pent-up capital has come in already.”</p>



<p>Adding another layer to this complex scenario is the upcoming Bitcoin halving event in April. This quadrennial occurrence, which cuts the miners’ rewards in half, is anticipated to have a long-term bullish impact on Bitcoin&#8217;s price, despite the current climate of uncertainty.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">A Battle of Titans</h3>



<p>In the meantime, a fascinating race is unfolding between BlackRock and Grayscale. With BlackRock&#8217;s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF now holding 238,500 Bitcoins and enjoying daily inflows of around $274 million, it&#8217;s rapidly closing the gap on Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin Trust ETF, which currently holds an estimated 350,252 Bitcoins. The latter, however, has been experiencing daily outflows of roughly $277 million over the last fortnight.</p>



<p>Should the current trend persist, BlackRock is poised to dethrone Grayscale as the world&#8217;s top institutional holder of Bitcoin by April 11. This forecasted shift has even caught the attention of crypto influencers like George Tung, who speculate that BlackRock&#8217;s ascendancy could occur within a mere two weeks.</p>



<p>Interestingly, the GBTC experienced its largest daily outflow on record on March 18, totaling $643 million. Despite this, senior Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas believes that the tide of outflows, significantly influenced by the bankruptcies of crypto firms like Genesis and Digital Currency Group, could soon subside.</p>



<p>Moreover, BlackRock&#8217;s recent overtaking of MicroStrategy in Bitcoin holdings marks another milestone in the ETF saga. Following an additional purchase of 9,000 Bitcoins on March 19, MicroStrategy now holds 214,246 Bitcoins, yet finds itself outpaced by BlackRock&#8217;s aggressive acquisition strategy.</p>



<p>As we navigate through this tumultuous phase, the dynamics between inflows and outflows, along with the impending halving event, paint a picture of a sector at a crossroads. The Bitcoin ETF landscape is evolving, with each development offering a new perspective on the future of cryptocurrency investments.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-04.06.12-Visualize-the-inquiry-into-whether-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-are-gradually-declining-asking-_What-is-going-on__-without-using-text.-Create-an-image-that-cap.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-04.06.12-Visualize-the-inquiry-into-whether-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-are-gradually-declining-asking-_What-is-going-on__-without-using-text.-Create-an-image-that-cap.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s economy shows no signs of recovery &#8211; IMF has a suggestion</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/chinas-economy-shows-no-signs-of-recovery/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The economic engine of China, once roaring, seems to be sputtering these days. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) chief, Kristalina Georgieva, threw down the gauntlet, presenting China with a stark choice at a recent international business meet in Beijing. It&#8217;s high time, she argued, for China to ditch the old playbook and champion pro-market reforms [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The economic engine of China, once roaring, seems to be sputtering these days. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) chief, Kristalina Georgieva, threw down the gauntlet, presenting China with a stark choice at a recent international business meet in Beijing. It&#8217;s high time, she argued, for China to ditch the old playbook and champion pro-market reforms to spark growth. This comes against the backdrop of a global economy that, while toughing out recent shocks, is bracing for a period of unimpressive growth due to a cocktail of low productivity and towering debt.<a href="https://archive.is/tjERZ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">A Fork in the Road for China</h2>



<p>At the heart of the discussion is China&#8217;s current crossroads situation. The country can either cling to the strategies that fueled its meteoric rise but now falter under new global realities, or it can pivot towards a future carved out by embracing market reforms. This debate unfolds as <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/china-surpasses-u-s-in-producing-ai-talent/" data-type="post" data-id="500493">China</a> hosts its premier international business conference, with heavyweights from Apple to ExxonMobil in attendance, suggesting the world is watching closely.</p>



<p>China&#8217;s Premier Li Qiang kicked off the forum with promises of easier market access for foreign companies and boosting domestic consumption. Yet, these assurances come at a time when China faces oversupply risks in several sectors, potentially leading to a flood of cheap exports on the global stage. Despite setting an optimistic growth target of 5% for the year, the shadows of a real estate downturn and demographic challenges loom large, threatening to drag the economy further down.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Roadmap to High-Quality Growth</h2>



<p>The term &#8220;high-quality growth&#8221; isn&#8217;t new to the Chinese leadership&#8217;s lexicon, but its invocation by the IMF&#8217;s Georgieva underscores a shared vision for China&#8217;s economic evolution. She posits that a suite of pro-market reforms could significantly bolster the nation&#8217;s GDP over the next decade and a half. From tackling the real estate glut to revamping the pension system, the suggested reforms aim at not just economic expansion but enhancing the quality of growth, focusing on human capital and leveling the playing field between private and state-run entities.</p>



<p>On the global stage, however, China&#8217;s path is fraught with challenges. The country&#8217;s commerce minister, Wang Wentao, has painted a grim picture of the international trade environment, marked by rising protectionism and geopolitical strife. Yet, China&#8217;s &#8220;new three&#8221; industries—electric vehicles, solar energy, and lithium batteries—are booming, signifying a strategic pivot towards sectors that could define the future of global energy and transportation.</p>



<p>However, this shift hasn&#8217;t been without its critics. The West, particularly the EU and the US, is on edge over the potential market disruption caused by cheap Chinese exports, leading to calls for protective tariffs and anti-subsidy probes. These tensions underscore a broader conflict between China&#8217;s state-driven economic model and the market-driven approaches of the West, with neither side showing signs of backing down.</p>



<p>In essence, China&#8217;s economic trajectory is at a pivotal moment. The choices made today—whether to double down on past strategies or embrace reform—will not only determine the country&#8217;s future but also reshape global trade and economic landscapes. With the IMF laying out a path for reform, the ball is in China&#8217;s court to navigate these turbulent waters, balancing domestic imperatives with global responsibilities. The road to recovery and sustained growth is complex, requiring a nuanced approach to policy-making that balances short-term needs with long-term visions for a prosperous, equitable global economy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-04.02.47-Visualize-the-scenario-where-Chinas-economy-shows-no-signs-of-recovery-and-the-IMF-has-a-suggestion-without-using-text.-Create-an-image-that-captur.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-04.02.47-Visualize-the-scenario-where-Chinas-economy-shows-no-signs-of-recovery-and-the-IMF-has-a-suggestion-without-using-text.-Create-an-image-that-captur.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Siemens and NVIDIA to Innovate Sustainable Shipbuilding with AI-driven Digital Twins</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/siemens-and-nvidia-ai-driven-digital-twins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital twins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Siemens]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501408</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Siemens, a global leader in industrial software, is intensifying its partnership with NVIDIA, a renowned provider of accelerated computing solutions, to advance digital twinning capabilities and propel the industrial metaverse forward.&#160; Siemens-NVIDIA Collaboration Redefines Industrial Visualization and AI Integration The collaboration between Siemens and NVIDIA represents a significant stride towards revolutionizing industrial processes through immersive [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Siemens, a global leader in industrial software, is intensifying its partnership with<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/nvidia-discloses-investment-in-soundhound-ai/"> NVIDIA</a>, a renowned provider of accelerated computing solutions, to advance digital twinning capabilities and propel the industrial metaverse forward.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Siemens-NVIDIA Collaboration Redefines Industrial Visualization and AI Integration</h2>



<p>The collaboration between Siemens and NVIDIA represents a significant stride towards revolutionizing industrial processes through immersive visualization and generative AI techniques.&nbsp;</p>



<p>By integrating NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs into the Siemens Xcelerator platform, the partnership aims to amplify the utilization of AI-driven digital twin technology across diverse industries.</p>



<p>During a demonstration at the NVIDIA GTC, Siemens and NVIDIA showcased the remarkable potential of generative AI in rendering complex data with unparalleled realism. This innovation empowers stakeholders to interact with digital twins in ways that closely resemble real-world experiences, enabling deeper insights and facilitating more informed decision-making processes.</p>



<p>Roland Busch, President and CEO of Siemens AG, highlighted the profound impact of this collaboration on product design, manufacturing, and service operations. He emphasized the critical role played by accelerated computing, generative AI, and Omniverse integration in propelling advancements within the Siemens Xcelerator portfolio.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Ultimately, this partnership is poised to shape the future landscape of industrial software by driving innovation and efficiency across various sectors.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Enhanced product lifecycle management with real-time digital twins</h2>



<p>Siemens is set to launch a new product later this year for Teamcenter X, its cloud-based Product Lifecycle Management (PLM) software. Powered by NVIDIA Omniverse technologies, this offering will empower engineering teams to create intuitive, photorealistic, real-time, and physics-based digital twins. By eliminating workflow inefficiencies and errors, it streamlines the product development process and enhances collaboration among stakeholders.</p>



<p>The integration of generative AI expedites tasks related to photorealistic renderings, such as defining materials and lighting environments. What once took days can now be accomplished within hours, significantly accelerating the pace of innovation. Moreover, by contextualizing engineering data within the digital twin, Siemens enables stakeholders across departments, from sales and marketing to decision-makers and customers, to gain deeper insights into product appearance and functionality.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Real-time visualization for complex engineering projects</h2>



<p>One notable application of this collaboration is exemplified through the partnership with HD Hyundai, a sustainable shipbuilder specializing in ammonia- and hydrogen-powered vessels. HD Hyundai faces the challenge of managing massive engineering datasets, with ships comprising over seven million discrete parts.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The photorealistic nature of the visualization enhances communication and collaboration among team members and stakeholders. Complex engineering concepts become more accessible and easier to understand when presented in a visually compelling format. This fosters greater alignment and synergy within the project team, leading to improved efficiency and ultimately, a higher-quality end product.</p>



<p>Leveraging the new product developed in collaboration with NVIDIA, HD Hyundai can seamlessly unify and visualize these intricate datasets, facilitating interactive exploration and informed decision-making throughout the shipbuilding process.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Pioneering innovation in industrial visualization and sustainability</h2>



<p>The integration of real-time, photorealistic visualization capabilities enables HD Hyundai to navigate the complexities of ship design with enhanced clarity and efficiency. By harnessing the power of NVIDIA Omniverse and Siemens Xcelerator, HD Hyundai advances its sustainability initiatives and drives innovation within the maritime industry.</p>



<p>The collaboration between Siemens and NVIDIA signifies a significant step towards realizing the potential of digital twinning technology in shaping the future of industrial processes. By combining accelerated computing, generative AI, and immersive visualization capabilities, the partners empower organizations to unlock new levels of productivity, efficiency, and innovation across various sectors.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As Siemens prepares to introduce the groundbreaking product for Teamcenter X later this year, the trajectory towards the industrial metaverse becomes increasingly tangible, offering boundless opportunities for digital transformation and growth.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Siemens_and_NVIDIA_to_Innovate_Sustainable_Shipbuildin_0-2.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Siemens_and_NVIDIA_to_Innovate_Sustainable_Shipbuildin_0-2.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI&#8217;s Impact on Cloud Networking: Revolutionizing Performance Demands</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ais-impact-on-cloud-networking/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James Kinoti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Innovators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501411</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The advent of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in cloud computing heralds a new era of demands for network performance. As AI workloads surge into the cloud, seamless connectivity to vast datasets becomes paramount.&#160; The essence of AI operations relies heavily on accessing and processing data swiftly, often distributed across various servers within or outside the cloud [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The advent of Artificial Intelligence (<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/british-military-face-ai-integration-hurdles/">AI</a>) in cloud computing heralds a new era of demands for network performance. As AI workloads surge into the cloud, seamless connectivity to vast datasets becomes paramount.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The essence of AI operations relies heavily on accessing and processing data swiftly, often distributed across various servers within or outside the cloud environment. Consequently, cloud networks face the challenge of delivering unparalleled performance levels to support these AI workloads efficiently.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The evolving landscape of cloud networking</h2>



<p>In response to the burgeoning requirements of AI, cloud networking solutions are evolving rapidly. Traditionally, cloud providers have offered &#8220;direct connect&#8221; services to bolster network speed and reliability, particularly for high-performance tasks such as video streaming and cloud desktops.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, conventional solutions may fall short of AI workloads demanding exceptional network performance. Integrating hardware-level optimizations, such as Data Processing Units (DPUs), emerges as a crucial strategy. Notably, companies like Nvidia spearhead innovations in networking hardware tailored explicitly for <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/the-conundrum-of-open-source-ai/">AI</a> applications.</p>



<p>Previously relegated to large enterprises with intricate cloud infrastructures, direct connect services are poised to witness broader adoption. Smaller organizations, keen on harnessing the power of cloud-based AI workflows, are increasingly turning to direct connects to optimize network performance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Navigating egress costs: A key consideration for cost optimization</h2>



<p>As AI workloads increase in the cloud, businesses must grapple with the implications of heightened egress fees. Cloud providers typically levy charges for data exiting their networks, potentially escalating networking expenses. Consequently, adept management of egress costs becomes imperative for effective cloud cost optimization strategies.</p>



<p>AI workloads exhibit fluctuating network consumption patterns, characterized by intermittent bursts of high-volume data transfers during training phases. Cloud networking solutions must adapt to accommodate these dynamic demands efficiently. The ability to scale network resources dynamically in response to varying workloads emerges as a critical aspect of network performance management.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Navigating the cloud networking terrain</h2>



<p>To harness the full potential of the cloud for hosting AI workloads, businesses must fine-tune their cloud networking strategies. This entails leveraging advanced networking services and hardware optimizations while optimizing cloud cost structures and managing network performance effectively. While the solutions in this domain continue to evolve, staying abreast of developments in cloud networking remains imperative for businesses venturing into AI deployment in the cloud.</p>



<p>As AI becomes increasingly intertwined with cloud computing, the landscape of cloud networking undergoes a profound transformation. The imperative for delivering exceptional network performance to support AI workloads necessitates innovative approaches to cloud networking solutions.&nbsp;</p>



<p>From embracing direct connect services to navigating egress costs and accommodating fluctuating network consumption, businesses must navigate this evolving terrain strategically. Optimizing cloud networking strategies emerges as a pivotal endeavor in leveraging the cloud for AI deployments, demanding a nuanced understanding of evolving technologies and cost optimization frameworks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_AIs_Impact_on_Cloud_Networking_Revolutionizing_Perform_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_AIs_Impact_on_Cloud_Networking_Revolutionizing_Perform_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shibarium hits new TVL high with DAMN coin launch</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/shibarium-hits-new-tvl-high-with-damn-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutuma Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BONE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shibarium]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu ecosystem&#8217;s layer-2 blockchain, Shibarium, has witnessed a new all-time high in its total value locked (TVL). The platform&#8217;s TVL has soared to an impressive $3.87 million. This surge marks a notable milestone, considering Shibarium&#8217;s TVL hovered below $1 million for the majority of the year. The recent increase in TVL reflects a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/whales-move-half-a-trillion-shiba-inu/"> Shiba Inu</a> ecosystem&#8217;s layer-2 blockchain, Shibarium, has witnessed a new all-time high in its total value locked (TVL). The platform&#8217;s TVL has soared to an impressive $3.87 million. This surge marks a notable milestone, considering Shibarium&#8217;s TVL hovered below $1 million for the majority of the year. The recent increase in TVL reflects a robust upward trajectory, showcasing the network&#8217;s growing adoption and investor interest.</p>



<p>The catalyst for this remarkable growth stems from the launch of the DAMN meme coin on WoofSwap, a decentralized exchange operating on Shibarium. DAMN&#8217;s introduction to the market on March 18 led to a dramatic price increase of over 523% in just three days. This event significantly contributed to the enhancement of WoofSwap&#8217;s TVL, which now stands at $2.46 million. This represents an increase of 9,292% over the previous week, underscoring the substantial impact of new projects on the network&#8217;s valuation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Shibarium TVL soars with new DeFi projects</strong></h2>



<p>Several elements have played a role in the accelerated growth of <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Shibarium" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Shibarium&#8217;s TVL</a>. Aside from the successful debut of DAMN, the broader crypto market&#8217;s relief rally has also been beneficial. After surpassing the $1 million mark in February, the network&#8217;s TVL maintained a steady level above this threshold. However, it recently experienced a sharp rise, escalating to $3.38 million from $1.43 million recorded the day before. This surge continued, bringing the current TVL to $3.87 million.</p>



<p>The introduction of new decentralized finance (DeFi) projects on Shibarium is anticipated to propel the network&#8217;s TVL further. For instance, K9 Finance, an upcoming liquid staking platform on Shibarium, aims to increase the network&#8217;s TVL by 50X. Such initiatives signal a promising future for Shibarium, potentially elevating the total value locked to $193.5 million. This optimistic outlook underscores the dynamic and evolving nature of the DeFi sector, where innovative projects continually attract investment and interest.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>SHIB and BONE fuel Shibarium&#8217;s TVL growth</strong></h2>



<p>The Shiba Inu ecosystem tokens, including SHIB and BONE, have experienced modest gains since March 22, contributing to the positive momentum within the Shibarium network. The community&#8217;s enthusiasm and the strategic launch of new tokens and projects play a crucial role in the network&#8217;s TVL growth. WoofSwap, closely followed by MARSWAP in terms of TVL, exemplifies the vibrant activity and diversity of projects within the Shibarium ecosystem. With $810,942 in TVL, MARSWAP is another significant contributor to the ecosystem&#8217;s strength.</p>



<p>The Shibarium network&#8217;s recent achievements highlight the importance of strategic project launches and community support in driving the value and adoption of blockchain platforms. As Shibarium continues to expand and attract new DeFi projects, its TVL is likely to reach new heights, further establishing its position in the cryptocurrency market. This growth trajectory not only benefits the Shiba Inu ecosystem but also contributes to the broader DeFi landscape, offering new opportunities for investors and developers alike.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/DALL·E-2024-02-26-14.35.32-Create-an-image-featuring-a-Shiba-Inu-dog-as-the-central-figure-symbolizing-the-Shiba-Inu-cryptocurrency.-The-Shiba-Inu-should-be-depicted-in-a-heroi.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/DALL·E-2024-02-26-14.35.32-Create-an-image-featuring-a-Shiba-Inu-dog-as-the-central-figure-symbolizing-the-Shiba-Inu-cryptocurrency.-The-Shiba-Inu-should-be-depicted-in-a-heroi.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch up on Asia&#8217;s top crypto stories of the week</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/catch-up-on-asias-top-crypto-stories/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asia crypto hub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto recap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501401</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Asia&#8217;s crypto scene has been buzzing with activity, packed with a mixture of warnings, regulatory shifts, and market dynamics that could give any crypto enthusiast a run for their money. This week, we&#8217;re diving deep into the heart of the continent&#8217;s digital currency developments, unearthing the stories that have stakeholders on the edge of their [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Asia&#8217;s crypto scene has been buzzing with activity, packed with a mixture of warnings, regulatory shifts, and market dynamics that could give any crypto enthusiast a run for their money. This week, we&#8217;re diving deep into the heart of the continent&#8217;s digital currency developments, unearthing the stories that have stakeholders on the edge of their seats. With the crypto world&#8217;s ever-evolving industry, staying updated is not just a necessity; it&#8217;s a survival tactic.<a href="https://wublock.substack.com/p/asias-weekly-top10-crypto-news-mar-0d1?r=jbpop&amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;utm_medium=web&amp;triedRedirect=true" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Regulatory Warnings and Legal Battles</h2>



<p>Starting off with Hong Kong, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) has stepped in to clear the air around the misuse of its name in the crypto sphere. Some opportunistic entities have been misleading the public, pretending to be part of the prestigious Hong Kong Dollar Digital Pilot Scheme. The HKMA was quick to clamp down on these claims, emphasizing that legitimate companies involved would never seek public funds under the scheme&#8217;s guise. Similarly, the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) flagged suspicious websites masquerading under the name &#8220;KKR Global,&#8221; luring unsuspecting victims into a web of fraudulent crypto investments.</p>



<p>Crossing over to South Korea, the crypto exchange scene is witnessing an unusual trend with Tether (USDT). The premium rates for <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/usdt-stablecoin-is-now-on-celo-blockchain/" data-type="post" data-id="482376">USDT</a> have soared, particularly on platforms like Upbit and Bithumb, drawing attention to a possible surge in demand or speculative trading activities in the region.</p>



<p>In legal arenas, Terraform&#8217;s co-founder Do Kwon finds himself a free man, albeit confined to the Balkans, as he navigates through a maze of international criminal charges. Meanwhile, Three Arrows Capital&#8217;s founder Kyle Davies is playing a game of geographical chess, attempting to avoid a fate similar to his colleague by staying clear of Singapore.</p>



<p>On a more personal note, Azuki&#8217;s founder Zagabond, chose an event in Shanghai to share his roots, born in Harbin, China. This revelation comes at a time when the Eastern and Western crypto communities seem more eager than ever to bridge their differences and unite under the banner of blockchain and digital currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Market Movements and Strategic Shifts</h2>



<p>The narrative also shifts towards the dynamics of the market and strategic decisions by key players. Hong Kong-listed Yuxing Technology made a significant pivot in its investment strategy by converting its Bitcoin and Ethereum holdings into stablecoins, amounting to a hefty $14.4 million. This move reflects a cautious yet optimistic outlook towards the stability offered by digital currencies like USDC and USDT, amidst the volatile nature of the crypto market.</p>



<p>OKX, a major player in the crypto exchange domain, announced its withdrawal from the Indian market, citing regulatory challenges. This decision underscores the broader regulatory uncertainty and the need for clear guidelines that can foster a healthy crypto ecosystem across Asia.</p>



<p>Victims of sophisticated scams have also been a focal point, with reports of individuals being lured into &#8220;pig killing&#8221; schemes and fraudulent legal advice, culminating in substantial financial losses. These incidents serve as a stark reminder of the dark underbelly of the crypto world, where vigilance and due diligence are paramount.</p>



<p>In the grand scheme of crypto regulations, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) has thrown in its two cents, urging Pakistan to widen its tax net to include capital gains from cryptocurrency investments. This advice is part of a larger dialogue with the country, aimed at securing financial stability and ensuring a comprehensive tax regime that captures the evolving nature of digital currencies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-04.02.37-Visualize-the-concept-of-catching-up-on-Asias-top-crypto-stories-of-the-week-without-using-text.-Create-an-image-that-symbolizes-the-gathering-of-in.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-04.02.37-Visualize-the-concept-of-catching-up-on-Asias-top-crypto-stories-of-the-week-without-using-text.-Create-an-image-that-symbolizes-the-gathering-of-in.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Financial guru Robert Kiyosaki to add 10 Bitcoin to portfolio by April</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/financial-guru-robert-kiyosaki-to-add-10-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutuma Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robert kiyosaki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki, the financial literacy educator and author of the best-selling book “Rich Dad Poor Dad,” announced plans to purchase 10 Bitcoin (BTC) by April. The decision underscores his growing admiration for Bitcoin as an investment vehicle. Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s investment, valued at approximately $670,000 based on current prices, highlights his belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s potential. He [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bullish-on-silver-amidst-rising-demand/">Robert Kiyosaki</a>, the financial literacy educator and author of the best-selling book “Rich Dad Poor Dad,” announced plans to purchase 10 Bitcoin (BTC) by April. The decision underscores his growing admiration for Bitcoin as an investment vehicle. Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s investment, valued at approximately $670,000 based on current prices, highlights his belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s potential. He has consistently recommended the cryptocurrency for portfolio diversification away from the U.S. Dollar.</p>



<p>Kiyosaki&#8217;s move comes in anticipation of Bitcoin&#8217;s upcoming halving event. This event will reduce the number of Bitcoins awarded to miners for each block processed from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC. Scheduled for April 20, the halving aims to make Bitcoin scarcer, potentially increasing its value. Kiyosaki encourages investors to acquire at least one-tenth of a Bitcoin through ETFs or by buying “Satoshis,” the smaller units of Bitcoin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Robert Kiyosaki predicts massive Bitcoin surge by 2025</strong></h2>



<p>The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/forget-the-bitcoin-halving-fear/"> Bitcoin halving</a> is a significant factor in Kiyosaki&#8217;s investment strategy. By reducing the reward for mining Bitcoin, the event makes the digital currency more scarce. Kiyosaki suggests this scarcity could drive Bitcoin&#8217;s value higher. He advises investors unable to afford a full Bitcoin to consider smaller units or ETFs. These ETFs have seen substantial investment, with a record $1 billion inflow in a single day, though recent weeks have shown a decline.</p>



<p>Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s bullish stance on Bitcoin includes a prediction that the cryptocurrency will reach $100,000 by September. He also forecasts a potential rise to $500,000 by 2025. These predictions stem from his analysis of U.S. debt, consumer spending habits, and geopolitical tensions. Kiyosaki believes these factors could boost the value of Bitcoin, along with gold and silver, in the coming years.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bitcoin ETFs open new investor doors</strong></h2>



<p>Beyond his investment plans, Robert Kiyosaki has shared <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1772115533502259692?s=20" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">optimistic forecasts </a>for Bitcoin&#8217;s future. He envisions the cryptocurrency hitting significant milestones in value over the next few years. His confidence is partly based on concerns over the U.S.&#8217;s financial stability and global geopolitical risks. These could enhance the appeal of Bitcoin as a safer asset compared to traditional currencies.</p>



<p>The launch of Bitcoin ETFs has provided investors with a new avenue to enter the cryptocurrency market. Despite a recent dip in investment flows, market sentiment appears poised for recovery. Kiyosaki&#8217;s recommendations to invest in Bitcoin through direct purchases or ETFs reflect a broader trend of growing interest in digital currencies. As the halving event approaches, the financial community watches closely to see how these predictions and strategies will unfold in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/DALL·E-2023-12-04-13.36.25-A-highly-detailed-and-realistic-depiction-of-a-shiny-golden-Bitcoin.-The-coin-is-positioned-centrally-on-a-dark-blurred-background-to-emphasize-its-f.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/DALL·E-2023-12-04-13.36.25-A-highly-detailed-and-realistic-depiction-of-a-shiny-golden-Bitcoin.-The-coin-is-positioned-centrally-on-a-dark-blurred-background-to-emphasize-its-f.jpg"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
