<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:42:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Motives Behind Amazon&#8217;s Investment in AI Startup Anthropic</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/amazons-investment-in-ai-startup-anthropic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Innovators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502986</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a bid to acquit itself to the new and fast-paced age of Generative AI (GenAI) where the competition is intense, American powerhouse Amazon has stated that it has a budget of about $2.75 billion and it is to be directed to an autonomous GenAI startup based in San Francisco, called Anthropic.&#160; Amazon&#8217;s massive investment [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a bid to acquit itself to the new and fast-paced age of Generative AI (GenAI) where the competition is intense, American powerhouse<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/amazon-completes-investment-in-anthropic/"> Amazon </a>has stated that it has a budget of about $2.75 billion and it is to be directed to an autonomous GenAI startup based in San Francisco, called Anthropic.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Amazon&#8217;s massive investment boosts Anthropic&#8217;s GenAI innovation</h2>



<p>The investment, as well as the largest one from the e-commerce and cloud computing titan, takes the overall financial commitment of Anthropic with this particular contributor to the $ 4, billion as a confirmation of the growing partnership between the two organizations during the GenAI revolution.</p>



<p>Anthropic remains the decision sorted after the digital present because of Claude, its human-determining AI technology, which it released in March 2023. After Amazon&#8217;s initial investment of $1.24 billion in September, the new financing round added around $7.4 billion of capitalized funds to Anthropic last year.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This partnership evidences Amazon Corporation&#8217;s aggressive attitude towards GenAI. It gives space to Anthropic to enhance the current model of Amazon Web Services (AWS) by developing parameters related to safety research and future growth.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Strategic alliances in the GenAI arena</h2>



<p>The burgeoning interest and financial inflow into GenAI from major cloud service providers underscore the technology&#8217;s potential to redefine various industries. Amazon&#8217;s Vice President of Data and AI at AWS, Swami Sivasubramanian, emphasized the transformative nature of GenAI, stating that the collaboration with Anthropic is poised to enhance customer experiences significantly.</p>



<p>This investment comes when competition among cloud providers intensifies, with Alphabet&#8217;s Google committing up to $2 billion in Anthropic, highlighting the strategic importance of GenAI innovations in shaping the future of cloud computing and AI technologies.</p>



<p>However, the aggressive investment strategies by tech giants in AI startups have not gone unnoticed by regulatory bodies. The United States Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has expressed concerns over the potential market implications of these partnerships, initiating a &#8220;market inquiry&#8221; into the investments and collaborations between AI developers and major cloud service providers.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This inquiry aims to examine the deals closely, including Microsoft&#8217;s arrangement with OpenAI and Google and Amazon&#8217;s investments in Anthropic, amid accusations of &#8220;round-tripping&#8221;—a practice where investments could misleadingly inflate cloud business revenues, potentially misleading investors.</p>



<p>This scrutiny comes in the wake of a decrease in the value of cloud deals in 2023, a downturn from the peak investment levels witnessed in 2021. The FTC&#8217;s investigation seeks to ensure fair competition and transparency within the rapidly evolving AI market, addressing concerns over the circular nature of investments that might advantage incumbents while posing barriers for emerging players.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Navigating the Future of AI and Cloud Computing</h2>



<p>As Amazon deepens its foray into GenAI through its strategic investment in Anthropic, the landscape of cloud computing and AI technology stands on the brink of significant transformation.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The move signifies Amazon&#8217;s commitment to leading in the GenAI space and highlights the critical role of cloud infrastructure in developing and deploying AI innovations. With regulatory eyes closely watching, the dynamics of investments, partnerships, and the competitive race in GenAI will undoubtedly shape the trajectory of technology development and deployment across industries.</p>



<p>Amidst this backdrop, companies and regulators are navigating uncharted territories, balancing fostering innovation and ensuring a competitive, transparent market. As GenAI continues to emerge as a pivotal technology, its potential to revolutionize customer experiences, operational efficiencies, and the broader technological landscape remains unparalleled, underscoring the strategic value of investments like Amazon&#8217;s in Anthropic.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Amazons_Investment_in_tech_Startup_Anthropic_0-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Amazons_Investment_in_tech_Startup_Anthropic_0-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let&#8217;s Break Down Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s Latest Essay</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/break-down-vitalik-buterins-latest-essay/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502976</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin, the brain behind Ethereum, dropped a thought bomb on the crypto community, challenging us to rethink what we know about decentralization. He&#8217;s not one to shy away from the tough topics, and this time, it&#8217;s no different. Buterin is throwing down the gauntlet, suggesting we might be doing decentralization all wrong. He&#8217;s proposing [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Vitalik Buterin, the brain behind Ethereum, dropped a thought bomb on the crypto community, challenging us to rethink what we know about decentralization. He&#8217;s not one to shy away from the tough topics, and this time, it&#8217;s no different. Buterin is throwing down the gauntlet, suggesting we might be doing decentralization all wrong. He&#8217;s proposing a wild idea: make the crypto world a fairer place by slapping bigger penalties on those who mess up in a way that screams, &#8220;I&#8217;m gaming the system.&#8221;<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-sentencing-hearing" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Rethinking Penalties: A Game Changer for Decentralization</h2>



<p>Buterin&#8217;s not just talking out of his hat here. He&#8217;s got a plan, and it&#8217;s all about making big players sweat a little when they screw up. Right now, in Ethereum land, if you mess up, you get a slap on the wrist, a penalty. But here&#8217;s where Buterin turns the tables: what if the more you and your clone army mess up together, the more you pay? </p>



<p>It&#8217;s like saying, &#8220;Oh, you thought you could outsmart the system by being everywhere at once? Think again.&#8221; This idea isn&#8217;t new to <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethereum-security-classification-could-open-eth-etf-doors-says-blackrock-ceo/" data-type="post" data-id="502956">Ethereum</a>, where they&#8217;ve already got some of this smart thinking in the slashing and inactivity leak mechanics. But Buterin&#8217;s saying it&#8217;s not enough. We need to dial it up for the everyday mistakes too, not just the once-in-a-blue-moon mega fails.</p>



<p>He&#8217;s got the numbers to back it up. Buterin and co. have been crunching the data, looking at when validators are supposed to do their thing and when they actually do it. They&#8217;re also peeking into who&#8217;s who in the Ethereum zoo, linking validator IDs to the big names like Lido, Coinbase, and yes, even Buterin himself. The results? When validators in the same crew are supposed to attest at the same time and don&#8217;t, it happens way more than it should by sheer chance. This isn&#8217;t just bad luck; it&#8217;s a pattern.</p>



<p>Buterin&#8217;s deep dive into the data shows us that, yes, these big validator clusters are messing up together more often than they should. It&#8217;s like they&#8217;re all tripping over the same cable. If things were really decentralized, these failures wouldn&#8217;t be so… cozy. They&#8217;d be all over the place, not huddled together, whispering, &#8220;Oops, we did it again.&#8221;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Crunching the Numbers: The Buterin Way</h2>



<p>Let&#8217;s get into the nitty-gritty of how Buterin suggests we fix this. Imagine every slot in the Ethereum blockchain is a little contest, and if you miss more slots than the average, you start to rack up penalties. But here&#8217;s the kicker: these penalties grow the more you and your buddies miss together. It&#8217;s a way to say, &#8220;Play fair, or pay up.&#8221; And this isn&#8217;t just theoretical. Buterin ran the numbers, and the results are pretty telling. The more this penalty system is put into play, the less advantage the big guys have. Suddenly, being a behemoth with a zillion validators doesn&#8217;t look so hot.</p>



<p>But what&#8217;s really going on here? Well, in the grand scheme of things, the total number of misses is pretty small. But for a big player, even a few misses can skew the numbers because they have so many validators. This means they can single-handedly bump up the failure rate for a slot, which, in turn, bumps up their penalties. It&#8217;s a self-own of epic proportions.</p>



<p>So, could a big staker just spread out their validators to avoid these penalties? Sure, but then they lose their economies of scale, which is a fancy way of saying, &#8220;It&#8217;s gonna cost you.&#8221; And that&#8217;s the beauty of Buterin&#8217;s proposal. It&#8217;s a subtle nudge to big players, saying, &#8220;Maybe don&#8217;t put all your eggs in one basket.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-28-00.15.14-This-image-illustrates-the-key-concepts-and-excitement-surrounding-Ethereums-latest-essay-on-enhanced-incentives-for-decentralized-staking.-It-featur.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-28-00.15.14-This-image-illustrates-the-key-concepts-and-excitement-surrounding-Ethereums-latest-essay-on-enhanced-incentives-for-decentralized-staking.-It-featur.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>On-Chain AI: The Next Big Thing in Web3?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/on-chain-ai-the-next-big-thing-in-web3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibiam Wayas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On-chain data]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Blockchain and AI are two powerful technologies that seem entirely separate. Over the past year, however, the blurry line between the two worlds has become clearer as Web3 projects continue to push and explore what is possible.&#160; The launch of ChatGPT over a year ago was a significant moment that sparked widespread interest in AI [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Blockchain and AI are two powerful technologies that seem entirely separate. Over the past year, however, the blurry line between the two worlds has become clearer as Web3 projects continue to push and explore what is possible.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The launch of ChatGPT over a year ago was a significant moment that sparked widespread interest in AI technology.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It&#8217;s fair to say that for many, ChatGPT served as the first real-world example that brought the technology to life in a way that resonated with a large audience. The tidal wave of AI’s potential swept across so many sectors, and the crypto industry was no exception.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Web3 Projects Forge Path for AI and Blockchain</h2>



<p>Several Web3 projects have been trying to forge a path to integrate these technologies, potentially unlocking billion-dollar possibilities. Some failed at it, but many projects have established a solid presence on that front, with the likes of Feitch.ai, SingularityNET, Akash Network, Render, and several other projects that account for over $20 billion in market cap.</p>



<p>There’s no longer a doubt that on-chain AI operations will metamorph into a bigger sub-section of the Web3 industry, seeing the efforts made by industry players, especially with <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ankrs-neura-blockchain-set-on-ai-cloud-computing-web3/">the recent launch of Neura</a>, which is arguably the first AI-centric blockchain that is purposely built to bridge the gap between AI and Web3.</p>



<p>Neura was launched by Web3 infrastructure provider Ankr on March 26. Its uniqueness lies in the fact that it seamlessly integrates with AI, cloud computing, and Web3 technologies, essentially creating an enabling environment for AI developers to deploy, train, and operate their models on the blockchain.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Training AI models devour vast amounts of computational power, which is a significant challenge for many developers, who often struggle to secure access to the necessary storage and powerful GPUs (Graphics Processing Units) required for the training process.</p>



<p>Neura will provide AI developers with the requisite foundational infrastructure to train their models, Ankr said. It will offer developers access to scalable“decentralised” GPU resources, a novel crypto-based crowdfunding model (Initial Model Offerings) to secure investments, and on-chain AI operations support, among other things.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Neura offers a superior operating system for the neural networks of AI models, supercharging them with trusted data, scalable access to GPU resources, smart contract automation, and new economic models more capable of handling by-the-second demands of future AI apps and payments,” said Chandler Song, Ankr’s Co-Founder and CEO.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Why On-chain AI?</h2>



<p>One of the most concerning aspects of the booming AI industry has been the monopolisation of AI technologies, coupled with a lack of transparency, control, and accessibility.</p>



<p>As earlier mentioned, AI thrives on vast resources – computational power, data sets, and specialised talent. This consequently creates an environment where large corporations with deep pockets can build a significant lead, potentially leading to an AI monopoly.</p>



<p>Also, many AI algorithms function as complex &#8220;black boxes.&#8221; Their inner workings are shrouded in mystery, making it difficult to understand how they arrive at their decisions.</p>



<p>These very characteristics that raise concerns about traditional AI development – lack of transparency, the potential for monopolisation, and centralised control – all make the case for why AI startups would want to deploy their models on blockchain.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Blockchain, which is the technology behind all cryptocurrencies, stands out for its core principle of immutability that ensures transactions and data are recorded and verifiable. By extension, AI algorithms will become more transparent if deployed on-chain, allowing for scrutiny and identification of potential biases.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-2024-03-28T132613.466.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-2024-03-28T132613.466.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let&#8217;s talk Sam Bankman-Fried: What to expect from his sentencing</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/lets-talk-sam-bankman-fried/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502970</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried, the ex-FTX CEO, is on the edge of his seat as March 28 approaches. That&#8217;s the day he finds out if he&#8217;s walking free or starting a long stint in prison after being found guilty of seven serious crimes. Judge Lewis Kaplan of the New York Southern District is the man of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried, the ex-FTX CEO, is on the edge of his seat as March 28 approaches. That&#8217;s the day he finds out if he&#8217;s walking free or starting a long stint in prison after being found guilty of seven serious crimes.<a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-sentencing-hearing" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<p>Judge Lewis Kaplan of the New York Southern District is the man of the hour, listening to the last pleas for and against Bankman-Fried. This courtroom drama started with <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ftxs-bankruptcy-estate-set-to-surpass-creditor-claims-amidst-tax-dispute/" data-type="post" data-id="502884">FTX&#8217;s</a> crash in 2022 and followed with Bankman-Fried&#8217;s arrest, extradition, trial, and conviction.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Sentence Debate</h2>



<p>In November 2023, a jury nailed Bankman-Fried for wire fraud, securities fraud, commodities fraud, and money laundering. His lawyers, hitting the ground running, asked for a 6.5-year jail time, arguing that the mess he caused only temporarily locked FTX investors out of their money.</p>



<p>The prosecution, on the other hand, is pushing for 40 to 50 years, emphasizing the gravity of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s actions. The legal tussle focuses on how much money was actually lost when FTX went under, a key factor in deciding the sentence length.</p>



<p>Legal eagle Mark Bini predicts a 30-year sentence, maybe even longer, considering the heated debate over the losses incurred. There&#8217;s a proposed plan to refund FTX users in cash, based on November 2022 crypto prices, but that means they&#8217;d miss out on any recent spikes in Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies&#8217; values.</p>



<p>An FTX user shared the devastation of losing their funds, highlighting the real-life impact of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s decisions. This case is charting new territory in dealing with high-profile digital asset figures facing trial and sentencing, with comparisons drawn to other notable cases like Ross Ulbricht of Silk Road and Elizabeth Holmes of Theranos.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Comparing Cases</h2>



<p>Bankman-Fried&#8217;s legal saga might not affect Changpeng “CZ” Zhao&#8217;s upcoming sentencing for a different type of crime at Binance, but Alex Mashinsky&#8217;s trial could feel some ripples, given the shared defense team and similar New York venue.</p>



<p>As D-Day looms, there&#8217;s no word if Bankman-Fried&#8217;s family will be there to support him. The judge will weigh various factors, including the nature of his offenses and the financial damage inflicted on FTX&#8217;s customers and investors.</p>



<p>The collapse of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s crypto exchange left an $8 billion hole and led to his conviction on several counts of fraud and money laundering. Despite the dire situation, FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy process has hinted at a possible full repayment to customers.</p>



<p>Bankman-Fried&#8217;s defense argues that the financial harm to those involved is nil, attributing the $8 billion gap to a liquidity crisis amid a customer withdrawal frenzy. Moreover, ongoing restructuring talks suggest FTX could repay its customers significantly more than their initial claims, thanks to a rebound in crypto and AI asset values.</p>



<p>Prosecutors dismiss these claims, highlighting that many customers won&#8217;t recover the real value of their deposits, as some cryptocurrencies have vanished. They also point out the enduring financial and emotional toll on FTX users, emphasizing that any future repayments won&#8217;t undo the immediate harm caused.</p>



<p>Investors like Sequoia Capital are also staring down substantial losses, with their stakes now worth zilch. The final outcome depends on resolving claims and finalizing the bankruptcy plan, but Bankman-Fried&#8217;s actions have left a mark that won&#8217;t easily be erased.</p>



<p>Legal experts are skeptical of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s defense swaying Judge Kaplan, noting the jury&#8217;s rejection of similar arguments. While some investors might have been more crypto-savvy, the notion that Bankman-Fried isn&#8217;t directly making victims whole is a sticking point.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-28-00.19.07-The-image-is-a-compelling-and-thought-provoking-representation-of-the-anticipation-surrounding-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-upcoming-sentencing-on-March-29th.-.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-28-00.19.07-The-image-is-a-compelling-and-thought-provoking-representation-of-the-anticipation-surrounding-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-upcoming-sentencing-on-March-29th.-.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI Bias Testing Mandated for Federal Agencies by the White House</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-bias-test-mandated-for-federal-agencies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 12:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502960</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In one of its major initiatives to spur the adoption of AI technologies by the government in the United States with a responsible approach, the White House has dictated the need to conduct biased tests on AI tools used across governmental agencies.&#160; The Executive Order, issued through OMB, presents one of the Biden administration’s key [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In one of its major initiatives to spur the adoption of AI technologies by the government in the United States with a responsible approach, the White House has dictated the need to conduct <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/how-serious-is-ai-bias-in-recruitment/">biased</a> tests on AI tools used across governmental agencies.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Executive Order, issued through OMB, presents one of the Biden administration’s key policy agendas designed to contain the least possible risks that may emerge, including discrimination, alongside privacy breaches.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Federal agencies prepare for AI oversight and accountability</h2>



<p>As announced in the government-wide policy, the federal agencies will compile strong operational systems to conform with people&#8217;s rights and safety. They should be implemented by December 1st, when artificial intelligence is applied in such a way that it can influence people&#8217;s lives. </p>



<p>In particular, these measures are designed to eliminate distinctions, infringement of the private sphere, and divergences among different sectors, including security in transportation, healthcare, and service delivery. Chiefs of artificial intelligence or Crime and Enforcement should be appointed in addition to other measures to ensure oversight</p>



<p>To oversee how the artificial intelligence guidance of the OMB is executed and to coordinate its use across the different offices, the Chief Artificial Intelligence Officers will be appointed. These officials will get involved in creating and guaranteeing that artificial intelligence deployments within the federal government are transparent and accountable.</p>



<p>Vice President Kamala Harris emphasized the intention for these domestic policies to serve as a model for global action, emphasizing the importance of prioritizing the public interest in artificial intelligence utilization. The administration plans to hire at least 100 employees focusing on artificial intelligence by the summer, further highlighting its commitment to this initiative.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Rigorous testing for high-risk systems</h2>



<p>Senior administration officials have outlined that high-risk systems will undergo rigorous testing to identify and mitigate potential biases and risks. This proactive approach underscores the administration&#8217;s commitment to ensuring the responsible use of artificial intelligence technology in government operations.</p>



<p>Under the new guidelines, Americans can seek remedies if they believe systems have led to false information or decisions affecting them. </p>



<p>Federal agencies must publish a list of systems, risk assessments, and management strategies. Waivers may be granted for software that does not comply with administration rules, but a justification must be provided, promoting transparency and accountability in artificial intelligence deployment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Challenges and future directions</h2>



<p>Alexandra Reeve Givens, President and CEO of the Center for Democracy and Technology, hailed the guidance as a significant step towards ensuring responsible <a href="https://cdn.leonardo.ai/users/5eb4088d-fbcd-4888-ab45-18947f562726/generations/a9ef1916-7bb5-4c6e-8e63-254b3fa23203/Default_the_White_House_0.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">AI </a>usage within federal agencies. </p>



<p>Givens emphasized the importance of rigorous processes in place to assess the potential impact of new technologies on individuals and communities.</p>



<p>While federal agencies have been utilizing AI technology for years, broader regulation of AI has stalled in Congress. As a result, the Biden administration is leveraging the government&#8217;s position as a major technology customer to establish safeguards and promote responsible AI adoption.</p>



<p>Despite the proactive measures taken by the administration, challenges remain, particularly concerning the perpetuation of biases in AI systems. Instances of racial bias and inaccuracies in AI-driven decision-making highlight the need for ongoing vigilance and oversight in AI deployment.</p>



<p>The White House&#8217;s mandate for bias testing and oversight of AI usage in federal agencies represents a significant step towards ensuring AI technology&#8217;s responsible and ethical adoption. By implementing concrete safeguards, promoting transparency, and fostering public accountability, the administration aims to address potential risks while harnessing AI&#8217;s transformative potential for society&#8217;s benefit.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_the_White_House_0-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_the_White_House_0-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC&#8217;s Ethereum security classification could open ETH ETF doors, says BlackRock CEO</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethereum-security-classification-could-open-eth-etf-doors-says-blackrock-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutuma Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larry Fink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502956</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the Fox Business Show, the CEO of BlackRock, the $9.1 trillion asset management firm, Larry Fink, talked about the likelihood of an Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF). Fink argued that designating Ethereum as a security would be positive for the ETF outlook. His remarks occur as the debate about the regulatory position of cryptocurrencies is [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>On the Fox Business Show, the CEO of<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/investor-insights-blackrocks-influence-on-ethereum-price/"> BlackRock</a>, the $9.1 trillion asset management firm, Larry Fink, talked about the likelihood of an Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF). Fink argued that designating Ethereum as a security would be positive for the ETF outlook. His remarks occur as the debate about the regulatory position of cryptocurrencies is ongoing, and Ethereum is at the root of the argument. The SEC’s attempts to possibly label Ethereum as security are being received with different reactions from the stakeholders.</p>



<p>ETF analyst Nate Geraci noted that Fink’s comments were “intriguing” and implied significant moves by the SEC to classify the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap as a security. Though some doubt that an Ether-based spot ETF will be approved any time soon, Geraci thinks that after security classification, it may be possible for the regulatory landscape to change for such a product. This is consistent with the SEC’s earlier approval of prospective ETFs for Ethereum, reflecting a more refined stance on regulation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BlackRock eyes Ethereum ETF amid regulatory talks</strong></h2>



<p>The sustained regulatory discussions and the positions taken by BlackRock illustrate the interactions among innovation, market demand, and regulatory control in the cryptocurrency industry. However, with the development of regulatory clarity, new investment products, like Ethereum ETFs, might become an important influence on the market. Both investors will closely watch these developments and those following the industry, as they are expected to define the future of cryptocurrency investment.</p>



<p><a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/video/6349827399112" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Contrarily, Fink showed </a>a favorable long-term opinion on Bitcoin due to unexpected large retail demand. The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/blackrocks-ibit-etf-hits-10-billion-aum/"> IBIT ETF </a>of BlackRock has set records, as it is the fastest-growing ETF, which highlights the enormous demand for Bitcoin. Yet, Robert Mitchnick, head of digital assets at BlackRock, observed low demand for Ethereum and other altcoins from their customers. Mitchnick noted the preference of Bitcoin to BlackRock, as well as reflecting the broader market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum ETF could mark cryptocurrency milestone</strong></h2>



<p>Even under a security classification, the possibility of an Ethereum ETF represents a key milestone for cryptocurrency investment products. Fink’s statements imply that BlackRock sees a prospect of Ethereum within the regulatory regime, which in turn creates new opportunities for investors. This progress also represents a more general transition and integration of cryptos into conventional financial systems. The regulatory controversies and BlackRock’s strategic stances bring out the evolving innovation, market demand, and regulatory oversight interaction in the cryptocurrency domain.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-26-14.08.16-Create-an-image-symbolizing-an-Ethereum-ETF-Exchange-Traded-Fund.-The-central-focus-should-be-a-large-glossy-Ethereum-logo-made-of-digital-futuri-1.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-26-14.08.16-Create-an-image-symbolizing-an-Ethereum-ETF-Exchange-Traded-Fund.-The-central-focus-should-be-a-large-glossy-Ethereum-logo-made-of-digital-futuri-1.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethena prepares for governance token launch with a major airdrop</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethena-prepares-for-governance-token-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airdrop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethena]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alongside the significant move in the DeFi sector, Ethena, the protocol that governs USDe, a $1.3 billion token, will launch its ENA governance token soon. The most important action follows on April 2nd when the project enters its new phase, facilitating the release of 750 million ENA tokens, or 5% of the entire supply, distributed [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Alongside the significant move in the DeFi sector<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethenas-usd-yield-surpasses-67-apy/">, Ethena</a>, the protocol that governs USDe, a $1.3 billion token, will launch its ENA governance token soon. The most important action follows on April 2nd when the project enters its new phase, facilitating the release of 750 million ENA tokens, or 5% of the entire supply, distributed among the platform’s universe of users.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Strengthening Ethena&#8217;s network through ENA airdrop initiatives</h2>



<p>The protocol<a href="https://mirror.xyz/0xF99d0E4E3435cc9C9868D1C6274DfaB3e2721341/uCBp9VeuLWs-ul1b6AOUAoMg5HBB_iizMIi-11N6nT8" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> set </a>down the entry procedure for the community members so they could partake in the airdrop while announcing that the engagement and commitment could help the platform grow.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Those looking to earn the airdrop must work on their worthiness, shown in the number of shards they collected (shards contain one&#8217;s stake and involvement in the ecosystem). The cutoff for earning shards is set for April 1, with a clear guideline:&nbsp;</p>



<p>If anyone in the community misses the date by unstaking, unlocking, or selling their USDe tokens before time fits, he/she will not be eligible for the AMAs. The distribution will be complete by listing ENA on well-established centralized exchanges, allowing new people to participate in the Ethena ecosystem.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Revolutionizing yield generation with Ethena&#8217;s innovative token strategy</h2>



<p>On top of that, 10% of the tokens are reserved for players and sold through airdrop, both a reward for current users and a lever allowing each of them to participate in <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethena-shakes-up-defi-inflows-yield/">Ethena</a>&#8216;s governance. </p>



<p>Post-airdrop, the project is laying out a line of fresh incentives to keep the users hooked on the platform. Besides, the project aims to develop a stable ecosystem that is a real strength.</p>



<p>The success and market value of Ethena, which are directly related to its creative technology idea for business-aimed token production, are proof of this. The USDe coin, sometimes called the &#8220;synthetic dollar,&#8221; opened up the option for steady yields by forcing liquid ether (ETH) staking tokens, including Lido&#8217;s stETH, to work as the backing assets. To create such a pair, we take a position worth long ETH perpetual futures of the same amount on the derivatives’ platform, trying to set a price at $1. Derivatives yield rates are examined via the &#8220;cash and carry&#8221; trade scheme.</p>



<p>This business structure has exceeded the expectations of Ethena, starting with 85 million dollar value of USDe token on the first day of the year and then crossing the milestone of north of 1300 billion at the end of the year, which can be seen from the DefiLlama pricing.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The swelling results from two factors: the possibility of wonderful profits prompted by the cryptocurrency interplay and the expectation of the ENA token airdropping, which is awaited.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ENA token launch catalyzing growth and decentralization in Ethena&#8217;s future</h2>



<p>Adding the ENA governance token to the Ethena community is significant for both Ethena and its participants. Through institutionalizing a governance architecture, the protocol is evolving to a more disintermediated and user-driven structure, in which token holders have a say and influence on the platform&#8217;s path and future.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This move is twofold. First, by definition, Ethena agrees with decentralized finance, further consolidating its position in the competitive market.</p>



<p>USA will focus on the token as a drive for expansion and enrichment and the governance structure to guarantee innovation, transparency, and good communal input. Smart contracts exploitation marketing campaigns are set to receive the intended spotlight from the existing DeFi contributors and new users, which will widen Ethena’s market hold in the blockchain sphere.</p>



<p>Ethena&#8217;s <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ethena-2-proposal-susde-integration-aave-v3/">ENA </a>token distribution via an airdrop emphasizes the dedication to communal representation and decentralized handling of the network, which the protocol has shown. With more developed functionality and integration of these features, such as increased risk management, the platform positioned itself for the DeFi space, which will inevitably spur growth and innovation.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Ethena_prepares_for_governance_token_launch_with_a_maj_0-2-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Ethena_prepares_for_governance_token_launch_with_a_maj_0-2-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Saver integrates Safe to bring account abstraction to DeFi</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/defi-saver-integrates-safe-to-bring-account-abstraction-to-defi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Corporate Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502940</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Delaware, USA, March 28th, 2024, Chainwire In a move to greatly improve the user experience of DeFi users in the Ethereum ecosystem, DeFi Saver integrated native support for Safe smart accounts and multisigs. DeFi Saver, one of the leading apps for creating, tracking, and managing DeFi positions on Ethereum just announced they’ve integrated account abstraction [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Delaware, USA, March 28th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<p>In a move to greatly improve the user experience of DeFi users in the Ethereum ecosystem, DeFi Saver integrated native support for Safe smart accounts and multisigs.</p>
<p><a href="https://defisaver.com/?utm_source=Chainwire&amp;utm_medium=Web+portals&amp;utm_campaign=Safe+release+announcement" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">DeFi Saver</a>, one of the leading apps for creating, tracking, and managing DeFi positions on Ethereum just announced they’ve integrated account abstraction leader <a href="https://safe.global/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Safe</a>, to take the experience of DeFi users to the next level. This comes on the back of Safe’s recently announced milestone of more than $100 billion in digital assets secured on Safe smart accounts, with more than 40 million transactions conducted on Safe infrastructure.</p>
<p>The update means that DeFi users of protocols such as Aave, Compound, Morpho Blue, Spark, CurveUSD and Liquity will be able to manage their positions more efficiently, through use of options that bundle or batch multiple actions into one single transaction using the power of the Safe smart accounts. This includes features such as leveraging up or unwinding in one transaction, doing collateral and debt swaps, moving whole active positions between different protocols, various automation features, but also even simpler things such as depositing collateral and borrowing funds in one, single transaction. All of this results in unnecessary steps being abstracted away from DeFi users and traders.</p>
<p>Besides all the advanced features that are made possible through use of a smart account, this update also allows DeFi users to greatly increase their security through the use of Safe multisigs, which are the security standard for asset ownership. Starting today, all current and new users can enjoy native multisig support at DeFi Saver moving forward.</p>
<p class="chainwire-video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c854bs17CMI"></iframe></p>
<p></p>
<p>Another important aspect for both teams is the composability and portability that users will enjoy. Since Safe is widely supported in DeFi apps and frontends, this means that all DeFi Saver users will be able to check and manage their positions through other apps. And, vice versa, all existing Safe users can now seamlessly connect to the DeFi Saver app and make use of the plethora of tools available.</p>
<p>&#8220;We believe that composability and portability are some of the greatest, most important aspects of DeFi and yet this primitive is being ignored by many teams opting to build small, proprietary, walled garden systems. That&#8217;s why we chose Safe and intend to keep building on the open, permissionless building blocks.&#8221; said <a href="https://twitter.com/NPalinkasevic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Nenad Palinkasevic</a>, the co-founder of DeFi Saver.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/SchorLukas" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Lukas Schor,</a> co-founder at Safe, commented, “Smart Accounts are critical infrastructure and we think that for DeFi mass adoption, we need the security of smart accounts, but also the UX benefits to already integrate within the top DeFi projects today. We welcome this move by DeFi Saver to accelerate the transition to smart accounts and Safe ecosystem.”  </p>
<p>Moving forward, the teams also highlighted that this change will allow great improvements to the user experience in DeFi through continued batching of multiple actions into single transactions, but also through features such as sign-only modes where all transactions would be handled for the users in the background, providing a quicker and smoother experience.</p>
<p><strong>About DeFi Saver</strong></p>
<p>DeFi Saver is a management application for decentralized finance protocols best known for their advanced leverage management features and automated liquidation protection options. Having initially started as a MakerDAO-focused dapp in the early days of DeFi, they quickly expanded support to more protocols, as well as multiple L2 networks. Today, DeFi Saver lets you utilize protocols such as Aave, Compound, Morpho Blue, Spark, CurveUSD and Liquity, across Ethereum mainnet, Arbitrum, Optimism and Base.</p>
<p><a href="https://defisaver.com/?utm_source=Chainwire&amp;utm_medium=Web+portals&amp;utm_campaign=Safe+release+announcement" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Website</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/DeFiSaver" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://discord.com/invite/XGDJHhZ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Discord</a>, <a href="https://blog.defisaver.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Blog</a>, <a href="https://github.com/defisaver" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">GitHub</a>, <a href="https://docs.defisaver.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Docs</a></p>
<p><strong>About Safe</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Safe (previously Gnosis Safe) is an onchain asset custody protocol, securing ~$100+ Billion in assets today. It is establishing a universal ‘<strong>smart account&#8217;</strong> standard for secure custody of digital assets, data, and identity. With Safe{Wallet}, its flagship web and mobile wallet, and Safe{Core} account abstraction infrastructure, Safe is on a mission to unlock digital ownership for everyone in web3, including DAOs, enterprises, retail, and institutional users. </p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://safe.global/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Website</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/safe" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://discord.com/invite/nrQVY2566v" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Discord</a>, <a href="https://safe.mirror.xyz/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Blog</a>, <a href="https://github.com/safe-global" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">GitHub</a>, <a href="https://docs.safe.global/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Docs</a></p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Filip Josipovic</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Defi Saver Inc.</strong><br /></span><span><strong>filip@decenter.com</strong><br /></span></p>
<p class="chainwire-disclaimer cp-box cp-box-gray"><i><strong>Disclaimer.</strong> This is a paid press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. <a href="https://cryptopolitan.com/">Cryptopolitan.com</a> is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/blog-cover-042x_1711615007VnRLDxVwtL.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/blog-cover-042x_1711615007VnRLDxVwtL.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investor Insights: Blackrock&#8217;s Influence on Ethereum Price</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/investor-insights-blackrocks-influence-on-ethereum-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joshua Ahorro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Thought Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502926</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Investors everywhere are searching for ways to understand the crypto market&#8217;s shifts. BlackRock, a giant in asset management, has made moves that affect Ethereum&#8217;s price. This blog will explore BlackRock’s influence on Ethereum, providing insights and predictions to guide your investments. Stay tuned for an eye-opening read. Key Takeaways Impact of BlackRock on Ethereum Price [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Investors everywhere are searching for ways to understand the crypto market&#8217;s shifts. BlackRock, a giant in asset management, has made moves that affect <a href="https://www.bybit.com/en/coin-price/ethereum/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Ethereum&#8217;s price</a>. This blog will explore BlackRock’s influence on Ethereum, providing insights and predictions to guide your investments.</p>



<p>Stay tuned for an eye-opening read.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Key Takeaways</strong></h3>



<ul>
<li>BlackRock launched its first crypto fund with a $5 million minimum, showing big interest in cryptocurrencies like Ethereum.</li>



<li>Despite people thinking BlackRock is heavily influencing crypto markets, their Digital Assets head says they&#8217;re mainly exploring blockchain and digital assets.</li>



<li>Market experts expect the approval of Ethereum ETFs will attract more investment and possibly lead to more trading and higher prices for Ethereum.</li>



<li>The success of Bitcoin ETFs hints at strong demand for an upcoming Ethereum ETF, suggesting this could bring even more investors into the market.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Impact of BlackRock on Ethereum Price</strong></h2>



<p>BlackRock&#8217;s involvement in crypto and unveiling of a $5 million minimum crypto fund has influenced Ethereum price. Analysts are projecting market impact from pending Ethereum ETFs linked to BlackRock&#8217;s activity.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Head of Digital Assets: &#8220;Misconception&#8221; about BlackRock&#8217;s involvement in crypto</strong></h3>



<p>The head of Digital Assets at BlackRock has addressed what they call a &#8220;misconception&#8221; about the firm&#8217;s role in cryptocurrencies. They stressed that while BlackRock is exploring digital assets, public perception tends to overestimate their involvement.</p>



<p>The company&#8217;s focus remains on understanding blockchain technology and how it could fit into their investment strategies.</p>



<p>Despite rumors, BlackRock&#8217;s direct impact on cryptocurrency markets, like Ethereum, is more nuanced than many think. They have shown interest by launching a fund dedicated to tokenized assets on the Ethereum network, hinting at careful entry into the crypto space.</p>



<p>This move signals a growing acceptance among institutional investors but doesn&#8217;t translate to controlling market trends or prices in digital currencies directly.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BlackRock unveils first crypto fund with $5 million minimum</strong></h3>



<p>BlackRock introduces crypto fund with $5 million minimum. BlackRock, a major player in asset management, steps into the crypto world by launching its debut digital currency investment fund.</p>



<p>The new fund demands a hefty $5 million buy-in to gain exposure to cryptocurrencies, marking a significant move for institutional investors looking to dip their toes into the increasingly popular realm of digital assets.</p>



<p>This launch signifies BlackRock&#8217;s acknowledgement of the growing importance of cryptocurrencies and could potentially pave the way for other traditional financial institutions to follow suit in embracing this ever-changing market.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Analysts project market impact of pending Ethereum ETFs</strong></h3>



<p>Market analysts anticipate a significant market impact once the pending Ethereum ETFs are approved. The introduction of these ETFs is expected to attract substantial investment, potentially leading to a surge in demand for Ethereum.</p>



<p>Additionally, it is predicted that the approval of Ethereum ETFs could contribute to heightened price volatility and increased trading activities within the crypto stocks realm. This development aligns with current investment trends and may further amplify the onchain metrics associated with Ethereum, underpinning its ever-evolving position in the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>&#8212;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Predictions and Insights on Ethereum Price</strong></h2>



<p>A $7.8 billion arbitrage window may open up with BlackRock&#8217;s ETF.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Impact of potential $7.8B arbitrage window with BlackRock&#8217;s ETF</strong></h3>



<p>The potential $7.8B arbitrage window with BlackRock&#8217;s ETF could significantly affect Ethereum&#8217;s price and market demand. The large capital influx through the ETF could create a substantial gap between the spot price of Ether and the value represented by shares in the ETF, leading to lucrative trading opportunities for investors.</p>



<p>This arbitrage window may spark heightened trading activity, influencing Ethereum&#8217;s price dynamics and increasing overall market liquidity. Moreover, it has the potential to attract institutional investors seeking exposure to Ethereum without directly owning the cryptocurrency itself, further amplifying demand and impacting its market valuation.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Record trading activity for Bitcoin ETF since launch, potential for ETH ETF demand to follow suit.</strong></h3>



<p>Recorded trading activity for Bitcoin ETF has been exceptionally high since its launch, indicating substantial demand and investor interest. This surge in trading activity sets a promising precedent for potential ETH ETF demand to mirror this trend, facilitating increased market participation and liquidity.</p>



<p>As crypto investment avenues broaden, the anticipation of heightened demand for an Ethereum ETF presents opportunities to diversify investment portfolios and capture the evolving landscape of digital assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>



<p>BlackRock&#8217;s introduction of a crypto fund with a minimum investment of $5 million has sparked discussions about its potential influence on Ethereum&#8217;s price. With the anticipation of pending Ethereum ETFs, analysts project significant market impact.</p>



<p>This could potentially lead to an ETH price surge and create arbitrage opportunities if BlackRock&#8217;s ETF gains approval. Moreover, the record trading activity for Bitcoin ETF sets the stage for potential demand for ETH ETFs as well.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-6272696_1280.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-6272696_1280.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple faces criticism from Forbes over XRPL&#8217;s role in global finance</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ripple-faces-criticism-from-forbes-over-xrpl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mutuma Maxwell]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=502919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the latest article, Forbes has classified the XRP Ledger (XRPL) and 19 other blockchains as not really working – to the point of calling them “zombie chains”. The research claims that these networks, among them XRPL, need more substantial use despite their presence within the blockchain ecosystem for more than a decade. Forbes’ analysis [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the latest article, Forbes has classified the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/circle-and-xrp-ledger-community-engage-in-talks-over-potential-usdc-support/"> XRP Ledger</a> (XRPL) and 19 other blockchains as not really working – to the point of calling them “zombie chains”. The research claims that these networks, among them XRPL, need more substantial use despite their presence within the blockchain ecosystem for more than a decade. Forbes’ analysis focuses on the XRPL in particular, even though the network demonstrates activity, with more than 5.1 million wallets indicating ongoing interest among users.</p>



<p>The report by Forbes highlights XRPL&#8217;s inability to impact global money significantly flows, questioning its relevance in the cross-border payments sector. According to Forbes, the network falls short of challenging SWIFT, the dominant player in cross-border transactions. Despite Ripple&#8217;s efforts through its ODL product, which reportedly processed substantial volumes of remittances, Forbes remains skeptical about XRPL&#8217;s effectiveness in replacing traditional systems.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>XRPL&#8217;s role in efficient payments overlooked</strong></h2>



<p>Forbes further criticizes the XRPL for its perceived lack of utility, despite a valuation exceeding $36 billion. The publication points to the low transaction fees on the XRP Ledger as an indicator of its limited use, with total costs in 2023 amounting to $583,000. Forbes views this as evidence of the network&#8217;s underperformance, ignoring the fact that XRPL&#8217;s low fees are designed to deter spam transactions, not as a primary revenue source.</p>



<p>The article has prompted a backlash from several figures within the cryptocurrency community. Critics argue Forbes&#8217; analysis needs more depth, overlooking the XRPL&#8217;s contributions to efficient, low-cost cross-border payments. Ripple&#8217;s recent achievements, such as strategic acquisitions and pilot programs for central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), were also dismissed by Forbes as too little, too late. This stance has led to debates about the criteria used to assess blockchain utility and the significance of transaction fees as a measure of success.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bitcoin, Ethereum only winners in Forbes review</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevenehrlich/2024/03/27/the-rise-of-cryptos-billion-dollar-zombies/?sh=5f9d406354b8" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Forbes&#8217; stance</a> on blockchain utility extends beyond XRPL, naming 20 networks it deems lacking in purpose. This list contrasts sharply with the publication&#8217;s approval of Bitcoin and Ethereum as the only blockchains with meaningful contributions. The criteria for such classifications raise questions about the evaluation methods for blockchain efficacy and the future of digital currencies in financial systems.</p>



<p>The article has received mixed reviews, with the insiders questioning the conclusions and promoting a more comprehensive vision of blockchain technology. The discussion highlights the dynamic nature of digital finance and the constant search for alternative models of traditional banking systems. In the course of the discourse, the roles of utility and success may be subjected to radical reinterpretation in the blockchain domain.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/DALL·E-2024-02-26-02.05.52-Visualize-the-concept-of-XRPL-XRP-Ledger-a-decentralized-cryptographic-ledger-powered-by-a-network-of-peer-to-peer-servers.-The-image-should-showca.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/DALL·E-2024-02-26-02.05.52-Visualize-the-concept-of-XRPL-XRP-Ledger-a-decentralized-cryptographic-ledger-powered-by-a-network-of-peer-to-peer-servers.-The-image-should-showca.webp"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
