<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:55:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Surge Alert: Bitcoin&#8217;s Futures Basis Climbs To New Heights, What This Means For BTC</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/surge-alert-bitcoin-futures-basis-climbs-to-new-heights/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598098</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s futures market is showcasing signs that have historically signalled bullish sentiment. Analysts are turning their attention to the Bitcoin futures basis—a metric representing the differential between the futures price of Bitcoin and its spot price. Recent data has revealed that this basis has escalated to unprecedented levels since Bitcoin&#8217;s all-time high of $69,000 in November 2021. Related Reading: Bitcoin’s 2024 Forecast: Analyst Predicts $60,000 Surge Before Halving And New ATH By Q4 Bullish Indications From Bitcoin Futures Deribit&#8217;s Chief Commercial Officer, Luuk Strijers, has highlighted the current state of the Bitcoin futures basis, which ranges between 18% to 25% annually, a rate reminiscent of the market conditions in 2021. According to Strijers&#8217;s comment, this elevated basis is not just a number but a lucrative opportunity for derivatives traders. By engaging in trades that involve buying Bitcoin in the spot market and simultaneously selling futures contracts at a premium, traders can secure a &#8220;dollar gain&#8221; that will materialize at the contract&#8217;s expiry, irrespective of Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility. Strijers further noted that this strategy is particularly appealing in the current climate, fueled by the influx of new investments following the approval of Bitcoin ETFs and anticipation surrounding the Bitcoin halving event. The significance of the heightened futures basis extends beyond the mechanics of derivatives trading. It further reflects broader market optimism, &#8220;bolstered&#8221; by recent regulatory approvals and macroeconomic factors influencing cryptocurrency. The disparity between Bitcoin&#8217;s spot and futures prices suggests a confident market outlook, propelled by the anticipation of continued investment inflows and the impact of the upcoming Bitcoin halving. Such conditions create a fertile ground for Bitcoin&#8217;s value to surge, as historical precedents have often linked bullish futures basis rates with periods of substantial price appreciation. Market Sentiment And Halving Cycles While Bitcoin&#8217;s current market performance exhibits a bearish trajectory, with a 3.9% dip bringing its price to $68,203, market analysts advise against interpreting this as a negative signal. Rekt Capital, a respected figure in crypto analysis, views the recent price correction as a &#8220;positive adjustment&#8221; preceding the much-anticipated Bitcoin halving in April. Halving events, which reduce the block reward for miners, thus slowing the rate of new Bitcoin entering circulation, have traditionally catalyzed significant price rallies due to the resulting supply constraints. Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis parallels current market movements and historical patterns observed in previous halving cycles. Related Reading: The $69,000 Bitcoin Question: Expert Forecasts When Price Will Breakout According to the analyst, despite the swift pace of these cycles, they exhibit a consistent sequence of a pre-halving rally followed by a retracement phase—both of which align with Bitcoin&#8217;s current trajectory. This cyclical perspective suggests that the recent dip is merely a temporary setback, setting the stage for the next bullish phase post-halving. #BTC Though there are signs of BTC experiencing an Accelerated Cycle&#8230; History still continues to repeat, nonetheless$BTC broke out into a &#8220;Pre-Halving Rally&#8221; right on schedule And now, #Bitcoin is transitioning into its &#8220;Pre-Halving Retrace&#8221; right on schedule#Crypto https://t.co/Egqxs9ritl pic.twitter.com/lj0IdQtBEE — Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) March 15, 2024 Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s futures market is showcasing signs that have historically signalled bullish sentiment. Analysts are turning their attention to the Bitcoin <a href="https://metrics.deribit.com/futures/BTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">futures basis</a>—a metric representing the differential between the futures price of Bitcoin and its spot price.</p>
<p>Recent data has revealed that this basis has escalated to unprecedented levels since Bitcoin&#8217;s <a href="http://The $69,000 Bitcoin Question: Expert Forecasts When Price Will Breakout" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">all-time high of $69,000</a> in November 2021.</p>

<h2>Bullish Indications From Bitcoin Futures</h2>
<p>Deribit&#8217;s Chief Commercial Officer, Luuk Strijers, has <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/282761/bitcoin-futures-basis-is-a-bullish-indicator-for-the-market-analyst-says" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> the current state of the Bitcoin futures basis, which ranges between 18% to 25% annually, a rate reminiscent of the market conditions in 2021.</p>
<p>According to Strijers&#8217;s comment, this elevated basis is not just a number but a lucrative opportunity for derivatives traders.</p>
<img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-598103 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C464" alt="Bitcoin Futures Premium Above The Index Price." width="860" height="464" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=2286 2286w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C464 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-17.30.19.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>By engaging in trades that involve buying Bitcoin in the spot market and simultaneously selling futures contracts at a premium, traders can secure a &#8220;dollar gain&#8221; that will materialize at the contract&#8217;s expiry, irrespective of Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility.</p>
<p>Strijers further noted that this strategy is particularly appealing in the current climate, fueled by the influx of new investments following the approval of Bitcoin ETFs and anticipation surrounding the Bitcoin halving event.</p>
<p>The significance of the heightened futures basis extends beyond the mechanics of derivatives trading. It further reflects broader market optimism, &#8220;bolstered&#8221; by recent regulatory approvals and macroeconomic factors influencing cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The disparity between Bitcoin&#8217;s spot and futures prices suggests a confident market outlook, propelled by the anticipation of continued investment inflows and the impact of the upcoming Bitcoin halving.</p>
<p>Such conditions create a fertile ground for Bitcoin&#8217;s value to surge, as historical precedents have often linked bullish futures basis rates with periods of<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/historical-data-signals-bitcoins-imminent-25-plunge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> substantial price appreciation</a>.</p>
<h2>Market Sentiment And Halving Cycles</h2>
<p>While Bitcoin&#8217;s current <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-2024-forecast-analyst-predicts-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market performance</a> exhibits a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-suffers-crash-to-65000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bearish trajectory</a>, with a 3.9% dip bringing its price to $68,203, market analysts advise against interpreting this as a negative signal. Rekt Capital, a respected figure in crypto analysis, <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1768592730928685149?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">views</a> the recent price correction as a &#8220;positive adjustment&#8221; preceding the much-anticipated Bitcoin halving in April.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/FLvIeQAC/" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556" loading="lazy"/>
<p>Halving events, which reduce the block reward for miners, thus slowing the rate of new Bitcoin entering circulation, have traditionally catalyzed significant price rallies due to the resulting supply constraints.</p>
<p>Rekt Capital&#8217;s analysis parallels <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-crash-failed-1-billion-hedge-fund-trade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">current market movements</a> and historical patterns observed in previous halving cycles.</p>

<p>According to the analyst, despite the swift pace of these cycles, they exhibit a consistent sequence of a pre-halving rally followed by a retracement phase—both of which align with Bitcoin&#8217;s current trajectory. This cyclical perspective suggests that the recent dip is merely a temporary setback, setting the stage for the next bullish phase post-halving.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#BTC</a></p>
<p>Though there are signs of BTC experiencing an Accelerated Cycle&#8230;</p>
<p>History still continues to repeat, nonetheless<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">$BTC</a> broke out into a &#8220;Pre-Halving Rally&#8221; right on schedule</p>
<p>And now, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> is transitioning into its &#8220;Pre-Halving Retrace&#8221; right on schedule<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://t.co/Egqxs9ritl" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">https://t.co/Egqxs9ritl</a> <a href="https://t.co/lj0IdQtBEE" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">pic.twitter.com/lj0IdQtBEE</a></p>
<p>— Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1768592730928685149?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 15, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin.jpeg?fit=460%2C329" width="460" height="329" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598098</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>United States Dominates Global Crypto Market With Massive $9.3 Billion In Profits</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/united-states-dominates-global-crypto-market-with-massive-9-3-billion-in-profits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto market analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market cap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto market news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market Recovery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market Sentiment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market update]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[total crypto market cap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent report by market intelligence firm Chainalysis, it has been revealed that global crypto gains in 2023 amounted to a staggering $37.6 billion. This profit surge reflects improved asset prices and market sentiment compared to 2022.  Although this figure falls short of the $159.7 billion gains witnessed during the 2021 bull market, it signifies a significant recovery from the estimated losses of $127.1 billion experienced in 2022. Sharp Surge In Crypto Gains The report suggests that despite similar growth rates in crypto asset prices in 2021 and 2023, the total gains for the latter year were lower. According to Chainalysis, this discrepancy could potentially be attributed to investors&#8217; decreased inclination to convert their crypto assets into cash.  The analysis further suggests that investors in 2023 seem to have anticipated further price increases, as crypto asset prices did not exceed previous all-time highs (ATHs) during the year, unlike in 2021. Related Reading: Altcoins Fall: Will Ethereum And Solana Bulls Surpass Expectations? Cryptocurrency gains remained relatively consistent throughout 2023, except for two consecutive months of losses in August and September, as seen in the image above. However, gains surged sharply thereafter, with November and December eclipsing all previous months. United States Leads Leading the pack in cryptocurrency gains was the United States, with an estimated $9.36 billion in profits in 2023. The United Kingdom secured the second position with an estimated $1.39 billion in crypto gains.  Notably, several upper and lower-middle-income countries, particularly in Asia, such as Vietnam, China, Indonesia, and India, achieved significant gains, each surpassing $1 billion and ranking within the top six countries worldwide.  Chainalysis had previously observed strong cryptocurrency adoption in these income categories, particularly in &#8220;lower-middle-income&#8221; countries, which demonstrated resilience even during the recent bear market. The gains estimates indicate that investors in these countries have reaped substantial benefits from embracing the asset class. Related Reading: Crypto Pundit Says God Candle Is Imminent For This Solana-Based Meme Coin Ultimately, the Chainalysis report suggests that the positive trends observed in 2023 have carried over into 2024, with prominent cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) hitting all-time highs of $73,700 following the approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and increased institutional adoption.  If these trends persist, the firm believes that it is conceivable that gains in 2024 will align more closely with those witnessed in 2021.  As of this writing, the total crypto market cap valuation stands at $2.5 trillion, a sharp drop of over 4% in the last 24 hours alone, and down from Thursday&#8217;s two-year high of $2.7 trillion. Bitcoin, on the other hand, is trading at $68,400 after dropping as low as $65,500 but has quickly regained its current trading price, limiting losses to 4% over the past 24 hours. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent report by market intelligence firm Chainalysis, it has been revealed that global crypto gains in 2023 amounted to a staggering $37.6 billion. This profit surge reflects improved asset prices and market sentiment compared to 2022. </p>
<p>Although this figure falls short of the $159.7 billion gains witnessed during the 2021 bull market, it signifies a significant recovery from the estimated losses of $127.1 billion experienced in 2022.</p>
<h2>Sharp Surge In Crypto Gains</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.chainalysis.com/blog/cryptocurrency-gains-by-country-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report </a>suggests that despite similar growth rates in crypto asset prices in 2021 and 2023, the total gains for the latter year were lower. According to Chainalysis, this discrepancy could potentially be attributed to investors&#8217; decreased inclination to convert their crypto assets into cash. </p>
<p>The analysis further suggests that investors in 2023 seem to have anticipated further price increases, as crypto asset prices did not exceed previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">all-time highs</a> (ATHs) during the year, unlike in 2021.
</p>

<img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-598123" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=829&#038;resize=829%2C346" alt="Crypto " width="829" height="346" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=829&#038;resize=829%2C346 829w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_78.jpg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 829px) 100vw, 829px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Cryptocurrency gains remained relatively consistent throughout 2023, except for two consecutive <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-crash-failed-1-billion-hedge-fund-trade/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">months of losses</a> in August and September, as seen in the image above. However, gains surged sharply thereafter, with November and December eclipsing all previous months.</p>
<h2>United States Leads</h2>
<p>Leading the pack in cryptocurrency gains was the United States, with an estimated $9.36 billion in profits in 2023. The United Kingdom secured the second position with an estimated $1.39 billion in crypto gains. </p>
<p>Notably, several upper and lower-middle-income countries, particularly in Asia, such as Vietnam, China, Indonesia, and India, achieved significant gains, each surpassing $1 billion and ranking within the top six countries worldwide. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-598122" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=761&#038;resize=761%2C232" alt="Crypto" width="761" height="232" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=761&#038;resize=761%2C232 761w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot_77.jpg?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 761px) 100vw, 761px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Chainalysis had previously observed strong cryptocurrency adoption in these income categories, particularly in &#8220;lower-middle-income&#8221; countries, which demonstrated resilience even during the recent <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/altcoins-fall-ethereum-solana-surpass-expectations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bear market</a>. The gains estimates indicate that investors in these countries have reaped substantial benefits from embracing the asset class.</p>



<p>Ultimately, the Chainalysis report suggests that the positive trends observed in 2023 have carried over into 2024, with prominent cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) hitting all-time highs of $73,700 following the approval of Bitcoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-suffers-crash-to-65000/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">exchange-traded funds</a> (ETFs) and increased institutional adoption. </p>
<p>If these trends persist, the firm believes that it is conceivable that gains in 2024 will align more closely with those witnessed in 2021. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/tplik6SJ/" alt="Crypto" width="1815" height="858"/>
<p>As of this writing, the total crypto market cap valuation stands at $2.5 trillion, a sharp drop of over 4% in the last 24 hours alone, and down from Thursday&#8217;s two-year high of $2.7 trillion. Bitcoin, on the other hand, is trading at $68,400 after dropping as low as $65,500 but has quickly regained its current trading price, limiting losses to 4% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-6-2.jpg?fit=390%2C260" width="390" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598120</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin FOMO: Over 533,330 Addresses Bought Above $70,180</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-fomo-533330-addresses-bought-70180/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin addresses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cost-Basis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin FOMO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data suggests more than 533,330 addresses FOMO&#8217;d into Bitcoin above $70,180. Following the latest plunge, these investors would all be in losses. Over 500K Bitcoin Addresses Have A Cost Basis Between $70,180 &#38; $71,340 As pointed out by analyst Ali in a post on X, many investors have bought at the recently high price levels. Below is the chart shared by the analyst that shows how the distribution of the BTC supply looks right now across the various price ranges. How the BTC cost basis distribution looks like for the price ranges near the current one &#124; Source: @ali_charts on X The data is from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, which has used on-chain data to determine the average acquisition price for any given address based on when its coins moved into its balance. Related Reading: Bitcoin To $53,200? Why History Says It’s Possible In the chart, the size of the dots represents the amount of coins that have their cost basis inside the corresponding range. It would appear that the $64,743 and $66,700 range is below the current price that hosts the cost basis of a significant amount of addresses. More particularly, 382,000 addresses acquired 275,450 BTC at these levels. As the Bitcoin spot price is currently trading above this range, all these investors would naturally be carrying some profits. Generally, investors are sensitive to retests of their cost basis, as such retests can potentially flip their profit-loss status. For holders who were in profit before the retest, the dip may appear as an opportunity to buy more. The emerging reaction can be significant when many hands share their cost basis inside the same narrow range. If this retest occurs from above, the asset could feel some support as these investors rush to accumulate more. Since the $64,743 to $66,700 range is dense with investors and is situated below the current spot price of the cryptocurrency, it could act as a major support center. &#8220;Monitoring this level closely is crucial, as losing it could shift the focus to the next significant demand zone between $60,760 and $62,790, safeguarded by 797,500 addresses with over 298,000 BTC,&#8221; notes Ali. Related Reading: Bitcoin Miners Brace For Impact As Difficulty Reaches Unprecedented Levels In terms of the levels above, the $70,180 to $71,340 range particularly stands out, as 533,330 addresses bought a total of almost 433,000 BTC. A lot of these new buyers would be those FOMO&#8217;ing into the asset after seeing it explore new all-time highs. This large block, however, may serve as a point of resistance for the cryptocurrency. These fresh hands might sell just as quickly as they bought in when a retest of their cost basis happens since they may be willing to just exit at their break-even, fearing more drops in the near future. BTC Price Bitcoin has seen a sharp correction during the past day, following which its spot price is now trading around the $67,900 level. BTC made a brief visit under the $66,000 level during this correction &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, IntoTheBlock.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data suggests more than 533,330 addresses FOMO&#8217;d into Bitcoin above $70,180. Following the latest plunge, these investors would all be in losses.</p>
<h2>Over 500K Bitcoin Addresses Have A Cost Basis Between $70,180 &amp; $71,340</h2>
<p>As pointed out by analyst Ali in a <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1768575782778028153" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, many investors have bought at the recently high price levels. Below is the chart shared by the analyst that shows how the distribution of the BTC supply looks right now across the various price ranges.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GIs8XsjX0AAfL-s?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Cost Basis" width="2552" height="860"/></p>

<p>The data is from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, which has used on-chain data to determine the average acquisition price for any given address based on when its coins moved into its balance.</p>

<p>In the chart, the size of the dots represents the amount of coins that have their cost basis inside the corresponding range. It would appear that the $64,743 and $66,700 range is below the current price that hosts the cost basis of a significant amount of addresses.</p>
<p>More particularly, 382,000 addresses acquired 275,450 BTC at these levels. As the Bitcoin spot price is currently trading above this range, all these investors would naturally be carrying some <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/95-bitcoin-now-profit-could-signal-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">profits</a>.</p>
<p>Generally, investors are sensitive to retests of their cost basis, as such retests can potentially flip their profit-loss status. For holders who were in profit before the retest, the dip may appear as an opportunity to buy more.</p>
<p>The emerging reaction can be significant when many hands share their cost basis inside the same narrow range. If this retest occurs from above, the asset could feel some <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/eth/ethereum-price-takes-hit-3680/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">support</a> as these investors rush to accumulate more.</p>
<p>Since the $64,743 to $66,700 range is dense with investors and is situated below the current spot price of the cryptocurrency, it could act as a major support center.</p>
<p>&#8220;Monitoring this level closely is crucial, as losing it could shift the focus to the next significant demand zone between $60,760 and $62,790, safeguarded by 797,500 addresses with over 298,000 BTC,&#8221; notes Ali.</p>

<p>In terms of the levels above, the $70,180 to $71,340 range particularly stands out, as 533,330 addresses bought a total of almost 433,000 BTC. A lot of these new buyers would be those FOMO&#8217;ing into the asset after seeing it explore new all-time highs.</p>
<p>This large block, however, may serve as a point of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-large-resistance-wall-ahead-level-watch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">resistance</a> for the cryptocurrency. These fresh hands might sell just as quickly as they bought in when a retest of their cost basis happens since they may be willing to just exit at their break-even, fearing more drops in the near future.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has seen a sharp correction during the past day, following which its spot price is now trading around the $67,900 level.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/dua2dSs7/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kanchanara-OqEPgkdX3RA-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598099</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind The Scenes Of Shiba Inu 12% Plunge: What On-Chain Analysis Tells Us</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/behind-the-scenes-of-shiba-inu-12-plunge-what-on-chain-analysis-tells-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), a popular memecoin, has experienced a notable decline. It dropped nearly 20% over the past week and continued a 13% fall in just the past 24 hours. This downturn occurs amid a broader bearish trend across the crypto landscape. However, detailed on-chain analysis has uncovered specific factors contributing to SHIB&#8217;s sharp decline. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Optimistic About A Shiba Inu Short-Term Surge To $0.000066 Whale Movements And Market Influence Insights from IntoTheBlock have shed light on large transaction activities, often indicative of &#8220;whale&#8221; movements, which have seen a general decrease since March 5, further compounding the downward pressure on SHIB&#8217;s price. The role of speculative trading in influencing SHIB&#8217;s market performance has also become increasingly apparent. Data pointing to the holding time of transacted coins suggests a shift towards short-term trading strategies among investors, possibly in pursuit of quick profits. Such behaviors are underscored by a significant reduction in the average holding period of coins, from four weeks to just two months as of mid-March, accompanied by a transaction volume of 2.12 trillion SHIB. This trend towards speculative trading has been a key driver behind the memecoin&#8217;s recent price movements, reflecting the broader dynamics within the cryptocurrency market. The decrease in large transactions involving Shiba Inu signifies dwindling confidence among whales, whose actions can profoundly impact market direction. The observed decline in whale activities aligns with a broader caution in the crypto market, where investors reevaluate their positions amid shifting market conditions. Shiba Inu Bright Horizon Despite the current downturn, Shiba Inu remains a focal point within the altcoin sector, buoyed by optimistic predictions from crypto analysts. Related Reading: Crypto Expert Says Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, PEPE, Others Are About To Explode Michaël van de Poppe, a well-regarded figure in the crypto analysis community, has recently posited that altcoins,  are set for significant rallies, potentially positioning Shiba Inu for a notable rebound as the market stabilizes. &#160; There&#8217;s still around 40-60% market capitalization to gain for the #Altcoins. That&#8217;s going to be a fun ride for the altcoins in the coming period. pic.twitter.com/qT0FRU4qpY — Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) March 7, 2024 This sentiment is echoed by Shiba Inu&#8217;s co-founder, Shytoshi Kusama, who has expressed confidence in SHIB&#8217;s ability to lead in the next bull market, citing the project&#8217;s comprehensive plans, community support, and execution as key differentiators. No. The community with the strongest tech, vision, plan, supporters, partners, and execution will. #SHIB But if you wanted some impressions why not say hi? https://t.co/jc6qJ11GJ6 — Shytoshi Kusama™ (@ShytoshiKusama) March 6, 2024 Regardless, SHIB has continued its bearish trajectory, with a market price now sitting at $0.00002916 at the time of writing. Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), a popular memecoin, has <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=all&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">experienced</a> a notable decline. It dropped nearly 20% over the past week and continued a 13% fall in just the past 24 hours. This downturn occurs amid a broader bearish trend across the crypto landscape.</p>
<p>However, detailed on-chain analysis has uncovered specific factors contributing to SHIB&#8217;s sharp decline.</p>

<h2>Whale Movements And Market Influence</h2>
<p>Insights from IntoTheBlock have shed light on large transaction activities, often indicative of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whale-1-25-trillion-shib/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">&#8220;whale&#8221; movements,</a> which have seen a general decrease since March 5, further compounding the downward pressure on SHIB&#8217;s price.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/u.today/sites/default/files/inline-images/15032024%200000.PNG?resize=1627%2C461&#038;ssl=1" alt="Decline whale activities." width="1627" height="461"  data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The role of speculative trading in influencing <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-optimistic-about-a-shiba-inu-short-term-surge-to-0-000066/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">SHIB&#8217;s market performance</a> has also become increasingly apparent. Data pointing to the holding time of transacted coins suggests a shift towards short-term trading strategies among investors, possibly in pursuit of quick profits.</p>
<p>Such behaviors are underscored by a significant reduction in the average holding period of coins, from four weeks to just two months as of mid-March, accompanied by a transaction volume of 2.12 trillion SHIB.</p>
<p>This trend towards speculative trading has been a key driver behind the memecoin&#8217;s recent price movements, reflecting the broader dynamics within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>The decrease in large transactions involving Shiba Inu signifies dwindling confidence among whales, whose actions can profoundly impact <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-price-skyrockets-heres-why/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">market direction</a>.</p>
<p>The observed decline in whale activities aligns with a broader caution in the crypto market, where investors reevaluate their positions amid shifting market conditions.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/VlYn5wEd/" alt="Shiba Inu (SHIB) price chart on TradingView" width="2770" height="1556"/>
<h2>Shiba Inu Bright Horizon</h2>
<p>Despite the current downturn, Shiba Inu remains a focal point within the altcoin sector, buoyed by optimistic predictions from crypto analysts.</p>

<p>Michaël van de Poppe, a well-regarded figure in the crypto analysis community, has recently <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/dogecoin-shiba-inu-pepe-explode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">posited that altcoins,  are set for significant rallies</a>, potentially positioning Shiba Inu for a notable rebound as the market stabilizes.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">There&#8217;s still around 40-60% market capitalization to gain for the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Altcoins</a>.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s going to be a fun ride for the altcoins in the coming period. <a href="https://t.co/qT0FRU4qpY" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/qT0FRU4qpY</a></p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1765728607010234712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 7, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>This sentiment is echoed by Shiba Inu&#8217;s co-founder, Shytoshi Kusama, who has <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-lead-dev-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">expressed confidence in SHIB&#8217;s ability</a> to lead in the next bull market, citing the project&#8217;s comprehensive plans, community support, and execution as key differentiators.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">No. The community with the strongest tech, vision, plan, supporters, partners, and execution will. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SHIB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#SHIB</a> But if you wanted some impressions why not say hi? <a href="https://t.co/jc6qJ11GJ6" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">https://t.co/jc6qJ11GJ6</a></p>
<p>— Shytoshi Kusama<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@ShytoshiKusama) <a href="https://twitter.com/ShytoshiKusama/status/1765358580985675904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Regardless, SHIB has continued its bearish trajectory, with a market price now sitting at $0.00002916 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SHIB-Shibarium.jpg?fit=350%2C250" width="350" height="250" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598080</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Key Trend Driving Altcoin Market Toward $425 Billion: Analyst</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/key-trend-driving-altcoin-market-toward-425-billion-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godspower Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot Exchange-Traded Funds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Technology Firm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jan3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MSTR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rekt Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Samson Mow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Amid the bullish sentiment around the crypto landscape, the Altcoin overall market cap has displayed positive strength as many investors and traders are throwing capital into several altcoins ahead of the bull cycle.  Altcoin Market To Rally Toward $425 Billion Since Bitcoin has surged to a new record high, many cryptocurrency analysts anticipate a surge in the altcoin market cap. Rekt Capital, a cryptocurrency expert and trader, has shared a positive prediction regarding the altcoins market cap with the community on X. The expert analysis delves into the current state of the market and its potential to surge higher in the coming months. His projections came in light of the altcoin season index showing advancement, which suggests that its season is almost here. Related Reading: Crypto Analyst Projects $7 Trillion Market Cap For Altcoins – Here’s When According to the analyst, the market has been &#8220;redirected into the blue-circled testing area,&#8221; which was caused by rejection from the &#8220;red-circled circle zone.&#8221; However, the market has rebounded since then, indicating an increased interest from market investors. Furthermore, Rekt Capital noted that the market has surpassed the &#8220;$315 billion red line of resistance.&#8221; As a result, the red line resistance level has now been changed to a &#8220;new support level.&#8221; Due to this, the crypto analyst anticipates a surge to the &#8220;light blue circle&#8221; at the $425 billion threshold in the upcoming months. The post read: The red-circled area rejected the Altcoin Market back into the blue-circled retesting zone. Since then, the Altcoin Market Cap has recovered, broken beyond the red $315bn resistance, and turned recently into new support. Next is the light blue circle, over time. However, Rekt Capital also asserted in another recent post that the &#8220;$315 billion mark is still being retested by alts market cap new support.&#8221; It has been unable to move past it despite today&#8217;s double-digit declines on several altcoins. Even though the market is still retesting the aforementioned level, Rekt Capital is confident that it will &#8220;revisit the $425 billion resistance&#8221; soon. He anticipates the market revisiting the level before the Bitcoin Halving event, expected to take place in April. Alts Gains Are Sustable And Likely To Crash Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Bitcoin technology firm JAN3, Samson Mow, has also shared his insights regarding the altcoin market. Despite anticipating a rise in the altcoin market, Mow highlighted that he expects alts to &#8220;crash in the upcoming weeks.&#8221;  Related Reading: Altcoin Market Cap Break From “Wyckoff Accumulation Phase”: Will Ethereum, XRP Fly? According to Mow, alts have been monitoring the &#8220;increase in Bitcoin&#8221; after launching BTC Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). However, altcoins do not possess &#8220;the $500 million to $1 billion&#8221; daily inflows seen with Bitcoin. Consequently, this should be the &#8220;major sign&#8221; that their gains &#8220;can not&#8221; be maintained. &#8220;MSTR has a $30 billion market cap, Solana is $73 billion. That is absurd. A correction is overdue,&#8221; he added. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the bullish sentiment around the crypto landscape, the Altcoin overall market cap has displayed positive strength as many investors and traders are throwing capital into several <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/top-3-altcoins-that-will-ride-the-2024-bull-wave-wif-scorpion-casino-and-pepe-fork-show-bullish-signs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">altcoins</a> ahead of the bull cycle. </p>
<h2>Altcoin Market To Rally Toward $425 Billion</h2>
<p>Since Bitcoin has surged to a new record high, many cryptocurrency analysts anticipate a surge in the altcoin market cap. Rekt Capital, a cryptocurrency expert and trader, has <a href="https://x.com/rektcapital/status/1768221258905170100?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> a positive prediction regarding the altcoins market cap with the community on X. </p>
<p>The expert analysis delves into the current state of the market and its potential to surge higher in the coming months. His projections came in light of the altcoin season index showing advancement, which suggests that its season is almost here.</p>

<p>According to the analyst, the market has been &#8220;redirected into the blue-circled testing area,&#8221; which was caused by rejection from the &#8220;red-circled circle zone.&#8221; However, the market has rebounded since then, indicating an increased <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ethereum/ethereum-altcoins-witnessing-whale-interest/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">interest</a> from market investors.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-598051 size-large" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C607" alt="Altcoin" width="860" height="607" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=1794 1794w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C607 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=120 120w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Rekt-Capital-Altcoin-Chart.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>Furthermore, Rekt Capital noted that the market has surpassed the &#8220;$315 billion red line of resistance.&#8221; As a result, the red line resistance level has now been changed to a &#8220;new support level.&#8221; Due to this, the crypto analyst anticipates a surge to the &#8220;light blue circle&#8221; at the $425 billion threshold in the upcoming months.</p>
<p>The post read:</p>
<blockquote><p>The red-circled area rejected the Altcoin Market back into the blue-circled retesting zone. Since then, the Altcoin Market Cap has recovered, broken beyond the red $315bn resistance, and turned recently into new support. Next is the light blue circle, over time.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Rekt Capital also asserted in another recent <a href="https://x.com/rektcapital/status/1768574715172446469?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> that the &#8220;$315 billion mark is still being retested by alts market cap new support.&#8221; It has been unable to move past it despite today&#8217;s double-digit declines on several altcoins.</p>
<p>Even though the market is still retesting the aforementioned level, Rekt Capital is confident that it will &#8220;revisit the $425 billion resistance&#8221; soon. He anticipates the market revisiting the level before the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/5-best-altcoins-to-not-miss-before-bitcoin-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Halving</a> event, expected to take place in April.</p>
<h2>Alts Gains Are Sustable And Likely To Crash</h2>
<p>Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Bitcoin technology firm JAN3, Samson Mow, has also <a href="https://x.com/Excellion/status/1768032607948997009?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">shared</a> his insights regarding the altcoin market. Despite anticipating a rise in the altcoin market, Mow highlighted that he expects alts to &#8220;crash in the upcoming weeks.&#8221; </p>

<p>According to Mow, alts have been monitoring the &#8220;increase in Bitcoin&#8221; after launching BTC Spot Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). However, altcoins do not possess &#8220;the $500 million to $1 billion&#8221; daily inflows seen with Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Consequently, this should be the &#8220;major sign&#8221; that their <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/stack-these-top-3-cheap-altcoins-for-potential-explosive-returns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">gains</a> &#8220;can not&#8221; be maintained. &#8220;MSTR has a $30 billion market cap, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-open-interest-plunges-20-what-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana</a> is $73 billion. That is absurd. A correction is overdue,&#8221; he added.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/6tX3gvPe/" alt="Altcoin" width="2273" height="1351"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/WhatsApp-Image-2024-02-29-at-10.27.55-AM.jpeg?fit=390%2C280" width="390" height="280" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598042</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analyst Predicts Further Upside For Shiba Inu, Here’s The Target</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-shiba-inu-target/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 23:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu is currently on a consolidation path after a strong upswing earlier in the month. Specifically, SHIB is currently down by 13% in the past seven days, although still up by 210% in a wider 30-day time frame. According to crypto analyst Javon Marks, Shiba Inu is on its way to another major breakout after the current consolidation. The analyst sees the meme coin surging to $0.000081, and then a further 90% increase to hit a new all-time high. Continued Uptrend For Shiba Inu Shiba Inu has seen massive gains recently, rallying 280% from $0.00001178 on the last day of February to $0.00004456 on March 5. This surge allowed the dog meme coin to outperform most cryptocurrencies amidst a wider bull market, taking a lot of traders by surprise. This price surge was accompanied by an increase in trading volume. Kaiko data reveals that Shiba Inu saw the largest volume among meme coins at $31 billion in just one week. Related Reading: Dogecoin Open Interest Maintains Record Highs, Is A Crash Coming? However, according to social media posts, analyst Javon Marks had predicted a surge as far back as October 2023, with a SHIB price target of $0.000081. In a recent update to his prediction, Javon noted that the price is set for even more growth, with the breakout target of $0.000081 still valid.  Since the attached and more original analysis, prices of $SHIB has shown MASSIVE STRENGTH, climbing approximately +531%, but these prices can be set for even more growth! With the breakout target still at $0.000081, prices of Shiba Inu could have another +147% move coming. A… https://t.co/ZjA5onlnBO pic.twitter.com/YuUllePvbl — JAVON⚡️MARKS (@JavonTM1) March 13, 2024 It&#8217;s interesting to note that SHIB has done approximately a 531% increase since Javon&#8217;s prediction in October. Furthermore, according to his analysis, a break and hold above $0.000081 could set the stage for another 90% upside to $0.0001553, a new all-time high for the meme coin. Current State Of Shiba Inu Shiba Inu has reversed since reaching $0.00004456 and has majorly traded between $0.0000365 and $0.0000295 in the past week. On-chain data points to a surge in trading volume during this time period. Particularly, IntoTheBlock&#8217;s large trader flow metric, which measures transactions greater than $100,000 has surged, reaching $578.11 million (17.62 trillion SHIB) on March 11th. The last 24 hours saw 9.94 trillion SHIB ($300.55 million) in large transactions.  Related Reading: Cardano Ready For Breakout As Network Adoption Hits Major Milestone While this surge in trading volume could mean an increased accumulation from large traders, it could also mean a selloff, as indicated by the recent drop in price. However, the crypto looks poised to resume price gains, and on-chain signals from ITB point to a bullish sentiment.  Lola, a SHIB enthusiast, listed on X, key factors that could contribute to the meme coin&#8217;s growth in the near future. These factors range from SHIB&#8217;s decentralization, global accessibility and adoption, its strong community, and an efficient deflationary burn mechanism. Notably, over 25.6 million SHIB tokens have been burnt in the past 24 hours. SHIB price retraces to $0.0000288 &#124; Source: SHIBUSDT on Tradingview.com Featured image from The Economic Times, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu is currently on a consolidation path after a strong <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/dogecoin-shiba-inu-pepe-explode/">upswing earlier in the month</a>. Specifically, SHIB is currently down by 13% in the past seven days, although still up by 210% in a wider 30-day time frame. According to crypto analyst Javon Marks, Shiba Inu is on its way to another major breakout after the current consolidation. The analyst sees the meme coin surging to $0.000081, and then a further 90% increase to hit a new all-time high.</p>
<h2>Continued Uptrend For Shiba Inu</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu has seen <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/shiba-inu-mania-price-surges-60-as-burn-rate-heats-up-by-over-22000/">massive gains recently</a>, rallying 280% from $0.00001178 on the last day of February to $0.00004456 on March 5. This surge allowed the dog meme coin to outperform most cryptocurrencies amidst a wider bull market, taking a lot of traders by surprise. This price surge was <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/shibarium-activity-skyrockets-by-30-with-shiba-inus-soaring-prices/">accompanied by an increase</a> in trading volume. Kaiko <a href="https://x.com/KaikoData/status/1767890872161694035?s=20" rel="nofollow">data </a>reveals that Shiba Inu saw the largest volume among meme coins at $31 billion in just one week.</p>

<p>However, according to social media posts, analyst Javon Marks had predicted a surge as far back as October 2023, with a SHIB price target of $0.000081. In a recent update to his prediction, Javon noted that the price is set for even more growth, with the breakout target of $0.000081 still valid. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Since the attached and more original analysis, prices of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$SHIB</a> has shown MASSIVE STRENGTH, climbing approximately +531%, but these prices can be set for even more growth!</p>
<p>With the breakout target still at $0.000081, prices of Shiba Inu could have another +147% move coming.</p>
<p>A… <a href="https://t.co/ZjA5onlnBO" rel="nofollow">https://t.co/ZjA5onlnBO</a> <a href="https://t.co/YuUllePvbl" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/YuUllePvbl</a></p>
<p>— JAVON<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />MARKS (@JavonTM1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JavonTM1/status/1768049122290929876?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 13, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>It&#8217;s interesting to note that SHIB has done approximately a 531% increase since Javon&#8217;s prediction in October. Furthermore, according to his analysis, a break and hold above $0.000081 could set the stage for another 90% upside to $0.0001553, a new all-time high for the meme coin.</p>
<h2>Current State Of Shiba Inu</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu has reversed since reaching $0.00004456 and has majorly traded between $0.0000365 and $0.0000295 in the past week. On-chain data points to a surge in trading volume during this time period. Particularly, <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/SHIB/deep-dive?group=financials&amp;chart=largeTransactions" rel="nofollow">IntoTheBlock&#8217;s </a>large trader flow metric, which measures transactions greater than $100,000 has surged, reaching $578.11 million (17.62 trillion SHIB) on March 11th. The last 24 hours saw 9.94 trillion SHIB ($300.55 million) in large transactions. </p>

<p>While this surge in trading volume could mean an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whales-shib/">increased accumulation</a> from large traders, it could also <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-pepe-whales-sold/" rel="nofollow">mean a selloff</a>, as indicated by the recent drop in price. However, the crypto looks poised to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-0-0001-target/" rel="nofollow">resume price gains</a>, and on-chain signals from ITB point to a bullish sentiment. </p>
<p>Lola, a SHIB enthusiast, <a href="https://x.com/CryptoLollla/status/1765527500380365287?s=20" rel="nofollow">listed on X</a>, key factors that could contribute to the meme coin&#8217;s growth in the near future. These factors range from SHIB&#8217;s decentralization, global accessibility and <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-shib-0-0008-ath/">adoption</a>, its strong community, and an efficient deflationary burn mechanism. Notably, over 25.6 million SHIB tokens <a href="https://www.shibburn.com/" rel="nofollow">have been burnt</a> in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/RvVMIBkP/" alt="Shiba Inu price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Shiba-Inu.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598030</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Analysts Foresee Another FLOKI Expansion Despite Market Drop</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/crypto-analysts-foresee-another-floki-expansion-despite-market-drop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubmar Garcia]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FLOKI and the dog-themed cryptocurrencies have been the talk of the town recently. BONK and dogwifhat (WIF) reached new all-time highs (ATH) this month, while the Viking dog-based token climbed to levels not seen since the previous bull run. During this rally, memecoins have soared alongside the rest of the cryptocurrencies. However, in the past 24 hours, the market went from flying to crashing as the prices of most cryptocurrencies followed the recent Bitcoin dip. Related Reading: Solana’s Biggest Memecoin Gains Over $680,000 In 3 Days As Investors Bet On Its Popularity Is FLOKI Ready To Continue Its Expansion? Last week, FLOKI, the fifth largest memecoin by market cap, soared by over 60% after announcing its listing in two major crypto exchanges in Asia and the Middle East. The news propelled the token’s price to $0.0002043. Crypto Analyst Byzantine General shared on X (formerly Twitter) his view on the token’s recent performance. According to the post, FLOKI was one of the few tokens that “held up nicely.” Based on that, Byzantine General observed that the price was consolidating before another expansion. One of the coins that held up nicely today is $FLOKI. Looks like it&#39;s just consolidating before another expansion. And lately it&#39;s basically been a higher beta $DOGE. pic.twitter.com/9MsrfInjvA &#8212; Byzantine General (@ByzGeneral) March 14, 2024 FLOKI has shown a rising trajectory this month, increasing 337% since March 1st. The chart in the post highlights the past four days, displaying that the Solana-based memecoin has consolidated between the $0.00026-$0.0003 price range. A broader look at the token’s price exhibits that it hovered between $0.000028-$0.000039 in the first two months of 2024 before breaking above the $0.000040 resistance level at the end of February. In the past 30 days, FLOKI has registered a stellar $649.4% growth. Similarly, the renowned trader and market analyst MacroCRG shared on X that “$FLOKI holding up like a mf chad” amid the market dip. According to the trader, the token will continue as one of the leaders “as long as the memecoin supercycle bid remains.” Market shits itself? It&#39;s oke, $FLOKI holding up like a mf chad New revamped roadmap coming soon + many product launches lined up for the rest of the year&#8230; As long as the memecoin supercycle bid remains&#8230; IMO @RealFlokiInu gonna continue being one of the leaders pic.twitter.com/2gsIE04Dkv &#8212; CRG (@MacroCRG) March 15, 2024 The analyst highlighted the project’s newly revamped roadmap as part of its “strengths.” Additionally, he pointed out that the web3 project has product launches lined up for the rest of the year. FLOKI’s Price Action The launch in the mainnet of the Valhalla Game, powered by FLOKI, is highly expected by the “Floki Vikings.” Undoubtedly, the community has shown massive support and confidence in the web3 project, as many expect it to skyrocket soon to a new ATH. The token’s price has closely followed the jumps and dips of BTC during the past seven days, as seen in the chart below. It registered a drop of 13.5% in the last 24 hours. BTC and FLOKI’s performance in the 7-day chart. Source: CoinGecko.com Coupled with the price drop, the daily trading volume decreased 21.3% to $837.2 million. Moreover, WIF recently flipped it, which took fourth place as the largest memecoin by market cap. By this metric, FLOKI’s $2.47 billion takes 52nd place in the global crypto market ranking after a 6.6% decrease in the last day. At writing time, FLOKI is trading at $0.000248. Despite the price decrease, the token still shows a remarkable 28.3% growth in the 7-day timeframe. Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin Price Down Today? 3 Key Reasons FLOKI is trading at $0.000248 in the 1-day chart. Source: FLOKIUSDT on TradingView.com Featured image from Unsplash.com, Chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">FLOKI and the dog-themed cryptocurrencies have been the talk of the town recently. BONK and dogwifhat (WIF) reached new all-time highs (ATH) this month, while the Viking dog-based token climbed to levels not seen since the previous bull run.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">During this rally, memecoins have soared alongside the rest of the cryptocurrencies. However, in the past 24 hours, the market went from flying to crashing as the prices of most cryptocurrencies followed the recent Bitcoin dip.</p>

<h2 style="font-weight: 400">Is FLOKI Ready To Continue Its Expansion?</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Last week, FLOKI, the fifth largest memecoin by market cap, soared by over 60% after announcing its <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/floki-skyrockets-to-new-all-time-high-soaring-60-following-two-major-listings/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">listing</a> in two major crypto exchanges in Asia and the Middle East. The news propelled the token’s price to $0.0002043.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Crypto Analyst Byzantine General shared on X (formerly Twitter) his view on the token’s recent performance. According to the post, FLOKI was one of the few tokens that “held up nicely.” Based on that, Byzantine General observed that the price was consolidating before another expansion.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">One of the coins that held up nicely today is <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24FLOKI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$FLOKI</a>. Looks like it&#39;s just consolidating before another expansion. And lately it&#39;s basically been a higher beta <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$DOGE</a>. <a href="https://t.co/9MsrfInjvA" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/9MsrfInjvA</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Byzantine General (@ByzGeneral) <a href="https://twitter.com/ByzGeneral/status/1768378307282706911?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 14, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">FLOKI has shown a rising trajectory this month, increasing 337% since March 1st. The chart in the post highlights the past four days, displaying that the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solana-tokens-among-top-gainers-jup-and-wen-soar-over-12-wif-hits-new-ath/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana-based</a> memecoin has consolidated between the $0.00026-$0.0003 price range.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">A broader look at the token’s price exhibits that it hovered between $0.000028-$0.000039 in the first two months of 2024 before breaking above the $0.000040 resistance level at the end of February. In the past 30 days, FLOKI has registered a stellar $649.4% growth.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Similarly, the renowned trader and market analyst MacroCRG shared on X that “$FLOKI holding up like a mf chad” amid the market dip. According to the trader, the token will continue as one of the leaders “as long as the memecoin supercycle bid remains.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Market shits itself? </p>
<p>It&#39;s oke, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24FLOKI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$FLOKI</a> holding up like a mf chad</p>
<p>New revamped roadmap coming soon + many product launches lined up for the rest of the year&#8230; </p>
<p>As long as the memecoin supercycle bid remains&#8230; IMO <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">@RealFlokiInu</a> gonna continue being one of the leaders <a href="https://t.co/2gsIE04Dkv" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/2gsIE04Dkv</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CRG (@MacroCRG) <a href="https://twitter.com/MacroCRG/status/1768624859267924235?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 15, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The analyst highlighted the project’s newly revamped roadmap as part of its “strengths.” Additionally, he pointed out that the web3 project has product launches lined up for the rest of the year.</p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">FLOKI’s Price Action</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The launch in the mainnet of the Valhalla Game, powered by FLOKI, is highly expected by the “Floki Vikings.” Undoubtedly, the community has shown massive support and confidence in the web3 project, as many <a href="https://x.com/smartestonx/status/1768334810525896725?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">expect</a> it to skyrocket soon to a new ATH.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The token’s price has closely followed the jumps and dips of BTC during the past seven days, as seen in the chart below. It registered a drop of 13.5% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-598085 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-15-a-las-8.23.25-a.-m.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C550" alt="BTC, FLOKI" width="860" height="550" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-15-a-las-8.23.25-a.-m.png?w=981 981w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-15-a-las-8.23.25-a.-m.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-15-a-las-8.23.25-a.-m.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-15-a-las-8.23.25-a.-m.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C550 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-15-a-las-8.23.25-a.-m.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">Coupled with the price drop, the daily trading volume decreased 21.3% to $837.2 million. Moreover, WIF recently flipped it, which took fourth place as the largest memecoin by market cap. By this metric, FLOKI’s $2.47 billion takes 52nd place in the global crypto market ranking after a 6.6% decrease in the last day.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">At writing time, FLOKI is trading at $0.000248. Despite the price decrease, the token still shows a remarkable 28.3% growth in the 7-day timeframe.</p>

<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-598083 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C433" alt="FLOKI, FLOKIUSDT, memecoin " width="860" height="433" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=1022 1022w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C433 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=360 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FLOKIUSDT_2024-03-15_08-12-18.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/markus-winkler-IrRbSND5EUc-unsplash.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598081</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bernstein Analysts Convinced Bitcoin Is Headed For $150,000, Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-headed-for-150000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Analysts from private wealth management firm, Bernstein have reaffirmed their previous Bitcoin prediction, emphasizing that the cryptocurrency has a greater chance to reach $150,000 by 2025.  Bitcoin $150,000 Price Forecast Grows Stronger Bernstein analysts Gautam Chhugani and Mahika Sapra said in a note to clients on Monday that they were now more convinced of Bitcoin’s exponential surge to new all-time highs at around $150,000 by mid-2025. The analyst’s statements were a reiteration of their earlier Bitcoin forecast in November 2023, when they predicted the price of Bitcoin to surge to $150,000. Related Reading: Crypto Expert Reveals Why XRP Is Primed For Growth In This Bull Market At the time, Bitcoin was trading around a price of $35,000, putting the analysts’ estimate at around five times the price of BTC. Now with BTC recently witnessing remarkable surges to new all time highs above $71,000, and potentially continuing its upward momentum, Bernstein analysts’ forecast seems more probable. Analysts from the private wealth investment firm have disclosed several factors that could trigger BTC&#8217;s bullish momentum. Highlighting the success and surging demand for Spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Funds (ETF), the company boldly affirmed that large volume of inflows into Spot Bitcoin ETFs could significantly contribute towards increasing the value of BTC.  “We estimated $10 billion inflows for 2024 and another $60 billion for 2025. In the last 40 trading days since the ETF launch on Jan 10, Bitcoin ETF inflows have crossed $9.5 billion already,” Bernstein analysts wrote.  Sharing the sentiment of most crypto analysts in the market, Bernstein analysts believe that the price of BTC could experience a fresh “break out” after the halving event in April 2024. At the time of writing, the cryptocurrency is trading at $68,218, witnessing a slight price correction of about 6.96% in the past 24 hours, according to CoinMarketCap.  Miners To Become Top Beneficiaries Of BTC Surge In their note, Bernstein analysts highlighted that investing in Bitcoin miners could be the best equity proxy to BTC. According to their analysis, BTC miners typically outperform during BTC bullish cycles and conversely underperform during bearish periods. Related Reading: Cardano Ready For Breakout As Network Adoption Hits Major Milestone As Bitcoin rapidly rises to all time highs above $71,000, Bernstein analysts expect that institutional interest in Bitcoin related equities could top over, with BTC miners becoming one of the largest beneficiaries. Despite various analysts predicting that the next Bitcoin halving could potentially become a death sentence to small mining companies and solo miners, Bernstein analysts have revealed that the rising price of BTC and elevated transaction fees could serve as a cushioning mechanism for miners during the halving period.  BTC price at $67,700 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from CryptoSlate, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Analysts from private wealth management firm, Bernstein have reaffirmed their previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-bulls-on-alert-top-analyst-anticipates-a-massive-rally-in-the-cards/">Bitcoin prediction</a>, emphasizing that the cryptocurrency has a greater chance to reach $150,000 by 2025. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin $150,000 Price Forecast Grows Stronger</h2>
<p>Bernstein analysts Gautam Chhugani and Mahika Sapra said in a note to clients on Monday that they were now more convinced of Bitcoin’s exponential surge to new all-time highs at around $150,000 by mid-2025. The analyst’s statements were a reiteration of their <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-to-hit-150k-by-2025-financial-firm/" rel="nofollow">earlier Bitcoin forecast</a> in November 2023, when they predicted the price of Bitcoin to surge to $150,000.</p>

<p>At the time, Bitcoin was <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-comeback-trading-desks-awaken/" rel="nofollow">trading around a price of $35,000</a>, putting the analysts’ estimate at around five times the price of BTC. Now with BTC recently witnessing remarkable <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-blasts-past-70000-in-wild-week-to-register-new-all-time-high/">surges to new all time highs</a> above $71,000, and potentially continuing its <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-primed-for-parabolic-ride-experts-say/" rel="nofollow">upward momentum</a>, Bernstein analysts’ forecast seems more probable.</p>
<p>Analysts from the private wealth investment firm have disclosed several factors that could trigger BTC&#8217;s bullish momentum. Highlighting the success and surging demand for <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-markets-swell-in-2024-spotlight-bitcoin-etfs/" rel="nofollow">Spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Funds (ETF)</a>, the company boldly affirmed that large volume of inflows into Spot Bitcoin ETFs could significantly contribute towards increasing the value of BTC. </p>
<p>“We estimated $10 billion inflows for 2024 and another $60 billion for 2025. In the last 40 trading days since the ETF launch on Jan 10, Bitcoin ETF inflows have crossed $9.5 billion already,” Bernstein analysts wrote. </p>
<p>Sharing the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-halving-is-200-days-away-this-happens-every-time-is-it-time-to-doubledown/">sentiment</a> of most crypto analysts in the market, Bernstein analysts believe that the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-peak-december-over-200000/" rel="nofollow">price of BTC</a> could experience a fresh “break out” after the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/when-is-the-next-btc-halving-date-bitcoin-halving-guide/">halving event in April 2024. </a>At the time of writing, the cryptocurrency is trading at $68,218, witnessing a slight price correction of about 6.96% in the past 24 hours, according to CoinMarketCap. </p>
<h2>Miners To Become Top Beneficiaries Of BTC Surge</h2>
<p>In their note, Bernstein analysts highlighted that investing in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-investment-strategies-shift-with-1-billion-surge/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin miners</a> could be the best equity proxy to BTC. According to their analysis, BTC miners typically outperform during <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/the-price-peak-puzzle-unraveling-the-timing-of-bitcoin-bull-market-peak/">BTC bullish cycles</a> and conversely underperform during bearish periods.</p>

<p>As Bitcoin rapidly rises to all time highs above $71,000, Bernstein analysts expect that institutional interest in Bitcoin related equities could top over, with <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-miners-enjoy-2nd-highest-daily-revenue-ever/" rel="nofollow">BTC miners becoming one of the largest beneficiaries. </a>Despite various analysts predicting that the next <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-pre-halving-danger-zone/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin halving</a> could potentially <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-halving-havoc-only-a-few-miners-may-survive/" rel="nofollow">become a death sentence to small mining companies</a> and solo miners, Bernstein analysts have revealed that the rising price of BTC and elevated transaction fees could serve as a cushioning mechanism for miners during the halving period. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/YAEKqxPq/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_474d43.jpeg?fit=310%2C163" width="310" height="163" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598027</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin To $53,200? Why History Says It&#8217;s Possible</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-to-53200-why-history-says-its-possible/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin crash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Realized Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Cost Basis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin short-term holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As Bitcoin drops below $68,000, history suggests this correction is rather tame for bull markets, as plunges to this deep on-chain level have been the norm. Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Realized Price Is Currently Around $53,200 As pointed out by CryptoQuant Netherlands community manager Maartunn in a post on X, BTC still has a decent margin over the realized price of the short-term holders. The &#8220;realized price&#8221; is an on-chain metric that keeps track of the average price at which the Bitcoin investors acquired their coins. The indicator calculates this value by going through the transaction history of each coin and assuming that the last transfer of it was the last time it was purchased (that is, the price at the time is its current cost basis). Related Reading: Why Is Bitcoin Price Down Today? 3 Key Reasons When the spot value of the cryptocurrency dips below the realized price, it means that the average investor is now in a state of loss. On the other hand, a break above implies the market as a whole has entered into net profits. In the context of the current discussion, the realized price for only a particular segment of the investors is of interest: the &#8220;short-term holders&#8221; (STHs). The STHs include all the investors who bought their coins within the past 155 days. Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price specifically for this cohort: Looks like the value of the metric has been trending up recently &#124; Source: @JA_Maartun on X As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin STH realized price has shot up recently as the price of the asset has gone up. This makes sense, as this group includes the most recent buyers, who would continuously be buying at higher prices in an uptrend, thus raising their average cost basis. At present, this cohort&#8217;s realized price is about $53,200. During the past day, BTC has seen a sharp drop that has taken its price below the $68,000 mark, but clearly, the STHs would still be in high profits even after this drawdown. &#8220;In previous bull markets, the average cost basis of short-term holders was fully reset multiple times,&#8221; explains Maartunn. This trend is most prominent in the data for the 2017 bull run when the price retested this level several times. An interesting pattern that has been held is that these retests of the level during bull trends have generally resulted in the cryptocurrency finding support and turning itself back around. The explanation for this trend may lie in the fickle nature of the STHs. The cost basis is an important level for these investors, and when a retest of it happens, they panic and show some reaction. Related Reading: Brace For Impact: MicroStrategy Is Planning Another $500 Million Bitcoin Purchase During uptrends, these holders are more likely to buy more when a retest of their cost basis occurs since they may think that the same price levels that were profitable earlier will be so again in the near future. Naturally, it&#8217;s not a certainty that Bitcoin would also end up retesting this level in this bull market. Still, a correction might reach close to it if the historical precedent is anything to go by. BTC Price Following its 7% drop in the past day, Bitcoin is trading at around $67,700. The price of the coin has registered a sharp drop over the last 24 hours &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Maxim Hopman on Unsplash.com, CryptoQuant.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Bitcoin drops below $68,000, history suggests this correction is rather tame for bull markets, as plunges to this deep on-chain level have been the norm.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Realized Price Is Currently Around $53,200</h2>
<p>As pointed out by CryptoQuant Netherlands community manager Maartunn in a <a href="https://twitter.com/JA_Maartun/status/1768547107437154332/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, BTC still has a decent margin over the realized price of the short-term holders.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-under-realized-price-163-days/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">realized price</a>&#8221; is an on-chain metric that keeps track of the average price at which the Bitcoin investors acquired their coins. The indicator calculates this value by going through the transaction history of each coin and assuming that the last transfer of it was the last time it was purchased (that is, the price at the time is its current cost basis).</p>

<p>When the spot value of the cryptocurrency dips below the realized price, it means that the average investor is now in a state of loss. On the other hand, a break above implies the market as a whole has entered into net profits.</p>
<p>In the context of the current discussion, the realized price for only a particular segment of the investors is of interest: the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-short-term-holders-2-6-btc-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">short-term holders</a>&#8221; (STHs). The STHs include all the investors who bought their coins within the past 155 days.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin realized price specifically for this cohort:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GIsi9o_XoAA-msc?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin Short-Term Holder Realized Price" width="4096" height="2580"/></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the Bitcoin STH realized price has shot up recently as the price of the asset has gone up. This makes sense, as this group includes the most recent buyers, who would continuously be buying at higher prices in an uptrend, thus raising their average cost basis.</p>
<p>At present, this cohort&#8217;s realized price is about $53,200. During the past day, BTC has seen a sharp drop that has taken its price below the $68,000 mark, but clearly, the STHs would still be in high profits even after this drawdown.</p>
<p>&#8220;In previous bull markets, the average cost basis of short-term holders was fully reset multiple times,&#8221; explains Maartunn. This trend is most prominent in the data for the 2017 bull run when the price retested this level several times.</p>
<p>An interesting pattern that has been held is that these retests of the level during bull trends have generally resulted in the cryptocurrency finding support and turning itself back around.</p>
<p>The explanation for this trend may lie in the fickle nature of the STHs. The cost basis is an important level for these investors, and when a retest of it happens, they panic and show some reaction.</p>

<p>During uptrends, these holders are more likely to buy more when a retest of their cost basis occurs since they may think that the same price levels that were profitable earlier will be so again in the near future.</p>
<p>Naturally, it&#8217;s not a certainty that Bitcoin would also end up retesting this level in this bull market. Still, a correction might reach close to it if the historical precedent is anything to go by.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Following its 7% drop in the past day, Bitcoin is trading at around $67,700.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/3P7y3J1n/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/maxim-hopman-fiXLQXAhCfk-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598000</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Pundit Says God Candle Is Imminent For This Solana-Based Meme Coin</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/god-candle-solana-meme-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MYRO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MYRO news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=598028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The crypto analyst who correctly called Dogwifhat’s (WIF) parabolic run has identified another Solana-based meme coin that could see a significant move to the upside. The analyst further suggested that WIF and this crypto token have striking similarities.  A ‘God Candle’ Incoming For Myro Meme Coin Crypto analyst Bluntz Capital mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that it won’t be long before the Myro (MYRO) token sees a god candle. The analyst added that everyone would wish they had bought the meme coin when it finally breaks its current all-time high of $0.4 and “starts doing rapid multiples.” Related Reading: Brace For Impact: MicroStrategy Is Planning Another $500 Million Bitcoin Purchase In a previous X post, Bluntz had suggested that MYRO is the next Solana-based meme coin to take off following WIF’s run to the top. The analyst had correctly predicted that WIF would attain the heights it is currently at right from when it was still trading at around $0.29. Back then, he stated that the meme coin would go “turbo parabolic.” Bluntz suggested that MYRO could follow a similar trajectory to WIF’s rise as he highlighted that both meme coins have the same chart pattern. MYRO, making a similar run to WIFs, could see it become the latest meme coin to join the billion-dollar club in terms of market cap. MYRO’s market cap currently stands at $340 million.  Meanwhile, Bluntz isn’t the only analyst that MYRO could see a parabolic price surge soon enough. Crypto analyst Crypto Shadow also hinted that the meme coin will likely go “parabolic” soon enough. He believes this move to the upside will see MYRO rank with top meme coins like Dogecoin (DOGE), Pepe (PEPE), and FLOKI.  Solana-Based WIF’s Insane Run WIF, another Solana-based meme coin, is currently having an insane run, similar to the kind of run other top meme coins like DOGE and Shiba Inu (SHIB) enjoyed during their breakout year in 2021. As a result, WIF is currently enjoying a year-to-date (YTD) gain of over 1,700%, making it one of the most profitable crypto tokens since the beginning of 2024.  Related Reading: Crypto Expert Reveals Why XRP Is Primed For Growth In This Bull Market WIF’s run has also seen it surpass BONK as the most valuable Solana meme coin, boasting a market cap of over $3 billion to BONK’s $2 billion. WIF now ranks as the fourth-largest by market cap, behind DOGE, SHIB, and PEPE. However, if it somehow sustains this bullish momentum, it could soon surpass PEPE.  Bluntz previously mentioned that WIF will flip at least two meme coins in this market cycle (it already flipped BONK) and further suggested that it could rise to become the second most valuable meme coin, only behind DOGE.  MYRO price at $0.32 &#124; Source: MYROUSDT on Tradingview.com Featured image from CoinMarketCap, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto analyst who correctly called <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogwifhat-wif-meme-coin-las-vegas-sphere/" rel="nofollow">Dogwifhat’s (WIF)</a> parabolic run has identified another <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coins-myro-wif/" rel="nofollow">Solana-based meme coin </a>that could see a significant move to the upside. The analyst further suggested that WIF and this crypto token <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/similarities-dogecoin-and-pepe/" rel="nofollow">have striking similarities</a>. </p>
<h2>A ‘God Candle’ Incoming For Myro Meme Coin</h2>
<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coin-trader/" rel="nofollow">Crypto analyst Bluntz Capital</a> mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://x.com/Bluntz_Capital/status/1768197923274367144?s=20" rel="nofollow">post</a> that it won’t be long before the Myro (MYRO) token sees a god candle. The analyst added that everyone would wish they had bought the meme coin when it finally breaks its current all-time high of $0.4 and “starts doing rapid multiples.”</p>

<p>In a previous <a href="https://x.com/Bluntz_Capital/status/1767952081506472384?s=20" rel="nofollow">X post</a>, Bluntz had suggested that MYRO is the next Solana-based meme coin to take off following WIF’s run to the top. The analyst had <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/wif-dogecoin-shiba-inu-parabolic/" rel="nofollow">correctly predicted</a> that WIF would attain the heights it is currently at right from when it was still trading at around $0.29. Back then, he stated that the meme coin would go “turbo parabolic.”</p>
<p>Bluntz suggested that MYRO could follow a similar trajectory to WIF’s rise as he <a href="https://x.com/Bluntz_Capital/status/1767956628584997048?s=20" rel="nofollow">highlighted</a> that both meme coins have the same chart pattern. MYRO, making a similar run to WIFs, could see it become the latest meme coin to join the billion-dollar club in terms of market cap. MYRO’s market cap currently stands at $340 million. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bluntz isn’t the only analyst that MYRO could see a parabolic price surge soon enough. Crypto analyst Crypto Shadow <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coin-parabolic-rally/" rel="nofollow">also hinted</a> that the meme coin will likely go “parabolic” soon enough. He believes this move to the upside will see MYRO rank with top meme coins like <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/similarities-dogecoin-and-pepe/" rel="nofollow">Dogecoin (DOGE), Pepe (PEPE)</a>, and FLOKI. </p>
<h2>Solana-Based WIF’s Insane Run</h2>
<p>WIF, another Solana-based meme coin, is currently having an insane run, similar to the kind of run other top meme coins like DOGE and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-price-0-0001-target/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> enjoyed during their <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-10-largest-meme-coin/" rel="nofollow">breakout year</a> in 2021. As a result, WIF is currently enjoying a year-to-date (YTD) gain of over 1,700%, making it one of the most profitable crypto tokens since the beginning of 2024. </p>

<p>WIF’s run has also seen it <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/why-bonk-keeps-on-rising-price-explodes-124-today-heres-the-scoop/">surpass BONK</a> as the most valuable Solana meme coin, boasting a market cap of over $3 billion to BONK’s $2 billion. WIF now ranks as the fourth-largest by market cap, behind DOGE, SHIB, and PEPE. However, if it somehow sustains this bullish momentum, it could soon surpass PEPE. </p>
<p>Bluntz <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-based-wif-meme-coins/" rel="nofollow">previously mentioned</a> that WIF will flip at least two meme coins in this market cycle (it already flipped BONK) and further suggested that it could rise to become the second most valuable meme coin, only behind DOGE. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/X7eoA99u/" alt="MYRO price chart from Tradingview.com (Solana)" width="3286" height="1530"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Solana-meme-coin-1.jpeg?fit=300%2C168" width="300" height="168" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598028</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
