<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>BeInCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://beincrypto.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://beincrypto.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:54:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/cropped-bic_favic-32x32.png</url>
	<title>BeInCrypto</title>
	<link>https://beincrypto.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Price Confirms First Downtrend In Seven Months &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-confirms-downtrend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaryamann Shrivastava]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX) Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron price is struggling to recover with the bearish market cues getting stronger for the asset. Will TRX continue to decline or make a recovery soon?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-confirms-downtrend/">Tron (TRX) Price Confirms First Downtrend In Seven Months &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The Tron (TRX) price took a downturn towards the end of February, just as most of the crypto market began trending upwards, with many even marking new all-time highs.</strong></p>



<p>This bearishness will likely continue going forward as trend indicators signal a drawdown for the altcoin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tron-price-downtrend-begins">Tron Price Downtrend Begins</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-analysis-bearish/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tron price was noting a potential rise</a> over the past week, which failed to trigger a recovery for the asset. The ongoing decline has considerably impacted the overall growth of the crypto asset and the network. </p>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-founder-justin-sun-bitcoin-holdings/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The project is losing traction</a> among users, which can be observed by the fall in the number of users on the network. Weekly average users have taken a hit in the past two weeks, falling by 10% from 5.79 million to 5.25 million.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" width="850" height="354" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-850x354.png" alt="Tron Weekly Users. " class="wp-image-489507" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-850x354.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-360x150.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-768x320.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-1536x639.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514-150x62.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-134514.png 1756w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Tron Weekly Users. Source: <a href="https://dune.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Dune</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Additionally, a chunk of the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/stablecoin-firm-cease-tron-blockchain-support-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">TRX supply is awaiting a profit trigger</a>, which, by its looks, will not take place anytime soon. About 1.36 billion TRX bought within the $0.1165 to $0.1205 range is hanging in uncertainty and might fall back into the loss-bearing territory.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/buy-tron/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Buy TRON (TRX) and Everything You Need To Know</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="850" height="273" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-850x273.png" alt="Tron GIOM. " class="wp-image-489508" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-850x273.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-360x116.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-768x246.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-1536x493.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199-150x48.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-199.png 1580w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Tron GIOM. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/">Into</a><a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TheBlock</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>This is because all signals point towards potential decline, which would turn the aforementioned price range into a resistance zone.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-trx-price-prediction-one-downtrend-ends-another-begins">TRX Price Prediction: One Downtrend Ends, Another Begins</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/stablecoin-firm-cease-tron-blockchain-support-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tron&#8217;s price is trading at $0.1174</a> at the time of writing after failing to breach the barrier marked at $0.1219. The decline, while seemingly halted, is potentially set to continue going forward. This is because the crypto asset that has been trading below the Ichimoku Cloud is now noting a confirmed downtrend.</p>



<p>The Ichimoku Cloud is a technical analysis tool that indicates support, resistance, trend direction, and momentum. Generally, when the price is below the cloud, bearish outcomes are possible; however, as the cloud turns bearish, the asset is expected to trade further lower.</p>



<p>Such is the case with <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/tronlink-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tron price as well since the Ichimoku Cloud</a> turned red over the last 48 hours. This is a signal confirming a downtrend for TRX, making this the first such instance in seven months since August 2023.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="850" height="373" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-850x373.png" alt="TRX/USDT 12-hour chart. " class="wp-image-489506" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-850x373.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-360x158.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-768x337.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-1536x675.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg-150x66.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/PtRlzXwg.png 1755w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">TRX/USDT 12-hour chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Thus, Tron&#8217;s price could note a further decline, potentially sending it to test the support level of $0.1123.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/trx-wallet/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">7 Best Tron Wallets for Storing TRX Tokens</a></strong></p>



<p>On the other hand, Ichimoku Cloud is known to be a leading indicator, and given the recent attempt at recovery, TRX might stabilize for a while. If so, Tron&#8217;s price could observe consolidation and continue moving sideways, potentially breaching $0.1219, invalidating the bearish thesis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/tron-price-confirms-downtrend/">Tron (TRX) Price Confirms First Downtrend In Seven Months &#8211; What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bic_TRON_neutral_3.png" medium="image" width="5120" height="2880" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bic_TRON_neutral_3.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>X (Twitter) AI Grok Hints at Dogecoin Payments</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-ai-grok-dogecoin-doge-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ali M.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AI Grok's conflicting responses on Dogecoin payments on X (Twitter) spotlight the potential for future cryptocurrency integration and the dynamic role of digital currencies in social media.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-ai-grok-dogecoin-doge-payments/">X (Twitter) AI Grok Hints at Dogecoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>X&#8217;s (formerly Twitter) AI, Grok, has opened up new possibilities for cryptocurrency enthusiasts. With a nod towards enhancing user financial interactions, Grok suggested that users can engage in Dogecoin (DOGE) transactions directly through the platform. </strong></p>



<p>This notion hints at X&#8217;s leap into the cryptocurrency market, placing Dogecoin alongside traditional payment methods.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-grok-suggests-dogecoin-payments-on-x-twitter">Grok Suggests Dogecoin Payments on X (Twitter)</h2>



<p>When <a href="https://x.com/kingthies/status/1772104656518566196?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">asked</a>, &#8220;Can I send or receive DOGE on X?,&#8221; the mobile version of Grok said the process is remarkably straightforward for those looking to engage in DOGE transactions. </p>



<p>According to X&#8217;s generative AI, users wishing to send <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/buy-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dogecoin</a> must first ensure their X wallet is funded with DOGE. By selecting the &#8220;Send&#8221; option within the app, users can then enter the recipient&#8217;s X username or their unique Dogecoin wallet address, specify the amount, and finalize the transaction. </p>



<p>Receiving DOGE follows a similar user-friendly procedure. Grok suggested that by accessing the &#8220;Receive&#8221; function, users are presented with their exclusive Dogecoin wallet address, which can be shared with potential senders or linked to their X username, facilitating the receipt of funds.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">FULFILL THE PROPHECY <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE</a> <a href="https://t.co/J3fweq2hKH">pic.twitter.com/J3fweq2hKH</a></p>&mdash; Crypto Thies (@kingthies) <a href="https://twitter.com/kingthies/status/1772104656518566196?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>However, the desktop version of Grok painted a different picture, stating that <a href="https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-dogecoin-doge/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">X currently does not support direct Dogecoin</a> transactions. It hinted at possible future integration, advising users to keep an eye on updates from X and Elon Musk.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“At the moment, there is no direct support for sending or receiving Dogecoin (DOGE) on the X platform. However, recent developments and rumors suggest that crypto assets like DOGE could be integrated into the platform&#8217;s payment offerings in the future. It&#8217;s essential to stay updated with the latest news and announcements from X and Elon Musk to be informed about any changes or updates regarding Dogecoin integration,” the desktop version of Grok stated.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>This discrepancy raises questions about the platform&#8217;s direction concerning cryptocurrency integration and its support for Dogecoin. </p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/doge-dogecoin-price-prediction-2019-2020-5-years-updated-04-28-19-doge-usd-reaches-resistance/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Prediction 2024 / 2025 / 2030</a></strong></p>



<p>This news could signal a significant shift for DOGE holders in how they use and accept the altcoin for payments. Indeed, such an integration could solidify Dogecoin&#8217;s position within the crypto market as more than a meme coin. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/x-twitter-ai-grok-dogecoin-doge-payments/">X (Twitter) AI Grok Hints at Dogecoin Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Up.png" medium="image" width="2560" height="1440" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-Up.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Country Plans to Shift its Focus Away From Bitcoin Mining</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/country-plans-shift-away-bitcoin-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ryan James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Iceland considers pivoting from its thriving Bitcoin mining sector to prioritize food security and sustainable energy. Prime Minister Katrín Jakobsdóttir expresses concerns over energy consumption's impact, prompting reevaluation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/country-plans-shift-away-bitcoin-mining/">This Country Plans to Shift its Focus Away From Bitcoin Mining</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>In a significant shift that may redefine its economic landscape, Iceland is contemplating a move away from its burgeoning Bitcoin mining sector. The country will address more pressing concerns related to food security and energy sustainability. </strong></p>



<p>Prime Minister Katrín Jakobsdóttir voiced her apprehensions about the nation&#8217;s energy consumption patterns. Especially in light of the increasing demands from the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6432a24b-b7c4-4c2f-85a8-79108dbe0644" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">cryptocurrency mining industry</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-bitcoin-mining-threatens-iceland-s-sustainability-pm-warns">Bitcoin Mining Threatens Iceland&#8217;s Sustainability, PM Warns</h2>



<p>Iceland, nestled atop the Mid-Atlantic ridge, is a haven for Bitcoin miners, thanks to its abundant renewable energy resources. The country&#8217;s vast reserves of hydro and geothermal energy have made it an attractive destination for data centers dedicated to the energy-intensive process of Bitcoin mining. </p>



<p>However, this has led to an unprecedented surge in energy consumption. Currently, the country consumes about 120 MW of power, making it the most <a href="https://beincrypto.com/iceland-leads-the-world-in-bitcoin-mining-but-not-everyone-is-thrilled/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin-mining-dense region globally</a>.</p>



<p>The Prime Minister expressed concerns over the sustainability of this energy consumption, especially considering the adverse impacts on other vital sectors like agriculture. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Data centers in Iceland use a significant share of our green energy,&#8221; Jakobsdóttir remarked, </p>
</blockquote>



<p>This revelation comes at a time when the global balance of Bitcoin mining is experiencing a shift. <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bitcoin-mining-invests-texas-facility-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">New players are continuously entering the mining scene</a>. Thanks to its cheap electricity and entrepreneurial spirit, Iceland, once a pioneer in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/iceland-largest-bitcoin-hash-rate-producer-capita/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">industrial-scale Bitcoin mining</a>, is now reevaluating its stance in light of broader economic and environmental considerations.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/bitcoin-mining-from-home/">Bitcoin Mining From Home: Is It Possible in 2024?</a></strong></p>



<p>The island&#8217;s alarming reliance on imports for basic food staples underscores the decision. With only 1% of grains and 43% of vegetables produced domestically. Jakobsdóttir&#8217;s proposed pivot towards bolstering food production signifies a strategic redirection of Iceland&#8217;s renewable energy resources to support more sustainable and essential sectors. This will ensure energy security for households and industries beyond crypto mining.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-mining-industry-prepares-for-post-halving-shake-up">Crypto Mining Industry Prepares for Post-Halving Shake-Up</h2>



<p>This strategic shift is reflective of a broader trend within the crypto-mining industry. Which is bracing for significant changes after the anticipated <a href="https://beincrypto.com/bitcoin-mining-stock-soars-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin halving event in April</a>. Industry experts, including Marathon Digital Holdings CEO Fred Thiel, have warned of the impending <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2024/03/22/large-scale-bitcoin-miners-are-competing-head-on-with-ai-companies-for-power-marathon-digital-ceo.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">financial pressures on smaller miners</a>. Which could lead to a consolidation in favor of larger players with more robust financial backing.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“Post halving I think you’ll see the smaller miners come under financial stress, which will enable the bigger miners to consolidate the industry,” Thiel stated.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>In navigating a crucial change, Iceland views its shift as more than just a way to secure energy and food. It&#8217;s also a sign of its dedication to sustainable growth. </p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/how-much-electricity-bitcoin-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How Much Electricity Does Bitcoin Mining Use?</a></strong></p>



<p>Hence, Iceland is redirecting its renewable energy from crypto mining to vital fields such as agriculture. This move showcases Iceland&#8217;s ability to merge tech progress with eco-friendly practices and economic stability.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/country-plans-shift-away-bitcoin-mining/">This Country Plans to Shift its Focus Away From Bitcoin Mining</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ecoway-crypto-green-mining.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ecoway-crypto-green-mining.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BloFin Announces Platinum Sponsor of TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BloFin, a top global crypto derivative exchange, is thrilled to reveal its platinum sponsorship for the highly anticipated TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024, a premier crypto event. This sponsorship marks a significant milestone for BloFin, following its successful participation as a Gold Sponsor at TOKEN2049, the premier blockchain event in Singapore in 2023. It is dedicated to &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/">BloFin Announces Platinum Sponsor of TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong><a href="https://blofin.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">BloFin</a>, a top global crypto derivative exchange, is thrilled to reveal its platinum sponsorship for the highly anticipated TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024, a premier crypto event. </strong></p>



<p>This sponsorship marks a significant milestone for BloFin, following its successful participation as a Gold Sponsor at TOKEN2049, the premier blockchain event in Singapore in 2023. It is dedicated to furthering the blockchain industry&#8217;s growth and development by partnering once again with TOKEN2049. As a Platinum Sponsor, BloFin aims to showcase its commitment to innovation, technology, and community engagement within the blockchain ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>



<p>TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024 promises to be a gathering of industry leaders, innovators, and enthusiasts from around the world, and BloFin&#8217;s sponsorship underscores its position as a key player in shaping the future of blockchain technology and digital asset trading.</p>



<p>Moreover, given Dubai&#8217;s status as a global hub for crypto innovation and the pivotal role of TOKEN2049 in the UAE, BloFin&#8217;s exclusive<a href="https://lu.ma/BloFinWhalesNightDubai" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> WhalesNight AfterParty</a> is poised to make waves. Scheduled to be held at the scenic Sobe Dubai Rooftop Sundowner, the event will commence at 19:30 (UTC+4) on April 18, 2024. </p>



<p>The BloFin WhalesNight AfterParty will bring together industry leaders, BloFin Whales (influencers), and BloFin VIPs from around the world. Attendees can look forward to engaging discussions, exciting news, and valuable networking opportunities in a vibrant and dynamic atmosphere. It will serve as a platform for participants to connect, share insights, and explore new opportunities in the ever-evolving cryptocurrency landscape. </p>



<p>With Dubai being a hub for innovation and technological advancement, this event is poised to make a significant impact on the future of blockchain technology and digital assets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/NfVei8AiU5macxITjam6_3ErHv6soiofADoNuNjeqgU57_J9-ladjnLc5rm8UFSE8ddJewqIT0KTrlXSVWFpXJJxYw7tnZLtvjnK1Vg7g8sZyT80JIvfEbdVkC_MlunZvQ-WFC2R8Q_3-FOKSRg6Kjk" alt=""/></figure>



<p>With years of experience in the blockchain industry, Matt Hu, the CEO of Blofin, is anticipating this opportunity and recognizes the significance of attending TOKEN 2049 in Dubai as a platinum sponsor for his product:&nbsp;</p>



<p>&#8220;Bitcoin is being heralded as the modern-day gold, while Dubai is on the rise as the world&#8217;s new financial epicenter. Dubai Token2049 presents an unparalleled platform for dialogue, not just for us, but for global users as well. As one of the most rapidly expanding exchanges, BloFin is excited to showcase our breakthroughs in product innovation, cutting-edge technology, and unparalleled security measures. We&#8217;re not stopping there; BloFin is committed to ongoing investment in our product suite, technological advancements, security protocols, and operational efficiencies to ensure our users receive nothing but the most exceptional and dependable services. Join us at Dubai Token2049 to witness the future of finance, today.&#8221;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Attendees at TOKEN2049 in Dubai will have the opportunity to delve into the diverse features of the Blofin ecosystem, spanning futures trading, copy trading, and more. Through interactions with experts, Web3 builders, thought leaders, and enthusiasts at TOKEN2049, BloFin aims to forge a robust foundation for the advancement and maturation of the blockchain ecosystem.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-about-blofin"><strong>About BloFin</strong></h2>



<p>BloFin is a secure and cryptocurrency centralized exchange (CEX) that offers the best services for perpetual &amp; futures trading with an extensive selection of over 300 USDT-M perpetual contracts. Aside from derivatives trading products, BloFin now provides more high-quality services including spot trading, copy trading, earning, API, and more. The team prioritizes user trust and platform transparency above all else. </p>



<p>BloFin is committed to prioritizing user fund security by partnering with Fireblocks to safeguard users&#8217; assets and providing insurance coverage for potential crypto-related incidents and we continue to shape the future of crypto trading. As BloFin continues to expand its global presence and influence, partnerships with leading industry events like TOKEN2049 serve as a testament to its commitment to excellence and leadership in the cryptocurrency and blockchain sectors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blofin-announces-platinum-sponsor-of-token2049-dubai-2024/">BloFin Announces Platinum Sponsor of TOKEN2049 Dubai 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/photo_2024-03-22-14.33.22.jpeg" medium="image" width="1280" height="640" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/photo_2024-03-22-14.33.22.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real-World Assets Exchange DigiFT Debuts US Treasury Bill Tokens</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/real-world-assets-rwa-treasury-bill-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ali M.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Real-World Assets (RWA) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiFT's new U.S. Treasury Bill tokens revolutionize blockchain investment, providing direct beneficial ownership and legal transparency. This marks a first in blockchain-based real-world asset exchanges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/real-world-assets-rwa-treasury-bill-tokens/">Real-World Assets Exchange DigiFT Debuts US Treasury Bill Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>DigiFT recently unveiled its latest offering in the form of US Treasury Bill depository receipt tokens. This innovation introduces direct beneficial ownership in US Treasury Bills to the blockchain. </strong></p>



<p>The significance of this launch lies in its approach to solving a longstanding issue within Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization—the challenge of legally and accurately representing ownership and interest.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-us-treasury-bill-tokens-now-on-real-world-assets-exchange">US Treasury Bill Tokens Now on Real-World Assets Exchange</h2>



<p>The concept of depositary receipts has a rich history in facilitating international investment, dating back to their inception in the 1920s. Traditionally, these instruments enabled investors to access foreign markets with relative ease. Adapting this established structure, DigiFT aims to address the legal representation of token holders&#8217; interests in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/real-world-asset-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Real-World Assets</a>.</p>



<p>Currently, the market is saturated with wrapped tokens, which often come entangled in legal frameworks that obscure direct ownership. This can pose significant hurdles for investors seeking to navigate the implications of their investments. By contrast, DigiFT’s <a href="https://www.digift.sg/announcements/first-rwa-depository-receipt-tokens.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">deployment</a> of depository receipt tokens offers a clear, legally coherent framework. </p>



<p>This model simplifies investment comprehension and ensures investors have a direct claim on the returns of the underlying assets.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/tokenization-rwas/">What is The Impact of Real World Asset (RWA) Tokenization?</a></strong></p>



<p>Henry Zhang, Founder and CEO of DigiFT, highlighted the importance of the DR structure. It helps address market needs, particularly in terms of direct ownership and return on investment. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“DigiFT&#8217;s innovative DR structure addresses a pain point in the current RWA market, empowering investors with direct ownership of underlying assets and returns. Looking ahead, DigiFT remains committed to expanding the universe of traditional financial assets in the Web3 space through the DR model, offering better investor protection and transparency,” Zhang said. </p>
</blockquote>



<p>As the first licensed Real-World Assets exchange, DigiFT merges deep financial insights with advanced technological capabilities. The newly launched US Treasury Tokens (DRUST) are emblematic of this fusion, providing a regulated, blockchain-based option for managing treasury and cash flows. Highly liquid US Treasury Bills directly back these tokens, which appeal to a broad spectrum of institutional investors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/real-world-assets-rwa-treasury-bill-tokens/">Real-World Assets Exchange DigiFT Debuts US Treasury Bill Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/BIC_Tokenization_token_2-covers.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/BIC_Tokenization_token_2-covers.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finticipate &#8211; Third Annual SEE Fintech Forum is back, promising insights into future fintech trends</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=485874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Finticipate thrilled to announce the upcoming third annual Finticipate &#8211; SEE Fintech Forum, scheduled for May 31st, 2024, at the Mona Plaza Hotel in Belgrade, and via online platform. This event promises to be a highlight on the calendars of industry leaders and enthusiasts alike. Building on the success of previous editions, Finticipate Vol3 – &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/">Finticipate &#8211; Third Annual SEE Fintech Forum is back, promising insights into future fintech trends</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Finticipate thrilled to announce the upcoming third annual Finticipate &#8211; SEE Fintech Forum, scheduled for May 31<sup>st</sup>, 2024, at the Mona Plaza Hotel in Belgrade, and via online platform. This event promises to be a highlight on the calendars of industry leaders and enthusiasts alike.</strong></p>



<p>Building on the success of previous editions, Finticipate Vol3 – SEE Fintech Forum is poised to bring together prominent figures from the regional and European fintech and finance communities. Attendees can anticipate the presence of regulatory authorities, traditional banks, innovative neobanks, crypto exchanges, web 3 service providers, burgeoning startups, fintech payment platforms, international fintech associations, established financial institutions, BNPL (Buy Now, Pay Later) services, and more.</p>



<p>This year, Finticipate aims to delve deep into the emerging trends that will shape the future of the fintech landscape. From disruptive technologies to regulatory shifts, the forum will offer invaluable insights and perspectives on the evolving industry dynamics.</p>



<p>&#8220;We are excited to once again convene thought leaders and industry pioneers at SEE Fintech Forum,&#8221; said Jasna Nedic, Program director at Finticipate. &#8220;As the fintech ecosystem continues to evolve, this event serves as a vital platform for collaboration, knowledge-sharing, and networking.&#8221;</p>



<p><strong>Rare Bird discount</strong> is still on, priced at <strong>€370 + VAT</strong> per person until <strong>April 30th</strong>. For companies registering 3 or more attendees, the fee is reduced to €320 + VAT per person. <strong>Standard registration costs €450 + VAT</strong>, whereas <strong>online registration</strong> is available for <strong>€130 + VAT</strong>. Seating is limited, so ensure you register on time to secure your spot!</p>



<p>Registration for the forum is now open via the official <a href="https://finticipate.com/registration/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">website</a>, or interested individuals can reach out via <a href="office@finticipate.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">email</a>. Limited slots are available, so early registration is encouraged.</p>



<p>Join Finticipate on May 31st as we embark on an immersive fintech journey, exploring diverse viewpoints on the most pressing topics shaping the industry&#8217;s future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-about-finticipate">About Finticipate</h2>



<p>Finticipate is a leading platform provided by New Angles Consulting dedicated to exploring the latest trends, innovations, and disruptions in the fintech and finance sectors. Through forum and online content, Finticipate fosters collaboration and knowledge-sharing among industry stakeholders, driving forward the evolution of financial technology worldwide. Visit <a href="https://finticipate.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">website</a> to learn more.<br><br><a href="https://finticipate.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Website</a> | <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/finticipate-see-fintech-forum/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">LinkedIn</a> | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/new_angles_consulting/?hl=sr" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Instagram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/finticipate-unveils-third-annual-see-fintech-forum-promising-insight-into-future-trends/">Finticipate &#8211; Third Annual SEE Fintech Forum is back, promising insights into future fintech trends</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Banner_1200x627.png" medium="image" width="1200" height="627" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Banner_1200x627.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>High-Risk Appetite Evident as PUNDU Meme Coin Raises $100 Million</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/solana-meme-coin-nears-100-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana-based PUNDU meme coin presale achieved exceptional success, raising nearly $100 million in record time.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/solana-meme-coin-nears-100-million/">High-Risk Appetite Evident as PUNDU Meme Coin Raises $100 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>DAO Maker has achieved a remarkable feat, securing nearly $100 million in a presale for the PUNDU meme coin.</strong></p>



<p>The significant investment contributed within 36 hours reflects a pronounced appetite for high-risk ventures in the crypto market. However, the overwhelming response resulted in an oversubscription, necessitating refunds for contributors who sent funds post-target attainment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-solana-meme-coins-in-high-demand">Solana Meme Coins in High Demand</h2>



<p>DAO Maker unveiled an impressive $97.6 million raised across Binance Smart Chain and <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana</a>, drawing support from over 20,000 users. PUNDU, introduced by the launchpad just days ago, swiftly captured investor interest, with contributions exchanging SOL and USDT for PUNDU allocations.</p>



<p>This success marks a milestone, establishing PUNDU&#8217;s presale as the largest for a meme coin. Most deposits originated from Binance Smart Chain, amassing $60 million. However, the Solana presale address also saw substantial activity. It received 212,404 SOL, equivalent to $37.6 million, surpassing the 33,333 SOL hard cap, highlighting the fervent <a href="https://beincrypto.com/crypto-traders-solana-base-meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">interest in meme coins within the Solana ecosystem.</a></p>



<p>While PUNDU awaits its launch date, the meme coin pledges a fair rollout, earmarking 40% of tokens for the presale, another 40% for liquidity pools, and distributing the remaining 10% equally between marketing efforts and long-term exchange listings.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/solana-platforms-buy/">6 Best Platforms To Buy Solana (SOL) in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>According to crypto investigator ZachXBT, Solana presales have raised more than 796,000 SOL, equivalent to around $149.20 million. Such mania urged Solana Labs Co-Founder Anatoly Yakovenko to <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">advise</a> investors to &#8220;stop&#8221; sending SOL presales.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;To me, it&#8217;s just a bizarre thing, I think, of people being terminally online and kind of having nothing better to do,&#8221; Yakovenko <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/podcasts/the-protocol/solana-its-meme-coin-craze-growth-and-vision-with-ceo-anatoly-yakovenko" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Stop doing this. <a href="https://t.co/wY7E38MqYh">https://t.co/wY7E38MqYh</a></p>&mdash; toly <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@aeyakovenko) <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko/status/1770086226919575677?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 19, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Moreover, the frenzy surrounding meme coins led to the emergence of racist tokens. These <a href="https://beincrypto.com/racist-memecoins-condemnation/">meme coins, with offensive names, symbols, and imagery</a>, include racial slurs, anti-Semitic references, and Nazi imagery.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/solana-meme-coin-nears-100-million/">High-Risk Appetite Evident as PUNDU Meme Coin Raises $100 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BIC_Memecoins_rocket_shib_positive.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BIC_Memecoins_rocket_shib_positive.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altcoin Trader Reveals Strategy For the Meme Coin Mania</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/altcoin-trader-strategy-meme-coin-mania/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 19:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rekt Fencer shares his controversial yet effective strategy for trading meme coins, leveraging 'sniping' and meticulous market analysis to achieve significant returns. Despite inherent risks, his method illuminates the lucrative potential of cryptocurrency trading.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/altcoin-trader-strategy-meme-coin-mania/">Altcoin Trader Reveals Strategy For the Meme Coin Mania</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Altcoin trader Rekt Fencer has caused a stir with his candid revelation on achieving a staggering 1,000X gains through meme coins. </strong></p>



<p>Fencer&#8217;s strategy, centered on the concept of &#8216;sniping&#8217; new token launches, is allegedly profitable even for those with investors modest capital.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-secrets-to-trading-meme-coins">Secrets to Trading Meme Coins</h2>



<p>Fencer <a href="https://x.com/rektfencer/status/1771821959963099517?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">explained</a> one of the easiest methods to achieve significant returns with <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">meme coins</a>. This approach, while controversial, has shown to be effective for him in a market where timing and information are everything.</p>



<p>The key to Fencer&#8217;s method lies in meticulous pre-analysis and constant monitoring of the market for new listings. By utilizing resources like DEX Screener, traders can identify trending narratives and potential catalysts that could drive the price of newly listed meme coins. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;The longer the narrative in the Top Gainers, the stronger it becomes,&#8221; Fencer noted </p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/top-meme-coins/">7 Hot Meme Coins and Altcoins that are Trending in 2024</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="403" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197-850x403.png" alt="DEX Screener Top Gainers" class="wp-image-488934" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197-850x403.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197-360x171.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197-768x364.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197-1536x728.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197-150x71.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-197.png 1795w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">DEX Screener Top Gainers. Source: <a href="https://dexscreener.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">DEX Screener</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Moreover, Fencer shed light on the critical role of sniper bots in executing this strategy. These bots are designed to buy tokens as quickly as possible at launch. Therefore, they can significantly increase the chances of securing a token before its value skyrockets. </p>



<p>Among the recommended tools are BONKbot for Solana on-chain trading, BananaGun for Ethereum and Solana, and <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/unibot-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Unibot</a>, a popular choice for EVM and soon Solana.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;To buy tokens as fast as possible, you need to use sniper bots. There isn&#8217;t a universal bot that works perfectly for every chain. Each bot has its own customization instructions. Mastering this skill isn&#8217;t easy, but the rewards that follow will more than compensate for your efforts,&#8221; Fencer added. </p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/ai-crypto-trading-bots/">13 Best AI Crypto Trading Bots To Maximize Your Profits</a></strong></p>



<p>However, Fencer&#8217;s method is not without its risks. The volatile nature of meme coins and the potential for <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/crypto-scams/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto scams</a> underscore the importance of diligence and risk management. Investors are advised to verify the security of tokens through platforms like Rug Check and Coin Scan. Traders must also be prepared for the possibility that not every investment will yield the anticipated returns.</p>



<p>Despite the inherent risks, Fencer&#8217;s strategy offers a tantalizing glimpse into the potential rewards of cryptocurrency trading. By combining thorough research, strategic use of technology, and an understanding of market dynamics, traders can position themselves to capture significant gains.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/altcoin-trader-strategy-meme-coin-mania/">Altcoin Trader Reveals Strategy For the Meme Coin Mania</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_Developer_1-covers_neutral.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_Developer_1-covers_neutral.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC Will Run Out of Bitcoin in 96 Days</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/grayscale-gbtc-bitcoin-outflows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488883</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale is exploring strategies to counteract these outflows, including introducing a mini fund as an alternative to GBTC.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/grayscale-gbtc-bitcoin-outflows/">Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC Will Run Out of Bitcoin in 96 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) have significantly impacted the crypto market since their debut in January. Even marker observers have been impressed with the record performance of these financial products. </strong></p>



<p>However, Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), one of the prominent products, has experienced consistent outflows, sparking concerns about its future trajectory.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-grayscale-s-gbtc-bitcoin-reserve-depletes">Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC Bitcoin Reserve Depletes</h2>



<p>Arkham Intelligence, a blockchain analytics firm, has forecasted that GBTC could deplete its Bitcoin reserves within the next 96 days if the current rate of redemptions persists. </p>



<p>Since its conversion into a spot Bitcoin ETF in January, Grayscale&#8217;s Bitcoin balance has plummeted by 266,470 BTC. This marks a significant decline from its initial holding of approximately 620,000 BTC. </p>



<p>The downward trend is attributed to <a href="https://beincrypto.com/grayscale-outtflows-skyrocket/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">consistent outflows from GBTC</a> averaging 25,900 BTC per week.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Grayscale started the year holding 618,280 BTC for their Bitcoin Trust GBTC. They now hold only 356,440 BTC. If they carry on like this, there’s only 14 weeks until they run out for good,&#8221; analysts at Arkham Intelligence <a href="https://x.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1771567644040458478?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">remarked</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/how-to-prepare-bitcoin-etf/">How To Trade a Bitcoin ETF: A Step-by-Step Approach</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="535" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-850x535.png" alt="Grayscale GBTC Bitcoin Holdings" class="wp-image-488928" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-850x535.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-360x227.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-768x484.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-1536x967.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-2048x1290.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Historical-Bitcoin-Holdings-Trend-2-150x94.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC Bitcoin Holdings. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>



<p>Grayscale&#8217;s CEO, Michael Sonnenshein, acknowledged the anticipated outflows, attributing them primarily to profit-taking investors and arbitragers exiting the fund. On the other hand, market observers have attributed the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/grayscale-outflow-bitcoin-price/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">GBTC outflows</a> to its high fee structure. At the same time, Eric Balchunas, a senior ETF analyst at Bloomberg, noted that the past week&#8217;s outflows were predominantly from the defunct crypto lender Genesis. </p>



<p>Grayscale is exploring various initiatives to counteract this outflow trend. Some of these include introducing a mini fund providing a cost-effective alternative to GBTC. Sonnenshein also mentioned the firm&#8217;s plan to reduce its 1.5% fee, which stands in stark contrast to competitors&#8217; rates ranging from 0.2% to 0.5%.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;We have seen this in countless other exposures, countless other markets, you name it, where typically when products are earlier in their lifecycle, when they’re new to be introduced, these tend to be higher. And, as those markets mature, and as those funds grow, those fees tend to come down, and we expect the same to be true of GBTC,&#8221; Sonnenshein <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/19/grayscale-ceo-says-gbtc-bitcoin-etf-fees-will-come-down-over-time.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/grayscale-gbtc-bitcoin-outflows/">Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC Will Run Out of Bitcoin in 96 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/bic_Grayscale-covers_negative.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/bic_Grayscale-covers_negative.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu&#8217;s (SHIB) Shibarium TVL Surges 170% in Two Days</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/shiba-inu-shibarium-tvl-increases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488881</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu ecosystem witnessed an unexpected decline in SHIB's burn rate despite the overall growth in trading activity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/shiba-inu-shibarium-tvl-increases/">Shiba Inu&#8217;s (SHIB) Shibarium TVL Surges 170% in Two Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Shibarium, the Layer 2 blockchain within the Shiba Inu (SHIB) ecosystem, has reached noteworthy milestones, indicative of its growing utility and adoption.</strong></p>



<p>On-chain data shows a remarkable surge in the total value of assets locked (TVL) on Shibarium, marking an increase of approximately 170% within the last two days. The value now stands at $3.85 million, underlining the platform&#8217;s expanding utility and user engagement.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-shibarium-s-tvl-surged-by-170">Shibarium&#8217;s TVL Surged by 170%</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/shiba-inu-price-rally-shibarium-tvl/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Shibarium&#8217;s TVL surge</a> can be attributed to the rollout of new features within the ecosystem. Notably, the recent introduction of the DAMN <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">meme coin</a> on the Woofswap decentralized exchange has added to <a href="https://beincrypto.com/crypto-traders-solana-base-meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">excitement revolving around meme coins</a> across various blockchains. </p>



<p>Among them, DAMN emerges as a notable contender, garnering significant attention from the Shib army and the broader crypto community. What sets DAMN apart is its feature enabling the burning of Bone Shibaswap, Shibarium&#8217;s native gas token, enhancing its appeal.</p>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/buy-shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Shiba Inu</a> market analyst Lucie explained that DAMN was &#8220;about the people — primarily BONE holders and the Shibarium community.&#8221;</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;We’re not spending on marketing; it’s a collective effort to spotlight our ecosystem. A little effort from each one of us can lead to great achievements. Let’s unite and propel forward together,&#8221; Lucie <a href="https://x.com/LucieSHIB/status/1771636575157260628?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/top-meme-coins/">7 Hot Meme Coins and Altcoins that are Trending in 2024</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="447" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM-850x447.png" alt="Shibarium's Total Value Locked" class="wp-image-488912" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM-850x447.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM-360x189.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM-768x404.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM-1536x808.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM-150x79.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-2.21.42-PM.png 1654w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Shibarium&#8217;s Total Value Locked. Source: <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Shibarium" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">DeFiLlama</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Interestingly, DAMN&#8217;s price has been on an uptrend since its debut, resulting in significant trading activity on the Woofswap decentralized exchange, which inadvertently impacted Shibarium&#8217;s TVL. The DEX currently commands approximately 64% of Shibarium&#8217;s total ecosystem activity.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-shiba-inu-shib-price-increases">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Increases</h2>



<p>Recent market data illustrates the Shiba Inu meme coin&#8217;s ongoing ascent, coinciding with its ecosystem&#8217;s expansion. According to BeInCrypto data, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SHIB&#8217;s price</a> has surged by over 2.45% within the last 24 hours, reaching $0.00002791. This upward trajectory extends a remarkable growth streak, surpassing 193% in the past month.</p>



<p>Notably, this surge aligns with a surge in short-term investors acquiring SHIB. This class of investors accumulated 64 trillion tokens over the last 30 days, according to analysts at IntoTheBlock.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Shiba Inu traders with holdings spanning less than a month have seen a remarkable surge, marking a 278% increase in the last 30 days,&#8221; IntoTheBlock&#8217;s content creator Slim Daddy <a href="https://x.com/felixreads/status/1771055582583165030?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/shiba-inu-shib-price-prediction/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Prediction 2024 / 2025 / 2030</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="281" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-193-850x281.png" alt="SHIB Holders" class="wp-image-488894" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-193-850x281.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-193-360x119.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-193-768x253.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-193-150x50.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-193.png 900w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Shiba Inu Short-Term Holders. Source: <a href="https://www.intotheblock.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>However, despite this positive momentum, the Shiba Inu ecosystem experienced an unexpected decline in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/shiba-inu-burn-rate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SHIB&#8217;s burn rate</a>. Over the previous week, the meme coin&#8217;s burn rate <a href="https://x.com/shibburn/status/1771869619239719134?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">dropped</a> by 52%, marked by approximately 360 million SHIB tokens being withdrawn from circulation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/shiba-inu-shibarium-tvl-increases/">Shiba Inu&#8217;s (SHIB) Shibarium TVL Surges 170% in Two Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/bic_Shiba_inu-covers_bullish.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/bic_Shiba_inu-covers_bullish.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spain Temporarily Suspends Telegram Following Media Companies&#8217; Complaints</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/spain-suspends-telegram-access/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telegram News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Spain's High Court suspends Telegram to investigate media companies' copyright complaints, impacting its 19% user base. The move prompts a debate on digital rights and copyright laws.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/spain-suspends-telegram-access/">Spain Temporarily Suspends Telegram Following Media Companies&#8217; Complaints</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Spain&#8217;s High Court has ordered a temporary suspension of the popular messaging app, Telegram, effective from March 25, 2024. </strong></p>



<p>This decision comes after several media companies, including Atresmedia, EGEDA, Mediaset, and Telefonica, lodged complaints alleging that Telegram facilitated the unauthorized sharing of their content. Judge Santiago Pedraz sanctioned the suspension to allow a thorough investigation into these claims.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-spain-suspends-telegram">Spain Suspends Telegram</h2>



<p>Under this <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/high-court-orders-temporary-suspension-telegrams-services-spain-2024-03-23/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">directive</a>, it will be incumbent upon mobile service providers across Spain to implement the blockade against Telegram&#8217;s operations. This measure marks a significant development, considering <a href="https://beincrypto.com/telegram-300-million-toncoin-price/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Telegram&#8217;s status</a> as the country&#8217;s fourth most utilized messaging platform. </p>



<p>The platform, celebrated for its robust encryption and privacy features, boasts a user base encompassing nearly 19% of the Spanish population.</p>



<p>FACUA, an NGO for the defense of consumer rights, warns of the enormous damages the judicial decision will cause for this messaging application&#8217;s millions of users and the companies, organizations, and public and private institutions that disseminate content lawfully through their channels on this platform.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s as if they shut down the internet because there are websites that illegally host content protected by copyright, as if they cut off all television signals because there are networks that engage in piracy,&#8221; FACUA Activist Rubén Sánchez <a href="https://facua.org/noticias/audiencia-nacional-ordena-bloqueo-telegram/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/crypto-social-media-scams/">Crypto Social Media Scams: How to Stay Safe</a></strong></p>



<p>The suspension raises questions about the balance between copyright protection and digital freedoms. Telegram, which reported over 700 million monthly active users globally in 2023, is at a critical juncture. The company&#8217;s response to the suspension, as well as further commentary from the High Court, remains pending.</p>



<p>This development <a href="https://beincrypto.com/telegram-channels-promoting-crypto-scams/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">affects millions of Telegram users</a> and sets a precedent for how digital platforms are regulated in Spain. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/spain-suspends-telegram-access/">Spain Temporarily Suspends Telegram Following Media Companies&#8217; Complaints</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/best-crypto-telegram-group-cover-850x478-1.jpg" medium="image" width="850" height="478" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/best-crypto-telegram-group-cover-850x478-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase’s Base Hits $2 Billion TVL: Airdrops, Meme Coins to Watch</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/coinbases-base-airdrops-meme-coins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=488891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase's Layer 2 solution, Base, surpasses $2 billion in Total Value Locked, marking a significant uptick in interest, particularly for meme coins and airdrops, setting the stage for further expansion.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/coinbases-base-airdrops-meme-coins/">Coinbase’s Base Hits $2 Billion TVL: Airdrops, Meme Coins to Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Coinbase&#8217;s Layer 2 solution, Base, has surpassed $2 billion in Total Value Locked (TVL), marking a 43.61% surge over the past week. </strong></p>



<p>This milestone reflects the growing traction and interest in this network, particularly focusing on meme coins and airdrops.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-coinbase-s-base-network-on-the-rise">Coinbase’s Base Network on the Rise</h2>



<p>Base, engineered on the Optimism tech stack, has been pivotal in scaling Ethereum by enhancing transaction speed and reducing costs, all while maintaining the robust security of the Ethereum mainnet. <a href="https://beincrypto.com/base-boom-headache-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The success of Base</a> can largely be attributed to its parent company, Coinbase. </p>



<p>This is a behemoth cryptocurrency exchange with a valuation surpassing $60 billion. Coinbase&#8217;s strategic positioning as the custodian for 90% of US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and its <a href="https://beincrypto.com/blackrock-crypto-giant-tokenized-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">alliance with giants like Blackrock</a> and Circle have significantly contributed to Base&#8217;s momentum. </p>



<p>Indeed, Jesse Pollak, the architect behind Base, <a href="https://x.com/jessepollak/status/1770130669110538680?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> that a substantial portion of Coinbase&#8217;s revenue is funneled into Base&#8217;s development. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;We are ramping up gas grants to let builders get started building for free and build gasless experiences, [as well as] builder grants to reward folks who make a positive impact on base and give them resources to build the next thing. Gas grants will be upfront, with path to scaling. Builder grants will be primarily retroactive because we&#8217;ve observed that creates aligned incentives and a strong builder culture,&#8221; Pollak said. <a href="https://twitter.com/jessepollak/status/1770130669110538680"></a></p>
</blockquote>



<p>This strategic move reflects Coinbase&#8217;s vision of leveraging Base as a gateway for over 110 million users into the crypto market. The platform&#8217;s integration with Coinbase&#8217;s expansive user base provides a fertile ground for user acquisition, a common challenge for new blockchains.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/coinbase-review/">Coinbase Review 2024: The Best Crypto Exchange for Beginners?</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="464" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-1.54.55-PM-850x464.png" alt="Base Network Users" class="wp-image-488899" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-1.54.55-PM-850x464.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-1.54.55-PM-360x196.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-1.54.55-PM-768x419.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-1.54.55-PM-150x82.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-24-at-1.54.55-PM.png 1444w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Base Network Users. Source: <a href="https://dune.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Dune</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>For this reason, this strategy has led to an unprecedented <a href="https://beincrypto.com/crypto-traders-solana-base-meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">uptick in Base&#8217;s adoption</a>. In March, daily new users hit 800,000, revenue climbed from $18 million to $28 million, and daily transactions soared from 500,000 to 2 million. </p>



<p>This surge is partially attributed to the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/dencun-upgrade-explained/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum Dencun upgrade</a>. The implementation of EIP-4844 drastically reduced network fees, making Base a formidable competitor for high-frequency trading.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-base-meme-coins-and-airdrops-to-watch">Base Meme Coins and Airdrops to Watch </h2>



<p>The momentum around Base suggests a growing interest in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">meme coins</a> and airdrops. With the ecosystem still in its infancy, the potential for discovery and investment in meme coins is vast. </p>



<p>According to analyst Miles Deutscher, a methodical approach involving the tracking of token trading volumes and holder counts can unveil promising opportunities within this space. Toshi Base, for instance, is a meme coin that stands due to its strong community and its position as a first mover.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Those who follow my content know I&#8217;m a proponent of following the leader when it comes to narrative trading, in this case TOSHI is the leading meme on Base,&#8221; Deutscher <a href="https://x.com/milesdeutscher/status/1771267594554916915?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">emphasized</a>. </p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/top-meme-coins/">7 Hot Meme Coins and Altcoins that are Trending in 2024</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="564" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-192-850x564.png" alt="Protocols Running on Base" class="wp-image-488892" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-192-850x564.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-192-360x239.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-192-768x510.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-192-150x100.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-192.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Protocols Running on Base. Source: <a href="https://twitter.com/degargoyle" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Gargoyle</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Moreover, the anticipation of new protocols launching on Base and the potential for ecosystem airdrops presents a lucrative prospect for users and investors. </p>



<p>Influencer Gargoyle <a href="https://x.com/degargoyle/status/1769739206828446188?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">pointed out</a> that the most profitable on Base may have a good chance of launching an airdrop. These include bridges like Across and Stargate, decentralized exchanges like ODOS and Aerodrome, and lending protocols like Moonwell and Seamless. </p>



<p>Although Base has no immediate plans for a native token, history suggests anything is possible. With opportunities abounding in meme coins and airdrops, Base appears poised for further expansion. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/coinbases-base-airdrops-meme-coins/">Coinbase’s Base Hits $2 Billion TVL: Airdrops, Meme Coins to Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_Coinbase_2-covers_neutral.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_Coinbase_2-covers_neutral.png"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
