<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>BeInCrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="https://beincrypto.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://beincrypto.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/cropped-bic_favic-32x32.png</url>
	<title>BeInCrypto</title>
	<link>https://beincrypto.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>South American Gold Miner Nilam Resources to Buy $1.70 Billion in Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/gold-miner-nilam-resources-buy-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=490027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nilam Resources, Inc., a South American gold miner, now invests in Bitcoin, acquiring MindWave and its 24,800 BTC, marking a strategic pivot towards the digital economy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/gold-miner-nilam-resources-buy-bitcoin/">South American Gold Miner Nilam Resources to Buy $1.70 Billion in Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Nilam Resources, a South American gold mining stalwart, announced a strategic shift towards Bitcoin. It detailed an ambitious acquisition of MindWave, which holds a staggering 24,800 BTC, among other assets.</strong></p>



<p>This transition marks a billion-dollar leap into cryptocurrencies, signaling robust confidence in Bitcoin&#8217;s value and potential.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gold-miner-buys-bitcoin">Gold Miner Buys Bitcoin</h2>



<p>Pranjali More, CEO of Nilam Resources, <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/03/25/2851986/0/en/Nilam-Resources-Enters-Letters-of-Intent-to-Acquire-24-800-Bitcoin.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">highlighted</a> the meticulous efforts and due diligence that culminated in this strategic direction. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;This acquisition and resulting strategic partnership align with NILA’s vision, mission, and core values—a future where finance is inclusive and sustainable, pioneering transparent, impactful solutions while driving positive change in the digital economy,&#8221; More stated.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>The deal involves Nilam Resources issuing a newly authorized Preferred Class of Series C Stock. These will be exchanged for the 24,800 BTC at a rate discounted from the current market prices. </p>



<p>This arrangement aims to enrich Nilam Resources&#8217; portfolio and enhance its ability to fund high-yield generating projects, leveraging these holdings as collateral.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/bitcoin-price-prediction/">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2024 / 2025 / 2030</a></strong></p>



<p>The embrace of Bitcoin by Nilam Resources reflects a <a href="https://beincrypto.com/goldman-sachs-interested-bitcoin-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">broader acceptance of cryptocurrency</a> as a legitimate and valuable asset in the financial system. As the acquisition progresses toward finalizing the Letter of Intent (LOI) into a legally binding agreement, anticipation builds around the potential impacts on the cryptocurrency market and traditional investment sectors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/gold-miner-nilam-resources-buy-bitcoin/">South American Gold Miner Nilam Resources to Buy $1.70 Billion in Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bic_Satoshi_Nakamoto-covers_owner_bitcoin.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bic_Satoshi_Nakamoto-covers_owner_bitcoin.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australian Fintech Stables Launches International Remittances Between Australia and The Philippines</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/stables-launches-international-remittances/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Advertorial]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Australian digital wallet provider and payment startup Stables has today announced the launch of international remittances for its thousands of users (focusing on the AU-PH Corridor). From today, Stables users in over 130 countries can send Australian Dollars or Philippine Pesos to over 140 million people across Australia and the Philippines, all powered by stablecoins.  &#8230; <a href="https://beincrypto.com/stables-launches-international-remittances/">Continued</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/stables-launches-international-remittances/">Australian Fintech Stables Launches International Remittances Between Australia and The Philippines</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Australian digital wallet provider and payment startup <a href="https://stables.money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Stables </a>has today announced the launch of international remittances for its thousands of users (focusing on the AU-PH Corridor). </strong></p>



<p>From today, <a href="https://stables.money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>Stables </strong></a>users in over 130 countries can send Australian Dollars or Philippine Pesos to over 140 million people across Australia and the Philippines, all powered by stablecoins. </p>



<p>As the largest importer of remittances within Southeast Asia, the Philippines has inflows in excess of $40 billion per year (with $5.76 billion from Australia alone). In recent years, the Philippines has increasingly adopted digital forms of payment due to 44% of the population aged 15 and over in the Philippines estimated to be unbanked, leading to increased acceptance of digital wallets and e-wallets like Gcash in the region.</p>



<p>With the market capitalisation of stablecoins hitting new highs in March 2024, totalling over US $140 billion, there is strong momentum this year for the cohort-leading venture. <a href="https://stables.money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>Stables </strong></a>and its Founders have an unwavering belief in stablecoins to offer users speed, low-cost settlement, security and reliability for its users. </p>



<p>On the recent announcement, Stables Co-Founder and CEO Erez Rachamim said, “This is the first time in Australian history that a company has embedded stablecoins in remittance rails with both domestic jurisdictions covered to deliver a payload with no middlemen, intra-day with sub 1% fees, we cannot wait to bring feature parity to the Philippines by May 2024,” Rachamim continued.</p>



<p>&#8220;Our vision at Stables has always been to simplify the usage of stablecoins and drive their widespread adoption globally to improve access to basic financial services in emerging markets where a significant portion of the population is underbanked,&#8221; said Erez Rachamim, CEO of Stables.</p>



<p>“Initially, Stables set out to reimagine how stablecoins could power everyday payments, and today, we’ve turned that into a reality. Our users can now send Philippines Pesos or Australian Dollars from their stablecoin balance directly into any local bank account or eWallet, without the need for the other party to have a Stables wallet or know that the funds started as a digital asset on the blockchain,” he continued.</p>



<p>“Stablecoin remittances are a lifeline for many who need to send money to their loved ones, as they provide faster, cheaper and more transparent transactions than traditional methods. Stablecoins are challenging the status quo of remittance services. We believe they will shape the future of cross-border payments, and the little guys will keep more money in their pockets,” says Rachamim.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Stables has forged strong relationships and partnerships with major global payment players like Mastercard in 2023, announcing the launch of the Stables Mastercard<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> virtual prepaid card in Australia. This groundbreaking solution allowed users to seamlessly and securely spend their stablecoin balance anywhere Mastercard cards are accepted, in-store or online.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Leveraging Circle Internet Financial (Circle)’s USDC, the Stables virtual card empowers customers to utilize their stablecoins in the physical world, meeting the growing demand for real-world spending among digital asset holders.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Founded in February 2021, Stables is on a mission to empower people to access the global financial system through transparent and fair stablecoin products. Stablecoin remittances offer cheaper alternatives but still face challenges to adoption. Stables hopes to bridge that gap as it aggressively moves into new international markets in 2024.</p>



<p><strong>For more information or to sign up, visit <a href="https://stables.money" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">website</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/PnvqrpWfIyf5CL1J0jEQYNLylJwfD3wKNWfiqt7z9jI-MQK2my-nVzkJ7VEIxBII25NFNxJmp3UIiVjnGJltr2EKb76agOe9zxY0D-zbj-Pcrjy9IJsdTNza_r5KjAa50jKpAiyTgWcgmWFxuhGjkD0" alt=""/></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-about-stables"><strong>About Stables</strong></h2>



<p>With a community of over 35,000 globally, Stables allows users to send, buy, and spend with their stablecoins &#8211; all on one balance. Founded in February 2021 and backed by leading VCs, Stables has assembled a stellar team focusing on bringing real-world use cases to digital assets. Powered by Mastercard, Australian users can pay with their USDC via Apple Pay and Google Pay in-store and online.</p>



<p>Stables is the brainchild of experienced fintech leaders <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/erez-rachamim-%F0%9F%A6%BE-b1a513a4/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Erez Rachamim</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/bbilotta/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Bernardo Bilotta</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-l-0a6710b7/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Daniel Li</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-nichols-sydney/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">David Nichols</a>, and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tonytao/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Tony Tao</a>. Stables employs 23 full-time staff, operating out of Sydney &amp; Melbourne.</p>



<p>Key investors in Stables include global venture capital funds Rocket Internet, Fintech Collective and DACM, as well as high-profile angel investors, including Alvin Singh and Bosco Tan (co-founders at Pocketbook) and Larry Diamond (co-founder at Zip Co).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/stables-launches-international-remittances/">Australian Fintech Stables Launches International Remittances Between Australia and The Philippines</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Снимок-экрана-2024-03-25-в-14.35.38.png" medium="image" width="1236" height="824" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Снимок-экрана-2024-03-25-в-14.35.38.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom (FTM) Price Prediction: Can It Hit a New 2-Year High?</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/fantom-price-prediction-new-yearly-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tiago Amaral]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fantom (FTM) showcases bullish signals with a shift from short-term trading to long-term holding. Despite an overbought RSI, EMA trends predict a potential surge, possibly setting a new 2-year high. Is FTM gearing up for unprecedented growth?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/fantom-price-prediction-new-yearly-high/">Fantom (FTM) Price Prediction: Can It Hit a New 2-Year High?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The dwindling supply of FTM among traders over the last few days signals a noticeable shift towards accumulation by mid-term and long-term holders, suggesting a strengthened belief in FTM&#8217;s future prospects. </strong></p>



<p>The FTM price is buoyed by positive market sentiment, with its 7-day RSI indicating high investor interest despite being in the overbought zone. The bullish trend suggested by the Exponential Moving Average (EMA) lines hints at FTM potentially reaching a 2-year high in the near future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rsi-is-at-overbought-levels">RSI Is at Overbought Levels</h2>



<p>The <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/fantom-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTM</a> 7-day RSI, a key indicator of whether an asset is overbought or oversold, currently stands at 77, showing a slight decrease from last week&#8217;s 81. </p>



<p>This metric, the Relative Strength Index (RSI), measures the magnitude of recent price changes to evaluate overbought or oversold conditions in the price of a stock or asset. Values above 70 typically indicate an asset is overbought and may be due for a price correction. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" width="850" height="288" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png" alt="FTM RSI 7D." class="wp-image-489727" style="aspect-ratio:2.951388888888889;width:1024px;height:auto" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-360x122.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-768x260.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-1536x520.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-2048x693.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Fantom-FTM-09.20.46-25-Mar-2024-150x51.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">FTM RSI 7D. Source: <a href="https://app.santiment.net/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Santiment</a>.</figcaption></figure>



<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that, in the past, FTM price has continued to grow for weeks even when the RSI suggested overbought conditions. This demonstrates that while the RSI can signal potential reversals, it does not guarantee them, and market dynamics can sustain price growth beyond traditional technical expectations.</p>



<p>Even with the overbought status, the buyer&#8217;s interest can continue growing. Since <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/how-to-add-fantom-metamask/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTM price</a> is also affected by other variables, like the overall sentiment around the crypto market, it could continue growing despite its RSI 7D above 70. </p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/top-yield-farms-on-fantom/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Top 5 Yield Farms On Fantom</a></strong></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ftm-supply-is-changing-hands">FTM Supply Is Changing Hands</h2>



<p>An analysis of FTM token movement between February 24 and March 23 reveals a dynamic shift in investor behavior. This period witnessed a surge in FTM held by Traders, defined as those with a holding period of less than a month. The FTM balance in their hands grew significantly, from 59.8 million to 198.9 million, representing a 232.61% increase. </p>



<p>This influx of traders often coincides with heightened price volatility, and indeed, the price of FTM mirrored this activity, rising <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/ftm-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">from $0.40 to $0.81</a> within the same timeframe. However, the trend among traders exhibited a shift after March 8. The growth in their FTM holdings continued but at a more moderate pace. </p>



<p>This pattern persisted until March 22, when a noteworthy change materialized. Between March 22 and 23, the supply of FTM in the hands of traders underwent a significant decline, dropping from 217 million to 124 million.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="850" height="567" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ITB_ftm_balance_by_time_held_undefined_2024-03-25T12_12_28.209Z-850x567.png" alt="Balance by Time Held." class="wp-image-489721" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ITB_ftm_balance_by_time_held_undefined_2024-03-25T12_12_28.209Z-850x567.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ITB_ftm_balance_by_time_held_undefined_2024-03-25T12_12_28.209Z-360x240.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ITB_ftm_balance_by_time_held_undefined_2024-03-25T12_12_28.209Z-768x512.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ITB_ftm_balance_by_time_held_undefined_2024-03-25T12_12_28.209Z-150x100.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ITB_ftm_balance_by_time_held_undefined_2024-03-25T12_12_28.209Z.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Balance by Time Held. Source: <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/FTM/deep-dive?group=all&amp;chart=all" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>.</figcaption></figure>



<p>This sudden decrease can likely be attributed to the substantial price appreciation witnessed in the preceding days. Following such a rapid surge, it is a common phenomenon for some investors to capitalize on favorable market conditions. This often involves liquidating their positions and securing profits. </p>



<p>Consequently, this selling pressure from short-term holders likely fueled the observed rise in FTM held by mid-term holders. Their supply increased from 515 million to 608 million. This shift in ownership suggests a potential transition from short-term, profit-driven traders to investors with a longer-term perspective on the FTM ecosystem. </p>



<p>The observed movement could indicate growing confidence in the project&#8217;s future potential, with investors adopting a more patient holding strategy. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ftm-price-prediction-can-it-reach-a-new-2-year-high">FTM Price Prediction: Can It Reach a New 2-Year High?</h2>



<p>Examining the 4-hour chart for FTM price, the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/moving-averages-explained/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exponential Moving Averages (EMAs)</a> paint a bullish picture. We see a distinct layering effect, with the shorter-term EMAs positioned above the longer-term ones. </p>



<p>This signifies that recent price action has been dominated by aggressive buyers pushing prices steadily upwards. The shorter-term momentum is clearly leading the charge, further fueling this optimistic outlook.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="850" height="386" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-850x386.png" alt="FTM 4-Hour Price Chart." class="wp-image-489767" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-850x386.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-360x163.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-768x349.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-1536x697.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-2048x930.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTMUSD_2024-03-25_10-20-28-150x68.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">FTM 4-Hour Price Chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/V4vUSDS5/?symbol=COINBASE%3ADOGEUSD" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a>. </figcaption></figure>



<p>Adding weight to this bullish narrative is the price action itself. The current price sits comfortably above the key 20 EMA, and support has been repeatedly found near the 50 EMA. This consistent buying pressure and support at these important levels reinforces the notion that bulls are in control.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/fantom-wallets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">9 Best Fantom (FTM) Wallets in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>Should this momentum continue and the price manage to break decisively through the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/best-wallet-for-altcoins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">$1.22 resistance level</a>, a significant price advance could be on the cards. </p>



<p>A potential surge towards $1.50, a level unseen since late March 2022, becomes a realistic possibility. However, if a downtrend occurs, FTM could drop to $0.70 or even below $0.60 soon. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/fantom-price-prediction-new-yearly-high/">Fantom (FTM) Price Prediction: Can It Hit a New 2-Year High?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bic_ftm_positive_run_race.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bic_ftm_positive_run_race.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Secures $884 Million to Sell Artificial Intelligence (AI) Startup</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/ftx-sell-artificial-intelligence-startup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX's $884 million sale of Anthropic shares, backed by tech giants, marks a strategic move in its bankruptcy recovery, highlighting the growing AI market value.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ftx-sell-artificial-intelligence-startup/">FTX Secures $884 Million to Sell Artificial Intelligence (AI) Startup</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>FTX has announced agreements totaling $884 million to sell a substantial portion of its shares in the AI startup Anthropic. </strong></p>



<p>This startup, supported by tech giants such as Amazon.com and Google, represents a significant part of FTX&#8217;s asset portfolio aimed at repaying creditors.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ftx-lands-884-million-deal">FTX Lands $884 Million Deal</h2>



<p>According to a recent <a href="https://www.deb.uscourts.gov/content/22-11068-ftx-trading-ltd-you-tube-link" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">court filing</a> with the US Bankruptcy Court in Wilmington, Delaware, the major chunk of this investment, nearly $500 million, will be acquired by ATIC Third International Investment. This is a subsidiary of the UAE&#8217;s sovereign fund Mubadala. </p>



<p>The rest of the shares are distributed among several key players in the financial and tech industries. These include Jane Street Global Trading and entities associated with Fidelity Investments.</p>



<p>The move to sell approximately two-thirds of its Anthropic shares could significantly impact FTX&#8217;s efforts to repay creditors. The company acquired a 7.8% stake in the AI startup with a $500 million investment in 2021. <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ftx-anthropic-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX&#8217;s strategic investment in Anthropic</a> notably paid off.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Given the increased interest in AI and large language models, there has been significant appreciation in the value of the Anthropic shares,&#8221; FTX <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-exchange-ftx-sell-shares-ai-startup-anthropic-2024-02-22/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/ftx-collapse-explained/">FTX Collapse Explained: How Sam Bankman-Fried’s Empire Fell</a></strong></p>



<p>Anthropic has been at the forefront of AI research and development. It has attracted considerable interest and substantial investments from Amazon and Google. With Amazon committing up to $4 billion and Google up to $2 billion recently, Anthropic&#8217;s valuation has surged.</p>



<p>This sale reflects <a href="https://beincrypto.com/pantera-capital-buy-solana-sol/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX&#8217;s commitment to its recovery plan</a>, aiming to repay customers in full. With $6.4 billion in cash reserves as of late February, up from over $5 billion early last year, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/crypto-exchange-ftx-warning-unauthorized-buyers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX is navigating its bankruptcy proceedings</a> with an emphasis on asset liquidity and creditor repayment.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ftx-sell-artificial-intelligence-startup/">FTX Secures $884 Million to Sell Artificial Intelligence (AI) Startup</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/BIC_FTX_FTT.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/BIC_FTX_FTT.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Targets Ripple Labs: Staggering $2 Billion Fine Looms</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/sec-ripple-lawsuit-2-billion-fine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=490002</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a groundbreaking case, the SEC aims to impose a $2 billion fine on Ripple Labs for the unregistered sale of XRP, underscoring the regulatory challenges in the cryptocurrency sector.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/sec-ripple-lawsuit-2-billion-fine/">SEC Targets Ripple Labs: Staggering $2 Billion Fine Looms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is aggressively pursuing a $2 billion fine against Ripple Labs. </strong></p>



<p>The heart of the matter dates back to 2013 when Ripple allegedly initiated fundraising through the sale of XRP without proper registration.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sec-demands-2-billion-in-penalties-from-ripple">SEC Demands $2 Billion in Penalties from Ripple</h2>



<p>The SEC&#8217;s complaint outlines that Ripple raised funds through these unregistered securities offerings in the US and globally. It claims the firm distributed billions of XRP in exchange for non-financial benefits, such as labor and market-making services. This controversial approach to financing has put Ripple in the regulatory spotlight.</p>



<p>Adding to the gravity of the situation, Ripple executives, including notable figures Larsen and Garlinghouse, are accused of personally profiting to the tune of approximately $600 million from unregistered sales of <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/xrp-ripple-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">XRP</a>. </p>



<p>As a result, the SEC is seeking $2 billion in fines and penalties from a New York judge in the ongoing case against the company.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Our response will be filed next month, but as we all have seen time and again, this is a regulator that trades in statements that are false, mischaracterized, and designed to mislead. They stayed true to form here. Rather than faithfully apply the law, the SEC remains bent on wanting to punish and intimidate Ripple &#8211; and the industry at large,&#8221; Ripple Chief Legal Officer Stuart Alderoty <a href="https://x.com/s_alderoty/status/1772339308151849153?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>. </p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/ripple-vs-sec/">Everything You Need To Know About Ripple vs SEC</a></strong></p>



<p>The SEC&#8217;s actions reflect the stringent regulatory environment governing cryptocurrencies and the agency&#8217;s commitment to enforcing existing securities laws. </p>



<p><strong><em>This is a developing story&#8230;</em></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/sec-ripple-lawsuit-2-billion-fine/">SEC Targets Ripple Labs: Staggering $2 Billion Fine Looms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/BIC_Gary_Gensler_SEC-covers_negative.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/BIC_Gary_Gensler_SEC-covers_negative.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon (MATIC) Price Forecast: Holding $1 Support or Lower?</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/matic-price-prediction-support-test/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaryamann Shrivastava]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon (MATIC) price is close to losing the support of $1 once again and will likely fall owing to the bearish market conditions. Can the altcoin defend itself?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/matic-price-prediction-support-test/">Polygon (MATIC) Price Forecast: Holding $1 Support or Lower?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The Polygon (MATIC) price managed to bring itself back above the $1 mark this week after nearly closing a daily candlestick below it.</strong></p>



<p>However, despite the bounce back, the altcoin did not manage to revive the investors’ interest, which might cause another decline.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-polygon-investors-are-taking-a-break">Polygon Investors Are Taking a Break</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/polygon-matic-network-outage/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polygon investors play a huge role</a> in impacting the direction of the MATIC price, and these holders are taking a turn for the worse. Following the recent correction and the more recent scare of the altcoin losing $1 for good, investors have seemingly decided to pull back for now.</p>



<p>This is evident from the decline in the participation of MATIC holders on the chain. The addresses conducting transactions on the network slipped to 314,000 from the average of 408,000 over the past week.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="288" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png" alt="Polygon Active Addresses. " class="wp-image-489777" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-360x122.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-768x260.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-1536x520.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-2048x693.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.26.53-25-Mar-2024-150x51.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Polygon Active Addresses. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://app.santiment.net/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Santiment</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>However, the existing investors were not the only ones to note a 23% fall in participation as the bearish market cues spooked potential investors as well.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/buy-polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Buy Polygon (MATIC) and Everything You Need To Know</a></strong></p>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/polygon-price-correction-continue/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">New addresses forming on the network</a> ended up taking a hit, too, as potential MATIC investors turned away due to hesitation. Consequently, the network growth plunged, falling to its lowest point since December 2023.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="288" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png" alt="Polygon Network Growth. " class="wp-image-489779" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-360x122.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-768x260.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-1536x520.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-2048x693.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Polygon-on-Polygon-MATIC-18.14.40-25-Mar-2024-150x51.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Polygon Network Growth. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://app.santiment.net/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Santiment</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>This indicates that the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/matic-price-rise-threatened-crucial-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polygon native token</a> will probably be available for a while before it becomes the preference of both old and new investors again.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-matic-price-prediction-an-important-support">MATIC Price Prediction: An Important Support</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/matic-price-drop-month-march/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">MATIC price is trading above the $1 support</a> level at the time of writing, closing in on breaching the resistance marked at $1.02. Nevertheless, considering the aforementioned factors, the chances of a decline below the $1 support are very high.</p>



<p>If the cryptocurrency does end up falling below the $1 mark, it will find some support at $0.92, which will result in a post at $0.88. MATIC will thus register a monthly low.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="373" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5-850x373.png" alt="MATIC/USDT 1-day chart. " class="wp-image-489778" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5-850x373.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5-360x158.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5-768x337.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5-1536x675.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5-150x66.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/hhXnMlq5.png 1755w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">MATIC/USDT 1-day chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/matic-wallets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">14 Best Polygon (MATIC) Wallets in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>However, if the $1.02 level is breached, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/polygon-price-correction-key-support/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">MATIC price can manage to flip the $1.09 resistance</a> level into support, which would invalidate the bearish thesis. This would allow the altcoin to recover its recent losses, too.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/matic-price-prediction-support-test/">Polygon (MATIC) Price Forecast: Holding $1 Support or Lower?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bic_Polygon_matic-covers_bearish.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bic_Polygon_matic-covers_bearish.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Clients Interested in Bitcoin as Halving Nears</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/goldman-sachs-interested-bitcoin-halving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489869</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Goldman Sachs is experiencing a surge in cryptocurrency interest, especially in Bitcoin, from hedge-fund clients as the market anticipates the next halving event, highlighting a significant moment for institutional investment in digital assets.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/goldman-sachs-interested-bitcoin-halving/">Goldman Sachs Clients Interested in Bitcoin as Halving Nears</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The anticipation surrounding Bitcoin&#8217;s upcoming halving has sparked a notable shift in investors&#8217; sentiment. Goldman Sachs, for instance, is witnessing a surge in interest from its hedge-fund clients towards the crypto market. </strong></p>



<p>This resurgence in enthusiasm is not limited to the speculative individual investor but extends to the sophisticated institutional investors.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-goldman-sachs-investors-want-to-bet-on-bitcoin">Goldman Sachs Investors Want to Bet on Bitcoin</h2>



<p>Max Minton, Goldman Sachs&#8217; Asia Pacific Head of Digital Assets, said that the approval of <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/how-to-prepare-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs)</a> has reignited the spark of interest among the firm&#8217;s clients. Many of them are either actively investing in the crypto market or exploring the potential to do so. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“It was a quieter year last year, but we’ve seen a pickup in interest from clients in onboarding, pipeline, and volume since the start of the year,” Minton <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-24/goldman-s-hedge-fund-clients-get-more-active-in-crypto-options" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>Goldman&#8217;s current clientele, mainly conventional hedge funds, generate the bulk of interest. Additionally, the institution is broadening its reach to encompass a diverse range of clients. These include asset managers, its own banking customers, and certain firms specializing in digital assets.</p>



<p>Minton mentioned that clients engage with cryptocurrency derivatives to make speculative predictions, enhance yields, and hedge. He also noted that products related to Bitcoin continue to attract the most attention from clients. However, the level of interest in products associated with Ethereum could shift based on the potential approval of <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/eth-etf-explained/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum ETFs</a> in the US.</p>



<p>The impetus for this renewed interest can also be attributed to the forthcoming <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/what-is-bitcoin-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin halving</a>. Scheduled for late April, this event will halve the reward for Bitcoin mining, prompting miners to upgrade to more efficient technology to maintain profitability. This quadrennial update is critical for sustaining the economic model of Bitcoin, with the reward decreasing to 3.125 BTC from the current 6.25.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/bitcoin-halving-investment-strategies/">Bitcoin Halving Cycles and Investment Strategies: What To Know</a></strong></p>



<p>After the 2012 halving, the market capitalization of Bitcoin surged by more than 8,000%. In a similar vein, following the 2016 halving, Bitcoin&#8217;s value experienced a more than 1,400% increase. Meanwhile, it saw a rise of over 700% subsequent to the 2020 halving.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="656" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-850x656.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Stock-to-Flow Model" class="wp-image-489876" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-850x656.jpg 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-360x278.jpg 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-768x593.jpg 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-1536x1186.jpg 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-2048x1581.jpg 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin_halving-150x116.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Bitcoin Stock-to-Flow Model. Source: <a href="https://www.globalxetfs.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Global X</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Although the stock-to-flow (S2F) model, typically applied to commodities like gold, has its flaws, it serves as one method for assessing Bitcoin&#8217;s value. This model has demonstrated a historical correlation with the price fluctuations of Bitcoin. As Bitcoin becomes increasingly scarce, experts project its value will climb from its current price.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Bitcoin (BTC) is poised for another seismic shift with its next halving event likely in April 2024. Historically, there is a correlation between halving events and subsequent increases in BTC’s price. Based on a stock-to-flow model, BTC could increase to over $130,000 by 2028,&#8221; Pedro Palandrani, Researcher at Global X, <a href="https://www.globalxetfs.com/the-bitcoin-halving-a-recurring-decimation-of-supply/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">wrote</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/bitcoin-price-prediction/">Bitcoin Price Prediction 2024 / 2025 / 2030</a></strong></p>



<p>From trading to blockchain innovation, Goldman Sachs&#8217; engagement with the cryptocurrency market reflects a broader institutional acceptance of digital assets. As the halving approaches, the bank&#8217;s proactive stance on digital assets, coupled with its clients&#8217; growing interest, represents a pivotal moment in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/goldman-sachs-interested-bitcoin-halving/">Goldman Sachs Clients Interested in Bitcoin as Halving Nears</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/bic_Goldman_Sachs_4-covers_bullish.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/bic_Goldman_Sachs_4-covers_bullish.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s Why Solana (SOL) Price Could Fall by 15% This Week</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/why-solana-sol-price-correction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaryamann Shrivastava]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489731</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana price is set to note further drawdown as the altcoin is losing the interest of institutional investors at the moment. A bounce back is possible if this happens.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/why-solana-sol-price-correction/">Here’s Why Solana (SOL) Price Could Fall by 15% This Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Solana (SOL) is losing the support of one of the most important groups of investors, the institutions.</strong></p>



<p>This will likely result in a massive correction for SOL unless the altcoin manages to do this.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-institutions-take-a-break-from-solana">Institutions Take a Break From Solana</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/top-solana-memecoins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana&#8217;s price, like every other cryptocurrency</a>, is bound to be impacted by the actions of institutional investors. These investors are the trigger factors of any bull run and just the same, they are also one of the biggest causes of a correction.</p>



<p>This is what is expected out of <a href="https://beincrypto.com/solana-price-analysis-consolidation/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SOL going forward since the altcoin has lost a substantial amount</a> of investment from institutions. According to CoinShares’ weekly flows report, Solana, along with Bitcoin and Ethereum, noted considerable outflows.</p>



<p>Nearly $5.6 million have been pulled out by these institutions in the past week, bringing the month-to-date flows to $18.2 million, down from $23.8 million. Consequently, the net flows since the beginning of the year have come down to $1 million.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="652" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173601-850x652.png" alt="Solana Institutional Flows. " class="wp-image-489734" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173601-850x652.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173601-360x276.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173601-768x589.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173601-150x115.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173601.png 933w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Solana Institutional Flows. Source: <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-175-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6af2a10c0b30" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">CoinShares</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>This will likely trigger a decline in price, and retail investors might not be able to save Solana from this bearishness.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/solana-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana (SOL) Price Prediction 2024/2025/2030</a></strong></p>



<p>The reason behind this is the lack of optimism among them, which is <a href="https://beincrypto.com/crypto-traders-solana-base-meme-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">evidenced by the funding rate of SOL</a>. The funding rate is a mechanism in derivatives markets ensuring a balance between long and short positions. Although the rates are positive at the moment, they have noted no growth in the last ten days.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="211" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422-850x211.png" alt="Solana Funding Rate. " class="wp-image-489735" style="aspect-ratio:4.028436018957346;width:1024px;height:auto" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422-850x211.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422-360x89.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422-768x191.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422-1536x382.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422-150x37.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-173422.png 1722w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Solana Funding Rate. Source: <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Coinglass</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>This shows that traders are not betting on an increase in Solana price, which will minimize the bullish counter impact.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sol-price-prediction-another-15-decline-on-the-cards">SOL Price Prediction: Another 15% Decline on the Cards?</h2>



<p><a href="https://beincrypto.com/research-solana-outperforms-crypto-layer-one/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana&#8217;s price is presently trading at $187</a>, crossing the resistance level marked at $183. However, the altcoin will likely fall back soon as it will fail to breach the $201 barrier as it did earlier this month.</p>



<p>This will potentially result in a drawdown, bringing Solana&#8217;s price down to $160, marking a 15% decline, falling through the support level marked at $168.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="373" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS-850x373.png" alt="SOL/USDT 1-day chart. " class="wp-image-489733" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS-850x373.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS-360x158.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS-768x337.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS-1536x675.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS-150x66.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/XaVJkTtS.png 1755w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">SOL/USDT 1-day chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/best-solana-wallets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">13 Best Solana (SOL) Wallets To Consider In March 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>On the other hand, should <a href="https://beincrypto.com/solana-price-drop-institutional-interest-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana&#8217;s price break past the $200 resistance level</a>, it would invalidate the bearish thesis. This would send SOL towards $220.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/why-solana-sol-price-correction/">Here’s Why Solana (SOL) Price Could Fall by 15% This Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/bic_-Solana_SOL_5-covers_bearish.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/bic_-Solana_SOL_5-covers_bearish.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>London Stock Exchange to Launch Crypto ETNs</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/london-stock-exchange-launch-crypto-etn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489909</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On May 28, 2024, the London Stock Exchange will start trading Bitcoin and Ethereum ETNs, blending traditional stock market strength with cryptocurrency innovation, pending FCA approval.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/london-stock-exchange-launch-crypto-etn/">London Stock Exchange to Launch Crypto ETNs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The London Stock Exchange (LSE) has confirmed its plans to open its doors to trading cryptocurrency Exchange-Traded Notes (ETNs), specifically Bitcoin and Ethereum. </strong></p>



<p>This strategic move marks a pivotal moment in financial innovation, blending the traditional robustness of the stock market with the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-etns-arrive-at-the-london-stock-exchange">Crypto ETNs Arrive at the London Stock Exchange</h2>



<p>The launch is conditional upon the approval of base prospectuses by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). This is a necessary step in listing these financial instruments on the Main Market and the FCA&#8217;s Official List. The <a href="https://docs.londonstockexchange.com/sites/default/files/documents/n0324.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">decision</a> to set the trading commencement for late May 28, 2024, is deliberate. It aims to include the maximum number of issuers right from the get-go. </p>



<p>This timing consideration also allows issuers ample time to meet the comprehensive requirements detailed in the Crypto ETN <a href="https://docs.londonstockexchange.com/sites/default/files/documents/crypto_etn_admission_factsheet.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">factsheet</a>. It also allows them to prepare the essential documentation for establishing a Crypto ETN program, including a letter outlining compliance. </p>



<p>Moreover, issuers interested in being part of this launch are required to submit specific details by April 15, 2024. </p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;In choosing this date we have taken into consideration that we need to ensure that issuers meet the requirements for consideration detailed in the Crypto ETN factsheet,&#8221; the London Stock Exchange wrote. </p>
</blockquote>



<p>This meticulous preparation reflects the LSE&#8217;s commitment to ensuring that all listed Crypto ETNs meet the highest standards of transparency and regulatory compliance. However, issuers who fail to comply by May 22, 2024, will be ineligible for the initial day of trading.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/best-crypto-apps-for-beginners/">10 Best Crypto Exchanges and Apps for Beginners in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>This initiative is a significant leap toward integrating cryptocurrencies into mainstream financial markets. It also reflects the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/london-stock-exchange-crypto-etn/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">London Stock Exchange&#8217;s authoritative stance in crypto</a>, fostering innovation while ensuring investor protection and market integrity. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/london-stock-exchange-launch-crypto-etn/">London Stock Exchange to Launch Crypto ETNs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bic_UK_economy_and_crypto_3-covers_bullish.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bic_UK_economy_and_crypto_3-covers_bullish.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nigeria Charges Binance With Tax Evasion</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/nigeria-charges-binance-tax-evasion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489797</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria charges Binance and its officials with tax evasion, aiming to bolster fiscal discipline and ensure cryptocurrency market tax compliance amidst global regulatory challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/nigeria-charges-binance-tax-evasion/">Nigeria Charges Binance With Tax Evasion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Nigeria&#8217;s Federal Government has formally charged Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, with tax evasion. </strong></p>



<p>This bold action, aimed at reinforcing fiscal discipline and securing the nation&#8217;s economic sovereignty, was initiated by the Federal Inland Revenue Service (FIRS) and is being adjudicated at the Federal High Court in Abuja.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nigeria-accuses-binance-of-tax-evasion">Nigeria Accuses Binance of Tax Evasion</h2>



<p>The FIRS has <a href="https://www.channelstv.com/2024/03/25/fg-files-tax-evasion-charges-against-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">accused</a> Binance and two of its high-ranking officials, <a href="https://beincrypto.com/binance-nigeria-hostages/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tigran Gambaryan and Nadeem Anjarwalla</a>, of evading Value-Added Tax (VAT) and Company Income Tax, alongside failing to fulfill tax filing obligations. This case marks a significant chapter in Nigeria&#8217;s effort to ensure tax compliance within the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>Binance&#8217;s alleged transgressions include the non-payment of various taxes, contravening the FIRS Establishment Act 2007. Notably, accusations against the exchange include failing to register for tax purposes in Nigeria and neglecting to issue VAT invoices. These are critical for tax assessment and collection.</p>



<p>These actions have breached Nigerian tax laws and hampered the government&#8217;s tax collection mechanisms.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;Any company that conducts business exceeding N25 million annually is deemed, by the Finance Act, to be present in Nigeria. According to this rule, Binance falls into that category. So, it is obligated to pay taxes,&#8221; the FIRS noted.</p>
</blockquote>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/binance-alternatives/">7 Best Binance Alternatives in 2024</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe loading="lazy" title="The Rise and Fall of Binance" width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q_CUjMjtvnI?feature=oembed&#038;enablejsapi=1&#038;origin=https://beincrypto.com" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>This legal confrontation comes on the heels of <a href="https://beincrypto.com/binance-pay-doj-fine-without-selling-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance&#8217;s admission of guilt</a> to violating US anti-money laundering regulations, resulting in a $4.3 billion fine. The current charges in <a href="https://beincrypto.com/nigeria-binance-forex-manipulation/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Nigeria spotlight the crypto giant&#8217;s regulatory challenges</a>. It emphasizes the Nigerian government&#8217;s resolve to combat financial impropriety and ensure tax compliance.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/nigeria-charges-binance-tax-evasion/">Nigeria Charges Binance With Tax Evasion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_binance_law_judge-covers.jpg" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/jpeg" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bic_binance_law_judge-covers.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Internet Computer (ICP) Price Hits 23-Month High &#8211; Can it Breach $18 Next?</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/icp-price-yearly-high-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaryamann Shrivastava]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Internet Computer price hit a new high this past week. The network at the same time reached an important milestone this week, which might lead to further rise.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/icp-price-yearly-high-analysis/">Internet Computer (ICP) Price Hits 23-Month High &#8211; Can it Breach $18 Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>The Internet Computer (ICP) price had a successful run over the past week, breaking through a crucial barrier.</strong></p>



<p>But will this growth continue down the line if investors’ bullishness is lost?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-internet-computer-reaches-new-milestone">Internet Computer Reaches New Milestone</h2>



<p>The <a href="https://beincrypto.com/internet-computer-icp-and-inqubeta-qubethrive-despite-mini-market-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Internet Computer price rallied</a> over the last few days as the network inched close to a new achievement. This milestone was reached during the intra-day trading hours on Monday as Internet Computer validated 3 billion blocks.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="564" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgSAjoaUAAAshA-850x564.jpeg" alt="Internet Computer reaches 3 Billion Blocks. " class="wp-image-489651" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgSAjoaUAAAshA-850x564.jpeg 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgSAjoaUAAAshA-360x239.jpeg 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgSAjoaUAAAshA-768x509.jpeg 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgSAjoaUAAAshA-150x99.jpeg 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgSAjoaUAAAshA.jpeg 1520w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Internet Computer reaches 3 Billion Blocks. Source: <a href="https://twitter.com/dfinity/status/1772186257944371664" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">X</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>This <a href="https://beincrypto.com/internet-computer-icp-price-increase-20/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">achievement came nearly three years</a> since the launch of the protocol in May 2021, processing over 44.87 blocks per second as of date.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/internet-computer-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Internet Computer (ICP) Price Prediction 2023/2025/2030</a></strong></p>



<p>In addition to this achievement, the altcoin is seeing considerable support from its investors who, despite the rally, are still optimistic about <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ai-token-internet-computer-icp-cracks-cmc-top-20-is-7-million-phenomenon-next/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">further increases in price</a>. This is evinced by the weighted sentiment of ICP holders, who are exhibiting bullishness at the time of writing.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="288" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png" alt="Internet Computer Weighted Sentiment. " class="wp-image-489649" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-850x288.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-360x122.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-768x260.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-1536x520.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-2048x693.png 2048w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Internet-Computer-ICP-16.00.02-25-Mar-2024-150x51.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">ICP Weighted Sentiment. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://app.santiment.net/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Santiment</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>Therefore, ICP price will likely see further growth, potentially even crossing the $18 mark.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-icp-price-prediction-what-comes-after-the-54-rally">ICP Price Prediction: What Comes After the 54% Rally?</h2>



<p>The Internet Computer price rose by 54.45% in the last few days, touching $17 and shooting up from $10.91. The altcoin lived up to the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/icp-price-prediction-march-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">prediction made by BeInCrypto</a>, where a rally to $15 was expected before the end of the month.</p>



<p>Going forward, despite the massive rally, ICP will potentially stretch its uptrend a little further to tag the resistance at $18. Crossing this barrier will push the altcoin to note a 30-month high.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="850" height="373" src="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI-850x373.png" alt="ICP/USDT 12-hour chart. " class="wp-image-489650" srcset="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI-850x373.png 850w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI-360x158.png 360w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI-768x337.png 768w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI-1536x675.png 1536w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI-150x66.png 150w, https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rS1W44ZI.png 1755w" sizes="(max-width: 850px) 100vw, 850px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">ICP/USDT 12-hour chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>However, the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/ai-token-internet-computer-icp-cracks-cmc-top-20-is-7-million-phenomenon-next/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ICP price will face resistance</a> in closing above the $17 resistance bar. The cryptocurrency has failed to do so in the past once, and another instance will likely result in some corrections.</p>



<p><strong>Read More: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/icp-token-explainer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Internet Computer (ICP) Coin Explainer for Beginners</a></strong></p>



<p>ICP might thus witness a drawdown to $15.34 while the market cools down, potentially invalidating the bullish thesis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/icp-price-yearly-high-analysis/">Internet Computer (ICP) Price Hits 23-Month High &#8211; Can it Breach $18 Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bic_man_altcoins_positive.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bic_man_altcoins_positive.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Binance Alternative, CommEX, Closes Down</title>
		<link>https://beincrypto.com/russian-crypto-exchange-commex-closes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bary Rahma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beincrypto.com/?p=489836</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CommEx, a key player in Russia's cryptocurrency market and known as the Binance alternative, is shutting down. Users must withdraw assets by May 10 to evade a 1% fee.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/russian-crypto-exchange-commex-closes/">Russian Binance Alternative, CommEX, Closes Down</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>CommEx, the crypto exchange heralded as the Russian alternative to Binance, announced it is shutting down. </strong></p>



<p>This development comes after CommEx took over Binance&#8217;s operations in Russia in a deal that was shrouded in secrecy. The announcement, made through its official Telegram channel, outlined a phased shutdown process beginning with the cessation of new user registrations effective immediately.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-exchange-commex-closes-doors">Crypto Exchange CommEX Closes Doors</h2>



<p>CommEx&#8217;s <a href="https://t.me/CommEX_RUChat/150597" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">decision</a> to halt operations has sent ripples through the cryptocurrency community in Russia. The phased closure will see the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/binance-quit-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">suspension of asset transfers from Binance</a>, alongside a stop on all fiat and cryptocurrency deposits starting today. </p>



<p>This move precedes the termination of futures trading set for later this week and the suspension of new peer-to-peer listings by April 2. The closure timeline extends to April 23, when the spot market will cease operations, culminating in the crypto exchange&#8217;s website becoming inaccessible by May 10.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;We are forced to announce a gradual suspension of operations on the CommEX platform starting March 25, 2024. We recommend promptly closing positions and withdrawing assets to external wallets,&#8221; CommEx wrote.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>In light of these developments, CommEx has advised its users to expediently close their positions and withdraw their cryptocurrencies to avoid a management fee of 1% on remaining balances post-May 10. This fee imposition indicates a firm end to the platform&#8217;s activities, pushing users to secure their investments without delay.</p>



<p><strong>Read more: <a href="https://beincrypto.com/learn/no-kyc-crypto-exchanges/">14 Best No KYC Crypto Exchanges in 2024</a></strong></p>



<p>The closure of CommEx comes after Binance&#8217;s strategic retreat from the <a href="https://beincrypto.com/russian-finance-minister-crypto-not-prohibited/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Russian market amidst increasing regulatory scrutiny</a>. Binance&#8217;s exit, through selling its Russian business to CommEx just before the latter&#8217;s launch, was a pivotal moment for the cryptocurrency market in Russia. </p>



<p>Now, as CommEx ceases operations, the market faces new challenges and uncertainties. This situation reflects the volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market, not just in Russia but globally, with regulatory pressures continuing to shape the operations of crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://beincrypto.com/russian-crypto-exchange-commex-closes/">Russian Binance Alternative, CommEX, Closes Down</a> appeared first on <a href="https://beincrypto.com">BeInCrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bic_Recession_negative_2.png" medium="image" width="1280" height="720" type="image/png" />
<media:thumbnail url="https://beincrypto.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bic_Recession_negative_2.png"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
