<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bitcoinist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:27:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/cropped-cropped-cropped-Icon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">225283986</site>	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Action: Why A 10% Drop Would Cost Traders $66 Million</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-10-drop-66-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE traders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin has been quite strong over the weekend despite other assets in the crypto space taking a beating. This has seen the meme coin favor long traders during this time. However, bulls are not completely out of the woods and a drop in price from here would be detrimental to the tune of tens of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="p2">Dogecoin Price Drop To $0.15 Would Wipe Out $66 Million</h2>
<p class="p2">The Dogecoin price is still holding steady above $0.17, but long traders face a threat if the price were to break down and retreat from here. According to <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/pro/futures/LiquidationMap" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> from Coinglass, there are a lot of traders who would lose money if the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-outperform-dogecoin/">DOGE price</a> were to fall 10% from its current level.</p>

<p class="p2">The liquidation heat map on the website shows that right above the $0.153 level, there is a lot of leveraged longs. A total of 2.43 million <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-outperform-dogecoin/">DOGE</a> in leveraged longs have their liquidation price at this point, and a drop below this price mark would lead to massive liquidations. In total, there are $66.89 million worth of longs at this level, and a 10% drop would trigger this liquidation trend.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-289440 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=640&#038;resize=640%2C264" alt="Dogecoin liquidation map" width="640" height="264" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=2756 2756w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=640&#038;resize=640%2C264 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=1536 1536w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=2048 2048w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" data-recalc-dims="1" />Source: Coinglass</p>
<p class="p2">On the other end of the spectrum, there are a large number of leveraged shorts that will be liquidated if the price were to rise another 10% from here. Coinglass data shows that the liquidation volumes, if Dogecoin moves above $0.1908, would cross more than $55 million.</p>
<p class="p2">In the shorter term, short traders stand to suffer $20 million in liquidations if the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/big-money-eyes-dogecoin-whale-activity-explodes-600/">DOGE price</a> reaches $0.18. Whole long traders risk a similar amount if the price of the meme coin breaks down below $0.17.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can DOGE Price Reclaim $0.2?</h2>
<p class="p2">The Dogecoin price continues to get a lot of support, and one of the most recent instances of this is the price surging when the social media platform X (formerly Twitter) announced that it had gotten a number of licenses for its money transmitter business.</p>

<p class="p2">Crypto analysts have also shown bullishness toward the meme coin, expecting the Dogecoin price to continue to rise. One such case is from crypto analyst DonAlt who <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-pundit-predicts-price-surge-for-dogecoin/">believes that the DOGE price could reach a new all-time high with a target at $1</a>.</p>
<p class="p2">DonAlt explains that the meme coin has being trading quite well alongside Bitcoin, so the possibility that it rallies towards $1 is high. The crypto analyst believes that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-surges-x-payments-secures-3-new-licenses/">DOGE</a> is a great investment and it would be a great buy if it does dip to $1 again.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yPABAshh/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?fit=304%2C166" width="304" height="166" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289398</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Shatters Profit-Taking Streak From 2021 Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-shatters-profit-taking-streak-2021-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin profit-taking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Profits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Record]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289443</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the recent Bitcoin consecutive profit-taking day streak has now surpassed the longest run from the 2021 bull rally. Bitcoin Has Now Seen 157 Straight Days Of Net Profit-Taking As analyst James Van Straten explained as a new post on X, BTC has already surpassed the longest profit-taking spree from the previous bull [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the recent Bitcoin consecutive profit-taking day streak has now surpassed the longest run from the 2021 bull rally.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Now Seen 157 Straight Days Of Net Profit-Taking</h2>
<p>As analyst James Van Straten explained as a new <a href="https://twitter.com/jvs_btc/status/1772226408451875076" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, BTC has already surpassed the longest profit-taking spree from the previous bull run during this rally so far.</p>
<p>The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-going-through-one-profit-taking-events-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Net Realized Profit/Loss</a>,&#8221; which tracks the net amount of profit or loss (in USD) that Bitcoin investors as a whole are realizing with their selling.</p>

<p>This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each sold coin to see what price it was moved at before this. Assuming that the last transaction of the coin was the last point at which it changed hands, the price at its time would have been its cost basis leading up to its latest sale.</p>
<p>The indicator then subtracts this price from the current spot price at which it&#8217;s being sold/transferred to calculate the realized profit or loss. Naturally, if this difference is positive, the coin&#8217;s sale is contributing to the profit-taking volume, while it being negative implies loss realization.</p>
<p>The Net Realized Profit/Loss sums up all these profits and losses for all the coins being sold at a given moment to output the overall situation in the market.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 7-day moving average (MA) of this Bitcoin indicator over the past few years:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GJg1wsVWQAEEwoU?format=jpg&amp;name=large" alt="Bitcoin Net Realized Profit/Loss" width="1800" height="1013" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the 7-day MA of the Bitcoin Net Realized Profit/Loss has been positive for the past few months. To be more particular, the indicator has held these values for 157 consecutive days now.</p>
<p>When this metric has green values, it means that the market as a whole is participating in a net amount of profit-taking. Similarly, red values imply the dominance of loss-taking.</p>
<p>It would appear that the investors have been taking net profit for 157 straight days now, which is longer than the longest profit-taking streak during the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-volume-79-lower-2021-bull-run-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">2021 bull run</a> (155 days).</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that Bitcoin Net Realized Profit/Loss shot especially high as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price explored <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-breaks-through-69000-setting-new-record/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">new all-time highs</a> earlier. The price top so far coincided with the peak of this spike in the indicator, where its 7-day MA value hit $3.6 billion.</p>
<p>This profit-taking level was similar to the largest event observed during the last bull run. According to Straten, this is one of the reasons the asset has seen such a massive selloff.</p>

<p>Despite hitting record levels already, the profit-taking may not be ending anytime soon; however, as the analyst says, &#8220;this trend will continue as we are in a bull run and is still relatively mild compared to the 2021 bull run.&#8221;</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Bullish momentum appears to have returned for Bitcoin as the cryptocurrency has surpassed the $69,000 level after a surge of more than 5% over the past day.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NtaxTQBf/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_1063376348-1.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289443</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stalls As Evening Star Forms: Can BTC Bulls Still Shine?</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-evening-star-btc-bulls-still-shine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GBTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; Severino, the Head of Research at NewsBTC and a certified CME, has identified an &#8220;Evening Star&#8221; candlestick pattern on the monthly chart of the Bitcoin CME futures. This formation, which traditionally indicates a potential trend reversal, is forming at a critical point for Bitcoin. According to Severino, there could be tell-tale signs suggesting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; Severino, the Head of Research at NewsBTC and a certified CME, has <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1772234677207625779" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">identified</a><a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1772234677207625779" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a>an &#8220;Evening Star&#8221; candlestick pattern on the monthly chart of the Bitcoin CME futures. This formation, which traditionally indicates a potential trend reversal, is forming at a critical point for Bitcoin. </p>
<p>According to Severino, there could be tell-tale signs suggesting that the Bitcoin upswing could end as the momentum fades.</p>
<h2>The Evening Star Formation: BTC Bull Run Over?</h2>
<p>Though there are concerns that the pattern is forming on the Bitcoin CME futures chart, it is absent from the spot BTCUSD chart on ordinary charts from Binance or Coinbase, for example. Accordingly, the lack of uniformity on charts has also left Severino questioning the reliability of the signal. </p>

<p>While the Evening Star pattern suggests a possible reversal, Severino cautions that Bitcoin could still reach higher highs in the coming months before peaking and reversing. However, the analyst stresses that predicting the exact timing of these events is a challenge. </p>
<p>Based on candlestick analysis, Severino predicts that Bitcoin could peak within the next two quarters, possibly in mid- or late Q3 2024. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EU4owKnQ/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EU4owKnQ/" alt="Bitcoin price trending upward on the daily chart | Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1787" height="904" /></a>
<p>When writing, Bitcoin is trading at around all-time highs. Following the cool-off of last week, the coin bounced back strongly over the weekend, wiping out some losses. The coin is technically within a bearish breakout formation, trading below the 20-day moving average, clear in the daily chart.</p>
<p>For the uptrend to continue and extend from the formation in the daily chart, BTC must push above $70,000. The validity of this uptrend will be solid if the leg up is with expanding trading volume. </p>

<p>Severino also notes that the leg up will be valid and the Evening Star formation invalid if there is a strong close above $74,000 by the end of the month. Bitcoin prices peaked at around $73,800 in early March, buoyed by expanding demand, especially from spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<h2>Spot Bitcoin ETFs Post More Outflows</h2>
<p>Despite the potential for a continued rally, some fundamental factors pose challenges. Notably, outflows from spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), particularly from the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), are rising. Rumors suggest that bankrupt crypto lender <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/genesis-face-21-million-penalty-sec-charges-settled/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Genesis</a> could be liquidating its GBTC holdings, adding further selling pressure to the market.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-289501" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768" alt="Outflows from spot BTC ETF issuers | Source: Lookonchain data" width="1024" height="768" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=2645 2645w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=560 560w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=879 879w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=1536 1536w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=2048 2048w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1" />
<p> By March 22, spot Bitcoin ETF issuers had experienced <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1771221747318075748" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">outflows</a> for five straight days, according to Lookonchain data. Nonetheless, as GBTC posts outflows, BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT continues attracting more clients seeking BTC exposure.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Crypto-news-Template176.jpg?fit=640%2C362" width="640" height="362" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289500</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Large Shiba Inu Transactions Spark Fears Of A Massive Dumping Spree</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-transactions-spree/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) whales look to be at it again following large transactions involving the meme token in the last 24 hours. As expected, these transactions have raised concerns that crypto investors might be looking to offload their tokens on the market.  Shiba Inu Whales Move Billions Of SHIB On-chain data shows that Shiba Inu [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-pepe-whales-sold/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) whales</a> look to be at it again following large transactions involving the meme token in the last 24 hours. As expected, these transactions have raised concerns that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-23-5-million-shiba-inu/">crypto investors</a> might be looking to offload their tokens on the market. </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Whales Move Billions Of SHIB</h2>
<p><a href="https://etherscan.io/advanced-filter?tkn=0x95aD61b0a150d79219dCF64E1E6Cc01f0B64C4cE&amp;txntype=2&amp;__cf_chl_rt_tk=.f2yRaOf1TUS7udrjffik62iaeQ_18gwUWkSmNcTtu4-1711353862-0.0.1.1-1471" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">On-chain data</a> shows that Shiba Inu whales moved billions of SHIB in different transactions. In one transaction, 77.2 billion SHIB tokens were moved to a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-support-bitcoin-developer-with-3-6-million/">Coinbase wallet</a>. Meanwhile, over 205 billion SHIB tokens were moved across different wallets, some of which were transferred to a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-gets-boost-robinhood-wallet/">Robinhood wallet</a>. </p>

<p>The transfer of some of these tokens to crypto trading platforms, Coinbase and Robinhood, has raised suspicions that these Shiba Inu whales might be planning to sell off their holdings to make some profits. If so, it could massively impact the meme coin’s price due to the magnitude of such transactions. </p>
<p>The SHIB community has seen several smart traders, including MakerDAO founder Rune Christensen, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/">take profits</a> over the past few weeks. This also contributed to the concern that these recent transactions might involve more whales who want to secure their profits. </p>
<p>However, while the possibility of a sell-off exists, this could be just investors using the recent price dip as an opportunity to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whales-shib/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">accumulate more</a> of the meme coin. SHIB experienced a significant price surge, which saw it climb to become the tenth-largest crypto token by market cap. However, it has dropped out of the top 10 after its recent price decline.</p>
<p>The theory of SHIB accumulation looks plausible considering that more upward trend is expected for the crypto token. Therefore, investors will still be looking to position themselves ahead of this bull run, which could see the meme coin <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-dogecoin-shib-excitement/">break its all-time high (ATH)</a>. </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Still Has Bullish Momentum</h2>
<p>SHIB may be ready for another upward movement if the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/">wave of profit-taking</a> by investors is now over. Crypto analyst Xanrox <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/">suggested</a> that the meme coin could hit a new ATH by July, which means more parabolic price moves are to be expected if this price prediction is to be realized by then. </p>

<p>SHIB’s fundamentals also suggest that it is only a matter of time before the upward trend continues. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-latest-shib-magazine/">Shiba Inu team</a> continues to develop innovations that can help propel SHIB’s price. Meanwhile, although Shibarium’s daily transactions continue to decline, they are likely to pick up at some point, with a massive increase in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burns-bright-shib/">SHIB burns</a> expected once that happens. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB is trading at $0.00002771, down almost 1% in the last 24 hours, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KS4stUfp/" alt="Shiba Inu price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Shiba-Inu-22.jpeg?fit=640%2C366" width="640" height="366" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289397</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Shockwave: Nearly $1 Billion Vanishes From Global Funds In Historic Outflow</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-shock-nearly-billion-vanishes-global-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CoinShares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Funds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outflow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last week, the crypto investment landscape witnessed a significant exodus of capital from global crypto funds. A recent report from CoinShares highlighted nearly $1 billion net outflow from these funds, marking a historic departure from a 7-week inflow streak that had cumulatively amassed $12.3 billion. A Closer Look At The Outflows The magnitude of these [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last week, the crypto investment landscape <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-175-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6af2a10c0b30" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">witnessed</a> a significant exodus of capital from global crypto funds. A recent report from CoinShares highlighted nearly $1 billion net outflow from these funds, marking a historic departure from a 7-week inflow streak that had cumulatively amassed $12.3 billion.</p>
<h2>A Closer Look At The Outflows</h2>
<p>The magnitude of these outflows at roughly $942 million is particularly notable, almost doubling the previous record of $500 million witnessed towards the end of January.</p>

<p>Major players in the asset management space, including BlackRock, Bitwise, Fidelity, Grayscale, ProShares, and 21Shares, felt the brunt of this wave of withdrawals, according to CoinShares.</p>
<p>The timing of these outflows coincided with a notable correction in the prices of underlying <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/iceland-prioritizes-food-over-crypto-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">cryptocurrencies</a>, which erased $10 billion from the fund&#8217;s assets under management (AUM). However, the combined AUM of $88 billion still hovers above prior cycle highs.</p>
<p>Notably, these outflows have pronounced impacted trading volumes and asset valuations within the crypto investment product sector. Last week&#8217;s trading volume plummeted by a third to $28 billion amidst a price correction that significantly diminished the AUM of these funds.</p>
<p>The US market, particularly new <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-noobs-panic-selling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">spot Bitcoin ETFs</a>, witnessed over $1 billion in inflows, which were insufficient to offset the nearly $2 billion <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/back-to-back-negative-bitcoin-etf-flows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">outflows from Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC fund</a> conversion.</p>
<p>According to CoinShares Head of Research James Butterfill, the &#8220;recent price correction&#8221; resulted in &#8220;hesitancy from investors, leading to much lower inflows into new ETF issuers in the US, which saw US$1.1bn inflows, partially offsetting incumbent Grayscale’s significant US$2bn outflows last week.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Global Crypto Sentiment And Market Responses</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, last week&#8217;s sentiment was not solely concentrated on US-based funds or Bitcoin. Investment products in Sweden, Hong Kong, Switzerland, and Germany also experienced outflows, though Brazil and Canada-based funds recorded inflows, showcasing a mixed global investor sentiment.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-289492 size-large" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?resize=980%2C582" alt="Crypto asset flows by country." width="980" height="582" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=1388 1388w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1" />
<p>Additionally, Ethereum, Solana, and Cardano-based products faced outflows, underscoring the broad impact of the market&#8217;s downturn. In contrast, other altcoin funds like Polkadot, Avalanche, and Litecoin saw net inflows, indicating selective investor interest in the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/doge-ada-cardano-altcoin-season/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">altcoin sector</a>.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-289495 size-large" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?resize=980%2C644" alt="Crypto asset flows." width="980" height="644" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=1396 1396w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1" />
<p>This period of market recalibration has also sparked a dialogue among industry leaders about the role and accessibility of Bitcoin ETFs in fostering broader market integration.</p>
<p>Bivu Das of Kraken UK and Daniel Seifert of Coinbase UK have both <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-buzz-in-uk-kraken-executive-pushes-for-market-access/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">advocated for the UK market&#8217;s access to Bitcoin ETFs</a>, citing the importance of such investment products in establishing a comprehensive crypto ecosystem.</p>

<p>As reported, by offering indirect exposure to Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements, these instruments propose a regulated and possibly more accessible avenue for investors, contributing to the diversification and maturity of the investment landscape in the digital currency market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ICYMI: Kraken UK Managing Director Bivu Das says he&#8217;d &#8220;absolutely&#8221; like to see a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> ETF in the UK, providing regulated access to crypto exposure currently lacking and boost UK&#8217;s crypto hub ambitions, and legitimize bitcoin for institutions.</p>
<p>— AP Crypto (@AP_Crypto_) <a href="https://twitter.com/AP_Crypto_/status/1771514821940547931?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Singapores-Top-Banker-Predicts-Endgame-For-Private-Cryptos.webp?fit=631%2C420" width="631" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289462</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terraform Labs In The Hot Seat: Trial Begins As Do Kwon&#8217;s Final Extradition Decision Looms</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/terraform-labs-in-the-hot-seat-trial-begins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon Extradition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Collapse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Crash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs vs SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289494</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terraform Labs is set to face a high-stakes trial on Monday, grappling with civil fraud allegations linked to the collapse of its TerraUSD stablecoin in 2022. Meanwhile, Terra co-founder Do Kwon remains in Montenegro awaiting the decision on whether he will be extradited to the United States or South Korea to face criminal charges.  Terraform [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terraform Labs is set to face a high-stakes trial on Monday, grappling with civil fraud allegations linked to the collapse of its <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/terraform-labs-accuses-sec-of-government-overreach/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">TerraUSD stablecoin</a> in 2022. Meanwhile, Terra co-founder Do Kwon remains in Montenegro awaiting the decision on whether he will be extradited to the United States or South Korea to face criminal charges. </p>
<h2>Terraform Labs Faces Trial Over $40 Billion TerraUSD Collapse</h2>
<p>The civil case against Terraform Labs centers on fraud allegations brought forth by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), stemming from the collapse of TerraUSD, which resulted in the loss of approximately $40 billion in investor assets. </p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-25/terraform-goes-on-trial-as-kwon-awaits-extradition-in-montenegro" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>, the trial will see a Manhattan jury deliberating the fraud claims, examining the SEC&#8217;s allegations regarding Terraform Labs&#8217; “deceitful practices.” </p>

<p>While the trial unfolds, Do Kwon finds himself caught in the Montenegro justice system, awaiting the crucial decision on his <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/do-kwon-released-from-prison-remanded-to-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">extradition</a>. Having faced criminal charges in both the US and South Korea, Kwon&#8217;s release from a Montenegro prison on Saturday was accompanied by the country&#8217;s Supreme Court reviewing earlier court rulings regarding his potential extradition to South Korea. </p>
<p>The circumstances surrounding Kwon&#8217;s extradition challenge SEC enforcers, as civil suits typically take a back seat to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/terraform-labs-166m-payment-under-sec-investigation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">criminal proceedings</a>. Until Kwon is in the US, a criminal trial cannot occur.</p>
<p>In light of these developments, the SEC is seeking a court order to enjoin Terraform Labs and Do Kwon from future violations of US securities laws. In addition, the SEC is seeking <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/montenegro-orders-do-kwon-extradition-to-s-korea/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">civil penalties</a> and disgorgement of ill-gotten gains. </p>
<p>The regulatory authority claims that Terraform Labs defrauded investors by falsely asserting that the popular Korean payment app, Chai, utilized Terraform&#8217;s blockchain technology for processing and settling cryptocurrency transactions. </p>
<p>The SEC further alleges that investors were misled about the stability of TerraUSD, which was purportedly algorithmically &#8220;pegged&#8221; to the US dollar. Terraform Labs strongly denies these allegations, criticizing the SEC&#8217;s characterization of cryptocurrency companies as “lawless.”</p>
<h2>Whistleblowers And Key Witnesses Take The Stand</h2>
<p>Having filed for <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/terraform-labs-files-for-bankruptcy-in-the-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection</a> in January, Terraform Labs argued it could not pay the penalties sought by federal regulators. Do Kwon, who owns approximately 92% of the company&#8217;s equity, faces the daunting task of navigating these legal battles while Terraform Labs&#8217; fate hangs in the balance. </p>
<p>US District Judge Jed Rakoff, who is presiding over the civil case, ruled in December that Terraform is liable for selling &#8220;unregistered securities.&#8221; This is in line with the SEC&#8217;s hinting that cryptocurrencies other than Bitcoin (BTC) are “securities” under the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/terraform-labs-sec-wins-trial-date-january-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Howey test</a>, which many pro-crypto advocates and companies believe is an &#8220;outdated set of rules and laws.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, Terraform maintains that its cryptocurrencies do not fall under the definition of securities, disputes the SEC&#8217;s jurisdiction, and intends to appeal the ruling.</p>

<p>During the trial, the jury is expected to hear evidence regarding the involvement of Jump Trading, a Chicago-based trading firm alleged to have entered into a “secretive arrangement” with Terraform Labs to support TerraUSD before its collapse. </p>
<p>According to Bloomberg, the SEC will allegedly present text messages between Terraform executives discussing the &#8220;depeg,&#8221; where TerraUSD lost its peg to the US dollar in May 2021. </p>
<p>Key witnesses include alleged whistleblowers, a Jump Trading executive, and the chief product officer at the Chai payment app, who aim to demonstrate Terraform and Kwon&#8217;s intentional deception. It is anticipated that Bill DiSomma, co-founder of Jump Trading, will also testify.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7Yd8hCYX/" alt="Terraform Labs" width="1814" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-7-2.jpg?fit=347%2C260" width="347" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289494</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s Why The Dogecoin Price Surged Over The Weekend</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-surged-weekend/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE price foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289395</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Popular doggy-themed cryptocurrency, Dogecoin, has recently experienced an exponential surge in its price value. Despite its previously sluggish price momentum, Dogecoin witnessed a massive $800 million increase in open interest over the weekend. Interestingly, a recent development indicates that Elon Musk’s X Payment LLC has greatly contributed to this price pump.  Why Dogecoin Price Rose [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular doggy-themed cryptocurrency, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-when-dogecoin-does-this/">Dogecoin,</a> has recently experienced an exponential surge in its price value. Despite its previously <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-growth-holder-activity/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">sluggish price momentum</a>, Dogecoin witnessed a massive $800 million increase in open interest over the weekend. Interestingly, a recent development indicates that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-makes-another-cryptic-tweet/">Elon Musk</a>’s X Payment LLC has greatly contributed to this price pump. </p>
<h2>Why Dogecoin Price Rose 35%</h2>
<p>Over the past 72 hours, the price of Dogecoin witnessed a 35% increase in its value, recording an impressive weekly high of $0.17 on Saturday.  According to <a href="https://app.santiment.net/projects/dogecoin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> from Santiment, a crypto analytics platform, the cryptocurrency has also witnessed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-open-interest-record-2/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">significant rise in open interest</a>, skyrocketing by a remarkable $800 million in value. </p>

<p>This <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-surges-x-payments-secures-3-new-licenses/">massive price surge</a> has been attributed to a recent development in Elon Musk’s payment subsidiary, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/x-payment-integration-dogecoin-included/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">X Payments LLC</a>. According to reports, X Payments has successfully expanded its operational capabilities to three new states. The platform has secured money transmitter licenses in Mexico, Oregon and Illinois.</p>
<p>Following the disclosure of this news, the sentiment surrounding Dogecoin had transformed, as <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/x-payments-dogecoin-integration/">speculations</a> about the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-outperform-dogecoin/">meme coin</a> potentially becoming a preferred payment method for the X Payments began to spread like wildfire. At the time of writing the cryptocurrency is trading at $0.172, reflecting a 14.27% price increase over the past seven days, according to CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p>Interestingly, Dogecoin has already been integrated as a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-gains-momentum-as-musk-hints-at-future-tesla-payments-is-doge-going-to-the-moon/">payment method within Musk’s Tesla</a> merchandise store. In 2023, the SpaceX CEO also teased about the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-x-peer-to-peer-payments/">possibility of DOGE payments on X</a> (formerly Twitter), pushing the broader crypto community on edge as they anticipated the potential inclusion of <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-tesla-dogecoin/">DOGE in the payments ecosystem.</a> </p>
<p>Presently, as X Payments expands its services and possibly prepares for a launch, speculations are growing stronger, driving up <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/doge/dogecoin-price-support-0-1220/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Dogecoin’s price</a> amidst the rising interest in the cryptocurrency’s potential integration with X Payments.</p>
<h2>DOGE Whales On The Move</h2>
<p>A recent <a href="https://x.com/ali_charts/status/1770798858718560581?s=46" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">report</a> has revealed that an <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/big-money-eyes-dogecoin-whale-activity-explodes-600/">anonymous Whale</a> made a substantial purchase of 25 million DOGE tokens, valued at $3.75 million, within the last 72 hours. The timing of this acquisition is particularly noteworthy as it aligns with the recent rise in Dogecoin’s price and open interest over the weekend. </p>

<p>The <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-whales-buying-spree/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Whale’s purchase</a> also coincides with X Payments expansion efforts into new regions, suggesting a potential shift in market sentiment as investors are now showing an <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-open-interest-record/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">elevated interest in DOGE</a>. If Dogecoin becomes integrated as a payment currency within X Payments, the cryptocurrency could witness a significant boost in adoption, potentially attracting more whales and new investors and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-pundit-predicts-price-surge-for-dogecoin/">triggering a substantial price surge.</a></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yPABAshh/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Dogecoin_0547cf.webp?fit=640%2C366" width="640" height="366" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289395</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Queries Why Ethereum Founder Buterin Left X</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-queries-ethereum-founder-buterin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum founder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vitalik buterin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[X]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk, the tech magnate behind SpaceX and Tesla, has raised questions about Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s apparent retreat from X, the platform Musk acquired in 2022 for $44 billion. The conversation was sparked by a post from &#8220;Autism Capital,&#8221; a crypto influencer with significant clout in the crypto dialogue, who lamented Buterin&#8217;s reduced engagement [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk, the tech magnate behind SpaceX and <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-tesla-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Tesla</a>, has raised questions about Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s apparent retreat from X, the platform Musk acquired in 2022 for $44 billion. The conversation was sparked by a post from &#8220;Autism Capital,&#8221; a crypto influencer with significant clout in the crypto dialogue, who lamented Buterin&#8217;s reduced engagement on X, advocating for its potential to significantly uplift Ethereum&#8217;s presence.</p>
<h2>Why Is The Ethereum Founder Avoiding X?</h2>
<p>“Vitalik needs to get back on X. Farcaster isn’t going to win the culture war. If he wants Ethereum to shine he should engage more on this platform, not sequester himself with his chosen peers on an island. He will have far more impact if he engages the bigger community here,” Autism Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1772172698195526057" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a>.</p>

<p>Musk&#8217;s straightforward inquiry, &#8220;Why did he leave?&#8221; posed on the platform, has since unleashed a broad spectrum of conjectures and insights from the cryptocurrency community. In the heart of the ensuing conversation, the issue of rampant <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-x-bots-dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">bot activity</a> on X was flagged as a potential deterrent for Buterin.</p>
<p>A poignant observation was made by a user referencing Tyler John&#8217;s analysis, who <a href="https://twitter.com/tyler_m_john/status/1749025877063606684?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">detailed</a> the spamming issue for the ETH co-founder: “Vitalik Buterin has to append every reply with &#8220;srry 4 ratio-ing&#8221; because immediately afterwards a deluge of sycophants, crypto bots, and followers rains down on the post with tickers, memes, and expressions of praise and all the OP can see is #ETH and $SOL for three days.”</p>
<p>Buterin responded to this in January, stating, “This is (part of) why I do most of my tweeting on farcaster these days srry 4 ratio-ing.”</p>

<p>In the midst of these discussions, Buterin&#8217;s recent <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">activity on X,</a> albeit limited, remains focused on promoting Ethereum&#8217;s technological strides. Prior to the conversation initiated by Musk and Autism Capital, Buterin highlighted the Ethereum Name Service (ENS), emphasizing its potential to eliminate vulnerabilities like multi-sig backdoors, reflecting his ongoing commitment to the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-buterin-plans-major-changes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Ethereum project</a> despite his sparse presence on X.</p>
<p>However, Buterin&#8217;s advocacy for Farcaster over X is notable. He has praised Farcaster for its decentralized nature and innovative features, such as the channel feature, which he believes offers a superior social media experience. &#8220;Farcaster’s channel feature makes it a better social media platform than X,&#8221; Buterin has stated, illustrating his support for platforms that align with his vision for a decentralized, user-empowered digital ecosystem.</p>
<p>At press time, Ethereum (ETH) price stood at $3,490. In the weekly chart, ETH held above the 0.618 Fib ($3.398), confirming the potential for further upside.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-289493" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472" alt="Ethereum price" width="1024" height="472" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=3628 3628w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=1536 1536w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=2048 2048w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=1140 1140w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHUSD_2024-03-25_15-02-48.png?resize=1024%2C472?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1" />

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1200x675_cmsv2_eb605d5a-81bd-5e3e-a58a-336de4416515-6500564.webp?fit=640%2C360" width="640" height="360" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289458</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
