<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bitcoinist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:18:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/cropped-cropped-cropped-Icon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">225283986</site>	<item>
		<title>FTX Set To Cash In $884 Million From Majority Stake Sale In Anthropic</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-set-to-cash-in-884-million-from-sale-anthropic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 03:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTT:USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTTUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX assets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX claims]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX creditors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX will sell two-thirds of its stake in artificial intelligence (AI) startup Anthropic for $884 million, according to a Bloomberg report. The move comes as FTX seeks to repay its creditors and bolster its cash reserves.  The sale involves various buyers, including ATIC Third International Investment Company LLC, associated with the United [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX will sell two-thirds of its stake in artificial intelligence (AI) startup Anthropic for $884 million, according to a Bloomberg <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/ip-law/ftx-to-sell-majority-of-anthropic-stake-for-884-million" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">report</a>. The move comes as FTX seeks to repay its creditors and bolster its cash reserves. </p>
<p>The sale involves various buyers, including ATIC Third International Investment Company LLC, associated with the United Arab Emirates (UAE) <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/uaes-address-unauthorized-digital-asset-usage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">sovereign wealth fund</a> Mubadala, Jane Street, Fidelity Management and Research, and venture capital firm HOF Capital.</p>
<h2>FTX Approved To Sell Ownership</h2>
<p>In 2021, FTX invested $500 million in Anthropic, a year before facing bankruptcy amidst allegations of fraud. Anthropic, known for its AI research work, attracted significant investments from tech giants <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/amazon-will-invest-4-billion-ftx-backed-ai-startup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Amazon </a>and Alphabet Inc.&#8217;s Google in 2023, valuing the startup at up to $6 billion.</p>

<p>The FTX bankruptcy estate currently owns an 8% stake in Anthropic, making it one of the estate&#8217;s most valuable assets. As of last month, the estate&#8217;s cash reserves were valued at approximately $6.4 billion. </p>
<p>FTX officials have expressed confidence in repaying all of the company&#8217;s <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-prosecutors-slams-questions-jury/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">creditors</a>, and the sale of the Anthropic stake is expected to significantly contribute to that effort.</p>
<p>As previously <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-creditors-1-billion-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">reported </a>by Bitcoinist, US bankruptcy Judge John Dorsey approved the decision to sell the Anthropic shares in February. Initially, FTX&#8217;s creditors had reservations about the sale, asserting that FTX had acquired the shares using customer funds. </p>
<p>However, FTX&#8217;s promise to use the sale proceeds to repay its creditors convinced them to approve the proposal. The condition for approval was that the sale proceeds be used to repay the creditors.</p>
<h2>Anthropic Undergoes Ownership Change</h2>
<p>According to Bloomberg, the sale of the majority stake in Anthropic will allow FTX to generate substantial funds, which will be crucial in addressing its financial obligations. </p>
<p>For Anthropic, the sale represents a change in ownership but does not diminish its position as a key artificial intelligence startup. The company&#8217;s previous investments from Amazon and Alphabet Inc.&#8217;s Google have bolstered its position in the rapidly growing field.</p>
<p>Following the sale of the majority of the exchange’s <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/former-ftx-executives-platform-secures-60-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">shares </a>in the startup, which company will have the majority of ownership in Antrophic remains to be seen. </p>

<p>FTX&#8217;s decision to sell its majority stake in Anthropic for $884 million is an important step in the bankruptcy reorganization process. By selling its stake, FTX aims to fully repay its creditors and strengthen its financial position. The sale also demonstrates the increased interest in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/worldcoin-up-46-in-wake-of-altman-board-reunion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">AI-related startups</a> that has significantly increased the exchange&#8217;s initial $500 million investment. </p>
<img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/kAtuBUuU/" alt="FTX" width="1815" height="858" />
<p>As of the current update, the native token of the exchange, FTT, is trading at $2.22, showing a 9% rebound in the last 24 hours. This follows its notable year-to-date surge of 74%. </p>
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-7-4.jpg?fit=390%2C260" width="390" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289559</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Houdini? Binance Exec Escapes From Nigerian Custody Amid Tax Evasion Charges – Report</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-houdini-binance-exec-escapes-from-nigerian-custody-amid-tax-evasion-charges-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubmar Garcia]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 01:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Nigeria]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigerian government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One of the two senior executives from crypto exchange Binance has escaped from the Nigerian authorities as criminal charges were pressed against him. The executive was first detained on February 26 as part of Nigeria’s actions against the exchange. According to local reports, Nigeria’s Federal Government filed Tax evasion charges against Binance amid the escapist [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400;">One of the two senior executives from crypto exchange Binance has escaped from the Nigerian authorities as criminal charges were pressed against him. The executive was <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/nigeria-detains-binances-crypto-crime-investigator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">first detained</a> on February 26 as part of Nigeria’s actions against the exchange.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">According to local reports, Nigeria’s Federal Government filed Tax evasion charges against Binance amid the escapist turmoil.</p>

<h2 style="font-weight: 400;">From Binance Executive To Crypto Escapist</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">A Nigerian newspaper <a href="https://www.premiumtimesng.com/news/top-news/680511-exclusive-detained-binance-executive-escapes-from-custody-in-nigeria.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">revealed</a> that Nadeem Anjarwalla, one of the two detained Binance executives, escaped from the government’s custody almost a month after his detention. According to the report, the executive fled the country on March 22.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">After the detention, Anjarwalla remained in custody at an Abuja guest house with Tigran Gambaryan, who was also detained. On Friday, guards on duty took the now-fugitive to a nearby mosque “for prayer in the spirit of the ongoing Ramadan fast.” However, Anjarwalla escaped and allegedly flew out of Abuja on a Middle East Airline.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The logistics for the escape have raised plenty of questions for authorities. The executive, who holds dual British and Kenyan citizenship, had his passport confiscated during the detention.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The investigation has unveiled that the fugitive fled the country with his Kenyan passport. Nonetheless, how he got access to this passport remains a mystery to authorities as he only carried his British travel document when detained in February.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Sources told the local news publication that the guest house where the Binance executives were held was “comfortable” and “allowed many rights.” The phone privileges are now believed to have been exploited by Anjarwalla to plot his escape.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities are working on discovering the fugitive&#8217;s intended destination to get him back into custody. Moreover, the country’s authorities are allegedly in talks with Interpol to issue an international arrest warrant.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">A Binance representative <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/25/binance-executive-escapes-nigerian-custody-as-authorities-file-new-tax-charges.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">confirmed</a> to CNBC that the exchange is aware of the situation and affirmed that they are collaborating with Nigerian authorities on the matter:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">We were made aware that Nadeem is no longer in Nigerian custody. Our primary focus remains on the safety of our employees and we are working collaboratively with Nigerian authorities to quickly resolve this issue.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400;">Binance Faces Tax Evasion Charges In Nigeria</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">As reported by Bitcoinist, Nigeria’s <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/nigeria-fines-binance-10-billion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">crackdown</a> on Binance saw the crypto exchange fined $10 billion earlier this month, alleging that the platform was responsible for the devaluation of the Nigerian naira.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Subsequently, the government sent a request to the exchange’s CEO, Richard Teng. The ultimatum demanded Teng to address the allegations of “terrorist financing, money laundering, and tax evasion” in the country.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The most recent reports <a href="https://punchng.com/fg-files-tax-evasion-charges-against-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">show</a> that the Nigerian government filed tax evasion charges against the crypto exchange as the shocking news of Anjarwalla&#8217;s escape hit the world.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The four charges were filed at the Federal High Court in Abuja by the Federal Inland Revenue Service. Besides Binance, Anjarwalla and Gambaryan appear as the second and third defendants against the accusations.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">Per the local report, the charges levied against the exchange include “non-payment of Value-Added Tax, Company Income Tax, failure to file tax returns, and complicity in aiding customers to evade taxes through its platform.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The Nigerian federal government also accused the crypto exchange of failing to register with the Federal Inland Revenue Service (FIRS) for tax purposes and “contravening existing tax regulations within the country.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">In November 2023, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binances-4-3b-settlement-marks-crucial-shift/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Binance</a> pleaded guilty to charges relating to anti-money laundering in the US. This resulted in a $4.3 billion settlement with authorities, including Changpeng Zhao, stepping down as the crypto exchange’s CEO.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-289535 size-large" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?resize=980%2C493" alt="BNB, BNBUSDT, Binance, crypto" width="980" height="493" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?w=1022 1022w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?w=360 360w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BNBUSDT_2024-03-25_12-41-40.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/vadim-artyukhin-_92BitC3QEU-unsplash.jpeg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289531</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Declares Binance A &#8216;Threat&#8217;, Imposes Access Restrictions On Philippine Users</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/binance-users-philippines-face-access-restriction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ronaldo Marquez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnbusdt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philippines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philippines crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philippines SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Philippines Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a significant regulatory step by blocking local access to Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume.  According to a release issued by the regulator on Monday, the SEC&#8217;s decision was based on Binance&#8217;s failure to obtain the necessary license from the commission to operate [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Philippines Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a significant regulatory step by blocking local access to Binance, the world&#8217;s largest <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-surging-beyond-80000-driven-by-etf-inflows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">cryptocurrency exchange</a> by trading volume. </p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/pr-2024/sec-proceeds-with-blocking-of-binance/#gsc.tab=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">release </a>issued by the regulator on Monday, the SEC&#8217;s decision was based on Binance&#8217;s failure to obtain the necessary license from the commission to operate as an investment and trading platform. </p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Website And Services Blocked </h2>
<p>In its March 12 meeting, the SEC approved filing a formal request with the National Telecommunications Commission (NTC) to assist in blocking Binance&#8217;s website and related web pages. </p>

<p>The SEC said Binance was offering investment and trading services without the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-implements-stricter-token-listing-procedure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">required license</a> and allegedly posed a &#8220;threat&#8221; to the safety of Filipino investors&#8217; funds. SEC Chairman Emilio Aquino emphasized the importance of protecting the interests of investors in the request sent to the NTC. Aquino states:</p>
<blockquote><p>The SEC has identified the aforementioned platform and concluded that the public’s continued access to these websites/apps poses a threat to the security of the funds of investing  Filipinos.</p></blockquote>
<p>With an average <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-investigates-300m-bome-token-pre-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">daily trading volume</a> of $65 billion and support for over 402 cryptocurrencies, Binance has gained a substantial user base of more than 183 million members in the Asian country, according to the regulator.</p>
<p>However, the SEC emphasized that Binance has not obtained the necessary license to solicit investments from the public or operate a securities exchange. Consequently, the SEC issued a public warning against investing in or using Binance&#8217;s services. </p>
<p>The commission has been actively exploring the possibility of blocking Binance&#8217;s website and online presence in the Philippines since November 2023. However, due to the “sizable operations” of Binance, the SEC has allowed sufficient time for investors to transition their portfolios toward authorized investment products and platforms.</p>
<h2>CommEX To Close Operations Following Binance Acquisition</h2>
<p>CommEX, the exchange that acquired Binance&#8217;s Russia business in September, has announced its decision to shut down. As per the company&#8217;s <a href="https://commex.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/9278429425807-CommEX-Notice-of-Operation-Suspension" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">statement </a>on its website, the delisting process will commence on May 10, rendering users unable to access any content associated with the exchange. However, a series of steps will be implemented, leading to the closure.</p>
<p>Effective March 25, 2024, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-russian-exodus-did-key-players-shift-commex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">CommEX </a>will stop new user registrations, asset transfers from Binance, and fiat and cryptocurrency deposit services. Then, on March 28, the exchange will stop opening positions for simple futures and futures trading and only allow users to close existing positions.</p>

<p>More changes will follow: Starting April 2, 2024, P2P services will prohibit merchants from creating new advertisements and prevent users from creating new orders; the system will automatically close existing P2P orders and advertising services.</p>
<p>Trading pairs for Simple Futures and Futures Trading will be delisted on April 18, prompting users to close all open positions to avoid automatic settlements. In addition, the<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/nigeria-detains-binances-crypto-crime-investigator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> spot market</a> will be closed on April 23rd, automatically canceling all spot orders and disabling the Convert feature.</p>
<p>Finally, on May 10, 2024, the official website of CommEX will be delisted, resulting in the unavailability of any content related to the exchange.</p>
<img decoding="async" class="size-large" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NgBPFfVs/" alt="Binance" width="1815" height="858" />
<p>Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_download-7-3.jpg?fit=390%2C260" width="390" height="260" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289511</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Action: Why A 10% Drop Would Cost Traders $66 Million</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-10-drop-66-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE traders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogeusdt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin has been quite strong over the weekend despite other assets in the crypto space taking a beating. This has seen the meme coin favor long traders during this time. However, bulls are not completely out of the woods and a drop in price from here would be detrimental to the tune of tens of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="p2">Dogecoin Price Drop To $0.15 Would Wipe Out $66 Million</h2>
<p class="p2">The Dogecoin price is still holding steady above $0.17, but long traders face a threat if the price were to break down and retreat from here. According to <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/pro/futures/LiquidationMap" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> from Coinglass, there are a lot of traders who would lose money if the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-outperform-dogecoin/">DOGE price</a> were to fall 10% from its current level.</p>

<p class="p2">The liquidation heat map on the website shows that right above the $0.153 level, there is a lot of leveraged longs. A total of 2.43 million <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-outperform-dogecoin/">DOGE</a> in leveraged longs have their liquidation price at this point, and a drop below this price mark would lead to massive liquidations. In total, there are $66.89 million worth of longs at this level, and a 10% drop would trigger this liquidation trend.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-289440 aligncenter" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=640&#038;resize=640%2C264" alt="Dogecoin liquidation map" width="640" height="264" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=2756 2756w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=640&#038;resize=640%2C264 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=1536 1536w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=2048 2048w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-13.40.09.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" data-recalc-dims="1" />Source: Coinglass</p>
<p class="p2">On the other end of the spectrum, there are a large number of leveraged shorts that will be liquidated if the price were to rise another 10% from here. Coinglass data shows that the liquidation volumes, if Dogecoin moves above $0.1908, would cross more than $55 million.</p>
<p class="p2">In the shorter term, short traders stand to suffer $20 million in liquidations if the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/big-money-eyes-dogecoin-whale-activity-explodes-600/">DOGE price</a> reaches $0.18. Whole long traders risk a similar amount if the price of the meme coin breaks down below $0.17.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Can DOGE Price Reclaim $0.2?</h2>
<p class="p2">The Dogecoin price continues to get a lot of support, and one of the most recent instances of this is the price surging when the social media platform X (formerly Twitter) announced that it had gotten a number of licenses for its money transmitter business.</p>

<p class="p2">Crypto analysts have also shown bullishness toward the meme coin, expecting the Dogecoin price to continue to rise. One such case is from crypto analyst DonAlt who <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-pundit-predicts-price-surge-for-dogecoin/">believes that the DOGE price could reach a new all-time high with a target at $1</a>.</p>
<p class="p2">DonAlt explains that the meme coin has being trading quite well alongside Bitcoin, so the possibility that it rallies towards $1 is high. The crypto analyst believes that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-surges-x-payments-secures-3-new-licenses/">DOGE</a> is a great investment and it would be a great buy if it does dip to $1 again.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/yPABAshh/" alt="Dogecoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Dogecoin-price.jpeg?fit=304%2C166" width="304" height="166" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289398</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Shatters Profit-Taking Streak From 2021 Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-shatters-profit-taking-streak-2021-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin profit-taking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Profits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Record]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289443</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the recent Bitcoin consecutive profit-taking day streak has now surpassed the longest run from the 2021 bull rally. Bitcoin Has Now Seen 157 Straight Days Of Net Profit-Taking As analyst James Van Straten explained as a new post on X, BTC has already surpassed the longest profit-taking spree from the previous bull [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On-chain data shows the recent Bitcoin consecutive profit-taking day streak has now surpassed the longest run from the 2021 bull rally.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Now Seen 157 Straight Days Of Net Profit-Taking</h2>
<p>As analyst James Van Straten explained as a new <a href="https://twitter.com/jvs_btc/status/1772226408451875076" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, BTC has already surpassed the longest profit-taking spree from the previous bull run during this rally so far.</p>
<p>The relevant indicator here is the &#8220;<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-going-through-one-profit-taking-events-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Net Realized Profit/Loss</a>,&#8221; which tracks the net amount of profit or loss (in USD) that Bitcoin investors as a whole are realizing with their selling.</p>

<p>This metric works by going through the on-chain history of each sold coin to see what price it was moved at before this. Assuming that the last transaction of the coin was the last point at which it changed hands, the price at its time would have been its cost basis leading up to its latest sale.</p>
<p>The indicator then subtracts this price from the current spot price at which it&#8217;s being sold/transferred to calculate the realized profit or loss. Naturally, if this difference is positive, the coin&#8217;s sale is contributing to the profit-taking volume, while it being negative implies loss realization.</p>
<p>The Net Realized Profit/Loss sums up all these profits and losses for all the coins being sold at a given moment to output the overall situation in the market.</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the 7-day moving average (MA) of this Bitcoin indicator over the past few years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GJg1wsVWQAEEwoU?format=jpg&amp;name=large" alt="Bitcoin Net Realized Profit/Loss" width="1800" height="1013" /></p>

<p>As displayed in the above graph, the 7-day MA of the Bitcoin Net Realized Profit/Loss has been positive for the past few months. To be more particular, the indicator has held these values for 157 consecutive days now.</p>
<p>When this metric has green values, it means that the market as a whole is participating in a net amount of profit-taking. Similarly, red values imply the dominance of loss-taking.</p>
<p>It would appear that the investors have been taking net profit for 157 straight days now, which is longer than the longest profit-taking streak during the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-volume-79-lower-2021-bull-run-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">2021 bull run</a> (155 days).</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that Bitcoin Net Realized Profit/Loss shot especially high as the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price explored <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-breaks-through-69000-setting-new-record/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">new all-time highs</a> earlier. The price top so far coincided with the peak of this spike in the indicator, where its 7-day MA value hit $3.6 billion.</p>
<p>This profit-taking level was similar to the largest event observed during the last bull run. According to Straten, this is one of the reasons the asset has seen such a massive selloff.</p>

<p>Despite hitting record levels already, the profit-taking may not be ending anytime soon; however, as the analyst says, &#8220;this trend will continue as we are in a bull run and is still relatively mild compared to the 2021 bull run.&#8221;</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Bullish momentum appears to have returned for Bitcoin as the cryptocurrency has surpassed the $69,000 level after a surge of more than 5% over the past day.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/NtaxTQBf/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/shutterstock_1063376348-1.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289443</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stalls As Evening Star Forms: Can BTC Bulls Still Shine?</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-evening-star-btc-bulls-still-shine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GBTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; Severino, the Head of Research at NewsBTC and a certified CME, has identified an &#8220;Evening Star&#8221; candlestick pattern on the monthly chart of the Bitcoin CME futures. This formation, which traditionally indicates a potential trend reversal, is forming at a critical point for Bitcoin. According to Severino, there could be tell-tale signs suggesting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tony &#8220;The Bull&#8221; Severino, the Head of Research at NewsBTC and a certified CME, has <a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1772234677207625779" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">identified</a><a href="https://twitter.com/tonythebullBTC/status/1772234677207625779" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a>an &#8220;Evening Star&#8221; candlestick pattern on the monthly chart of the Bitcoin CME futures. This formation, which traditionally indicates a potential trend reversal, is forming at a critical point for Bitcoin. </p>
<p>According to Severino, there could be tell-tale signs suggesting that the Bitcoin upswing could end as the momentum fades.</p>
<h2>The Evening Star Formation: BTC Bull Run Over?</h2>
<p>Though there are concerns that the pattern is forming on the Bitcoin CME futures chart, it is absent from the spot BTCUSD chart on ordinary charts from Binance or Coinbase, for example. Accordingly, the lack of uniformity on charts has also left Severino questioning the reliability of the signal. </p>

<p>While the Evening Star pattern suggests a possible reversal, Severino cautions that Bitcoin could still reach higher highs in the coming months before peaking and reversing. However, the analyst stresses that predicting the exact timing of these events is a challenge. </p>
<p>Based on candlestick analysis, Severino predicts that Bitcoin could peak within the next two quarters, possibly in mid- or late Q3 2024. </p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EU4owKnQ/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/EU4owKnQ/" alt="Bitcoin price trending upward on the daily chart | Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1787" height="904" /></a>
<p>When writing, Bitcoin is trading at around all-time highs. Following the cool-off of last week, the coin bounced back strongly over the weekend, wiping out some losses. The coin is technically within a bearish breakout formation, trading below the 20-day moving average, clear in the daily chart.</p>
<p>For the uptrend to continue and extend from the formation in the daily chart, BTC must push above $70,000. The validity of this uptrend will be solid if the leg up is with expanding trading volume. </p>

<p>Severino also notes that the leg up will be valid and the Evening Star formation invalid if there is a strong close above $74,000 by the end of the month. Bitcoin prices peaked at around $73,800 in early March, buoyed by expanding demand, especially from spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<h2>Spot Bitcoin ETFs Post More Outflows</h2>
<p>Despite the potential for a continued rally, some fundamental factors pose challenges. Notably, outflows from spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), particularly from the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), are rising. Rumors suggest that bankrupt crypto lender <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/genesis-face-21-million-penalty-sec-charges-settled/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Genesis</a> could be liquidating its GBTC holdings, adding further selling pressure to the market.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-289501" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768" alt="Outflows from spot BTC ETF issuers | Source: Lookonchain data" width="1024" height="768" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=2645 2645w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=560 560w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=879 879w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=1536 1536w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=2048 2048w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJSkwmTacAAmJM3.png?resize=1024%2C768?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1" />
<p> By March 22, spot Bitcoin ETF issuers had experienced <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1771221747318075748" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">outflows</a> for five straight days, according to Lookonchain data. Nonetheless, as GBTC posts outflows, BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT continues attracting more clients seeking BTC exposure.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Crypto-news-Template176.jpg?fit=640%2C362" width="640" height="362" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289500</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Large Shiba Inu Transactions Spark Fears Of A Massive Dumping Spree</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-transactions-spree/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) whales look to be at it again following large transactions involving the meme token in the last 24 hours. As expected, these transactions have raised concerns that crypto investors might be looking to offload their tokens on the market.  Shiba Inu Whales Move Billions Of SHIB On-chain data shows that Shiba Inu [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-pepe-whales-sold/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) whales</a> look to be at it again following large transactions involving the meme token in the last 24 hours. As expected, these transactions have raised concerns that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-23-5-million-shiba-inu/">crypto investors</a> might be looking to offload their tokens on the market. </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Whales Move Billions Of SHIB</h2>
<p><a href="https://etherscan.io/advanced-filter?tkn=0x95aD61b0a150d79219dCF64E1E6Cc01f0B64C4cE&amp;txntype=2&amp;__cf_chl_rt_tk=.f2yRaOf1TUS7udrjffik62iaeQ_18gwUWkSmNcTtu4-1711353862-0.0.1.1-1471" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">On-chain data</a> shows that Shiba Inu whales moved billions of SHIB in different transactions. In one transaction, 77.2 billion SHIB tokens were moved to a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-support-bitcoin-developer-with-3-6-million/">Coinbase wallet</a>. Meanwhile, over 205 billion SHIB tokens were moved across different wallets, some of which were transferred to a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-gets-boost-robinhood-wallet/">Robinhood wallet</a>. </p>

<p>The transfer of some of these tokens to crypto trading platforms, Coinbase and Robinhood, has raised suspicions that these Shiba Inu whales might be planning to sell off their holdings to make some profits. If so, it could massively impact the meme coin’s price due to the magnitude of such transactions. </p>
<p>The SHIB community has seen several smart traders, including MakerDAO founder Rune Christensen, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/">take profits</a> over the past few weeks. This also contributed to the concern that these recent transactions might involve more whales who want to secure their profits. </p>
<p>However, while the possibility of a sell-off exists, this could be just investors using the recent price dip as an opportunity to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/shiba-inu-whales-shib/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">accumulate more</a> of the meme coin. SHIB experienced a significant price surge, which saw it climb to become the tenth-largest crypto token by market cap. However, it has dropped out of the top 10 after its recent price decline.</p>
<p>The theory of SHIB accumulation looks plausible considering that more upward trend is expected for the crypto token. Therefore, investors will still be looking to position themselves ahead of this bull run, which could see the meme coin <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-dogecoin-shib-excitement/">break its all-time high (ATH)</a>. </p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Still Has Bullish Momentum</h2>
<p>SHIB may be ready for another upward movement if the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/">wave of profit-taking</a> by investors is now over. Crypto analyst Xanrox <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whale-dumps-substantial-holdings-on-the-market-heres-how-much/">suggested</a> that the meme coin could hit a new ATH by July, which means more parabolic price moves are to be expected if this price prediction is to be realized by then. </p>

<p>SHIB’s fundamentals also suggest that it is only a matter of time before the upward trend continues. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-latest-shib-magazine/">Shiba Inu team</a> continues to develop innovations that can help propel SHIB’s price. Meanwhile, although Shibarium’s daily transactions continue to decline, they are likely to pick up at some point, with a massive increase in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burns-bright-shib/">SHIB burns</a> expected once that happens. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, SHIB is trading at $0.00002771, down almost 1% in the last 24 hours, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/KS4stUfp/" alt="Shiba Inu price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Shiba-Inu-22.jpeg?fit=640%2C366" width="640" height="366" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289397</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Shockwave: Nearly $1 Billion Vanishes From Global Funds In Historic Outflow</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-shock-nearly-billion-vanishes-global-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samuel Edyme]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CoinShares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Funds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outflow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Last week, the crypto investment landscape witnessed a significant exodus of capital from global crypto funds. A recent report from CoinShares highlighted nearly $1 billion net outflow from these funds, marking a historic departure from a 7-week inflow streak that had cumulatively amassed $12.3 billion. A Closer Look At The Outflows The magnitude of these [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last week, the crypto investment landscape <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-175-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6af2a10c0b30" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">witnessed</a> a significant exodus of capital from global crypto funds. A recent report from CoinShares highlighted nearly $1 billion net outflow from these funds, marking a historic departure from a 7-week inflow streak that had cumulatively amassed $12.3 billion.</p>
<h2>A Closer Look At The Outflows</h2>
<p>The magnitude of these outflows at roughly $942 million is particularly notable, almost doubling the previous record of $500 million witnessed towards the end of January.</p>

<p>Major players in the asset management space, including BlackRock, Bitwise, Fidelity, Grayscale, ProShares, and 21Shares, felt the brunt of this wave of withdrawals, according to CoinShares.</p>
<p>The timing of these outflows coincided with a notable correction in the prices of underlying <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/iceland-prioritizes-food-over-crypto-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">cryptocurrencies</a>, which erased $10 billion from the fund&#8217;s assets under management (AUM). However, the combined AUM of $88 billion still hovers above prior cycle highs.</p>
<p>Notably, these outflows have pronounced impacted trading volumes and asset valuations within the crypto investment product sector. Last week&#8217;s trading volume plummeted by a third to $28 billion amidst a price correction that significantly diminished the AUM of these funds.</p>
<p>The US market, particularly new <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-noobs-panic-selling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">spot Bitcoin ETFs</a>, witnessed over $1 billion in inflows, which were insufficient to offset the nearly $2 billion <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/back-to-back-negative-bitcoin-etf-flows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">outflows from Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC fund</a> conversion.</p>
<p>According to CoinShares Head of Research James Butterfill, the &#8220;recent price correction&#8221; resulted in &#8220;hesitancy from investors, leading to much lower inflows into new ETF issuers in the US, which saw US$1.1bn inflows, partially offsetting incumbent Grayscale’s significant US$2bn outflows last week.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Global Crypto Sentiment And Market Responses</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, last week&#8217;s sentiment was not solely concentrated on US-based funds or Bitcoin. Investment products in Sweden, Hong Kong, Switzerland, and Germany also experienced outflows, though Brazil and Canada-based funds recorded inflows, showcasing a mixed global investor sentiment.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-289492 size-large" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?resize=980%2C582" alt="Crypto asset flows by country." width="980" height="582" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=1388 1388w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-14.57.15.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1" />
<p>Additionally, Ethereum, Solana, and Cardano-based products faced outflows, underscoring the broad impact of the market&#8217;s downturn. In contrast, other altcoin funds like Polkadot, Avalanche, and Litecoin saw net inflows, indicating selective investor interest in the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/doge-ada-cardano-altcoin-season/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">altcoin sector</a>.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-289495 size-large" src="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?resize=980%2C644" alt="Crypto asset flows." width="980" height="644" srcset="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=1396 1396w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=640 640w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=768 768w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=980 980w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=750 750w, https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-25-at-15.02.47.png?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" data-recalc-dims="1" />
<p>This period of market recalibration has also sparked a dialogue among industry leaders about the role and accessibility of Bitcoin ETFs in fostering broader market integration.</p>
<p>Bivu Das of Kraken UK and Daniel Seifert of Coinbase UK have both <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-buzz-in-uk-kraken-executive-pushes-for-market-access/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">advocated for the UK market&#8217;s access to Bitcoin ETFs</a>, citing the importance of such investment products in establishing a comprehensive crypto ecosystem.</p>

<p>As reported, by offering indirect exposure to Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements, these instruments propose a regulated and possibly more accessible avenue for investors, contributing to the diversification and maturity of the investment landscape in the digital currency market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ICYMI: Kraken UK Managing Director Bivu Das says he&#8217;d &#8220;absolutely&#8221; like to see a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">#Bitcoin</a> ETF in the UK, providing regulated access to crypto exposure currently lacking and boost UK&#8217;s crypto hub ambitions, and legitimize bitcoin for institutions.</p>
<p>— AP Crypto (@AP_Crypto_) <a href="https://twitter.com/AP_Crypto_/status/1771514821940547931?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Featured image from Unsplash, Chart from TradingView</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Singapores-Top-Banker-Predicts-Endgame-For-Private-Cryptos.webp?fit=631%2C420" width="631" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289462</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
