<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://bitcoinist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 07:09:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/cropped-cropped-cropped-Icon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Bitcoinist.com</title>
	<link>https://bitcoinist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">225283986</site>	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin ETF Buzz In UK: Kraken Executive Pushes For Market Access</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-buzz-in-uk-kraken-executive-pushes-for-market-access/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The simmering debate over Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the UK has reignited, with industry leaders calling for wider access for investors. This comes on the heels of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving Bitcoin ETFs in January, sparking a surge in investment and renewed calls for a similar move by the UK&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:374">The simmering debate over Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the UK has reignited, with industry leaders calling for wider access for investors. This comes on the heels of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving Bitcoin ETFs in January, sparking a surge in investment and renewed calls for a similar move by the UK&#8217;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:335"><strong>UK&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF Advocacy</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:335">Bivu Das, Managing Director of Kraken UK, believes Bitcoin ETFs offer a &#8220;basic fundamental&#8221; for establishing the UK as a true crypto hub. These instruments allow investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements without directly owning the cryptocurrency itself, potentially offering a more regulated and accessible entry point.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ICYMI: Kraken UK Managing Director Bivu Das says he&#8217;d &#8220;absolutely&#8221; like to see a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> ETF in the UK, providing regulated access to crypto exposure currently lacking and boost UK&#8217;s crypto hub ambitions, and legitimize bitcoin for institutions.</p>
<p>— AP Crypto (@AP_Crypto_) <a href="https://twitter.com/AP_Crypto_/status/1771514821940547931?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:306">However, the FCA remains cautious. In 2021, they banned the retail sale of crypto-derivative products, including exchange-traded products (ETPs) backed by cryptocurrencies. This stance, some argue, puts the UK at a disadvantage compared to the US, where retail investors can readily invest in <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-alert-analyst-issues-major-warning/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin ETFs.</a></p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:271">Das contends that the regulatory landscape has evolved since the 2021 ban. He believes ETFs could even alleviate some regulatory concerns, as investors wouldn&#8217;t directly hold the underlying Bitcoin. This could potentially pave the way for a more open approach from the FCA.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:271"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/WjE9FkAe/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:271">There are signs the FCA might be inching towards a more accommodating stance. They recently approved the launch of crypto ETNs, but only for institutional investors. This move, while limited, could be seen as a cautious step towards wider crypto investment opportunities.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:288">While the regulatory body remains cautious, warning of potential risks for retail investors in the volatile crypto market, the FCA&#8217;s recent actions suggest a willingness to explore the space further.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="15:1-15:269"><strong>Expanding UK&#8217;s Investment Options</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:269">Coinbase UK CEO, Daniel Seifert, echoes Das&#8217; sentiment. He believes &#8220;consumers have more options&#8221; with a wider range of investment products like ETFs. This push for increased investor choice aligns with a broader trend towards democratizing access to financial markets.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:367">However, the FCA faces a delicate balancing act. While fostering innovation in the crypto sector is crucial for maintaining the UK&#8217;s financial competitiveness, protecting retail investors from potential harm remains a top priority. The high volatility of the crypto market raises concerns about the suitability of such complex instruments for inexperienced investors.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:369">The recent influx of billions into US<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Bitcoin</a> ETFs highlights the growing investor appetite for these products. This surge in demand could put further pressure on the FCA to revisit its stance. The potential benefits of increased investment and a more robust crypto ecosystem could outweigh the perceived risks, eventually leading to a more open regulatory environment.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:527">The future of Bitcoin ETFs in the UK remains uncertain. The FCA is likely to take a measured approach, carefully evaluating the potential benefits and risks before making any significant changes. However, the growing global acceptance of Bitcoin ETFs, coupled with increasing investor demand, suggests that a more open approach from the FCA might be inevitable.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:527"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_a28a48.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289193</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Bitcoin Miners Move Old Equipment Overseas &#8211; Here’s Why</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/us-bitcoin-miners-move-old-equipment-overseas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bloomberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethiopia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin halving, one of the most anticipated crypto events in 2024, is less than a month away, and miners seem to be in full preparation for its aftermath. The April event is expected to slash mining rewards on the Bitcoin network in half, making the validation of transactions less lucrative. As of now, miners [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin halving, one of the most anticipated crypto events in 2024, is less than a month away, and miners seem to be in full preparation for its aftermath. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-halving-could-bring-uncertainty-to-mining-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">April event is expected to slash mining rewards on the Bitcoin network in half</a>, making the validation of transactions less lucrative.</p>
<p>As of now, miners receive 6.25 BTC for each validated block added to the network. However, the halving will split their revenue to 3.125 BTC for each block. Interestingly, many miners in the United States seem to be making adjustments, including upgrading to more efficient mining computers, to ensure they remain profitable.</p>
<h2>Why Bitcoin Mining Machines Are Being Moved Out Of The US</h2>
<p>According to crypto-mining services and logistics provider Luxor Technology, about 600,000 S19 series mining rigs, which account for a large proportion of machines currently in use in the United States, are being moved out of the country. The mining computers are being transferred (or sold) primarily to countries in Africa and South America, a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-23/bitcoin-halving-spurs-exodus-of-old-us-mining-computers-abroad" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bloomberg report</a> revealed.</p>

<p>The S19 series are older models of Bitcoin mining machines, and they might not be cost-efficient to run in countries like the US, where energy costs are relatively high. <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-halving-havoc-only-a-few-miners-may-survive/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">This explains why the miners in the country</a> are ditching the older computers for more efficient ones.</p>
<p>The report quoted another major player in the Bitcoin mining industry, saying that while the S19 series and similar models might not be cost-effective to operate in the United States, they “can still generate decent profits and get an extended life if hosted” in certain regions in Africa.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, some miners opt to sell their hardware, with buyers of the old machines operating in parts of the world with cheap power. Many of these buyers are from Paraguay, Uruguay, Tanzania, and, most notably, Ethiopia.</p>
<p>According to Luxor, the upcoming halving event has been influencing the behavior of buyers towards the purchase of old mining machines. “Some buyers are waiting until after the event to purchase older computers, assuming their prices will drop even more,” the company revealed.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">With the Bitcoin halving approaching, Luxor estimates that around 600,000 S19 bitcoin rigs, the majority of machines currently in use, are moving primarily out of the U.S. to places like Africa and South America, where energy is cheaper. The S19 can cost up to $11,500 per unit to…</p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1771719313260712434?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2>Ethiopia: The Next Crypto Mining Hub?</h2>
<p>Ethiopia, a country located in the Horn of Africa, is forging a strong reputation for itself in the crypto and Bitcoin mining niche. As inferred earlier, a significant proportion of the old US machines are being transferred to the East African nation.</p>

<p>Ethiopia’s cheap electricity has been pinpointed as the major factor driving this development. The Bloomberg report revealed that electricity is about 3 cents per kWh in Ethiopia, while it ranges between <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ex-white-house-official-says-bitcoin-could-reach-170000-post-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">3 to 6 cents in the US</a>.</p>
<p>Earlier in February, Bloomberg disclosed that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-migration-chinese-miners-flock-to-ethiopia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Chinese crypto mining companies are increasing their investment in Ethiopia</a>. While China’s strict stance against cryptocurrency is believed to have played a role, Ethiopia’s cheap power seems to have played a bigger part in the firms’ move.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/rBHhUwUm/" alt="Bitcoin" width="2174" height="1434" /></p>



]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Mining.jpg?fit=640%2C420" width="640" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289178</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Co-founder Emin Gün Sirer Warns Of Risky L2 Projects &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/avalanche-emin-gun-sirer-warns-of-risky-l2-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Semilore Faleti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche Co-founder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Emin Gün Sirer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[L2 projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[L2 solutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289183</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Co-founder of Avalanche blockchain, Emin Gün Sirer, has raised an alert on the infiltration of certain layer-2 solutions, which poses risks to investors. In an X post on March 23, the Ava Labs boss expressed concerns over these “trash” projects while educating users on several of their common characteristics. Related Reading: Blasted By Deception: Layer [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Co-founder of <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/citibank-trials-tokenization-equity-funds-avalanche/">Avalanche blockchain</a>, Emin Gün Sirer, has raised an alert on the infiltration of certain layer-2 solutions, which poses risks to investors. In an <a href="https://twitter.com/el33th4xor/status/1771658050228617428" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">X post on March 23</a>, the Ava Labs boss expressed concerns over these “trash” projects while educating users on several of their common characteristics.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Hey y&#39;all,</p>
<p>We all ignored the huge red flags associated with SBF because &quot;he looked smart&quot; and &quot;he made a lot of money.&quot; Then it turned out that he was dumb as rocks, was a sociopath, and was just stealing our money.</p>
<p>The next cycle is going to be even more noisy, with even…</p>
<p>&mdash; Emin Gün Sirer<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f53a.png" alt="🔺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@el33th4xor) <a href="https://twitter.com/el33th4xor/status/1771658050228617428?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
Related Reading: <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/rug-pull-layer-2-project-suffers-500-eth-exploit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Blasted By Deception: Layer 2 Project Suffers 500 ETH Rug Pull Onslaught</a>
<h2>Red Flags To Watch For In L2 Projects &#8211; Avalanche Co-founder </h2>
<p>According to Gün Sirer, the rise in substandard L2 projects represents the next big hazard in the crypto ecosystem following the crypto exchange heist pulled off by former<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-50-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> FTX founder and CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)</a>. The prominent crypto figure argued the procedures involved in launching an L2 solution were rather loose, allowing the influx of bad actors who created projects with no actual value. </p>
<p>In the interest of promoting investor security, Emin Gün Sirer then proceeded to list several red flags that accompany these risky L2 solutions. Firstly, he stated that there is usually a discrepancy between the project’s narrative and technology, i.e., its marketing pitch does not align with its technical implementation. </p>
<p>Examples of such projects are those with centralized sequencers without fraud-proof, which is against the cryptocurrency principles of decentralization and security. Emin Gün Sirer also highlighted L2 solutions that conduct token sales to raise funds rather than for a specific, practical purpose on the network, indicating it was likely to be a dubious investment. </p>
<p>Furthermore, the Avalanche co-founder also spoke about L2 projects in which founders sold their personal native tokens before the launch. Regardless of the motive, Gün Sirer characterized a large volume of native token sales pre-launch as a massive red flag. </p>
<p>Another point the crypto figure highlighted was projects with low-float tokens which allow for artificial inflation of the token’s value through manipulation tactics as commonly done by SBF. Finally, Gün Sirer advised investors to pay attention to project founders&#8217; morals and habits and screening for any form of personal misconduct.
</p>
<p>Related Reading: <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-scams-persist-exit-scams-hacks-cost-crypto-sector-160-million-in-february/">Crypto Scams Persist: Exit Scams, Hacks Cost Crypto Sector $160 Million In February</a></p>
<h2>The Simple Authenticity Test By Emin Gün Sirer</h2>
<p>In addition to the red flags mentioned above, Emin Gün Sirer also proposed a simple test that could help investors in screening through the masses of L2 projects being launched daily for authentic, profitable ventures. </p>
<p>Firstly, the Ava Labs founder suggested identifying the main issues &#8211; known as “blockers” &#8211; in the crypto space at any time. He stated that, for example, issues such as scalability and performance were quite significant until blockchains such as Avalanche and<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coin-mania-breaks-records/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> Solana</a> emerged with solutions. </p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Emin Gün Sirer believes that supporting multiple use cases on the same platform as well as integration with traditional finance (TradFi) are currently critical issues facing the crypto ecosystem. Before investing in an L2 solution, the Avalanche co-founder advises users to assess where the project offers a genuine solution to these challenges. </p>

<img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/XzGc4o9M/" alt="Emin Gün Sirer" width="1480" height="893" />Total crypto market valued at $2.368 trillion on the daily chart | Source:<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/xg17RJqK/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> TOTAL chart on Tradingview.com</a>





]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Emin-Gun-Sirer.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289183</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Delays Decision On Grayscale’s Ethereum ETF &#8211; Here’s The New Deadline</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/sec-delays-decision-on-grayscales-ethereum-etf-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Opeyemi Sule]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Futures ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[James Seyffart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot Ethereum ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has announced an extension &#8211; yet again &#8211; of the deadline for asset management firm Grayscale’s Ethereum Futures Trust exchange-traded fund (ETF). Initially published for comment in the Federal Register on October 3, 2023, the SEC claims to be extending the deadline to have “sufficient time to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-ceo-predicts-sec-setback-in-ethereum-case/">United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> has announced an extension &#8211; yet again &#8211; of the deadline for asset management firm Grayscale’s Ethereum Futures Trust exchange-traded fund (ETF). Initially published for comment in the Federal Register on October 3, 2023, the SEC claims to be extending the deadline to have “sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change.”</p>
<h2>Final Deadline For Grayscale’s Futures Ethereum ETF</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/rules/sro/nysearca/2024/34-99842.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">March 22 filing</a>, the SEC disclosed that it will prolong the decision-making process for Grayscale’s Ethereum Futures ETF. The commission has now moved the deadline from March 31 to May 30 to decide whether or not to approve the investment product.</p>
<p>A part of the SEC’s filing read: </p>
<blockquote><p>The Commission finds that it is appropriate to designate a longer period within which to issue an order approving or disapproving the proposed rule change so that it has sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised therein. Accordingly, the Commission, pursuant to Section 19(b)(2) of the Act,10 designates May 30, 2024, as the date by which the Commission shall either approve or disapprove the proposed rule change.</p></blockquote>

<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-delays-fidelity-spot-ethereum-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">James Seyffart</a>, a Bloomberg ETF analyst, did not express surprise at this deadline extension. “There&#8217;s the delay order for Grayscale&#8217;s Ethereum Futures ETF Filing &#8212; as expected,” the analyst said in his <a href="https://x.com/JSeyff/status/1771296290149683490?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post on the X</a> platform.</p>
<p>In November, Seyffart said he believes that Grayscale’s application for an Ether Futures ETF is “nothing but a trojan horse” to get approval for its spot ETH exchange-traded product. Hence, it would be interesting to see how this latest delay influences the clearance of the spot ETH ETF, especially considering the slim odds of approval.</p>
<p>The<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-initiates-grayscales-spot-ethereum-etf-decision/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> SEC delayed its decision on whether to approve Grayscale’s spot Ethereum ETF</a> earlier in January while also opening the application to public comments. In the most recent development, the asset management revised its 19b-4 form in a bid to force the regulator’s hand.</p>
<h2>Approval Of ETH Spot ETF Seems Very Unlikely: Alex Thorn</h2>
<p>Alex Thorn, Galaxy Digital’s head of research, has <a href="https://www.galaxy.com/insights/research/top-stories-of-the-week-3-22-24/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">said</a> the approval of the Ethereum spot ETFs is looking very unlikely at the moment. This reasoning is based on the SEC’s subpoena of crypto firms and lack of engagement with potential ETF issuers.</p>
<p>According to a recent report, the SEC sent subpoenas to various crypto companies regarding their relationships with the Ethereum Foundation. </p>

<p>Thorn posits that the SEC could be investigating whether the original Ethereum ICO (Initial Coin Offering) was an unregistered securities offering rather than <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-in-the-hot-seat-sec-security-label-looms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">classifying the secondary trading of Ether today as securities trading</a>.</p>
<p>The analyst mentioned that it is unclear how this probe alone hurts the chance of ETH ETF approval. However, he believes that when this is combined with the fact that the SEC is not actively communicating with applicants, the authorization of the ETFs in May seems very unlikely.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/r6RYoWoK/" alt="Grayscale" width="2174" height="1434" /></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/iStock-904735154.webp?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289000</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Getting Ready For Prison Sentence? US Gov&#8217;t Gets Greenlight To Sell Assets</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-getting-ready-for-prison-sentence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289085</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder and former chief executive officer (CEO) of defunct crypto exchange FTX readies for his prison sentence, prosecutors have formally requested the court to authorize the sale of two jets linked to the former crypto billionaire. With the defendant and his legal team already in agreement, the final step hinges on  [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/ftx-scam-crypto-sam-bankman-fried-story/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, the founder and former chief executive officer (CEO) of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/major-reveals-from-the-ftx-bankruptcy-filing-whats-the-takeaway/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">defunct crypto exchange FTX</a> readies for his prison sentence, prosecutors have formally requested the court to authorize the sale of two jets linked to the former crypto billionaire. With the defendant and his legal team already in agreement, the final step hinges on  the court’s approval. </p>

<h2><b>Prosecutors Push For Sale Of Luxury Jets</b></h2>
<p>In a March 22 <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.416.1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">filing</a> with the United States District Court for the Southern District, US, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-10-billion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">prosecutors in the government’s case against Bankman-Fried</a> have proposed a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/sam-bankman-fried-jail/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">court order</a> to sell two multi-million dollar jets connected to FTX and its founder. </p>
<p>As <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590939/gov.uscourts.nysd.590939.416.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">stated</a> by Atty. Damian Williams in a letter to Judge Lewis Kaplan, the government is seeking to conduct an interlocutory sale of two luxury jets, a Bombardier Global 5000 BD-700-1A11 and an Embraer Legacy EMB-135BJ.</p>
<p>According to the filing, the sale of the two private aircraft has been sought to prevent their devaluation, as these <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/ftx-ceos-asset-recovery-escalates-as-sam-bankman-fried-trial-looms/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">assets</a> were previously slated for forfeiture in October 2023 due to their connection to <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/ftx/sam-bankman-fried-allegedly-used-customer-funds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Bankman-Fried’s criminal case</a>.  </p>
<p>Currently, the government has not disclosed the precise selling price for the private aircrafts. However, they have appraised the jets at $15.9 million and $12.5 million, respectively. </p>
<p>Furthermore, Williams has revealed that the court order was made in agreement with multiple parties including FTX’s former executive, Ryan Salame, the defendant, the founder of Trans-Island Airways, Paul Aranha, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-revised-settlement-proposal-amid-objection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">FTX debtors</a>, the government, Capital Peak Aviation and Island Air Capital (IAC). </p>
<p>The attorney disclosed that the Embraer Legacy aircraft will be transported to a Florida airport by the IAC, with the delivery expected within 30 days of the court order. </p>
<p>As for the Global 5000 aircraft, the filing has revealed that it remains under secure custody, controlled by the United States Marshals Service (USMS). The USMS will manage the jet’s sale proceedings, which will be held in escrow within the enforcement agency’s Seized Asset Deposit Fund (SADF) until further order of the court. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/lW6sL8Hs/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><b>Sam Bankman-Fried Sentence Date Fast Approaching</b></h2>
<p><a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftxs-sam-bankman-fried-should-receive-50-year-jail/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, who was <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-convicted/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">found guilty</a> in November 2023 on all seven counts of <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-fraud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">fraud</a> by a jury in New York, will potentially face a staggering amount of years in prison for his alleged crimes. The <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-prison-2/#:~:text=A%20recent%20court%20filing%20revealed,100%20years%20locked%20behind%20bars." target="_blank" rel="noopener ">former FTX CEO’s sentence date</a> is fast approaching, scheduled for Thursday, March 28.</p>

<p>Prosecutors in the case are <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-50-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">seeking a prison sentence of 40 to 50 years</a>, potentially leading the 32-year-old former crypto billionaire to be incarcerated until the age of 70 to 80 years. Conversely, attorneys representing the FTX founder propose a sentence of approximately five to six years. </p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_923af4.jpg?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289085</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler Says Crypto Industry Needs ‘Disinfectant’ &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/gary-gensler-says-crypto-needs-disinfectant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289041</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a passionate address to Columbia Law School, Gary Gensler, the Chair of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), delivered a scathing critique of crypto industry participants who evade registration requirements. Promoting Transparency in Cryptocurrency Gensler&#8217;s speech focused on the need for transparency and mandatory disclosure in the cryptocurrency markets, drawing on the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a passionate address to Columbia Law School, Gary Gensler, the Chair of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), delivered <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/speech/gensler-remarks-columbia-law-school-032224" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">a scathing critique of crypto industry participants</a> who evade registration requirements.</p>
<h2><strong>Promoting Transparency in Cryptocurrency</strong></h2>
<p>Gensler&#8217;s speech focused on the need for transparency and mandatory disclosure in the cryptocurrency markets, drawing on the famous quote by Supreme Court Justice Louis Brandeis that &#8220;Sunlight is said to be the best of disinfectants.&#8221;</p>

<p>Gensler expressed his concern about certain participants in the crypto securities markets who seek to avoid registration requirements, thereby evading mandatory disclosure. He stressed the importance of transparency in the industry and highlighted the potential benefits of applying stricter regulatory oversight.</p>
<p>By shining a light on the practices and operations of market participants, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/trader-warns-sec-chair-gensler-shouldnt-be-trusted/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Gensler</a> aimed to promote a more accountable and trustworthy crypto ecosystem.</p>
<blockquote>
&#8220;There are participants in crypto securities markets that seek to avoid these registration requirements. No registration means no mandatory disclosure. Many would agree that the crypto markets could use a little disinfectant,&#8221; he said.
</blockquote>
<p>The SEC Chair&#8217;s remarks come at a time when the commission is actively pursuing<a href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-crypto-lawyers-leave-as-genslers-grip-tightens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener "> enforcement actions against major crypto firms,</a> including Kraken, Binance, Ripple, and Coinbase. These actions underscore the SEC&#8217;s commitment to ensuring compliance within the industry.</p>
<p>However, Gensler&#8217;s focus on transparency goes beyond enforcement, as he believes that the entire crypto market can benefit from increased disclosure and regulatory compliance.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/alD4Mo1l/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><strong>Gensler&#8217;s Regulatory Vision</strong></h2>
<p>Advocacy groups and crypto companies have long called for clear regulatory guidelines to foster innovation within the United States. While Gensler acknowledged the importance of innovation, he emphasized that it should not come at the expense of transparency and investor protection.</p>
<p>By advocating for mandatory disclosure and registration requirements, Gensler seeks to strike a balance between fostering innovation and maintaining market integrity.</p>
<p>Gensler&#8217;s call for transparency aligns with his previous warnings that cryptocurrency exchanges must register with the SEC and adhere to the same rules as traditional financial companies. He has consistently emphasized the need for accountability and regulation in the crypto space, aiming to ensure that investors are adequately informed and protected.</p>

<p>In addition to his focus on transparency, Gensler also addressed the risks associated with investing in cryptocurrencies. He likened Bitcoin to a roller coaster ride, cautioning investors about the volatility of the asset. While acknowledging the market&#8217;s enthusiasm, he stressed the importance of evaluating the fundamentals of cryptocurrencies to make informed investment decisions.</p>
<p>As Gensler&#8217;s &#8220;disinfectant&#8221; tirade reverberates throughout the cryptocurrency industry, stakeholders are left contemplating the future of regulation and transparency.</p>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s ongoing enforcement actions and his steadfast commitment to mandatory disclosure signal a shift toward greater scrutiny and accountability in the market.</p>
<p>The impact of Gensler&#8217;s speech and the SEC&#8217;s actions will likely be felt across the industry. Market participants may face increased pressure to comply with registration requirements and provide transparent disclosures. This could potentially lead to a more robust and trustworthy crypto ecosystem, attracting both institutional and retail investors.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_ca527b.webp?fit=629%2C420" width="629" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289041</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Pundit Predicts Massive Price Surge For Dogecoin &#8211; Here’s The Target</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-pundit-predicts-price-surge-for-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto analyst DonAlt has provided a bullish narrative for the foremost meme coin, Dogecoin (DOGE). This follows his recent statement suggesting that DOGE could still move over 500% from its current price levels.  Dogecoin Could Rise To $1 DonAlt mentioned in a video on his YouTube channel that DOGE “it isn’t too unlikely for Dogecoin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto analyst DonAlt has provided a bullish narrative for the foremost meme coin, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/big-money-eyes-dogecoin-whale-activity-explodes-600/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a>. This follows his recent statement suggesting that DOGE could still <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-too-much-firepower/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">move over 500%</a> from its current price levels. </p>
<h2><b>Dogecoin Could Rise To $1</b></h2>
<p>DonAlt mentioned in a video on his YouTube channel that DOGE “it isn’t too unlikely for Dogecoin to go to $1.” This raises the possibility of the meme coin breaking its all-time high (ATH) of $0.7376 on its road to $1, which no doubt presents <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-10-largest-meme-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">mouth-watering gains for investors</a>. </p>

<p>The crypto analyst made this statement while revealing that Dogecoin was <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/altcoin/dogecoin-shiba-inu-pepe-explode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">one of the altcoins</a> he had his eyes on. He added that he found the meme coin “interesting” because it dipped back into support on the PTC chart. Meanwhile, DonAlt suggested that $0.1 is a good entry point for those looking to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-when-dogecoin-does-this/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">invest in DOGE</a> and stated that he will probably buy if it drops to that level. </p>
<p>The crypto analyst remarked that he would also look to Bitcoin’s price movement to determine whether or not to buy Dogecoin now. If Bitcoin confirms a bullish sentiment, he will buy the meme coin at whatever price level he finds it at since it is still a long way from hitting $1. </p>
<p>Interestingly, the crypto analyst suggested that <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-coinbase-futures-listing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">DOGE</a> was a better investment than Bitcoin. He stated that DOGE could trade as high as $2 if Bitcoin never drops back to the $60,000 range. That is why he finds investing in the meme coin more attractive than buying the flagship crypto at $60,000 and seeing it <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-new-ath-by-year-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">rise to $90,000</a>. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/pMXavQzo/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><b>Shiba Inu Could Also See Significant Gains</b></h2>
<p>Crypto analyst and trader Xanrox also <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-surge-crypto-shib/#:~:text=In%20a%20recent%20analysis%2C%20Xanrox,next%20wave%20to%20the%20upside.%E2%80%9D" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">recently predicted</a> that DOGE’s top contender, <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-23-5-million-shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a>, could witness a price surge of over 300%. This also means that SHIB, like DOGE, could hit a new ATH in this <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-shiba-inu-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">market cycle</a>. Meanwhile, analysts like Javon Marks have also <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-shiba-inu-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">raised</a> the possibility of SHIB deleting another zero and rising to as high as $0.0001553. </p>
<p>These massive price predictions for DOGE and SHIB again underscore the battle between these crypto tokens to assert themselves as the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-shiba-inu-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">most valuable meme coin</a>. So far, they have made significant moves in the market since the beginning of the year. However, there is a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/shiba-inu/crypto-analyst-shiba-inu-target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">growing feeling</a> that SHIB could overtake DOGE at some point. </p>

<p>SHIB has already seen more gains since the beginning of the year, boasting a year-to-date (YTD) gain of over 160% compared to DOGE’s 80%.</p>
<p><em>Featured image from Mary Taylor/Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_971d4f.png?fit=633%2C420" width="633" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289072</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Metaverse Guru Clears The Air Amid Scam Speculations</title>
		<link>https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-metaverse-guru-denies-scam-claims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://bitcoinist.com/?p=289034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent turn of events, Marcie Jastrow, the advisor for the Shiba Inu Metaverse project, has found herself at the center of controversy surrounding allegations of scam affiliation. The accusations surfaced after Jastrow dissociated herself from a company and removed any trace of her association with it on her LinkedIn account. Trophias, a former [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent turn of events, Marcie Jastrow, the advisor for the Shiba Inu Metaverse project, has found herself at the center of controversy surrounding allegations of scam affiliation.</p>
<p>The accusations surfaced after Jastrow dissociated herself from a company and removed any trace of her association with it on her LinkedIn account. Trophias, a former member of the SHIB Defense Breed, went as far as labeling Jastrow a &#8220;professional scammer.&#8221;</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">And yet I’m the crazy one….</p>
<p>Marcie Jastrow is a professional scammer. She got rid of her “new” company from LinkedIn.</p>
<p>Marcie is in way over her head.</p>
<p>— Crypto Fox (@ShibaTrophias) <a href="https://twitter.com/ShibaTrophias/status/1770932939670610301?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2><strong>Jastrow&#8217;s Response</strong></h2>
<p>Jastrow swiftly responded to these allegations, vehemently denying any involvement in scams. She clarified that her decision to dissociate from the company was driven by disputes over intellectual property rights, rather than any fraudulent activities.</p>
<p>Jastrow emphasized that the situation had become a distraction, leading her to sever all ties with the company. While she did not address Trophias directly, her statement aimed to set the record straight.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">This &#8211; let&#8217;s help our Welly Frens. How many projects are actually showing real world use cases on Farm to table. In addition, buying a franchise and owning your destiny isn&#8217;t a bad idea either &#8211; no pun intented <a href="https://t.co/OpLksyznYD" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/OpLksyznYD</a></p>
<p>— Marcie Jastrow (@marciejastrow) <a href="https://twitter.com/marciejastrow/status/1770870080131485916?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p>However, Jastrow&#8217;s call for assistance for the Welly Friends project, which focuses on blockchain adoption in the agricultural scene, drew criticism from some quarters.</p>
<p>Detractors argued that she should prioritize the <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shiba Inu</a> Metaverse project instead. The conflicting opinions regarding Jastrow&#8217;s priorities and resource allocation have further fueled the ongoing debate.</p>
<p>Investors, despite the lack of recent updates on the Shiba Inu Metaverse project&#8217;s progress, have maintained a positive outlook. Their confidence is evident from the Shibpreme team&#8217;s purchase of approximately 73 Metaverse lands for an astonishing $27,503 back in June 2023.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/R1LR2U1I/" width="1835" height="883" /></p>

<h2><strong>Shiba Inu Metaverse Scrutiny</strong></h2>
<p>The <a href="https://medium.com/@raamjai/shiba-inus-metaverse-project-enters-exciting-new-phase-486b77329691" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Shiba Inu Metaverse project</a>, which has been relatively quiet in the headlines as development progresses behind the scenes, now finds itself under scrutiny due to the allegations surrounding Jastrow. Trophias&#8217; accusations have raised questions about the project&#8217;s integrity, but without concrete evidence, it is difficult to ascertain the veracity of the claims.</p>
<p>The ongoing dispute over intellectual property rights adds another layer of complexity to the situation. While Jastrow has clarified her stance, the lack of transparency surrounding the specifics of the dispute leaves room for speculation. It remains to be seen how the project will address these concerns and provide clarity to investors and supporters.</p>

<p><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_c548d6.webp?fit=630%2C420" width="630" height="420" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">289034</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
