<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoSlate</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptoslate.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptoslate.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News and Real-time Coin Data</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 20:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cropped-cryptoslate-transparent-icon-256x256-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CryptoSlate</title>
	<link>https://cryptoslate.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Asia&#8217;s crypto revolution: Web3 growth in the East</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/asias-crypto-revolution-web3-growth-in-the-east/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/asias-crypto-revolution-web3-growth-in-the-east/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Elaine Zhu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guest Post]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Op-Ed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404654</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the years, the Asia Pacific region (APAC) has established itself as an impressive environment for the rapidly growing technology industry. From the bustling tech hub of Singapore to the financial might of Hong Kong, the flourishing Web3 community in Vietnam, and the impressive technological creativity of Japan, APAC has consistently been at the forefront [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/asias-crypto-revolution-web3-growth-in-the-east/">Asia&#8217;s crypto revolution: Web3 growth in the East</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the years, the Asia Pacific region (APAC) has established itself as an impressive environment for the rapidly growing technology industry. From the bustling tech hub of Singapore to the financial might of Hong Kong, the flourishing Web3 community in Vietnam, and the impressive technological creativity of Japan, APAC has consistently been at the forefront of </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">innovation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With governments actively embracing blockchain, a highly skilled digital native population, and leading industry projects setting their sights on the region, APAC is set to lead the charge in shaping the future of Web3. </span></p>
<h2><b>Governments and Regulators Setting Pace </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the critical drivers of this journey is the progressive regulatory stance in key jurisdictions. Last year, Singapore became one of the first countries to implement </span><strong><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/15/singapore-among-worlds-first-to-agree-stablecoin-crypto-regulation.html">stablecoin regulation</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This solidifies the city-state&#8217;s commitment to fostering a secure crypto ecosystem for investors and provides a blueprint for others to follow. Singapore is setting clear standards and leading by example to show the world how regulatory frameworks can bring more trust and security to the ever-evolving crypto landscape. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hong Kong is also solidifying its position as a crypto hub. Introducing a </span><strong><a href="https://www.kwm.com/global/en/insights/latest-thinking/hong-kongs-new-virtual-asset-regime-what-you-need-to-know.html#:~:text=The%20VASP%20Licensing%20Regime%20requires%20the%20licensed%20exchange%20to%20implement,licensed%20exchange%20and%20its%20clients.">licensing regime for Virtual Asset Service Providers (VASPs) </a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">and a regulatory framework for retail trading is a testament to the city&#8217;s dedication to embracing the future of financial technology. Furthermore, Hong Kong has embraced blockchain technology as a major component of its financial model.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spearheaded in collaboration with the United Nations and the Bank of International Settlements, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority launched a groundbreaking initiative known as &#8216;</span><strong><a href="https://www.hkma.gov.hk/eng/key-functions/international-financial-centre/bond-market-development/government-green-bond-programme/">Project Genesis 2.0</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8216; which yielded two innovative prototypes for green bonds in 2023, successfully executing the sale of the world&#8217;s inaugural tokenized green bond, valued at over </span><strong><a href="https://www.hkma.gov.hk/eng/news-and-media/press-releases/2023/02/20230216-3/">$100 million USD</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="http://cryptoslate.com/places/japan">Japan</a> has signaled its commitment to improving the business and regulatory environment for Web3 companies. In a </span><strong><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/25/japan-signals-more-web3-promotion-policies-are-to-come/">speech</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> at last year&#8217;s WebX conference in Tokyo, Japan&#8217;s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida emphasized that the government intends to accommodate Web3 technologies, particularly regarding regulations around digital assets and content sharing. ]</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Prime Minister emphatically stated that </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Web3 is part of the new form of capitalism,&#8221; leaving no doubts about the nation&#8217;s fierce commitment to fostering innovation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lastly, the approval of BTC spot ETFs in the US, stewarded by premier financial institutions such as BlackRock and Fidelity, represents a very positive milestone for the industry within American borders and could signal increased activity in APAC. Before this approval, </span><strong><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/ubs-allows-wealthy-clients-to-trade-crypto-etfs-in-hong-kong-1.1996590">UBS and HSBC</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> made strides to offer customers access to new investment vehicles. With the creation of new regulated institutional products, the possibilities for increased market participation have grown exponentially.</span></p>
<h2><b>Digital Natives Leading the Way</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Perhaps the region&#8217;s most valuable positive element is the highly skilled and motivated </span><strong><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/apac/2022/01/19/how-digital-natives-are-helping-fuel-asias-rise-as-the-worlds-innovation-engine/">digital natives</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">. For so long, institutions and society have depended on specialized technologists and developers to lead the way in the field. But now, younger generations born into a digital world are transforming how new technologies are understood, regulated, implemented, and utilized.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is most clear in the APAC region where progressive regulations, thanks to a novel working relationship between technologists, business leaders, and government officials, have resulted in a projected </span><strong><a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP50587223">US $126.9 billion</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of spending from digital native businesses by 2026. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The economic impacts of this exponential growth will be revolutionary, not only in the region but across the globe. On top of the impressive economic impacts, we can only begin to imagine how the new technologies and services created in this environment will positively impact industries from finance and banking to content sharing and entertainment.</span></p>
<h2><b>Leading Web3 Adoption in 2024?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&#8217;s no secret that adopting new technologies is an intricate process that requires extensive collaboration between technologists, businesses, and policymakers. This has historically been an arduous process for the tech industry, particularly due to the complexity of the subject matter, among other factors. Consequently, the regulatory framework brought forth by policymakers is often not reflective of industry, market, or consumer needs.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Around the world, governments have struggled to balance their objectives and the tech industry&#8217;s needs. But, in the east, an impressive movement spearheaded by a digitally oriented population is underway &#8211; one that is successfully fostering the necessary collaboration between industry leaders and public officials while ensuring the industry continues to see the same success. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For these reasons, APAC is on the brink of claiming its position as the world&#8217;s important region for Web3 innovation. With a convergence of technological prowess, innovative regulations, and a rapidly growing digital native economy, APAC nations have seamlessly embraced the innovative principles that define Web3, and the region is poised to serve not only as a catalyst but as a leader, in the global advancement of  Web3 technologies. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/asias-crypto-revolution-web3-growth-in-the-east/">Asia&#8217;s crypto revolution: Web3 growth in the East</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/asias-crypto-revolution-web3-growth-in-the-east/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/hongkong.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/hongkong.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How AI and crypto are shaping the future of finance</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/how-ai-and-crypto-are-shaping-the-future-of-finance/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/how-ai-and-crypto-are-shaping-the-future-of-finance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shane Neagle]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guest Post]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Op-Ed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=403482</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the last three years, the crypto space has undergone massive upheavals. Alongside the boosting from stimulus packages in 2021, venture capital (VC) firms had invested $33 billion in crypto and blockchain startups. The following year, the Federal Reserve triggered a domino of crypto bankruptcies with its interest rate hiking cycle, starting from the Terra [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/how-ai-and-crypto-are-shaping-the-future-of-finance/">How AI and crypto are shaping the future of finance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the last three years, the crypto space has undergone massive upheavals. Alongside the boosting from stimulus packages in 2021, venture capital (VC) firms had invested </span><a href="https://docsend.com/view/pwgbawfj6sc8q7de"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>$33</strong></span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> billion in crypto and blockchain startups.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The following year, the Federal Reserve triggered a domino of crypto bankruptcies with its interest rate hiking cycle, starting from the Terra (LUNA) crash and culminating in the FTX Ponzi scheme collapse.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The promise of DeFi lost its luster, not helped by over $3 billion lost in DeFi hacks during 2023. The ongoing Bitcoin bull run shows the lack of altcoin confidence as the so-called </span><strong><a href="https://www.blockchaincenter.net/en/altcoin-season-index/">Altcoin Season</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is yet to manifest.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In June 2023, BlackRock&#8217;s head of strategic partnerships, Joseph Chalom, </span><strong><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/blackrock-sees-institutional-adoption-of-defi-many-years-away-1.1936818">noted</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that DeFi&#8217;s institutional adoption is “many, many, many years away”. However, there is a case to be made that the emerging AI narrative can fuse with blockchain technology and its applications.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taking in lessons from the previous cycle, what would that AI-crypto landscape look like?</span></p>
<h2><strong>Laying the AI Foundation with Crypto Composability</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking back, it is safe to say that “DeFi” was subsumed by companies on top of tokenized layers, such as Celsius Network or BlockFi, rendering DeFi into CeFi. These companies successfully drove crypto adoption as such, only to end up sullying the very word “crypto”.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A renewed DeFi v2 should then focus on a superior user experience that doesn’t spark the demand for centralized companies to make it so. Most importantly, DeFi security must be fortified. The most promising solution in that direction is the zero-knowledge Ethereum Virtual Machine &#8211; zkEVM.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By abstracting chain transactions via zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs), zkEVM increases network throughput and reduces gas costs. On top of that, zkEVM simplifies the user experience by facilitating alternative token payments for gas fees. In other words, zkEVM-like solutions pave the road to scalability needed for AI applications.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AI applications inherently involve high volumes of data, making it a potential bottleneck for blockchain networks. With this obstacle ahead, Polygon zkEVM makes it possible to generate AI artwork via the Midjourney image generator. In </span><strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?app=desktop&amp;v=c0XYK5z8s_g">this process</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">, the results could be tokenized as NFTs with low fees.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Building further on smart contracts of other kinds, the crypto space has laid the groundwork for AI with composability and permissionless access. Combined, this creates an autonomous and efficient infrastructure for financial markets. As every piece of market action can be disassembled into smart contracts, composability brings innovation across three composability layers:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Morphological &#8211; components communicating between DeFi protocols, creating new meta-features.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Atomic &#8211; ability for each smart contract to function independently or in conjunction with other protocols’ smart contracts.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Syntactic &#8211; ability for protocols to communicate based on standardized protocols. </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In practice, this translates to Lego DeFi bricks. For instance, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/compound/">Compound (COMP)</a> allows users to supply liquidity into smart contract pools. This is one of DeFi’s revolutionary pillars as users no longer require someone&#8217;s permission to either loan or borrow. With smart contracts acting as liquidity pools, borrowers can tap into them by providing collateral. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Liquidity providers gain cTokens in return as interest. If the supplied token is USDC, the yielding one will be cUSDC. However these tokens can be integrated across the DeFi board into all protocols compatible with the ERC-20 standard.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In other words, composability creates opportunities for the multiplicity of yields, so that no smart contract is left idle. The problem is, how to efficiently handle this rise in complexity? This is where AI comes into play.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Amplifying Efficiency with AI</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When thinking of artificial intelligence (AI), the main feature that comes to mind is superhuman processing. Financial markets have long ago become too complex for human minds to handle. Instead, humans have come to rely on predictive algorithms, automation and personalization.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In TradFi, this typically translates to robo advisors prompting users on their needs and risk tolerances. A robo advisor would then generate a profile to manage the user&#8217;s portfolio. In the blockchain composability arena, such AI algorithms would gain much greater flexibility to siphon yields.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By reading the market conditions on the fly as they access transparent smart contracts, AI agents have the potential to reduce market inefficiencies, reduce human error, and increase market coordination. The latter already exists in the form of automated market makers (AMMs) that deliver asset price discovery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By analyzing order flows, liquidity and volatility in real-time, AI agents are ideally suited to optimize liquidity supply and even prevent DeFi </span><strong><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/aave-and-yearn-finance-exploited-for-over-10m-in-stablecoins/">flash loan exploits</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by coordinating between DeFi platforms and limiting transaction sizes. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Inevitably, as AI agents increase market efficiency through real-time market monitoring and machine learning, new prediction markets could emerge as liquidity deepens. The job of humans would then be to set bots to arbitrate against other bots.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At </span><strong><a href="https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/ai-trends-2023/#:~:text=In%202023%2C%20AI%20startups%20raised,a%20whole%20(%2D30%25).">$42.5 billion</a></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> across 2,500 equity rounds in 2023, AI investments have already outpaced the crypto peak of 2021. But which <a href="http://cryptoslate.com/cryptos/ai">AI-crypto projects</a> showcase the trend?</span></p>
<h2><strong>Spotlight on AI-Crypto Innovators</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since the launch of ChatGPT by OpenAI in November 2022, AI has been an attention grabber. The attention previously reserved for memecoins became diverted into AI advancements in reasoning, art generation, coding and most recently, text-to-video generation via Sora.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Across these fields of human interest, they all rely on the scaling of data centers. Unlike crypto tokens, which are smart contracts, AI tokens are the base blocks of text that the AI agent disassembles into relationship units. Depending on the attunement of each AI model, these tokens represent contextual windows for the relationships between concepts.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For each user prompt, it is challenging to allow maximum processing capacity. When the AI model breaks the text into tokens, the output relies on the token size. In turn, the token size determines the quality of the generated content, whatever it may be.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Obviously, the larger the token size, the larger the potential for an AI model to consider the greater number of concepts when generating content. Given such inherent limitations, <a href="http://cryptoslate.com/cryptos/ai">AI tokens</a> naturally fit blockchain tech.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just as Web3 gaming tokenizes in-game assets for decentralized ownership, tradeable currency and reward incentives, the same can be done with AI. Case in point, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/fetch/">Fetch.AI (FET)</a> is an open-access protocol to connect Autonomous Economic Agents, via the Open Economic Framework to the Fetch Smart Ledger.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FET token aims to monetize network transactions, pay for AI model deployment, reward network participants and pay for other services. And just as people connect with DeFi services via wallets, they can connect with Fetch.AI’s agentverse with a Fetch Wallet to take advantage of deployed AI protocols.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For instance, one of the many AI agents currently in beta </span><a href="https://agentverse.ai/?types=Hosted%2CLocal%2CMailbox&amp;search=&amp;status=Active&amp;sort=TotalInteractions&amp;dev_categories=FetchMember&amp;protocols="><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>agentverse</strong></span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is PDF Summarization Agent.</span></p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-403485" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto.jpg" alt="" width="1273" height="223" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto.jpg 1273w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-300x53.jpg 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-1024x179.jpg 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-768x135.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1273px) 100vw, 1273px" /></p>
<p class="p1">As a prospective pathway to democratizing AI agent access and deployment, FET token has gained 300% value since the beginning of the year. According to Market Research Future, AI agents market is forecasted to grow to <a href="https://www.marketresearchfuture.com/sample_request/12255?trk=article-ssr-frontend-pulse_little-text-block"><span class="s1">$110.42 billion</span></a> by 2032 from $6.03 billion 2023. This represents a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 43.80%.</p>
<p class="p1">Ultimately, we are likely to see an ecosystem of AI agents interacting with DeFi protocols and other services that would benefit from automating real-time decisions. This may expand to AI agents aiding self-driving EVs or even helping execute delicate surgeries and patient care. <span class="s1"><a href="https://www.facs.org/for-medical-professionals/news-publications/news-and-articles/bulletin/2023/june-2023-volume-108-issue-6/ai-is-poised-to-revolutionize-surgery/">Pediatric surgeon</a></span> Dr. Danielle Walsh at the University of Kentucky College of Medicine in Lexington said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p3">“A patient who wakes up at 1:00 in the morning 2 days after a surgical operation can contact the chatbot to ask, ‘I’m having this symptom, is this normal?’”</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p5">In medical diagnostics, Massachusetts-based Lantheus Holdings (LNTH) had already deployed its PYLARIFY AI imaging agent for early prostate cancer detection. With AI-crypto projects like Fetch.AI, many such services could be tokenized to full extent.</p>
<h2 class="p6">The Road Ahead: Challenges and Opportunities</h2>
<p class="p1">Ahead of AI integration, blockchain platforms face the same problem &#8211; institutional adoption. Do smaller protocols have a chance to penetrate the mainstream, or is this reserved for institutions?</p>
<p class="p1">DeFi may have paved the way for tokenized financial markets, but big players are likelier to instill public confidence.</p>
<p class="p1">For instance, the <strong><a href="https://www.digitalasset.com/hubfs/Canton/Canton%2520Network%2520-%2520White%2520Paper.pdf"><span class="s1">Canton Network</span></a>, which is</strong> supported by Big Bank and Big Tech, may supplant smaller DeFi fish. Eventually, the convenience of <strong><a href="https://relayfi.com/blog/same-day-ach"><span class="s1">same-day bank transfers</span></a></strong> could be seamlessly integrated into blockchain networks. This is especially pertinent given that Microsoft is powering the Canton Network with Azure cloud while developing AI products.</p>
<p class="p1">At the same time, plenty of users would prefer to stay within open-access ecosystems, riding the value appreciation of AI-crypto tokens. Moreover, crypto protocols don’t have to be directly geared toward AI agent deployment. Case in point, The Graph (GRT) could be used for AI apps as a blockchain data indexing service.</p>
<p class="p1">Based on this speculation, this “Google of Blockchain&#8221; has gained a 103% boost year-to-date. One of the most prospective crypto projects aiding AI could be Injective Protocol (INJ). As it “injects” AI algorithms into aforementioned DeFi market actions, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/injective/">Injective</a> aims to simplify and automate complex DeFi operations.</p>
<p class="p1">At the base layer of the AI-crypto intersection could be <strong><a href="https://allora.network/"><span class="s1">Allora Network</span></a></strong>, using its zero-knowledge machine learning (zkML) and federated learning to build AI apps for augmented DeFi experience.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-403486" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-2.jpg" alt="" width="936" height="638" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-2.jpg 936w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-2-300x204.jpg 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-2-768x523.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></p>
<p class="p1">If the rollout of these open apps is successful, institutional networks such as Canton would have diminished appeal. This dynamic will largely depend on regulatory agencies, which are yet to materialize rules even for the crypto space.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Conclusion</h2>
<p class="p3">AI is poised to make data more intelligible, actionable and pertinent to a specific user. On the other hand, blockchain technology formalized and decentralized the logic of human action into self-executing smart contracts.</p>
<p class="p3">When the two spheres meet, we get AI agents with a renewed purpose. A new generation of tokenized robo-advisors that take full advantage of DeFi composability. And as AI agents explore new possibilities, new markets will emerge.</p>
<p class="p3">From predictive analysis to injecting liquidity into on-chain markets, AI agents are ready to craft a hyper-financialized future where, <strong><a href="https://tokenist.com/investing/how-to-invest-in-bitcoin/"><span class="s1">starting from Bitcoin</span></a></strong> itself, humans will encounter plenty of building blocks to capitalize on.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/how-ai-and-crypto-are-shaping-the-future-of-finance/">How AI and crypto are shaping the future of finance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/how-ai-and-crypto-are-shaping-the-future-of-finance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-3.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-crypto-3.jpg" length="1456" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale amends Ethereum ETF filing, says investors &#8216;want and deserve&#8217; the fund</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/grayscale-amends-ethereum-etf-filing-says-investors-want-and-deserve-the-fund/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/grayscale-amends-ethereum-etf-filing-says-investors-want-and-deserve-the-fund/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale amended a regulatory filing through which it intends to convert its Ethereum Trust to a spot exchange-traded fund (ETF). The company&#8217;s March 15 amendment strengthens its earlier filing in multiple ways. The update supports the argument that surveillance sharing within the CME ETH market is sufficient to protect against fraud and manipulation in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/grayscale-amends-ethereum-etf-filing-says-investors-want-and-deserve-the-fund/">Grayscale amends Ethereum ETF filing, says investors &#8216;want and deserve&#8217; the fund</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/grayscale-investments/">Grayscale</a> amended a regulatory filing through which it intends to convert its <span class="css-1qaijid r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0 r-poiln3"><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> Trust </span>to a spot exchange-traded fund (ETF).</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s <a href="https://www.nyse.com/publicdocs/nyse/markets/nyse-arca/rule-filings/filings/2024/SR-NYSEArca-2023-70_Am._1.pdf">March 15</a> amendment strengthens its earlier filing in multiple ways. The update supports the argument that surveillance sharing within the CME ETH market is sufficient to protect against fraud and manipulation in the spot ETH market.</p>
<p>Grayscale&#8217;s latest amendment includes a correlation analysis conducted by <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/coinbase/">Coinbase</a> as evidence of sufficient market correlation. Coinbase found that the CME ETH futures market has been &#8220;consistently and highly correlated&#8221; with the spot Ethereum market for roughly the past three years.</p>
<p>The rate is higher than the correlation that the SEC found between the CME Bitcoin futures market and the spot <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> market.</p>
<p>Grayscale&#8217;s amendment also expands on the creation and redemption of ETF shares. Notably, this section describes only cash creations and redemptions. It accordingly states that authorized participants cannot purchase, hold, deliver, or receive ETH.</p>
<p>According to the filing, Grayscale Ethereum Trust now holds $11.8 billion in assets under management (AUM) instead of $4.8 billion of AUM. The conversion of the fund to an ETF would unlock over $1.73 billion of value instead of the $1.6 billion previously estimated.</p>
<h2>Grayscale advocates for ETF</h2>
<p><span class="css-1qaijid r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0 r-poiln3">Craig Salm</span>, Grayscale&#8217;s <span class="css-1qaijid r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0 r-poiln3">Chief Legal Officer, acknowledged the filing and emphasized the expected broad appeal of spot Ethereum ETFs. He <a href="https://twitter.com/craigsalm/status/1768750794021511218">wrote on X</a> that investors </span>&#8220;want and deserve access to Ethereum in the form of a spot Ethereum ETF.&#8221;</p>
<p>Salm added that the case for an Ethereum ETF &#8220;is just as strong as it was for spot Bitcoin ETFs.&#8221;</p>
<p>Market manipulation and creation/redemption methods were key concerns before spot Bitcoin ETFs gained approval this January. Grayscale&#8217;s latest amendment is vital as it addresses those same issues in the context of Ethereum ETFs.</p>
<p>Grayscale&#8217;s amendment comes alongside declining expectations of regulatory approval. <a href="https://polymarket.com/event/ethereum-etf-approved-by-may-31">Polymarket</a> places the odds of Ethereum ETF approval by the end of May at just 26% as of March 15.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/grayscale-amends-ethereum-etf-filing-says-investors-want-and-deserve-the-fund/">Grayscale amends Ethereum ETF filing, says investors &#8216;want and deserve&#8217; the fund</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/grayscale-amends-ethereum-etf-filing-says-investors-want-and-deserve-the-fund/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/grayscale-ethereum.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/grayscale-ethereum.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts warn MicroStrategy&#8217;s plan to fuel Bitcoin buys with debt could backfire</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/analysts-warn-microstrategys-plan-to-fuel-bitcoin-buys-with-debt-could-backfire/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/analysts-warn-microstrategys-plan-to-fuel-bitcoin-buys-with-debt-could-backfire/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Watch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy could raise as much as $600 million from its latest convertible debt offering to purchase more Bitcoin. However, JPMorgan analysts have reportedly cautioned that the firm&#8217;s reliance on debt to purchase Bitcoin could exacerbate a market downturn. The firm, led by BTC advocate Michael Saylor, has acquired over 15,000 BTC worth nearly $1 billion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/analysts-warn-microstrategys-plan-to-fuel-bitcoin-buys-with-debt-could-backfire/">Analysts warn MicroStrategy&#8217;s plan to fuel Bitcoin buys with debt could backfire</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/microstrategy/">MicroStrategy</a> could raise as much as $600 million from its latest convertible debt offering to purchase more <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/jpmorgan/">JPMorgan</a> analysts have <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/microstrategy-bitcoin-acquisition-debt-crypto-rally-price-high-downturn-pullback-2024-3">reportedly</a> cautioned that the firm&#8217;s reliance on debt to purchase Bitcoin could exacerbate a market downturn.</p>
<p>The firm, led by BTC advocate <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/michael-saylor/">Michael Saylor</a>, has <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/mstr-rallies-10-as-microstrategy-buys-155-million-bitcoin-in-10-days/">acquired over 15,000 BTC worth nearly $1 billion</a> since the year began, primarily <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/microstrategy-spends-821-million-to-grow-bitcoin-hoard-to-205000/">financed through a convertible debt offering</a>.</p>
<p>According to the analysts, this funding approach has turned MicroStrategy into a <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoin-long-traders-still-leveraged-at-over-40-billion-notional-value-above-50k/">leveraged player</a> in the Bitcoin arena, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/bitcoin-holders-rejoice-as-value-breaks-unprecedented-71000-milestone-marking-new-ath/">amplifying the ongoing market rally</a>.</p>
<p>They added that such debt-funded Bitcoin acquisitions contribute to market froth and increase the likelihood of more significant deleveraging in future downturns.</p>
<p>Despite Bitcoin&#8217;s recent surge to a record-breaking high of over $73,000, a <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/bitcoins-sudden-price-correction-wipes-out-over-666-million-from-long-traders-in-24-hours/">sharp downturn</a> has occurred, with prices dipping approximately 4% to around $68,000 as of press time, according to <em>CryptoSlate&#8217;s</em> <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">data</a>.</p>
<h2>Pricing details</h2>
<p>According to a March 15 <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/press/microstrategy-announces-pricing-of-offering-of-convertible-senior-notes_03-15-2024">statement</a>, MicroStrategy plans to price its latest issuance of senior convertible notes at $525 million, with purchasers also granted an option to acquire up to an additional $78.5 million of the offering.</p>
<p>As such, the anticipated proceeds from this offering range between $515 million and approximately $592.3 million. The notes are slated to mature by March 2031, carrying an annual interest rate of 0.875%, payable semi-annually.</p>
<p>Investors who hold these notes will enjoy certain rights like the ability to request repurchase under certain conditions. Additionally, they will retain the flexibility to convert their notes into either cash or shares of MicroStrategy&#8217;s class A common stock.</p>
<p>The conversion rate for these notes stands at $2,327.31 per share, marking a premium of roughly 40% over MicroStrategy&#8217;s average share price of $1662.20.</p>
<p>The private offering targets qualified institutional buyers and remains subject to prevailing market conditions and other pertinent factors. Its sales would close by March 18.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/analysts-warn-microstrategys-plan-to-fuel-bitcoin-buys-with-debt-could-backfire/">Analysts warn MicroStrategy&#8217;s plan to fuel Bitcoin buys with debt could backfire</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/analysts-warn-microstrategys-plan-to-fuel-bitcoin-buys-with-debt-could-backfire/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/microstrategy-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/microstrategy-1.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI crypto traders take profits pushing tokens down up to 20% after scorching 2024 rally</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-traders-take-profits-pushing-tokens-down-up-to-20-after-scorching-2024-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-traders-take-profits-pushing-tokens-down-up-to-20-after-scorching-2024-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Liam 'Akiba' Wright]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 23:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After a face-melting rally in the AI crypto sector over the past few months, investors appear to have taken a profit-taking approach over the past few days. The sector soared past $10 billion in mid-February, buoyed by Bittensor&#8217;s remarkable climb to a $4 billion market cap with an increase of over 220% in 2024. By [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-traders-take-profits-pushing-tokens-down-up-to-20-after-scorching-2024-rally/">AI crypto traders take profits pushing tokens down up to 20% after scorching 2024 rally</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a face-melting rally in the <a href="/cryptos/ai/">AI crypto sector</a> over the past few months, investors appear to have taken a profit-taking approach over the past few days. The sector <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-sector-nears-10-billion-market-cap-as-bittensor-surges-220-in-2024/">soared past $10 billion</a> in mid-February, buoyed by Bittensor&#8217;s remarkable climb to a $4 billion market cap with an increase of over 220% in 2024. By March, the sector had exploded to <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-market-cap-doubles-to-25-billion-in-20-days/">over $25 billion in market cap</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_404902" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-404902" style="width: 2854px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-404902 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35.png" alt="Top AI coins surge in 2024 (Source: TradingView)" width="2854" height="1608" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35.png 2854w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35-1024x577.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35-768x433.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35-1536x865.png 1536w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-05-35-2048x1154.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 2854px) 100vw, 2854px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-404902" class="wp-caption-text">Top AI coins surge in 2024 (Source: TradingView)</figcaption></figure>
<p>Around March 9, several projects hit new all-time highs, including <a href="/coins/bittensor">Bittensor</a>, <a href="/coins/fetch">Fetch</a>, OriginTrail, <a href="/coins/worldcoin">Worldcoin</a>, and <a href="/coins/arkham">Arkham</a>, pushing the market cap close to $30 billion.</p>
<p>In the past few days, the sector has cooled to below $25 billion in market cap as investors seem to be taking profits after a potentially overheated market surge. While <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoin-long-traders-still-leveraged-at-over-40-billion-notional-value-above-50k/">Bitcoin has also dipped</a>, as of press time, it sits just 6% below its all-time high, while the top 10 AI crypto projects are mostly down over 20%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_404954" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-404954" style="width: 2140px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-404954 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55.png" alt="Top 10 AI coins" width="2140" height="1244" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55.png 2140w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55-300x174.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55-1024x595.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55-768x446.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55-1536x893.png 1536w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-15-at-22.58.55-2048x1191.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 2140px) 100vw, 2140px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-404954" class="wp-caption-text">Top 10 AI coins</figcaption></figure>
<p>Interestingly, many AI crypto coins have not recently been as closely correlated with Bitcoin as the rest of the market. Bittensor and Fetch, specifically have seemingly been treading their own course, moving down only when Bitcoin has made substantial moves. Even then, the coins often had a delayed reaction or moved against Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Fetch increased 140% in four days since March 6 before slightly retracing approximately 20%. Across the board, since the sector&#8217;s peak on March 9, Fetch is down 4%, ICP is down 11%, The Graph is down 12%, Singularity is down 13%, and Bittensor is down 12.8%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_404903" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-404903" style="width: 2854px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-404903 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21.png" alt="Top AI coins fall in past days (Source: TradingView)" width="2854" height="1608" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21.png 2854w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21-1024x577.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21-768x433.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21-1536x865.png 1536w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BTCUSD_2024-03-15_19-04-21-2048x1154.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 2854px) 100vw, 2854px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-404903" class="wp-caption-text">Top AI coins fall in past days (Source: TradingView)</figcaption></figure>
<p>While the rise of AI in 2023 saw an influx of new AI-related memecoins and hype projects, those currently sitting toward the top of the sector chart are primarily focused on real-life implementation of decentralized AI tooling. The work has attracted the attention of Ethereum&#8217;s Vitalik Buterin, Erik Voorhees, and other notable players in the crypto space.</p>
<p>The importance of decentralized AI models likely aligns with that of decentralized finance as the progress of AI development continues to ramp up. Blockchain and tokenization appear solid bedfellows for a distributed AI network, indicating the recent retracement is possibly profit-taking rather than investors losing faith in the burgeoning sector. However, with such rapid gains, it is also likely that investors will be eager to see progress in delivering technology.</p>
<p>Many of the top progress have live mainnets with projects actively building. The critical next step is to see whether a network effect can bring users on chain to engage with this fascinating cross-section of AI and blockchain. Bittensor, for one, is undoubtedly seeing demand for adoption as the cost to register one of its 32 subnets has risen from around $200,000 to over $5 million this month alone, with the price set by market forces rather than any centralized entity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-traders-take-profits-pushing-tokens-down-up-to-20-after-scorching-2024-rally/">AI crypto traders take profits pushing tokens down up to 20% after scorching 2024 rally</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/ai-crypto-traders-take-profits-pushing-tokens-down-up-to-20-after-scorching-2024-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-token-down.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ai-token-down.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vanguard CEO says Bitcoin ETFs do not &#8216;belong in a long-term portfolio&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-ceo-says-bitcoin-etfs-do-not-belong-in-a-long-term-portfolio/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-ceo-says-bitcoin-etfs-do-not-belong-in-a-long-term-portfolio/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vanguard CEO Tim Buckley said Bitcoin needs to &#8220;change as an asset class&#8221; for the investment firm to consider it as a viable option and has no intention of changing its mind about spot Bitcoin ETFs until that happens. Buckley made the statement in a preview clip of an upcoming webcast posted on March 15. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-ceo-says-bitcoin-etfs-do-not-belong-in-a-long-term-portfolio/">Vanguard CEO says Bitcoin ETFs do not &#8216;belong in a long-term portfolio&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vanguard CEO Tim Buckley said Bitcoin needs to &#8220;change as an asset class&#8221; for the investment firm to consider it as a viable option and has no intention of changing its mind about spot Bitcoin ETFs until that happens.</p>
<p>Buckley made the statement in a preview clip of an upcoming webcast posted on <a href="https://investor.vanguard.com/investor-resources-education/news/vanguards-perspective-on-bitcoin-etfs#modal-transcript">March 15</a>. The full conversation with CIO Greg Davis will be published on March 19.</p>
<h2>Too volatile</h2>
<p>Buckley said that Vanguard does not intend to change its stance toward the <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/products/category/bitcoin-etf/">spot Bitcoin ETFs</a>, primarily because it does not believe they belong in long-term and retirement portfolios. He added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Something like bitcoin is just too volatile and it&#8217;s not a store of value — it hasn&#8217;t been&#8230; It is speculative, really tough to think about how it belongs in a long-term portfolio.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Vanguard CEO said that Bitcoin prices recently fell alongside stock prices, and it is difficult to predict the flagship crypto&#8217;s growth. These factors make it difficult to determine how to include Bitcoin ETFs in portfolios.</p>
<p>Buckley said the firm focuses on investing in asset classes with underlying cash flows, such as stocks or bonds, which are easier to value and model.</p>
<p>Buckley <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-ceo-to-retire-but-firm-unlikely-to-change-anti-crypto-stance/">plans to retire</a> before the end of 2024 but his departure is unlikely to change Vanguard&#8217;s stance as the beliefs are part of the firm&#8217;s investment philosophy.</p>
<h2>Vanguard&#8217;s past complaints</h2>
<p>Vanguard <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-to-ban-all-bitcoin-etfs-on-its-platform/">previously confirmed</a> that it would not offer access to spot Bitcoin ETFs shortly after the funds gained approval in January 2024. The company commented more extensively on its concerns later in the month and said that Bitcoin was an &#8220;immature asset class.&#8221;</p>
<p>Vanguard&#8217;s Global Head of ETF Capital Markets and Broker and Index Relations, Janel Jackson, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-says-bitcoin-is-immature-asset-class/">notably commented</a> that crypto &#8220;can create havoc within a portfolio&#8221; due to its short history and lack of inherent value and cash flow.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the firm&#8217;s Head of Brokerage &amp; Investments, Andrew Kadjeski, explained that the firm aims to serve long-term, buy-and-hold investors.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s history of avoiding short-term market trends, including steering clear of internet funds in the 1990s and removing access to leveraged and inverse funds and ETFs in 2019 and over-the-counter stocks in 2022, illustrates a historic strategy of prioritizing long-term stability over short-term gains.</p>
<p>Vanguard&#8217;s stance has generated significant discussion within the investment community, with some clients expressing frustration over the firm&#8217;s reluctance to include Bitcoin in its investment offerings.</p>
<p>Despite the controversy and potential market pressure, Vanguard remains steadfast in its traditional investment approach, focusing on asset classes it deems fundamental for sustained investment success.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-ceo-says-bitcoin-etfs-do-not-belong-in-a-long-term-portfolio/">Vanguard CEO says Bitcoin ETFs do not &#8216;belong in a long-term portfolio&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/vanguard-ceo-says-bitcoin-etfs-do-not-belong-in-a-long-term-portfolio/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/vanguard-ceo.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/vanguard-ceo.jpg" length="1792" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Labs spun-off into independent entity outside the Binance group umbrella</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/binance-labs-spun-off-into-independent-entity-outside-the-binance-group-umbrella/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/binance-labs-spun-off-into-independent-entity-outside-the-binance-group-umbrella/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404861</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance spun off its $10 billion venture capital arm, Binance Labs, into an independent entity that will no longer be under the group&#8217;s purview weeks ago. Bloomberg drew attention to the silent change in a March 15 report, which revealed that Binance Labs had added a disclaimer about the change on its website earlier in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/binance-labs-spun-off-into-independent-entity-outside-the-binance-group-umbrella/">Binance Labs spun-off into independent entity outside the Binance group umbrella</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/binance/">Binance</a> spun off its $10 billion venture capital arm, Binance Labs, into an independent entity that will no longer be under the group&#8217;s purview weeks ago.</p>
<p>Bloomberg drew attention to the silent change in a <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/top-crypto-exchange-binance-spins-off-10-billion-venture-unit-1.2047231">March 15</a> report, which revealed that Binance Labs had added a disclaimer about the change on its website earlier in the year.</p>
<p>Based on snapshots from Archive.org, the venture firm added the disclaimer in late February:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Binance Labs is an independent venture and not part of the Binance Group nor is it involved in any of the businesses operated by the Binance Group (including but not limited to the Binance cryptocurrency exchange).&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The spin-off is one of the most significant decisions made under the exchange&#8217;s new CEO, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/richard-teng/">Richard Teng</a>, since taking over four months ago. He previously headed the exchange&#8217;s Singapore division and has no publicly listed role at Binance Labs.</p>
<p>The companies did not respond to a request for comment as of press time, and the reasons behind the decision to split the venture capital division are unclear.</p>
<h2>Licensing the brand</h2>
<p>Binance Labs Investment Director Alex Odagiu told Bloomberg that the venture capital firm operates independently but will continue to use the Binance brand name under a licensing agreement.</p>
<p>Despite its newfound independence, Binance Labs remains dedicated to its foundational mission of discovering and investing in promising crypto projects. Odagiu reaffirmed the commitment, stressing that the venture&#8217;s focus on supporting innovation within the blockchain ecosystem remains unchanged.</p>
<p>The separation entails distinct contractual agreements for Binance Labs staff, mirroring the organizational structure seen in other Binance-supported entities such as the BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Bloomberg identified the value of Binance Labs as close to $10 billion. The company&#8217;s website indicates that it has supported more than 200 crypto projects over six years. Its portfolio notably includes the top-twenty market cap blockchain Polygon, the metaverse-focused platform <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/the-sandbox/">The Sandbox</a>, and the decentralized finance platform CurveFi.</p>
<h2>Binance reshuffled leadership</h2>
<p>This strategic pivot comes in the wake of Binance&#8217;s recent settlement with US regulatory bodies, culminating in a hefty <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/binance-founder-changpeng-zhao-sentencing-rescheduled-for-april-30/">$4.3 billion fine</a> and the replacement of its founder, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/changpeng-zhao/">Changpeng Zhao</a>, with Teng as CEO.</p>
<p>The reorganization appears to be part of a broader strategy to navigate the post-settlement landscape, ensuring compliance and operational resilience.</p>
<p>Under the leadership of Binance co-founder Yi He,  Binance Labs has emerged as a pivotal force in the crypto venture capital arena.</p>
<p>Funded primarily through the exchange&#8217;s profits, it has established itself as a key player, supporting approximately 250 projects, including notable names like <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/sky-mavis/">Sky Mavis</a>, <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/aptos/">Aptos Labs</a>, and <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/polygon/">Polygon</a>.</p>
<p>The venture operates both as an investor and an incubator, with a focus on nurturing startups across various blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/binance-labs-spun-off-into-independent-entity-outside-the-binance-group-umbrella/">Binance Labs spun-off into independent entity outside the Binance group umbrella</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/binance-labs-spun-off-into-independent-entity-outside-the-binance-group-umbrella/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/binance_.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/binance_.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US prosecutors want SBF to serve at least four decades in prison</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/us-prosecutors-want-sbf-to-serve-at-least-four-decades-in-prison/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/us-prosecutors-want-sbf-to-serve-at-least-four-decades-in-prison/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Assad Jafri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404867</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Federal prosecutors have requested a prison sentence of 40 to 50 years for FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) following his conviction for conducting one of the most significant financial frauds in recent times through the misappropriation of over $8 billion of customer funds. The US Attorney&#8217;s Office for the Southern District of New York filed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/us-prosecutors-want-sbf-to-serve-at-least-four-decades-in-prison/">US prosecutors want SBF to serve at least four decades in prison</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Federal prosecutors have requested a prison sentence of 40 to 50 years for <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/ftx/">FTX</a> founder <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/sam-bankman-fried/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> (SBF) following his <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sbf-housed-with-ex-honduras-president-in-jail-is-trading-mackerel-and-giving-crypto-tips/">conviction</a> for conducting one of the most significant financial frauds in recent times through the misappropriation of over $8 billion of customer funds.</p>
<p>The US Attorney&#8217;s Office for the Southern District of New York filed a <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.410.0_2.pdf">sentencing memorandum</a> detailing SBF&#8217;s wide-ranging fraudulent activities on March 15.</p>
<p>According to the filing, his malpractices not only undermined the integrity of the financial and political systems but also left tens of thousands of victims across several continents grappling with significant losses.</p>
<h2>Greed and ambition</h2>
<p>The government&#8217;s filing paints a picture of SBF as a figure driven by <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/billions-in-user-funds-were-lost-crypto-community-reacts-to-sbf-guilty-verdict/">unparalleled greed and ambition</a>, whose actions reached into the political arena through unlawful contributions and even extended overseas with attempts to bribe Chinese government officials.</p>
<p>Beyond the financial deceit at FTX and Alameda Research, a trading firm he founded, SBF was also involved in banking misconduct, including operating an unlicensed money transmitting business and misleading banks to facilitate his operations.</p>
<p>In the aftermath of FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy, SBF attempted to <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sbfs-defense-claims-ftx-had-no-fiduciary-relationship-with-customers-on-technicality/">deflect blame and evade responsibility</a>, further complicating the legal proceedings and highlighting a persistent refusal to acknowledge the scope of his wrongdoing.</p>
<p>The prosecutors also outlined instances of obstruction of justice, including his use of encrypted messaging to delete evidence and tampering with witnesses.</p>
<h2>Extraordinary punishment for extraordinary crimes</h2>
<p>The request for a 40 to 50-year sentence emphasizes the severity of SBF&#8217;s actions and reflects the prosecution&#8217;s stance on the need for a punishment that matches the extraordinary impact of his crimes.</p>
<p>The memorandum argues that such a sentence is necessary not only to provide justice for the victims but also to serve as a deterrent against similar crimes in the rapidly evolving crypto sector.</p>
<p>In addition to the prison term, the government is seeking forfeiture of assets acquired through the criminal activities and has proposed victim compensation through remission as an alternative to traditional restitution. This approach aims to address the financial harm suffered by the victims, some of whom lost their life savings in the collapse of FTX.</p>
<p>SBF&#8217;s sentencing is set for March 28, marking a pivotal moment in bringing justice to the thousands of FTX customers who were wronged. The case stands as a significant chapter in the legal challenges facing the digital finance world.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/us-prosecutors-want-sbf-to-serve-at-least-four-decades-in-prison/">US prosecutors want SBF to serve at least four decades in prison</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/us-prosecutors-want-sbf-to-serve-at-least-four-decades-in-prison/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/sam-bankman-fried-sbf-6.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/sam-bankman-fried-sbf-6.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana defies overall market trend to hit new all-time high market cap</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/solana-defies-overall-market-trend-to-hit-new-all-time-high-market-cap/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/solana-defies-overall-market-trend-to-hit-new-all-time-high-market-cap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Assad Jafri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Watch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=404831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL) broke new ground on March 15 after an 11% rally brought its market capitalization to a new all-time high of $82.5 billion at a price of $186.77 per token despite the overall downtrend, which saw the market contract by 4%. This achievement surpasses its prior peak market cap of approximately $77.9 billion — [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/solana-defies-overall-market-trend-to-hit-new-all-time-high-market-cap/">Solana defies overall market trend to hit new all-time high market cap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana (<a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/solana/">SOL</a>) broke new ground on March 15 after an 11% rally brought its market capitalization to a new all-time high of $82.5 billion at a price of $186.77 per token despite the overall downtrend, which saw the market contract by 4%.</p>
<p>This achievement surpasses its prior peak market cap of approximately $77.9 billion — observed in November 2021 at its all-time high of $259.96 — signaling strong investor confidence and a growing interest in the digital asset.</p>
<p>SOL was trading at $181.35 as of press time — up 9.29% over the past 24 hours, with a market cap hovering just above $80 billion, according to <em>CryptoSlate</em> <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/solana/">data</a>.</p>
<h2>Sol ecosystem thriving</h2>
<p>Adding to Solana&#8217;s impressive week, the network saw a record-breaking number of new addresses, with a daily average of 738,040 new addresses based on a seven-day moving average.</p>
<p>This uptick in new addresses highlights the growing community and interest in the Solana ecosystem, which saw a green day of trading, with most tokens recording significant gains.</p>
<p>DEX native tokens — including Raydium and the recently launched Jupiter and Jito —  saw double-digit gains over the past day.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/raydium/">RAY</a> and <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/jupiter-ag/">JUP</a> were up more than 30%, while <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/jito/">JITO</a> recorded gains 10%.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the largest Solana-based memecoins like <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/dogwifhat/">WIF</a> and <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bonk1/">BONK</a> saw a drawdown mimicking the wider market as investors turned to smaller cap tokens on DEXs amid renewed memecoin frenzy.</p>
<h2>Memecoin fever</h2>
<p>The current enthusiasm surrounding Solana is largely fueled by the <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/revolut-to-launch-new-crypto-exchange-amidst-reports-of-listing-solanas-bonk-memecoin/">vibrant trading activity</a> related to newly launched <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/cryptos/meme/">memecoins</a> on the network following a <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/pepe-leads-memecoin-rally-with-blistering-118-surge-over-48-hours/">dramatic surge</a> in memecoins this year.</p>
<p>Noteworthy gains were observed in memecoins like Dogwifhat, Popcat, and Bonk, which have posted gains ranging from 117% to 554% over the past 30 days. This surge in memecoin activity has drawn considerable attention to Solana, highlighting its utility and growing relevance in the crypto space.</p>
<p>The appeal of memecoins on the Solana network has been attributed to their accessibility and entertainment value. The trend reflects a broader interest in engaging with the crypto market in a fun and accessible manner.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/solana-defies-overall-market-trend-to-hit-new-all-time-high-market-cap/">Solana defies overall market trend to hit new all-time high market cap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/solana-defies-overall-market-trend-to-hit-new-all-time-high-market-cap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/solana-yearly-high.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/solana-yearly-high.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Satoshi&#8217;s Vision down 17% against Bitcoin after Satoshi&#8217;s Verdict</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/insights/satoshis-vision-down-17-against-bitcoin-following-satoshis-verdict/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Liam 'Akiba' Wright]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?post_type=crypto_insight&#038;p=404837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While Bitcoin has seen a pullback from its recently set new all-time high of $73,750 on March 14, currently trading down around 8%, other Bitcoin forks have fared much worse. Following the morning of the landmark ruling against Craig Wright on March 14, Bitcoin Satoshi&#8217;s Vision is down 17% against BTC. Other Bitcoin forks, such [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/satoshis-vision-down-17-against-bitcoin-following-satoshis-verdict/">Satoshi&#8217;s Vision down 17% against Bitcoin after Satoshi&#8217;s Verdict</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While Bitcoin has seen a pullback from its recently set new all-time high of $73,750 on March 14, currently trading down around 8%, other Bitcoin forks have fared much worse. Following the morning of the landmark ruling against Craig Wright on March 14, Bitcoin Satoshi&#8217;s Vision is down 17% against BTC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_404823" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-404823" style="width: 2854px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-404823 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37.png" alt="Bitcoin forks against BTC (Source: TradingView)" width="2854" height="1608" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37.png 2854w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37-1024x577.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37-768x433.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37-1536x865.png 1536w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_16-17-37-2048x1154.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 2854px) 100vw, 2854px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-404823" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin forks against BTC (Source: TradingView)</figcaption></figure>
<p>Other Bitcoin forks, such as Bitcoin Cash, are also down against BTC but at a more modest 3% and 7%, respectively.</p>
<p>Craig Wright&#8217;s Bitcoin fork Bitcoin SV is down around 80% from its all-time high compared to Bitcoin, which is currently rocking around price discovery ranges. While Bitcoin SV is up around 360% from its all-time low set in July 2023 in dollar terms, it is near its all-time low when denominated in BTC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_404839" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-404839" style="width: 2854px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-404839" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43.png" alt="Bitcoin SV vs Bitcoin (Source: TradingView)" width="2854" height="1608" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43.png 2854w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43-1024x577.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43-768x433.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43-1536x865.png 1536w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BSVBTC_2024-03-15_17-04-43-2048x1154.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 2854px) 100vw, 2854px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-404839" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin SV vs Bitcoin (Source: TradingView)<span style="color: #383838; font-size: 16px;"> </span></figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/satoshis-vision-down-17-against-bitcoin-following-satoshis-verdict/">Satoshi&#8217;s Vision down 17% against Bitcoin after Satoshi&#8217;s Verdict</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btcforks.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btcforks.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
