<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptonews</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptonews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptonews.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:52:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ ‘Duped Financier Out of $4.1m’</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-fraudsters-duped-financier-out-of-4-1m.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Alper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Police]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188567</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Suspected South Korean crypto fraudsters allegedly fooled a wealthy financier into parting with over $4.1 million, the nation’s police force said on March 25.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-fraudsters-duped-financier-out-of-4-1m.htm">South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ ‘Duped Financier Out of $4.1m’</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Suspected South Korean crypto fraudsters allegedly fooled a wealthy financier into parting with over $4.1 million, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bithumb-ipo-plans-accelerate-as-south-korean-crypto-exchange-eyes-public-listing.htm">the nation</a>’s police force said on March 25.</p>
<p>Per <a href="https://www.chosun.com/national/regional/yeongnam/2024/03/25/FVRT27FQDVFSXFMXRJF5CDAYLM/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chosun Ilbo</a>, officers in Busan’s Haeundae District arrested a “group of people in their 20s and 30s.”</p>
<p>Police think the group “defrauded a financier in his 60s” by convincing him that he would receive 70% profits on his investment.</p>
<h2>South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ Said Profits Would Materialize ‘in a Month’</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The group of suspects were arrested on charges of aiding and abetting fraud.</p>
<p>Officers said that the group approached the financier in September 2022. Between the same month and December 2022, police said, the group convinced the alleged victim to make six separate payments.</p>
<p>They also told the financier that he could expect to receive his profits in just four weeks, police said.</p>
<h2>Group Used Fake Documents, Police Claim</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The group allegedly told the man that he should capitalize on “a boom time for crypto.” Police said the suspects “forged balance certificate files” to make it look like they were holding around $15 million worth of tokens.</p>
<p>The reality, police said, was that the group “barely had any virtual currency in their trading accounts.”</p>
<p>The group, police claimed, also sought to win the man’s confidence by using an accomplice to pose as a rich real estate agent working in Seoul’s affluent Gangnam District.</p>
<p>The accomplice pretended to sign a $3 million contract with the group, supposedly entrusting them with his money.</p>
<p>This contract also proved to be “forged,” police spokespeople explained.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Do Kwon went from crypto king to fugitive to the subject of an extradition contest between the US and South Korea. Here&#39;s what you need to know. <a href="https://t.co/2ghUBxJLL0">https://t.co/2ghUBxJLL0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg Crypto (@crypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto/status/1772080995715486116?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Fraud Cases Rise as Crypto Booms</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
South Korean crypto fraudsters are becoming increasingly active in the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kimchi-premium-returns-bitcoin-trades-at-10-price-premium-in-south-korea-against-global-exchanges.htm">crypto-keen nation</a>. Earlier this month, a law firm manager was <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-law-firm-chief-jailed-for-stealing-customer-money-to-invest-in-crypto.htm">jailed for stealing customer money to make private crypto investments</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188582" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188582" style="width: 1801px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188582" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503.png" alt="Trading volumes on the Upbit crypto exchange over the past week." width="1801" height="601" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503.png 1801w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-300x100.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-1024x342.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-768x256.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-1536x513.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142557/1711376756-upbit-2503-150x50.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1801px) 100vw, 1801px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188582" class="wp-caption-text">Trading volumes on the South Korean Upbit crypto exchange over the past week. (Source: CoinGecko)</figcaption></figure>
<p>Also this month, police <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-consultancy-firm-duped-elderly-investors-out-of-7-5m.htm">launched a probe into a crypto consultancy that reputedly preyed on elderly investors</a>.</p>
<p>Officers think the firm fooled people in their late 50s and 60s into paying the firm for bogus “insider crypto tips.”</p>
<p>OTC-related crypto thefts are also on the rise, with officers <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-police-arrest-multinational-gang-of-otc-crypto-thieves.htm">last month arresting a “multinational” gang of suspected thieves</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-fraudsters-duped-financier-out-of-4-1m.htm">South Korean ‘Crypto Fraudsters’ ‘Duped Financier Out of $4.1m’</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25142026/1711376426-1711353992286_processed.jpg" length="145386" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE Introduces CBDC Implementation Strategy &#8211; Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Inside</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-central-bank-cbdc-strategy.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188841</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>The UAE's central bank has announced a comprehensive strategy to implement a central bank digital currency (CBDC) for retail and wholesale use. In partnership with technology providers R3 and G42 Cloud, the UAE envisions that digital dirham will streamline cross-border transactions, enhance financial inclusion, and prepare the nation for a tokenized future.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-central-bank-cbdc-strategy.htm">UAE Introduces CBDC Implementation Strategy &#8211; Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Inside</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United Arab Emirates (UAE) is now readying a central bank digital currency (CBDC) for retail and wholesale use, according to a Central Bank of UAE (CBUAE) announcement on Saturday.</p>
<p>The national bank kicked off its <a href="https://www.centralbank.ae/media/q5nldmrv/cbuae-launches-the-central-bank-digital-currency-strategy-the-digital-dirham-en.pdf">digital dirham implementation strategy</a> during a signing event on March 23 with R3 and G42 Cloud, companies that will serve as the digital currency’s infrastructure and technology providers.</p>
<h2>Implementing A UAE CBDC</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
R3 is a major CBDC tech developer that’s been involved with numerous Bank of International Settlements (BIS) projects. Meanwhile, G42 Cloud is part of the AI holding company G42, which agreed to cooperate with OpenAI on financial services technology in October.</p>
<p>“As part of the UAE&#8217;s digital transformation, CBDC will help address the pain points of domestic and cross-border payments, enhance financial inclusion, and the move towards a cashless society,” read the CBUAE’s weekend statement.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The latest update to our CBDC Tracker shows that all of the founding members of BRICS are in the pilot phase of CBDC exploration. </p>
<p>New members–Saudi Arabia, Iran and the UAE–are also developing wholesale CBDCs.</p>
<p>Check out more of our takeaways: <a href="https://t.co/WORkdfYL09">https://t.co/WORkdfYL09</a> <a href="https://t.co/CBJHSVp5sg">pic.twitter.com/CBJHSVp5sg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Atlantic Council GeoEconomics Center (@ACGeoEcon) <a href="https://twitter.com/ACGeoEcon/status/1772252619798442344?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The first phase of UAE CBDC implementation marks one of nine initiatives in the CBUAE’s Financial Infrastructure Transformation (FIT) Programme. It also features three “pillars” intended for construction over the next 12 to 15 months.</p>
<p>The first is the soft launch of mBridge, which will help the bank facilitate real-time cross-border transactions to settle international trades. Last month, the central bank completed its very first <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-and-china-complete-first-13-6m-cross-border-cbdc-transaction.htm">cross-border transaction</a> using the digital dirham and Chinese digital yuan, valued at $13.6 million, through mBridge.</p>
<p>After that, the bank will begin proof of concept work on CBDC bridges with India, whose <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/reserve-bank-of-india-furthers-cbdc-efforts-report.htm">Reserve Bank</a> is making technological advances surrounding the privacy of its own developing CBDC. Finally, the bank will begin proof of concept work around domestic CBDC use cases, including retail and wholesale payments.</p>
<h2>Why CBUAE Wants A Digital Dirham</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Aside from strengthening the nation’s payment infrastructure, CBUAE claims it will prepare the country for a potential “tokenized” world in the future, where normal people interact with blockchain-based tokens for financial and non-financial purposes.</p>
<p>“CBDC will accelerate our digitalization journey and promote financial inclusion,” said CBUAE Governor H.E. Khaled Mohamed Balama. “We look forward to exploring the opportunities that CBDC will bring to the wider economy and society.”</p>
<p>Last month, Bridge Tower Capital and Deus X launched a $250 million joint venture to build digital asset infrastructure in the UAE. The venture, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bridgetower-capital-and-deus-x-capital-launch-250-million-digital-asset-platform-in-uae.htm">BridgeTower Middle East</a>, promotes institutional crypto adoption across the region.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-central-bank-cbdc-strategy.htm">UAE Introduces CBDC Implementation Strategy &#8211; Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s Inside</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/1707379145-uae.jpg" length="197371" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU Launches Probe into Tech Giants Apple, Google, Meta, and Amazon Over Digital Markets Act Violations</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-launches-probe-tech-giants-over-digital-markets-act-violations.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Commission has begun an extensive investigation targeted at Apple, Amazon, Alphabet, and Meta over non-compliance practices under the new Digital Markets Act (DMA). The notice of the inquiry was disclosed by the commission on March 25, and it represents the EU’s first major attempt to curb anti-competitive practices by big tech companies labeled as "gatekeepers" by the commission.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-launches-probe-tech-giants-over-digital-markets-act-violations.htm">EU Launches Probe into Tech Giants Apple, Google, Meta, and Amazon Over Digital Markets Act Violations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The European Commission began an extensive investigation targeted at Apple, Amazon, Alphabet, and Meta over non-compliance practices under the new Digital Markets Act (DMA) on March 25.</p>
<p>The commission inquiry represents the EU’s first major attempt to curb anti-competitive practices by big tech companies labeled as &#8220;gatekeepers&#8221; by the commission.</p>
<h2>EU Targets Apple, Google, Meta Practices</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_24_1689">According to the announcement</a>, the European Commission has opened five separate investigations to scrutinize the business practices of Apple, Google, and Meta, which may violate the DMA rules on fair competition.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today, we&#39;ve opened five non-compliance investigations under the Digital Markets Act.</p>
<p>It concerns:<br />Alphabet’s rules on steering in Google Play <br />Alphabet’s self-preferencing on Google Search<br />Apple’s rules on steering in the App Store <br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f539.png" alt="🔹" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Apple&#39;s choice screen for Safari… <a href="https://t.co/kiZ7sLQa8B">pic.twitter.com/kiZ7sLQa8B</a></p>
<p>&mdash; European Commission (@EU_Commission) <a href="https://twitter.com/EU_Commission/status/1772207590212063397?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The investigation will examine Alphabet (Google&#8217;s parent company) and <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/02/28/eu-antitrust-regulators-target-apples-anti-steering-developer-restrictions-but-drop-in-app-purchases-case/">Apple&#8217;s restrictive “anti-steering” policies</a>. Under these rules, tech firms are forbidden from blocking businesses from providing cheaper purchase alternatives outside their app stores.</p>
<p>“Today, the Commission has opened non-compliance investigations under the Digital Markets Act (DMA) into Alphabet’s rules on steering in Google Play and self-preferencing on Google Search, Apple’s rules on steering in the App Store and the choice screen for Safari and Meta’s ‘pay or consent model,&#8221; the commission explained.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, an investigation has commenced into Apple&#8217;s user preference. This probe would confirm if Apple has fully allowed its users to uninstall its default apps and change default settings for services like web browsers on iOS devices.</p>
<p>Alphabet is also facing another non-compliance scrutiny over the claim that it abused dominance in its <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitfinder-next-generation-crypto-search-engine.htm">search engine recommendations</a> for users.</p>
<p>The inquiry is to ensure Google does not only recommend its specialized Google Shopping data to users over other comparable search results from competitors.</p>
<p>The final investigation would see the EU probe Meta’s “pay or consent” model for Facebook and Instagram. The policy requires users to either purchase a subscription for an ad-free experience or consent to data tracking on the free version.</p>
<h2>Rigorous Enforcement of the Digital Markets Act (DMA)</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The DMA was launched in November 2022 and fully took effect on March 7, 2024. It was created to allow fair competition in digital markets, which <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/big-tech-joins-hands-to-foster-the-creation-of-metaverse-standards.htm">big tech companies</a> have long dominated.</p>
<p>EU Commissioner for Competition Margrethe Vestager has disclosed that, despite the market law launch in 2022, tech firms &#8220;seem to be at odds with the DMA&#8217;s intent.&#8221;</p>
<p>She, however, warned that any company found culpable for violating the tech law would incur a potential fine of up to 10% of the company&#8217;s global revenue and 20% for repeated offenses.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Apple seems to be the first company to be fined for its anti-steering provisions by the EU.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/04/apple-hit-with-more-than-1point95-billion-eu-antitrust-fine-over-music-streaming.html">EU fined the iPhone maker $1.95 billion</a> earlier this month for restricting app developers from suggesting cheaper music subscription services to iOS users.</p>
<p>The company was also accused of offering “higher fees” and a less secure and unresponsive user experience. This even came earlier before the US Department of Justice <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-files-lawsuit-against-apple-over-unfair-rules-targeting-crypto-apps.htm">(DOJ) filed a lawsuit against Apple</a> on unfair rules targeting crypto apps.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Alphabet has insisted on operating in conformity with the digital regulations. This follows Alphabet Director of Competition <a href="https://www.pymnts.com/cpi_posts/google-addresses-criticism-over-changes-imposed-by-eu-tech-rules/">Oliver Bethell&#8217;s statement</a> that the tech company has made &#8220;significant changes&#8221; to its operations in Europe.</p>
<p>The EU investigation is expected to be completed within 12 months, which would give an insight into whether the tech giants have opened up the digital market for fair competition or made changes that best suit their operations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-launches-probe-tech-giants-over-digital-markets-act-violations.htm">EU Launches Probe into Tech Giants Apple, Google, Meta, and Amazon Over Digital Markets Act Violations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25191019/1711393819-1711381335585_processed.webp" length="80318" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senator Elizabeth Warren Criticizes Crypto, Claims It Threatens U.S. Security and &#8220;Helps Terrorists</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-criticizes-crypto-says-it-threatens-u-s-security.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julia Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pig butchering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188790</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) criticized North Korea’s crypto usage and the rise of crypto “pig butchering” scams at a Thursday hearing of the Senate of Armed Services, claiming that cryptocurrency as a whole poses “a threat to our national security.” Warren has long been openly anti-crypto, going so far as to push her Digital Assets Anti-Money Laundering Act (DAAMLA) once </span>more on Thursday ahead of Congress' two-week recess.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-criticizes-crypto-says-it-threatens-u-s-security.htm">Senator Elizabeth Warren Criticizes Crypto, Claims It Threatens U.S. Security and &#8220;Helps Terrorists</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) criticized North Korea’s crypto usage and the rise of crypto “pig butchering” scams at a Thursday hearing of the Senate of Armed Services, claiming that cryptocurrency as a whole poses “a threat to our national security.”</span></p>
<h2>Senator Elizabeth Warren Blasts Crypto, Calls Out North Korea</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Questioning </span><span>Admiral John C. Aquilino of the United States Indo-Pacific Command, <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/icymi-at-hearing-warren-warns-of-threats-posed-by-north-koreas-crypto-funded-weapons-program-and-pig-butchering-scams-to-national-security">Warren alleged</a> that North Korea could pay for over 56 intercontinental ballistic missiles with the $1.7 billion worth of crypto the country stole in 2022.</span></p>
<p><span>When asked by Warren if the number surprised him, Aquilino confessed it did not. </span></p>
<p><span>North Korea has long been known for its crypto malware groups, with state-sponsored hacking collective the <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy1933">Lazarus Group</a> and crypto mixer Sinbad sanctioned </span><span>by the U.S. Treasury Department’s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) in November 2023 </span><span>for illicit activities.</span></p>
<p><iframe title="At Hearing, Warren Warns of North Korea’s Crypto-Funded Weapons Program and Pig-Butchering Scams" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tXEWNIIwiTw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><span>“(Crypto) is helping rogue states,” said Warren. “It’s helping terrorists. It&#8217;s helping criminal organizations fund their operations on a scale like we have never seen before.”</span></p>
<p><span>However, blockchain intelligence firm </span><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-money-laundering-dropped-almost-30-in-2023-chainalysis.htm">Chainalysis’ 2024 Crypto Crime Report</a> found that funds sent to crypto mixers from illicit addresses decreased by nearly half a billion dollars last year “likely due to law enforcement and regulatory efforts.”</span></p>
<h2>Senate Hearing Address Pig Butchering Scams And More</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Warren’s criticism of crypto did not stop with North Korea, however. In her testimony Thursday, the senator claimed that </span><span>“more than 40,000 people in the United States lost more than $3.5 billion dollars in pig butchering crypto scams that we know of” in last year alone.</span></p>
<p><span>Common across southeast Asia, “pig butchering” involves perpetrators </span><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/cryptocurrency-scams.htm">exploiting a victim&#8217;s trust</a> in order to increase the amount of funds a given victim will send to them.</span></p>
<p><span>“Now, pig butchering is just one scam,” Warren continued. “There are many more. A recent study found that these criminal gangs have stolen and laundered more than $75 billion dollars in crypto in just the last four years.”</span></p>
<p>As Senator Elizabeth Warren criticizes crypto, not everyone may agree with her, but she paints a vivid picture of the far-reaching consequences of crypto-related crimes.</p>
<h2>Warren Pushes DAAMLA Yet Again</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Additionally, Senator Elizabeth Warren used the hearing to push her bipartisan bill known as the <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/warren-marshall-introduce-bipartisan-legislation-to-crack-down-on-cryptocurrency-money-laundering-financing-of-terrorists-and-rogue-nations">Digital Assets Anti-Money Laundering Act</a> (DAAMLA), which seeks to close loopholes in anti-terrorist funding while subjecting key players in the digital asset industry to tougher regulations.</span></p>
<p><span>“I&#8217;ve got a bipartisan bill, Republicans and Democrats, with 20 senators that would put a stop to it,” she said. “I think it is time to pass this bill.”</span></p>
<p>The senator&#8217;s comments come amidst increased conversations about <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/crypto-regulations/">cryptocurrency regulation</a> in light of last October&#8217;s terrorist attack in Israel that saw Hamas claim the lives of over 1200 Israelis.</p>
<p>As Senator Elizabeth Warren criticizes crypto and pushes for stronger oversight, she faces a formidable challenger in her upcoming senate race: pro-crypto Republican candidate John Deaton.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-criticizes-crypto-says-it-threatens-u-s-security.htm">Senator Elizabeth Warren Criticizes Crypto, Claims It Threatens U.S. Security and &#8220;Helps Terrorists</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25201015/1711397414-julia_63915_the_capitol_building_in_dc_with_cryptocurrencies_ou_fb6c6e8f-a1e4-4d77-9e68-6329d59aca1f-2.jpg" length="150091" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – wTAI, EPICBOTS, ISHI</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dexscreener-wtai-epicbots-ishi.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188801</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While blue-chip cryptos are pumping on Monday, with Bitcoin (BTC) pushing back above $70,000 and Ether (ETH) back in the $2,600s, traders looking for even faster gains continue to turn to the on-chain shitcoin markets in the hunt for top crypto gainers today.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dexscreener-wtai-epicbots-ishi.htm">Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – wTAI, EPICBOTS, ISHI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_186695" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186695" style="width: 738px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-186695" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/20231622/1710976582-screenshot-2024-03-20-181516.png" alt="Traders use platforms like DEXScreener to find the top crypto gainers today." width="738" height="415" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/20231622/1710976582-screenshot-2024-03-20-181516.png 738w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/20231622/1710976582-screenshot-2024-03-20-181516-300x169.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/20231622/1710976582-screenshot-2024-03-20-181516-150x84.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 738px) 100vw, 738px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-186695" class="wp-caption-text">Traders use platforms like DEXScreener to find the top crypto gainers today. Source: DEXScreener&#8217;s X Account</figcaption></figure>
<p>While blue-chip cryptos are pumping on Monday, with Bitcoin (BTC) pushing back above $70,000 and Ether (ETH) back in the $2,600s, traders looking for even faster gains continue to turn to the on-chain shitcoin markets in the hunt for top crypto gainers today.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and Ether are both up over 7% in the past 24 hours, as per <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">CoinMarketCap</a>. And while both could go a lot higher, some traders don’t want to wait 6-12 months for 2x gains.</p>
<p>Many would prefer to gamble on newly launched shitcoins that can potentially double their money in a few hours, or 10x their money in a day.</p>
<p>On-chain markets refer to the market for digital assets that have been issued directly on top of an existing blockchain.</p>
<p>For example, the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/price-predictions/shiba-inu-price-prediction/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) token</a> is issued on Ethereum as an ERC-20 token.</p>
<p>These tokens can then be traded on decentralized exchanges (<a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-decentralized-exchanges/">DEX</a>), and also perhaps on centralized exchanges if they get big enough.</p>
<p>They are often referred to as <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-meme-coins.htm">meme coin</a> (or shitcoin) markets and virtually anyone can issue a token at any time.</p>
<p>As a result, these <a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/cryptocurrency-scams.htm">on-chain markets are replete with scams</a> and pump-and-dump schemes.</p>
<p>But <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-shitcoins-buy/">shitcoin markets</a> are the only place to find tokens that can rally in the 50-100x region.</p>
<p>Here are a few of the top crypto gainers today on Ethereum that traders will be monitoring, as per <a href="https://dexscreener.com/">DEXScreener</a>.</p>
<h2>Top Crypto to Buy Today</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<h3><strong>Wrapped Trade AI (wTAI)</strong></h3>
<p>A just-launched shitcoin called Wrapped Trade AI (wTAI), which appears to be attempting to piggyback off of the gaining tokenization narrative, is pumping since its launch on Monday.</p>
<p>The token’s market cap was last around $7.4 million, with $330,000 in liquidity.</p>
<p>wTAI doesn’t appear to be a scam. But it could be a pump and dump designed to siphon money from speculators. That’s because it has a 20% buy tax and a 20% sell tax.</p>
<p>Traders need to make sure to always do their due diligence. That includes looking deeply into the legitimacy of a project before investing.</p>
<h3><strong>EPICBOTS ($EPICBOTS)</strong></h3>
<p>EPICBOTs, a supposed AI-infused Telegram bot protocol, is pumping hard on Monday. As per <a href="https://dexscreener.com/ethereum/0xb5d3ed5e7cf8d0f4000cef0ab80e96e066c0f8c8">DEXScreener</a>, it was last up 100% in 24 hours with a market cap of $3.4 million.</p>
<p>The token has $350,000 in locked liquidity, reducing rug pull risk.</p>
<p>But that doesn’t mean the token isn’t a scam. DEXScreener’s smart contract audit reveals four concerning aspects to the token’s contract.</p>
<p>These include a modifiable tax, a whitelist function and a 5% buy and sell tax.</p>
<h3><strong>Ishi ($ISHI)</strong></h3>
<p>A recently launched Shiba Inu-themed meme coin called Ishi ($ISHI) is making a comeback on Monday.</p>
<p>It was last up 30% in 24 hours, as per <a href="https://dexscreener.com/ethereum/0x048d3180ecf61b82f47078f6ebb3298326d70431">DEXScreener</a>, its market cap having recovered to around $2.1 million.</p>
<p>The token has $200,000 in locked liquidity, reducing rug pull risk. But the token has a modifiable tax, a blacklist and a whitelist.</p>
<p>It could easily be a scam token still. So potential investors must never risk more than they can afford to lose, and should do their due diligence.</p>
<h2><strong>Crypto Alternatives to Consider</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Investing in low-cap shitcoins is a very risky strategy.</p>
<p>An innocent-looking project could easily turn out to be a scam, and a few big sell orders could easily drive the price 80% lower.</p>
<p>A strategy that is still risky, but arguably has a better risk reward is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">getting involved in crypto presales</a>.</p>
<p>The idea is that investors secure tokens of up-and-coming, high-potential crypto projects/protocols at a discounted early price.</p>
<p>These projects then put those funds to work, paying for protocol development and marketing.</p>
<p>While lots can go wrong when investing in crypto presales—unforeseen circumstances can prevent a project from delivering on its vision—savvy presale investors routinely secure gains of 10x or more.</p>
<p>With hundreds of presale projects vying for investor funds, analysts at Cryptonews have been combing the market.</p>
<p>Here are 14 of the presale projects with the highest potential.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">See the 14 Cryptocurrencies</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dexscreener-wtai-epicbots-ishi.htm">Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – wTAI, EPICBOTS, ISHI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/20231622/1710976582-screenshot-2024-03-20-181516.png" length="73226" type="image/png" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Whales Bet on New Web3 VR Crypto – The Next Major Trend?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-bet-on-new-web3-vr-crypto-the-next-major-trend.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Hakki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5scape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5thscape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investors who want an early lead in Web3&#8217;s game-changing technological landscape are accumulating VR token 5thScape (5SCAPE) in the second stage of a presale that has so far raised $2.4 million. 5thScape is the world’s first virtual and augmented reality cryptocurrency gaming ecosystem, offering a wealth of immersive experiences with hyper-realistic gameplay. The $5SCAPE token that investors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-bet-on-new-web3-vr-crypto-the-next-major-trend.htm">Crypto Whales Bet on New Web3 VR Crypto – The Next Major Trend?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investors who want an early lead in Web3&#8217;s game-changing technological landscape are accumulating VR token 5thScape (5SCAPE) in the second stage of a presale that has so far raised $2.4 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cryptonews.com/ext/5thscape/en" rel="sponsored nofollow">5thScape</a><span> </span>is the world’s first virtual and augmented reality cryptocurrency gaming ecosystem, offering a wealth of immersive experiences with hyper-realistic gameplay.</p>
<p>The $5SCAPE token that investors are snapping up gives holders access to an exclusive selection of VR games, educational resources, and blockbuster movies.</p>
<p>One of the early standout titles is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/5th-scape-5scape-presale-picking-up-as-team-reveals-info-about-upcoming-vr-game.htm">Cage Conquest</a>, expected later this year. It&#8217;s a warts-and-all VR MMA fighting game where players can step in the ring to participate in strategic training sessions and online tournaments to earn crypto rewards.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Official Trailer: MMA Cage Conquest | Step into the Cage and Become a Champion" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SS3vuTOKrmg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>The ICO only began a few weeks ago and it has already taken in millions of dollars and tens of thousands of curious followers across social media, but what exactly is 5thScape?</p>
<h2>5thScape is a Pioneering VR and Web 3 Application</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span>Web 3 is a kind of singularity moment for its believers. That&#8217;s because it promises to unlock the full gamut of what crypto is capable of as web interfaces become more interactive and more transactions come on chain.</p>
<p>In industry that is itself an innovation, cryptocurrency projects that nurture and pioneer the development of blockchain’s utility potential ultimately have the most staying power.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s through the interaction, integration and intersections of blockchain, virtual and augmented realities, and AI that we find the Web 3&#8217;s full potential. A vision of the smart, responsive, decentralized internet that users interface with in three dimensions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5thScape, the cutting-edge crypto project poised to revolutionize augmented and virtual reality, offers investors an opportunity to dive into the future of immersive gaming. </p>
<p>With plans for innovative VR hardware and a diverse range of games, including Cage Conquest and Epic… <a href="https://t.co/FaIicOGq3w">pic.twitter.com/FaIicOGq3w</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 5th Scape (@5th_scape) <a href="https://twitter.com/5th_scape/status/1771437391716180079?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>If adoption is the endgame for every player, then Web 3 is the promised land. Now, we already have a small and developing corner of Web 3: the metaverse.</p>
<p>While a fully virtual and augmented reality metaverse is still a long way away—current popular metaverse titles like Axie Infinity and The Sandbox are closer to conventional video games—5thScape drags the metaverse out of the future and into the present day.</p>
<p>As a tokenized gaming platform, 5thScape is already at the forefront of the metaverse.</p>
<p>Participation is easy, gamers simply buy and hold tokens to get access to the platform, where they will be able to game and stream for free.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the project team took development back to first principles and designed all the software and hardware in-house.</p>
<h2>Unpacking 5thScape&#8217;s (5SCAPE) Upside Potential</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span></span>5SCAPE has a market capitalization of $15 million and is currently priced at<span> </span><span>$</span><span>0.00215, although this is due to rise 15% to $0.00248 when the third round begins soon.</span></p>
<p><span>The team has allocated eighty percent of the total token supply for the ongoing presale.</span></p>
<p><span>When it ends, 5SCAPE’s fixed listing price will be $0.01, giving the token a possible prelaunch upside potential of over 365%. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Exciting news from 5th Scape! The VR-focused cryptocurrency has raised $1.7 million in its presale phase, and has showcased the potential for innovation in the digital space. </p>
<p>Get ready to explore hyper-realistic experiences and next-gen gaming with 5th Scape&#39;s groundbreaking… <a href="https://t.co/5DrCHwVm77">pic.twitter.com/5DrCHwVm77</a></p>
<p>&mdash; 5th Scape (@5th_scape) <a href="https://twitter.com/5th_scape/status/1770721210449412167?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The 5thScape platform and its native 5SCAPE token are fully audited, with KYC compliance. The team behind it are<span> also </span><a href="https://docs.5thscape.com/team">transparent</a>.</p>
<p>Join the community over on the project’s social channels can stay informed of tasks to claim even more 5SCAPE rewards before the protocol launches.</p>
<p>5thScape has already clocked tens of thousands of followers for a social media presence spread across on<span> </span><a href="https://discord.com/invite/5thscape"><span>Discord</span></a><span>, </span><a href="https://t.me/fifthScape"><span>Telegram</span></a><span>, </span><a href="https://twitter.com/5th_scape"><span>X/Twitter</span></a><span> and </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@5thScape"><span>YouTube</span></a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/5thscape" rel="sponsored nofollow"><strong>Interested? Buy 5thScape Here</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-bet-on-new-web3-vr-crypto-the-next-major-trend.htm">Crypto Whales Bet on New Web3 VR Crypto – The Next Major Trend?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25153753/1711381073-1711380808514_processed.jpg" length="57089" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert Kiyosaki Recommends Buying One-Tenth Of A Bitcoin, Backs Michael Saylor</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/robert-kiyosaki-recommends-bitcoin-backs-michael-saylor.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>Famed 'Rich Dad Poor Dad' author Robert Kiyosaki doubles down on Bitcoin, plans to buy more ahead of April's halving event. He anticipates a price surge to $100K by September, driven by dollar weakness. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/robert-kiyosaki-recommends-bitcoin-backs-michael-saylor.htm">Robert Kiyosaki Recommends Buying One-Tenth Of A Bitcoin, Backs Michael Saylor</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>Bestselling author of &#8216;Rich Dad Poor Dad,&#8217; Robert Kiyosaki, urged followers on Monday to purchase Bitcoin (BTC) ahead of the April halving event.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1772115533502259692">In a post to Twitter</a>, the author promised to buy 10 more BTC before the start of April due to his conviction around the event, which will cut the rate at which new BTC is produced in half.</p>
<h2>Get Bitcoin While You Can, Says Robert Kiyosaki</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
“If you can’t afford a whole Bitcoin, you may want to consider buying 1/10 of a coin, via the new ETFs or Satoshi’s,” wrote Kiyosaki. “If the Bitcoin process works as designed you may own a whole Bitcoin by the end of this year.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I am buying 10 more Bitcoin before April. Why?  The “Having.” If you can’t afford a whole Bitcoin  you may want to consider buying 1/10 of a coin, via the new ETFs or Satoshi’s.</p>
<p>If the Bitcoin process works as designed you may own a whole Bitcoin by the end of this year. </p>
<p>I…</p>
<p>&mdash; Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1772115533502259692?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Bitcoin’s price surged by over 3.5% to $69,700 on Monday, carrying momentum from its weekend rebound from below $64,000. This followed a massive pullback for the cryptocurrency over the last two weeks as Bitcoin spot ETFs – which have proven remarkably successful since launching in January – suffered <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-lose-326-million-in-largest-daily-outflow-since-launch.htm">unusually large outflows</a> of over $800 million last week.</p>
<p>Kiyosaki said he expects Bitcoin to reach $100,000 by September – not merely because of the ETFs, but because of the weakness of the US dollar. In that spirit, he recommended silver coins and gold as the next best buys for those who are “not into Bitcoin.”</p>
<p>“The ‘smart money’ knows the US is the biggest debtor nation in the world,” he said, citing high consumer and small business debt, domestic bank troubles, and a world “on the brink of war.”</p>
<h2>Stay Away From Cash</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Bitcoin is often compared to precious metals by proponents who view its limited supply of 21 million coins as a defense against the debasement of the US dollar, whose increasing supply devalues the currency against more scarce assets over time.</p>
<p>Kiyosaki echoed the words of MicroStrategy executive chairman <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-is-not-currency-but-still-plans-to-hodl-for-100-years.htm">Michael Saylor</a>, who said in a recent interview that those who save in cash or fiat currency are best labeled as “poor.”</p>
<p>“Please start acquiring gold, silver, Bitcoin, if you already have not started,” said Kiyosaki. “Please don’t be a poor person saving fake money.”</p>
<p>According to blockchain data, there are currently over 4.5 million Bitcoin addresses holding over 0.1 BTC, as Kiyosaki recommends. That said, one investor can store their holdings across multiple Bitcoin addresses, and one address could represent the holdings of thousands or millions of investors (ex. Binance’s Bitcoin address).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/robert-kiyosaki-recommends-bitcoin-backs-michael-saylor.htm">Robert Kiyosaki Recommends Buying One-Tenth Of A Bitcoin, Backs Michael Saylor</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/1708326452-1708326415236_processed.jpg" length="77392" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles as Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Takes Effect</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/philippines-to-block-binance-exchange-amid-regulatory-concerns.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philippines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>The Philippines SEC's Ban on Binance prohibits local access to the exchange's website and applications. This decision stems from Binance's alleged unlicensed operations and offering of investment opportunities to Filipinos.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/philippines-to-block-binance-exchange-amid-regulatory-concerns.htm">Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles as Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Takes Effect</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Philippines Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has revealed its plan to block local access to Binance, effectively implementing the Philippines SEC&#8217;s ban on Binance. This was contained in a notice published by the financial regulator on March 25.</p>
<p>This decision follows the SEC’s accusation of the exchange&#8217;s continuous offering of various investment and trading opportunities to Filipinos without obtaining the necessary license from the commission.</p>
<h2>Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Urges Google &amp; Meta to Restrict Binance-related Adverts</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/pr-2024/sec-proceeds-with-blocking-of-binance/#gsc.tab=0">According to the published media briefing</a>, the Philippines SEC had previously filed a formal request to the National Telecommunication Commission (NTC) on March 12, 2024, to block access to the Binance website, applications, and other web pages used by the exchange.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">JUST IN : The Philippine SEC stated that it will continue to block Binance and block citizens’ access to Binance’s main website and related platforms, saying that Binance is a threat to the security of the Philippines.</p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto News Updates (@CryptoNewsUpd8s) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoNewsUpd8s/status/1772226888674463920?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The commission has now deepened its ban on Binance by requesting Google and Meta to block all marketing campaigns related to the crypto exchange in the Philippines.</p>
<p>As stated by the SEC, all previous campaigns and trade offerings were done illegally as the exchange is yet to secure a license from its agency to solicit investment or create/operate an exchange as required by <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/377527899/REPUBLIC-ACT-NO-8799-THE-SECURITIES-REGULATION-CODE">Republic Act No. 8799</a> or the <a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/2019Legislation_RA-8799-Securities-Regulation-Code-2000.pdf">Securities Regulation Code (SRC)</a>.</p>
<p>The regulatory agency had, however, informed residents that the crypto exchange is not authorized to sell or offer securities in the Philippines while also stating that Binance&#8217;s continuous crypto promotions may have criminal liability.</p>
<p>The notice read,</p>
<blockquote><p>“Those who act as salesmen, brokers, dealers or agents, representatives, promoters, recruiters, influencers, endorsers, and enablers of Binance in selling or convincing people to invest in its platform within the Philippines, even through online means, may be held criminally liable under Section 28 of the SRC.”</p></blockquote>
<p>This ban is expected to be effective within a three-month period – providing ample time for Filipino traders to close their investment positions held on Binance.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the SEC Chair Emilio B. Aquino has reiterated that the regulatory body believes that Filipinos&#8217; continuous access to Binance websites and associated mobile applications &#8220;poses a threat to the security of the funds of investing Filipinos.&#8221;</p>
<p><span>It should be noted this latest move by the Philippines SEC came after <a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023Advisory-against-Binance.pdf">issuing a </a></span><a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023Advisory-against-Binance.pdf"><span>warning notice </span></a><span><a href="https://www.sec.gov.ph/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/2023Advisory-against-Binance.pdf">to Binance</a> on November 28, 2023. </span></p>
<p>The Philippines SEC&#8217;s ban on Binance serves as a clear warning to other unregulated exchanges operating within the country, underlining the importance of compliance with local securities laws.</p>
<h2>Binance Regulatory Blows Continue</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The Philippines SEC&#8217;s ban on Binance is not an isolated incident, as the exchange has faced increasing regulatory scrutiny worldwide.</p>
<p>In 2023, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) filed charges against Binance for allegedly operating an illegal digital asset derivatives exchange and evading federal laws.</p>
<p>Similarly, the US Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101">charged Binance Holdings LTD and ex-CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ)</a> for allegedly operating unregistered exchanges, broker exchanges, clearing houses, and the unregistered offer and sale of securities.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/binance-and-ceo-plead-guilty-federal-charges-4b-resolution">Binance and CZ pleaded guilty to a range of federal charges</a>, including anti-money laundering violations and unlicensed money transmission, on November 21, 2023. This was after a series of investigations by the SEC, the US Department of Justice (DOJ), and the CFTC.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/changpeng-cz-zhao-steps-down-from-binance-us-board-of-directors.htm">CZ later resigned as the CEO of Binance</a>, which was part of the agreement with the DOJ.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> CEO CZ Steps Down as CEO<br />As Part Of $4 Billion Settlement With US <a href="https://t.co/63nqhU1dPh">pic.twitter.com/63nqhU1dPh</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ahmed CEO (@Ahmedxmtj) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ahmedxmtj/status/1727066068202762664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8837-23">CFTC announced on December 18, 2023</a>, that the US District Court for the Northern District of Illinois ordered CZ to pay $150 million, and the exchange ruled to pay $2.7 billion to conclude enforcement action.</p>
<p>At press time, CZ is free on a $175 million release bond but awaits court sentence in reaction to his role in Binance money laundering charges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/philippines-to-block-binance-exchange-amid-regulatory-concerns.htm">Binance Faces Regulatory Hurdles as Philippines SEC&#8217;s Ban on Binance Takes Effect</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25165842/1711385922-1711380765008_processed.webp" length="41810" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Crypto to Buy Today March 25 – Arweave, Internet Computer, Dogwifhat</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-25-arweave-internet-computer-dogwifhat.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Best Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As crypto prices pick up on Monday and Bitcoin (BTC) pushes back to the north of $70,000, investors are hunting feverishly for the best crypto to buy today to secure quick gains.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-25-arweave-internet-computer-dogwifhat.htm">Best Crypto to Buy Today March 25 – Arweave, Internet Computer, Dogwifhat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>As crypto prices pick up on Monday and Bitcoin (BTC) pushes back to the north of $70,000, investors are hunting feverishly for the best crypto to buy today to secure quick gains.</span>For investors taking their first steps into the market, Bitcoin is certainly a candidate for <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-crypto-to-buy/">best crypto to buy today</a>.</p>
<p>BTC is likely to soon retake its all-time highs thanks to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/great-central-bank-policy-reversal-kicks-off-2024-03-22/">optimism surrounding central bank easing</a>. Sell pressure from GBTC may also be easing, meaning spot Bitcoin ETFs could become a tailwind once again.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-halving/">With the halving just around the corner</a>, Bitcoin remains odds on to test $100,000 at some point this year.</p>
<p>That means possible 40% gains from current levels.</p>
<p>But many crypto investors have already built up sizeable exposure to major blue-chip cryptos like Bitcoin.</p>
<p>They may instead be looking to up their risk and gain exposure to assets with 5-10x potential.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/best-altcoins.htm">Here are some altcoins with strong bullish momentum</a> that could be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h2><strong>Best Crypto to Buy Today</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<h3><strong>Arweave (AR)</strong></h3>
<p>Decentralized storage network (DSN) Arweave’s native token AR has pumped a considerable 20% on Monday, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/arweave/">as per CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Last at $43, AR is eyeing a near-term retest of its all-time highs around $48. A retest of all-time highs above $90 is also on the cards for 2024.</p>
<p>Its modest market cap of still under $3 billion suggests plenty of upside room for the crypto. The prospect of 3-4x gains makes AR one of the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h3><strong>Internet Computer (ICP)</strong></h3>
<p>Up nearly 20% in 24 hours, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/internet-computer/">Internet Computer (ICP)</a> is one of the best-performing cryptos on Monday.</p>
<p>Last at $17, ICP is attempting to break convincingly out of its multi-week $10-16 range.</p>
<p>But ICP is still down over 96% down from its record peaks from 2021 around $350.</p>
<p>Its modest market cap of currently under $8 billion suggests there is plenty of room for growth.</p>
<p>ICP may not hit its 2021 highs soon, but 10x gains are certainly on the cards. That means it could easily be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h3><strong>Dogwifhat (WIF)</strong></h3>
<p>Dogwifhat (WIF) is leading the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-meme-coins.htm">meme coin market</a> on Monday, up 18% in the past 24 hours <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/dogwifhat/">as per CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Last at $2.80, WIF is eyeing a retest of its all-time highs above $3.50. WIF’s market cap was last $2.8 billion.</p>
<p>With Dogecoin’s market cap last around $24 billion, WIF could have a lot higher yet to run.</p>
<p>The prospect of 10x gains from here ranks WIF as potentially the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h2><strong>Crypto Alternatives to Consider</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
All of the above coins offer potential investors a great chance to make 10x gains.</p>
<p>But, for those looking for a better probability of near-term gains, an alternative high-risk, high-reward investment strategy to consider is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">getting involved in crypto presales</a>.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Top 3 Pre-Sales You Need to Jump on NOW! &#x1f4b0;" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c2ZI1XD9Pq0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>This is where investors buy the tokens of upstart crypto projects to help fund their development.</p>
<p>These tokens are nearly always sold cheaply, and there is a long history of presales delivering huge exponential gains to early investors.</p>
<p>Many of these projects have fantastic teams behind them and a great vision to deliver a one-of-a-kind crypto application/platform.</p>
<p>The team at Cryptonews.com spends a lot of time combing through presale projects to help out investors.</p>
<p>Here is a list of what the team deems as the best crypto presales of 2024.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">See the 13 Cryptocurrencies</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-25-arweave-internet-computer-dogwifhat.htm">Best Crypto to Buy Today March 25 – Arweave, Internet Computer, Dogwifhat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1704831868-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__2__720.jpg" length="65337" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trial Against Terraform Labs And Do Kwon Begins In NYC Following Prison Release</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/trial-against-terraform-labs-and-do-kwon-begins-in-nyc-following-prison-release.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julia Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Luna]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188699</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) trial against Terraform Labs founder Do Kwon is set to begin in New York on Monday. As jury selection gets underway, the trial formally marks the beginning of the United States' quest for justice against Kwon following the collapse of Terra which saw over $40 billion of market value erased.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trial-against-terraform-labs-and-do-kwon-begins-in-nyc-following-prison-release.htm">Trial Against Terraform Labs And Do Kwon Begins In NYC Following Prison Release</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) trial against Terraform Labs founder Do Kwon is set to begin in Manhattan federal court Monday, though the former crypto tycoon will not be present.</span></p>
<h2>Jury Selection Underway For Kwon&#8217;s SEC Trial In NYC</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The landmark civil trial stems from the SEC’s original complaint against Kwon in February 2023 over the dramatic May 2022 collapse of Terraform Labs’ TerraUSD “stablecoin,” which led to the loss of over $40 billion in market value.</span></p>
<p><span>“As alleged in our complaint, the Terraform ecosystem was neither decentralized, nor finance,” Director of the SEC’s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-32">said in a statement at the time</a>. “It was simply a fraud propped up by a so-called algorithmic “stablecoin” – the price of which was controlled by the defendants, not any code.”</span></p>
<p><span>Kwon stands accused of violating the registration and anti-fraud provisions of the Securities Act and the Exchange Act. Despite the high-profile nature of the crime, civil trials typically result in hefty monetary fees or injunctions as opposed to actual prison time for convicted defendants.</span></p>
<h2>U.S. And South Korea Locked Into Legal Battle For Kwon</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The start of Monday’s trial comes on the heels of Kwon’s Saturday release from a Montenegrin prison as the Balkan country’s Supreme Court debates his extradition location.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">DO KWON PLACED IN &quot;RECEPTION CENTER&quot; IN MONTENEGRO AFTER PRISON RELEASE</p>
<p>Kwon was reportedly interrogated by a local inspector for five hours before being moved to the camp. He is expected to remain guarded in the facility until the local court makes a new decision on his… <a href="https://t.co/c921NzFrMl">pic.twitter.com/c921NzFrMl</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Mario Nawfal’s Roundtable (@RoundtableSpace) <a href="https://twitter.com/RoundtableSpace/status/1772185451455234318?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>Both the U.S. and Kwon’s native South Korea have been battling for his extradition, causing numerous </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwons-appeal-in-document-forgery-case-rejected-by-montenegro-high-court.htm"><span>international legal hurdles</span></a><span> regarding the crypto fugitive’s fate.</span></p>
<p><span>South Korea originally issued an arrest warrant for Kwon in September 2022 for violating the country’s national markets law, prompting a nearly year-long manhunt for the founder of Terraform Labs across Europe and Asia.</span></p>
<p><span>Kwon was finally detained in Montenegro in March 2023 for attempting to use a fake Costa Rican passport to fly to Dubai following multiple attempts to track him down, including an Interpol red notice for his arrest.</span></p>
<p><span>He was ordered to serve four months in Montenegro’s </span><span>Spuž Prison on document forgery charges. </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwon-released-from-prison-with-extradition-verdict-underway.htm"><span>Following his release</span></a><span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/do-kwon-released-from-prison-with-extradition-verdict-underway.htm"> over the weekend</a>, officials barred Kwon’s passport from being used in hopes of preventing him from fleeing the country.</span></p>
<h2>Terra Collapse Was A Tipping Point For Crypto</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The collapse of Terra is regarded by many to have caused major damage to the cryptocurrency ecosystem, with </span><span>blockchain analytics firm Nansen </span><span>alleging the <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/research/blockchain-analysis-the-collapse-of-alameda-and-ftx">collapse set off crypto exchange FTX’s ultimate demise</a>.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4a5.png" alt="💥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> GM CryptoX &#8211; 2 x important dates for the bad boys of crypto </p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f538.png" alt="🔸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Today is the start of Do Kwons US <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SEC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SEC</a> trial<br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f538.png" alt="🔸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Thursday sees the sentencing of former <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FTX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FTX</a> CEO <br /> Sam Bankman Fried <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SBF?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SBF</a> <a href="https://t.co/XhJ0Mv3Rvb">pic.twitter.com/XhJ0Mv3Rvb</a></p>
<p>&mdash; RR2Capital (@RR2Capital) <a href="https://twitter.com/RR2Capital/status/1772188235499782261?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>FTX founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, is expected back in Manhattan federal court later this week to be sentenced following his <a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/disgraced-former-ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-friend-found-guilty-on-all-seven-fraud-charges.htm">November 2023 crypto fraud conviction</a>.</span></p>
<p><span>It is currently unclear when Kwon’s extradition will be, much less where.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trial-against-terraform-labs-and-do-kwon-begins-in-nyc-following-prison-release.htm">Trial Against Terraform Labs And Do Kwon Begins In NYC Following Prison Release</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25162612/1711383971-julia_63915_give_me_a_court_briefing_with_cryptocurrencies_6258ada2-042b-4f9f-9a44-1251ed7482e4-2.jpg" length="112514" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is It Too Late to Buy Internet Computer? ICP Price Up 20%, Bitcoin Rival Secures $8.8M Funding</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/is-it-too-late-to-buy-internet-computer-icp-price-up-20-bitcoin-rival-secures-8-8m-funding.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Hakki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Green Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ICP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Computer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The price of Internet Computer (ICP) has shot up 20% in the last 24 hours as the token underpinning the blockchain-based computing ecosystem far outpaces market leaders Bitcoin and Ethereum today. Crypto prices are broadly rallying across the spectrum right now. Market leader Bitcoin (BTC) grew 2.6% in the last 24 hours to trade at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/is-it-too-late-to-buy-internet-computer-icp-price-up-20-bitcoin-rival-secures-8-8m-funding.htm">Is It Too Late to Buy Internet Computer? ICP Price Up 20%, Bitcoin Rival Secures $8.8M Funding</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Internet Computer (ICP) has shot up 20% in the last 24 hours as the token underpinning the blockchain-based computing ecosystem far outpaces market leaders Bitcoin and Ethereum today.</p>
<p>Crypto prices are broadly rallying across the spectrum right now. Market leader Bitcoin (BTC) grew 2.6% in the last 24 hours to trade at <span>$66,842, while its nearest contender Ethereum (ETH) </span> grew 1.8% to trade at <span>$3,441 as of this writing, according to CoinGecko <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/">data</a>. </span></p>
<p>Today, ICP is the clear leader of the top 25 biggest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, though. No other leading cryptocurrency came close in terms of gains, except NEAR Protocol (NEAR) and Toncoin (TON), which both grew by a little over 10% overnight.</p>
<p>The value added by ICP&#8217;s rally led to the token flipping NEAR for 21st place in the early hours of the morning GMT.</p>
<p>The only other cryptocurrency project enjoying a marked surge in the top 100 right now is Solana-based meme coin DogWifHat (WIF) which ballooned a blistering 21.7% to trade at $2.74.</p>
<p>ICP is a b<span>lockchain protocol that offers an alternative </span></p>
<p><span> The Internet Computer attempts to offer a decentralized alternative to the centralized cloud-based data centres powering popular web applications currently. Its easy interface means anyone can create and deploy a dApp on ICP&#8217;s public blockchain. </span></p>
<p>ICP&#8217;s trading chart reflects a bumpier February than many other cryptocurrencies. In March, ICP joined the market-wide rally, but it began to depreciate a fortnight into March and posted heavy losses by Wednesday as it bottomed out at $11. With a Relative Strength Index (RSI) of 73, ICP is currently overbought, so an imminent correction is likely to occur.</p>
<figure id="attachment_188477" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188477" style="width: 1006px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188477" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25120633/1711368393-icpusd_2024-03-25_12-01-20.png" alt="" width="1006" height="643" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25120633/1711368393-icpusd_2024-03-25_12-01-20.png 1006w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25120633/1711368393-icpusd_2024-03-25_12-01-20-300x192.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25120633/1711368393-icpusd_2024-03-25_12-01-20-768x491.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25120633/1711368393-icpusd_2024-03-25_12-01-20-150x96.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1006px) 100vw, 1006px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188477" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Is Green Bitcoin The Hottest Altcoin After ICP</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The Internet Computer Protocol is about more than a token, it&#8217;s an ecosystem that taps blockchain to unlock a fountain of new Web 3 innovations.</p>
<p>As such, the ICP token checks all the right boxes for a potentially very smart crypto investment for any blockchain acolyte. It is easier to argue the case for ICP still being here in a decade than it is for raw meme coins like DOGE, PEPE and WIF.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin" rel="sponsored nofollow">Green Bitcoin (GBTC)</a><span> is another alt coin project that is raking in the money from excited early speculators. It has </span>just raised $8.8 million in just over two weeks of its presale.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">With Decentralized and Centralized exchange listings not far away, the momentum Green Bitcoin is generating is getting intense.</p>
<p>We love the movement! <a href="https://t.co/QeOhyUA35f">pic.twitter.com/QeOhyUA35f</a></p>
<p>&mdash; GreenBitcoin (@GreenBTCtoken) <a href="https://twitter.com/GreenBTCtoken/status/1771637913387958733?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>GBTC has a hardcap of 21 million, a clear nod to its inspiration, Bitcoin. Limiting the number of tokens in circulation creates value through scarcity.</p>
<p>However, GBTC’s use of Ethereum’s proof-of-stake (PoS) blockchain over Bitcoin’s less energy-efficient proof-of-work mechanism makes it cleaner and greener than its inspiration.</p>
<p>Green Bitcoin touts itself as a “gamified green staking” project. Essentially, token holders participate through the staking platform, where they earn GBTC rewards by predicting Bitcoin price trends.</p>
<p>Holders can stake tokens for up to six months to earn even bigger rewards. Staking is a fundamental part of Green Bitcoin’s tokenomics. By reducing GBTC’s circulating supply, staking helps drive the price over the long term.</p>
<p>Anyone can get involved by visiting <a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin" rel="sponsored nofollow">the official Green Bitcoin website</a> and connecting a crypto wallet.</p>
<p>1 GBTC presently costs $1.1062, with the price due to rise in a little over six days.</p>
<p>There are still a few weeks left of the presale, and the token could rally sharply by the time it’s listed on major exchanges.</p>
<p><strong>Get in early and<span> </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin" rel="sponsored nofollow">Buy Green Bitcoin Now</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/is-it-too-late-to-buy-internet-computer-icp-price-up-20-bitcoin-rival-secures-8-8m-funding.htm">Is It Too Late to Buy Internet Computer? ICP Price Up 20%, Bitcoin Rival Secures $8.8M Funding</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25165806/1711385886-1711385856233_processed.jpg" length="264804" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Regulator Issues Alert Against Suspicious Crypto Platform HKCEXP</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-regulator-issues-alert-against-suspicious-crypto-platform-hkcexp.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HKCEXP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SFC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Securities and Futures Commission of Hong Kong (SFC) has issued a warning regarding HKCEXP, an allegedly suspicious trading platform claiming to be registered with the regulator.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-regulator-issues-alert-against-suspicious-crypto-platform-hkcexp.htm">Hong Kong Regulator Issues Alert Against Suspicious Crypto Platform HKCEXP</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Securities and Futures Commission of Hong Kong (SFC) has issued a warning regarding HKCEXP, an allegedly suspicious crypto trading platform claiming to be registered with the regulator.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">HKCEXP allegedly warned as it lured investors by falsely claiming to be an &#8220;SFC-registered business.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SFC warns investors of HKCEXP</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">In June 2023, Hong Kong officially started its crypto licensing regime for virtual asset trading platforms, allowing licensed exchanges to offer retail trading services.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SFC said in February that investors should only trade on licensed trading platforms. The regulator had </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-ends-crypto-exchange-license-applications-noncompliant-platforms-to-close-by-may-31.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">set a deadline of February 29</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for crypto exchanges to apply for operational licenses. Exchanges failing to submit their applications were required </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">to cease operations in Hong Kong by May 31</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SFC advised investors to act swiftly if they trade on platforms that do not appear on either the &#8220;list of licensed virtual asset trading platforms&#8221; or the &#8220;list of virtual asset trading platform applicants.&#8221; The regulator urged these investors to &#8220;make preparations early,&#8221; such as by closing their accounts. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Among the 22 crypto trading platforms that applied for licenses, four had previously opted into the SFC&#8217;s regulatory framework for crypto trading platforms.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_188696" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188696" style="width: 1870px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-188696 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407.png" alt="" width="1870" height="627" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407.png 1870w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407-300x101.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407-1024x343.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407-768x258.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407-1536x515.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160442/1711382682-screenshot-2024-03-25-170407-150x50.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1870px) 100vw, 1870px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188696" class="wp-caption-text">Hong Kong SFC Adds HKCEXP to its list of suspicious crypto exchanges.</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the SFC&#8217;s efforts to disseminate information, Hong Kong continues to be faced with fake entities posing as legitimate crypto exchanges. The regulator <a href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/alert-list/suspicious-virtual-asset-trading-platforms">warns of HKCEXP,</a> the latest crypto exchange falsely claiming to be registered with the regulator.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SFC accused <a href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/alert-list/3018">HKCEXP of providing a fraudulent Hong Kong address</a> for registration. Additionally, one Hong Kong citizen who had used the platform reported to the SFC that the exchange imposed excessive fees for fund withdrawals.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SFC will maintain a public list of licensed crypto platforms to promote safe crypto trading. The SFC stated that any exchange that fails to apply for licensing faces restrictions on operations and marketing activities in Hong Kong.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Major Crypto Exchanges Apply for Licensing in Hong Kong as Regulators Crack Down</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the SFC, 22 exchanges </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/Welcome-to-the-Fintech-Contact-Point/Virtual-assets/Virtual-asset-trading-platforms-operators/Lists-of-virtual-asset-trading-platforms" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">have submitted applications</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> before the February 29 deadline. Among these applicants are prominent names in the crypto industry, such as OKX, Bybit, Bullish, Crypto.com, Huobi HK, Matrixport HK, and Gate.HK. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The HKVAEX crypto platform, reportedly associated with Binance, has also submitted its application for consideration. The Hong Kong SFC has already granted licenses to two platforms — namely </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchange-hashkey-operator-raises-100m.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">HashKey Exchange</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in November 2022 and OSL Digital Securities, getting the nod a month later in December 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Once licensed by the Hong Kong SFC, crypto exchanges can onboard retail investors to trade Bitcoin and Ether. The SFC is currently reviewing various altcoins and stablecoins for trading approval.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On February 23, BitForex, an exchange, went offline after $57 million was reportedly withdrawn from the exchange&#8217;s hot wallets. Last year, Japanese regulators flagged BitForex for operating without proper registration.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite being purportedly headquartered in the region, the SFC also flagged BitForex for lacking a license to operate a Virtual Asset Trading Platform (VATP) in Hong Kong. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange&#8217;s users on its official Telegram channel have reported various account issues, including login difficulties and missing asset information on the dashboard. Some users also shared pop-up screens indicating they were blocked from accessing the company&#8217;s website. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SFC advises investors to verify trading platforms using </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://apps.sfc.hk/publicregWeb/searchByName?locale=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">its public register</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> of licensed persons and institutions and the list of licensed virtual asset trading platforms to access relevant information about licensed entities, including their official websites.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-regulator-issues-alert-against-suspicious-crypto-platform-hkcexp.htm">Hong Kong Regulator Issues Alert Against Suspicious Crypto Platform HKCEXP</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25161947/1711383587-1711383570821_processed.jpg" length="142293" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Asset Investment Products See Record Outflows of $942M After 7-Week Inflow Streak</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-asset-investment-products-see-record-outflows-of-942m-after-7-week-inflow-streak.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ruholamin Haqshanas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Asset]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot ETFs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Digital asset investment products experienced a record outflow of $942 million from March 16 to 22, marking the end of a seven-week streak of substantial inflows totaling $12.3 billion. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-asset-investment-products-see-record-outflows-of-942m-after-7-week-inflow-streak.htm">Digital Asset Investment Products See Record Outflows of $942M After 7-Week Inflow Streak</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Digital asset investment products experienced a record outflow of $942 million from March 16 to 22, marking the end of a seven-week streak of substantial inflows totaling $12.3 billion. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-175-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6af2a10c0b30" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report from CoinShares</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, trade turnover amounted to $28 billion, following a record-breaking $43 billion the previous week.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The primary driver behind this negative shift was the outflows from Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC (Grayscale Bitcoin Trust), which amounted to $2 billion, surpassing the net inflows into its competitors by $1.1 billion. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Consequently, the market witnessed a significant withdrawal of $904 million from Bitcoin (BTC)-related investment instruments, a stark contrast to the highest-ever influx of $2.86 billion the previous week.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Total Volume of Crypto AUM Decrease by $10 Billion</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">As a result of the outflows and the price retracement, the total volume of digital assets under management decreased by $10 billion, settling at $88.2 billion. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Just a week prior, this metric had surpassed the $100 billion mark. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, clients withdrew $3.7 million from structures enabling short positions on BTC, following the previous week&#8217;s peak investment of $26 million since the beginning of the year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We believe the recent price correction led to hesitancy from investors, leading to much lower inflows into new ETF issuers in the US, which saw US$1.1bn inflows, partially offsetting incumbent Grayscale’s significant US$2bn outflows last week,&#8221; CoinShares wrote. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Digital asset investment products experienced a weekly outflow of $942 million, ending a 7-week streak of inflows up to $12.3 billion. </p>
<p>ETF issuers in the US managed to gather $1.1 billion in inflows, which helped to mitigate the impact of Grayscale’s $2 billion outflows <a href="https://t.co/eKSBE1mEv6">pic.twitter.com/eKSBE1mEv6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Satoshi Club (@esatoshiclub) <a href="https://twitter.com/esatoshiclub/status/1772226751860441520?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In Ethereum (ETH) funds, outflows increased from $13.9 million to $34.2 million. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similarly, investors withdrew $5.6 million and $3.7 million from instruments based on Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA), respectively. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, products tied to Polkadot (DOT), Avalanche (AVA), and Litecoin (LTC) experienced inflows of $5 million, $2.9 million, and $2 million, respectively.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that just a week earlier, cryptocurrency investment products had witnessed a substantial inflow of $2.92 billion, following $2.69 billion in the previous reporting period. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thus, the total inflow for the year reached an impressive $13.2 billion, surpassing the entire 2021 figure of $10.6 billion.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin ETFs See Four Consecutive Days of Outflows</span></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Last Thursday, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust’s (GBTC) ETF experienced another day of significant outflows, with nearly $359 million exiting the fund.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This followed a week of substantial outflows, with March 18 witnessing the largest </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gbtc-sees-643m-outflow-as-bitcoin-drops-below-65k.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">single-day outflow of $642 million</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, according to data from Farside Investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The figures brought the total outflows for GBTC last week to $1.8 billion, marking the </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spot-bitcoin-etfs-see-fourth-consecutive-day-of-net-outflows.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">fourth consecutive day of net outflows</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> across all 10 Bitcoin ETFs.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the recent slide in Bitcoin prices, investment firm Bernstein has raised its year-end forecast for the cryptocurrency. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.investors.com/news/bitcoin-price-target-90000-crypto-miner-outlooks-bernstein/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">research note</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Bernstein revised its price target for bitcoin to $90,000, up from the previous projection of $80,000. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm also expressed optimism about cryptocurrency mining stocks, citing Bitcoin’s rise to around $74,000 and the positive response to new spot BTC ETFs.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-asset-investment-products-see-record-outflows-of-942m-after-7-week-inflow-streak.htm">Digital Asset Investment Products See Record Outflows of $942M After 7-Week Inflow Streak</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25163455/1711384495-1711384435289_processed.jpg" length="161114" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What’s Happening In Crypto Today? Daily Crypto News Digest</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-news-today.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sead Fadilpašić]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Best Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=170143</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In crypto news today:</p>
<ul>
<li><span>Why is crypto up today?</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>Animoca-Backed OPEN Launches to Bring the $85 Billion Ticketing Industry On-chain</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>KuCoin Becomes the First FIU-Compliant Crypto Exchange in India</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>XRP Healthcare Partner with NHS collaborator Isansys</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-news-today.htm">What’s Happening In Crypto Today? Daily Crypto News Digest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of blockchain and crypto news today – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s news.</em></p>
<div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;">
<p>In crypto news today:</p>
<ul>
<li><span>Why is crypto up today?</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>Animoca-Backed OPEN Launches to Bring the $85 Billion Ticketing Industry On-chain</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>KuCoin Becomes the First FIU-Compliant Crypto Exchange in India</span></li>
<li><span></span><span>XRP Healthcare Partner with NHS collaborator Isansys</span></li>
</ul>
</div></div>
<p>__________</p>
<h2><b>Why is crypto up today?</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Over the past 24 hours, the total market capitalization increased 4.1% to $2.681 trillion.</span></p>
<p><span>Out of the top 100 coins per market cap, only 10 have dropped, </span><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/"><span>according</span></a><span> to </span><b>CoinGecko</b><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>The biggest fall among these is </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ronin/"><b>Ronin (RON)’s</b></a><span> 3.1% to $4.11.</span></p>
<p><span>In this category, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ondo-finance/"><b>Ondo</b></a><span> is the best performer, having risen 28.2% to $0.9459. </span></p>
<p><span>Among the top 10 coins, the price of only one decreased. </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/dogecoin/"><b>Dogecoin (DOGE)</b></a><span> is down 1.2% to $0.1719.</span></p>
<p><span>The best performer in this category is </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/sol-solana/"><b>Solana (SOL)</b></a><span>. It appreciated 7.5% to $186.88.</span></p>
<p><span>The rest rose between </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ripple/"><b>XRP’s</b></a><span> 0.2% and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/binance-coin/"><b>BNB’s</b></a><span> 5.7%. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/"><b>Bitcoin (BTC)</b></a><span> increased 3.3% to $67,027, while </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ethereum/"><b>Ethereum (ETH)</b></a><span> went up 3% to $3,452.</span></p>
<p><span>Meanwhile, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-upgrades-coinbase-to-neutral-as-bitcoin-prices-rally.htm"><b>Goldman Sachs’</b></a><span> hedge fund clients are showing </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-hedge-fund-spike-crypto-options-engagement.htm"><span>increased interest in crypto derivatives</span></a><span>, prompted by the resurgence of the crypto market.</span></p>
<p><span>Max Minton, Goldman’s Asia Pacific head of digital assets, said that there has been a noticeable increase in client interest, onboarding, pipeline, and trading volume since the beginning of the year.</span></p>
<p><span>On the other hand, Emin Gün Sirer, the co-founder of </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/avax-avalanche/"><b>Avalanche</b></a><span> blockchain, has warned about </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/warning-from-emin-gun-sirer-deceptive-trends-threaten-integrity-of-crypto-markets.htm"><span>deceptive trends</span></a><span> infiltrating certain layer-2 (L2) solutions, posing risks to investors.</span></p>
<p><span>And speaking of warnings, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-expands-bitcoin-mining-presence-with-texas-acquisition.htm"><b>Marathon Digital Holdings</b></a><span> CEO Fred Thiel cautioned that smaller miners would </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-ceo-warns-bitcoin-halving-challenges-small-miners.htm"><span>face financial strain</span></a><span> following Bitcoin halving in April.</span></p>
<h2><b>Animoca-Backed OPEN Launches to Bring the $85 Billion Ticketing Industry On-chain</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>in crypto news today, the </span><b>OPEN Ticketing Ecosystem</b><span> has recently rebranded, aiming to “become the number one home for on-chain </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/toby-rush-ceo-of-deem-future-of-web3-mobile-nft-ticketing-sports-power-of-open-ecosystems-ep-272.htm"><span>ticketing</span></a><span>,” backed by </span><b>Animoca</b><span>, </span><b>Merit Circle</b><span>, </span><b>Redbeard Ventures</b><span>, and the </span><b>Tezos Foundation</b><span>, with tooling running on </span><b>Polygon</b><span>, </span><b>Base</b><span>, </span><b>Solana</b><span>, and </span><b>Tezos</b><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>Per the press release shared with </span><i><span>Cryptonews</span></i><span>, OPEN is the official rebrand of the established </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/get-protocol-secures-45-million-funding-disrupt-ticketing-industry-with-nfts.htm"><b>GET Protocol</b></a><span>, which was launched in 2016.</span></p>
<p><span>It is an ecosystem of builders, projects, and backers. They joined hands to challenge the status quo and bring the ticketing industry onchain, thus “restoring rightful control back to event organizers, artists and their fans,” it said.</span></p>
<p><span>As billions in revenue are captured every year by centralized ticketing monopolies, artists, organizers, and fans suffer.</span></p>
<p><span>The centralized ticketing industry is currently valued at $85 billion. At the same time, the on-chain ticketing industry is valued at $30 million. </span></p>
<p><span>OPEN plans to put 1% of the events industry on-chain in the next five years.</span></p>
<p><span>The OPEN Ticketing Ecosystem has already issued 5 million tickets globally since 2016, from events such as stadium shows to comedy clubs and museums. </span></p>
<p><span>OPEN “provides state of the art global on-chain ticketing infrastructure used around the world and the newly rebranded platform is an industry-wide ticketing coalition with prominent partners that will launch the beginnings of the on-chain ticketing industry,” it said.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ticketing integrators that use OPEN’s ticketing infrastructure are required to top up <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24OPN&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$OPN</a> from the open market to pay and fuel the tickets they sell for their events. </p>
<p>Attendees don&#39;t need to know about crypto, they pay in their local FIAT currency &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24OPN&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$OPN</a> fuel flows behind the… <a href="https://t.co/QTjjfMB0tB">pic.twitter.com/QTjjfMB0tB</a></p>
<p>&mdash; OPEN Ticketing Ecosystem (@onopenxyz) <a href="https://twitter.com/onopenxyz/status/1771200187324670298?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>A newly launched event financing system followed the OPEN rebranding. It helps organizers and artists fund their events, “without signing their soul away to a ticketing monopoly.” </span></p>
<p><span>The collaborators plan additional “massive integrations” in the near future, boosting the annual ticket volume on OPEN to 20 million.</span></p>
<p><span>Furthermore, OPEN is launching the OPN token on March 28. Holders will be able stake their tokens and receive a portion of real-world ticketing yield.</span></p>
<p><span>Ticketeers use OPN to fuel all tickets processed through OPEN. </span></p>
<p><span>When an attendee enters an event, OPN “flows behind the scenes to token stakers” via the decentralized autonomous organization (</span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/paul-frambot-ceo-of-morpho-labs-on-defi-2-0-modular-layered-protocols-and-the-next-evolution-of-defi-ep-318.htm"><span>DAO</span></a><span>) and ecosystem treasury, providing real-world yield on a global scale, said the team.</span></p>
<p><span>Thus, OPN has real-world demand outside of the crypto industry and a $30 million market cap, bringing billions of value onchain and tapping into a multi-billion-dollar revenue stream for holders, it added.</span></p>
<h2><b>KuCoin Becomes the First FIU-Compliant Crypto Exchange in India</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Crypto exchange </span><a href="https://www.kucoin.com/r/af/rMSG95L"><b>KuCoin</b></a><span> announced that it became the first </span><b>Financial Intelligence Unit</b><span> (</span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/indian-government-rejects-binances-plea-to-resume-operations-demands-pmla-compliance.htm"><span>FIU</span></a><span>)-compliant global crypto exchange in </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/okx-ceases-operations-in-india-citing-regulatory-hurdles.htm"><span>India</span></a><span>. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.prnewswire.co.uk/news-releases/kucoin-pioneers-as-the-first-fiu-compliant-global-crypto-exchange-in-india-302097402.html"><span>According</span></a><span> to the press release, this is “a pivotal moment in the evolving Indian cryptocurrency landscape amid recent regulatory changes.” </span></p>
<p><span>Furthermore, along with the registration with FIU, the exchange proposes to undertake several initiatives to serve its Indian users better. </span></p>
<p><span>These include localized payment solutions and collaborating with local banks and fiat partners to introduce direct on-ramp and off-ramp services tailored for India.</span></p>
<p><span>It also proposes to launch a partnership enrollment program to onboard more partners and provide an easier service.</span></p>
<p><span>The exchange further aims for a strategic investment focus: promoting investment and support for blockchain projects led by entrepreneurs with an India focus, aiding the sustainable growth of the local crypto ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span>Its next proposal is regulatory and security alliances, thus continuing to support regulatory and government authorities in promoting a secure and regulated industry landscape.</span></p>
<p><span>The partnerships for education and ecosystem proposal aims to see the exchange partner with educational institutions through KuCoin Campus to foster blockchain understanding and offer access to KuCoin&#8217;s Web3, technology, and ecosystem resources.</span></p>
<p><span>Finally, ‘Glo-cal strategy and team localization’ proposes establishing a dedicated, localized team to better understand and serve the specific needs of Indian investors and users. </span></p>
<p><span>‘Glo-cal’ stands for going global with a localization focus, said the exchange.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4e2.png" alt="📢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> JUST-IN: <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/KuCoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#KuCoin</a> named <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/India?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#India</a>&#39;s first <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FIU?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FIU</a>-compliant global crypto exchange! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1ee-1f1f3.png" alt="🇮🇳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f389.png" alt="🎉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/stJuqA7CAY">pic.twitter.com/stJuqA7CAY</a></p>
<p>&mdash; KuCoin (@kucoincom) <a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1771216139768533368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>CEO Johnny Lyu commented that “by successfully completing this registration in India, we are set to enhance the Indian users&#8217; experience and reaffirm our dedication to compliance and security.”</span></p>
<p><span>The registration is a milestone that allows the company “to advance the conversation on crypto adoption in India,” said Lyu, and to accelerate its investment and educational initiatives in the country, “aiming to stimulate industry growth and foster the blockchain landscape&#8217;s sustainable development.” </span></p>
<h2><b>XRP Healthcare Partner with NHS collaborator Isansys</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
In other crypto news today, <b>XRP Healthcare</b><span>, the Pharma and Healthcare platform on the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-records-3-million-nfts-minted-on-its-xrp-ledger-adoption-on-the-rise.htm"><b>XRP Ledger</b></a><span>, has announced a strategic partnership with </span><b>Isansys Lifecare</b><span>, an innovator in the digital healthcare technology sector, to enhance healthcare infrastructure and services across Uganda. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.prnewswire.co.uk/news-releases/xrp-healthcare-partner-with-nhs-collaborator-isansys-lifecare-to-revolutionize-healthcare-services-in-uganda-302097745.html"><span>According</span></a><span> to the press release, the collaboration is “set to transform patient care through the integration of advanced patient monitoring systems into the pharmacies, medical centres and hospitals they are set to acquire during this year throughout the country.”</span></p>
<p><span>XRP Healthcare will deploy Isansys’ Patient Status Engine (PSE), a continuous monitoring platform that will enable remote patient monitoring (RPM), which is particularly beneficial in Uganda&#8217;s remote areas. </span></p>
<p><span>Furthermore, this initiative will focus on enhancing operational efficiency, reducing healthcare costs, and improving patient care and safety across all healthcare facilities involved in the merger and acquisition process.</span></p>
<p><span>This will allow patients to be treated from home, “freeing up valuable bed spaces and being able to prioritize more urgent cases.”</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Exciting Announcement <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4e2.png" alt="📢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> </p>
<p>XRP Healthcare Partner with NHS collaborator Isansys Lifecare to Revolutionize Healthcare Services in Uganda</p>
<p>Discover why this groundbreaking partnership is set to redefine the landscape <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b07.png" alt="⬇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/wmLWWZxid9">https://t.co/wmLWWZxid9</a> <a href="https://t.co/ykW3hQRcGi">pic.twitter.com/ykW3hQRcGi</a></p>
<p>&mdash; XRP Healthcare (@XRPHealthcare) <a href="https://twitter.com/XRPHealthcare/status/1772143786606387663?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span>Meanwhile, Isansys’ technology is designed for seamless integration and scalability. This will ensure that the healthcare facilities acquired by XRP Healthcare, regardless of size, can maintain high standards of care and operational efficiency. </span></p>
<p><span>The partnership also supports research and development efforts to introduce new healthcare solutions tailored to meet the unique challenges of this country’s healthcare system.</span></p>
<p><span>Isansys Lifecare, under the leadership of Keith Errey, who has guided companies to public listings, has made successful partnership with the </span><b>National Health Service</b><span> (NHS) in the UK, and leading hospitals in Scandinavia and Europe.</span></p>
<p><span>“This background ensures that XRP Healthcare&#8217;s initiative is supported by unparalleled expertise and experience, critical for achieving its goals of better healthcare for all in Uganda,” the announcement said.</span></p>
<p><span>Whitney Lynn, Chairman of XRP Healthcare, stated that they will be integrating Isansys’ technology into the acquisitions this year.</span></p>
<p><span>Keith Errey, CEO of Isansys Lifecare, commented that Isansys’ patient monitoring systems will “play a crucial role in upgrading and implementing new systems for private medical centres and hospitals once acquired by XRP Healthcare.” </span></p>
<p><span>CEO of XRP Healthcare Kain Roomes added that by integrating Isansys’ patient monitoring technology with the recent successful import of the first </span><b>NASA</b><span>-designed ventilator, facilitated by </span><b>DHL:</b></p>
<blockquote><p><span> “We are poised to make significant strides in improving healthcare outcomes and saving lives across Africa. […] I am confident that together, we will positively impact countless lives by delivering advanced, life-saving healthcare solutions to those who need them most.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>For the latest crypto news updates, bookmark this page and subscribe to our newsletter!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-news-today.htm">What’s Happening In Crypto Today? Daily Crypto News Digest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/21102913/1708511352-1708505536885_processed.jpg" length="149135" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Retakes $70,000 On Central Bank Easing Hopes, Potential Easing GBTC Sell Pressure – New ATHs Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-retakes-70000-on-central-bank-easing-hopes-potential-easing-gbtc-sell-pressure-new-aths-next.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188688</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin (BTC) price pushed back above $70,000 on Monday for the first time in 9 days as traders focused on the theme of global central bank easing, a possible easing on GBTC sell pressure and BlackRock’s first major entry into the realm of asset tokenization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-retakes-70000-on-central-bank-easing-hopes-potential-easing-gbtc-sell-pressure-new-aths-next.htm">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Retakes $70,000 On Central Bank Easing Hopes, Potential Easing GBTC Sell Pressure – New ATHs Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_188690" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188690" style="width: 1200px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-188690" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed.jpg" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) Price Retakes $70,000 On Central Bank Easing Hopes, Potential Easing GBTC Sell Pressure – New ATHs Next?" width="1200" height="686" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed.jpg 1200w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed-1024x585.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed-150x86.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-188690" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Retakes $70,000 On Central Bank Easing Hopes, Potential Easing GBTC Sell Pressure – New ATHs Next? / Source: Cryptonews</figcaption></figure>
<p>The Bitcoin (BTC) price pushed back above $70,000 on Monday for the first time in 9 days as traders focused on the theme of global central bank easing, a possible easing on GBTC sell pressure and BlackRock’s first major entry into the realm of asset tokenization.</p>
<p>Last changing hands just under $70,000, the Bitcoin price is <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">up 6% in 24 hours</a> and back above its 2021 peaks.</p>
<p>Two US Federal Reserve policymakers were on the wires talking about rate cuts on Monday.</p>
<p>That comes a week after the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/federal-reserve-expected-cut-rates-lift-bidens-prospects-2024-03-25/">Fed</a>, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/ecb-increasingly-likely-cut-rates-before-summer-break-nagel-says-2024-03-22/">ECB</a> and <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-england-sees-economy-moving-right-direction-rate-cuts-2024-03-21/">BoE</a> all teed up rate cuts later in 2024 at meetings last week, despite sticky inflation pressures in some economies. The <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/swiss-national-bank-surprises-with-interest-rate-cut-2024-03-21/">Swiss National Bank also delivered a surprise rate cut last week</a>.</p>
<p>As per <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-175-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6af2a10c0b30">CoinShares’ weekly fund flows blog</a>, US spot Bitcoin ETFs saw big net outflows last week.</p>
<p>This was driven by a whopping $2 billion in funds exiting <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gbtc-bleeds-another-443-million-as-bitcoin-price-drops-below-61000.htm">Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust</a> (GBTC). This was only partially offset by a $1.1 billion inflow into the other newly launched US spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>GBTC liquidation by bankrupt estates such as Genesis have been cited as driving much of the outflows.</p>
<p>If bankruptcy-related GBTC selling is set to slow, that could remove a key short-term headwind to the market.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-fund-securitize-hints-at-asset-tokenization.htm">BlackRock last week launched its first tokenized fund on Ethereum</a>. The fund, called the BlackRock Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund (BUIDL), is fully collateralized by cash, T-bills and repurchase agreements.</p>
<p>Some analysts implied BlackRock’s latest steps to legitimize and promote crypto adoption could also be supporting market sentiment on Monday.</p>
<h2><strong>Bitcoin Price Poised to Retake All-Time Highs Above $73,000?</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
As the Bitcoin price probes $70,000, bulls are asking whether it could soon retake all-time highs.</p>
<p>Bitcoin snapped a short-term downward trend line on Sunday that had been in play since the market peaked at $73,800.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin price is also back above its 21DMA, suggesting momentum is back on the side of the bulls. Technically speaking, the door is very much open to a short-term retest of all-time highs.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-188691 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443.png" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) Price Retakes $70,000 On Central Bank Easing Hopes, Potential Easing GBTC Sell Pressure – New ATHs Next?" width="1777" height="710" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443.png 1777w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443-300x120.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443-1024x409.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443-768x307.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443-1536x614.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160232/1711382552-screenshot-2024-03-25-105443-150x60.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1777px) 100vw, 1777px" /></p>
<p>Bullish fundamentals support this view. Narratives surrounding central bank easing, the upcoming <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-halving/">halving</a> and HODLer reluctance to sell suggest upside price risks lay ahead.</p>
<p>As per analysts at Blockware Solutions in their latest newsletter, mute average on-chain transfer volume suggests “nobody wants to sell”.</p>
<p>&#8220;Average on-chain transfer volume (USD Denominated) is well below the 2021 bull market peak”.</p>
<p>Once key wild card to the short-term price action is whether GBTC outflows suddenly pick up once again.</p>
<p>Another point to note – major Bitcoin rallies haven’t historically gotten going until a few months after the halving, not before.</p>
<p>But Bitcoin is a maturing asset class, and old rules and models don’t necessarily still apply.</p>
<p>All said, the probability that Bitcoin challenges $100,000 at some point this year remains very high.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Alternative to Consider &#8211; Green Bitcoin ($GBTC)</strong></p>
<p>Bitcoin could easily 2x from current levels during the current bull market.</p>
<p>Those are impressive gains. But some highly risk-tolerant investors will be looking to secure much bigger gains during the coming bull market.</p>
<p>Investors like this will often spend a lot of time assessing various options in the altcoins, or even meme coin markets.</p>
<p>But one type of investment opportunity they shouldn&#8217;t neglect to look into is that of the presale.</p>
<p>Crypto presales are where up-and-coming web3 start-ups/protocols sell their native token at a big discount to early buyers to fund development.</p>
<p>Analysts at Cryptonews.com spend a lot of time combing the presale market. And one project that has caught their eye is an exciting protocol called <a href="https://greenbitcoin.xyz/">Green Bitcoin ($GBTC).</a></p>
<p>Green Bitcoin introduces the new concept of gamified green staking. Stakers of the $GBTC token can boost their APY rewards by engaging in weekly price prediction challenges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing Green Bitcoin: A Revolutionary Predict-To-Earn Token.</p>
<p>Join us on our Gamified Green Staking Platform, where your predictions can turn into profits!</p>
<p>Website: <a href="https://t.co/dG5cEeCtRs">https://t.co/dG5cEeCtRs</a><br />Telegram: <a href="https://t.co/bWanoe0vHv">https://t.co/bWanoe0vHv</a> <a href="https://t.co/eXuGQBkxio">pic.twitter.com/eXuGQBkxio</a></p>
<p>&mdash; GreenBitcoin (@GreenBTCtoken) <a href="https://twitter.com/GreenBTCtoken/status/1731315050349002862?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>And, given it is issued on Ethereum, $GBTC is powered by the eco-friendly proof-of-stake network validation mechanism.</p>
<p>The project has already raised a whopping nearly $9 million as investors raise to get involved before the presale sells out.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-retakes-70000-on-central-bank-easing-hopes-potential-easing-gbtc-sell-pressure-new-aths-next.htm">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Retakes $70,000 On Central Bank Easing Hopes, Potential Easing GBTC Sell Pressure – New ATHs Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25160152/1711382512-1711382465922_processed.jpg" length="162661" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arkham Intelligence Predicts Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC to Run Out of Bitcoin in 96 Days</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arkham-intelligence-predicts-grayscales-gbtc-to-run-out-of-bitcoin-in-96-days.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sujha Sundararajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the start of the year, Grayscale possessed 618.28K BTC for their Bitcoin Trust GBTC. They now hold only 356.44K BTC.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arkham-intelligence-predicts-grayscales-gbtc-to-run-out-of-bitcoin-in-96-days.htm">Arkham Intelligence Predicts Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC to Run Out of Bitcoin in 96 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain analytics company Arkham predicts that crypto investment firm Grayscale’s GBTC product will run-out of all its <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> holdings in 96 days, at the current rate of redemptions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">At the current rate of redemptions, GBTC runs out of Bitcoin to sell in 96 DAYS.</p>
<p>Since GBTC started trading as an ETF on 11th January, Grayscale has transferred 266.47K BTC out of their wallets for GBTC redemptions.</p>
<p>That’s a rate of 25.9K BTC per week. <a href="https://t.co/tMT7T73ena">pic.twitter.com/tMT7T73ena</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Arkham (@ArkhamIntel) <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1771567638587814221?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“Since GBTC started trading as an ETF on 11th January, Grayscale has transferred 266.47K BTC out of their wallets for GBTC redemptions.” The rate of redemption equals to 25.9K BTC per week, the report added.</p>
<p>At the start of the year, Grayscale <a href="https://platform.arkhamintelligence.com/explorer/entity/grayscale">possessed 618.28K BTC</a> for their Bitcoin Trust GBTC. “They now hold only 356.44K BTC,” Arkham estimates.</p>
<blockquote><p>“If they carry on like this, there’s only 14 weeks until they run out for good.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Grayscale, the world’s largest crypto asset manager, experienced a significant decrease in its Bitcoin holdings since converting its GBTC into an exchange-traded fund (ETF) in mid-January.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/bitmexresearch/status/1764801064715383117">BitMEX data</a> showed that GBTC saw its 36th consecutive day of outflows on March 4. <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscales-bitcoin-holdings-drop-by-33.htm">Cryptonews reported</a> early this month that since GBTC’s conversion to an ETF, the total outflow has reached a staggering $9.26 billion.</p>
<p>This is mainly because Grayscale introduced a new feature at the time of the launch of its spot Bitcoin ETF. The feature enables investors to redeem their shares for Bitcoin, which was not possible previously.</p>
<p>Furthermore, GBTC has higher fees compared to the ETFs of Blackrock’s and Fidelity’s, thus contributing to the outflow.</p>
<p>This resulted in the company <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-files-for-mini-bitcoin-spot-etf-to-stop-gbtc-bleed.htm">filing for ‘mini’ BTC ETF</a> to stop the excessive outflows. The mini trust is mainly to compensate for losses to existing GBTC holders, investors, the company noted.</p>
<h2>Theories Linked to GBTC’s Bleed</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
According to Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchuna, the worst could be over for GBTC, but not.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">What a pounding. Thought worst was over. Guess not. Who is leaving now that wasn’t motivated to leave past two months? <a href="https://t.co/YNX1dBt2FM">https://t.co/YNX1dBt2FM</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1770953684815405074?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 21, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>He noted that the uptick in outflows is more likely related to the recent bankruptcies because of the size and consistency.</p>
<p>“The flows in Feb showed what retail outflows look like, smaller and random pattern,” he added. “The worst is probably close to being over. Once it is, only retail will be left and flows should look more like the Feb trickle.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arkham-intelligence-predicts-grayscales-gbtc-to-run-out-of-bitcoin-in-96-days.htm">Arkham Intelligence Predicts Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC to Run Out of Bitcoin in 96 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25155451/1711382091-1711380930225_processed.jpg" length="90381" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CommEx, Successor to Binance in Russia, Announces Shutdown and Halts Deposits</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/commex-binance-russia-shutdown-halts-deposits.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CommEx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CommEx, the exchange that took over Binance's operations in Russia in September 2023, has announced it is closing down and has stopped accepting deposits.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/commex-binance-russia-shutdown-halts-deposits.htm">CommEx, Successor to Binance in Russia, Announces Shutdown and Halts Deposits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CommEx, the exchange that took over Binance&#8217;s operations in Russia in September 2023, has announced it is closing down and has stopped accepting deposits.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the exchange has refrained from stating the motives behind this decision, it has outlined that it will wind down all operations before May 10, 2024.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CommEx Announces Suspension of Trading Operations</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We regret to inform you that CommEX is winding down its service starting March 25, 2024. All services will be completely terminated by May 10, 2024.</p>
<p>Please close your positions &amp; withdraw assets ASAP.</p>
<p>Learn more <a href="https://t.co/1MSZajVjQm">https://t.co/1MSZajVjQm</a> <a href="https://t.co/y2S4HISFvT">pic.twitter.com/y2S4HISFvT</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CommEX (@CommEX_com) <a href="https://twitter.com/CommEX_com/status/1772227862449226126?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://t.me/CommEX_RUChat/150597" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announcement was posted on</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> CommEx&#8217;s official Telegram group on March 25, informing users of the gradual suspension of operations. They urged users to withdraw their assets to third-party wallets promptly.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;With regret, after a thorough analysis of the current situation and a review of strategic plans, we are forced to announce the decision to suspend the work of the trading platform,&#8221; said CommEx</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the provided timeline, CommEX will cease new user registrations and Asset Transfer from Binance on March 25 and discontinue fiat &amp; cryptocurrency deposit services from April 2. CommEx will halt futures trading on March 28, and all existing peer-to-peer orders and listings will be automatically closed on April 5.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">By April 23, the spot trading platform will be completely shut down, with the website set to be suspended by May 10.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, CommEX stated in the announcement that asset management fees will be imposed for users who still have asset balances on the platform after May 10, 2024. The exchange will charge the account asset management cost 1% of the snapshot assets per day starting May 10, 2024.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CommEX also warned users that it would never contact anyone for withdrawals via phone calls, text messages, or emails; any attempt of such should be flagged as a fraudulent practice. It also warns users not to give their personal account information or verification codes to strangers or third parties.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance Sells Russian Business Citing Regulatory Challenges</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Last year, Crypto exchange Binance </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-crypto-exchange-gauges-complete-exit-from-russian-market-amid-sanctions.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sold the entirety of its Russian business</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to CommEX as key executives stepped down from the Russian arm of the exchange in September 2</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">023. This all happened when </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance faced major regulatory challenges related to complying with Western sanctions against Russia. However, as of August 2023, despite regulatory pressure, Binance was still promoting its services for Russian users.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance later sold its Russian business to CommEx, but details about the deal, including information about CommEx&#8217;s founders and executives, remain undisclosed. The exchange officially launched the day before the news was announced. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Many crypto observers have speculated that <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/commex-says-they-are-not-owned-by-binance-but-some-core-members-are-ex-binance-veterans.htm">CommEX was just a new name for Binance</a>, allowing the exchange to continue operations in Russia without issues with Western sanctions against the country. Skeptics have found significant evidence for such claims, including CommEX hiring prominent former Russia-related executives from Binance.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-changpeng-zhao-denies-ownership-of-commex-following-sale-of-russian-entity.htm">Binance continued to deny the allegations of possible ties</a> between the platform and CommEX. &#8220;With this sale, Binance fully exits Russia. We have no plans to get back,&#8221; a spokesperson for Binance said.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At the time, Binance said there would be no ongoing revenue split from the sale, and its founder, Changpeng Zhao, denied that he owned the exchange. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Also, the similarities between Binance and CommEx websites led some to dub CommEx the &#8220;Russian version&#8221; of Binance US. At the time of the sale, Russia was a significant market for Binance, accounting for 6.9% of total visits to Binance.com.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/commex-binance-russia-shutdown-halts-deposits.htm">CommEx, Successor to Binance in Russia, Announces Shutdown and Halts Deposits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25154916/1711381755-commex-successor-to-binance-in-russia-announces-shutdown-and-halts-deposits.jpg" length="109027" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GRAPH Token Goes Viral on Solana and This New Dogecoin ICO is Poised for Takeoff</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/graph-token-goes-viral-on-solana-and-this-new-dogecoin-ico-is-poised-for-takeoff.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Cooling]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry Talk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana meme coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLGraph]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the latest dazzling Solana meme coin pump, a Graph token spin-off called &#8216;SOLGraph&#8217; has skyrocketed in popularity as prices hit new highs. This article will provide an analysis of GRAPH’s current price trends, and look to see whether the latest incarnation of Dogecoin, represents a more promising investment opportunity at this time. GRAPH Price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/graph-token-goes-viral-on-solana-and-this-new-dogecoin-ico-is-poised-for-takeoff.htm">GRAPH Token Goes Viral on Solana and This New Dogecoin ICO is Poised for Takeoff</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the latest dazzling Solana meme coin pump, a Graph token spin-off called &#8216;SOLGraph&#8217; has skyrocketed in popularity as prices hit new highs.</p>
<p>This article will provide an analysis of GRAPH’s current price trends, and look to see whether the latest incarnation of <a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20">Dogecoin</a>, represents a more promising investment opportunity at this time.</p>
<h2><strong>GRAPH Price Analysis: As SOLGraph Explodes In Huge Overnight Move &#8211; Is Retracement Set To Take Hold?</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
SOLGraph is unique amongst the meme coin trend, in so far as having actual utility, with the token forming the settlement layer of a new SocialFi project on the Google App-store.</p>
<p>As price action attempts to consolidate, SOLGraph is currently trading at a market price of $1.00 (representing  24-hour change of -25%).</p>
<p>This comes amidst a tumultuous retracement move, which has left GRAPH price battling to establish consolidation above support between $0.90 and $1.</p>
<p>Launched at just 9 AM (UTC) on March 24, SOLGraph gained quick traction, exploding to hit resistance at $0.72 in the opening hour.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-188487" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122003/1711369203-graph_usd-ray-dextools-io_2024-03-25_10-34-43.png" alt="" width="1473" height="631" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122003/1711369203-graph_usd-ray-dextools-io_2024-03-25_10-34-43.png 1473w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122003/1711369203-graph_usd-ray-dextools-io_2024-03-25_10-34-43-300x129.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122003/1711369203-graph_usd-ray-dextools-io_2024-03-25_10-34-43-1024x439.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122003/1711369203-graph_usd-ray-dextools-io_2024-03-25_10-34-43-768x329.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122003/1711369203-graph_usd-ray-dextools-io_2024-03-25_10-34-43-150x64.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1473px) 100vw, 1473px" /></p>
<p>A brief period of consolidation here saw price action swing up, to hit an all-time high at $2.08 around 11 AM &#8211; a move fuelled by an influx of over $4m in trading volume.</p>
<p>Yet, in the hours since, a retracement move has gripped the chart, with price action tumbling in a volatile return to lower support &#8211; however, if 2.32k GRAPH token holders can defend this zone successfully, it could set the stage for a major resumption of upside moves.</p>
<p>Indeed, SOLGraph&#8217;s market cap is still standing relatively low at $1.06m, therefore GRAPH token current prices represent a strong potential entry for late-stage investors with as much as a 5x gain on the short-time frame possible from here.</p>
<p>But, for Solana meme coin traders looking for bigger rewards, the key to success is getting in early, and an emerging Dogecoin presale offers the opportunity to do just that &#8211; meet Dogecoin20.</p>
<h2><strong>Last Chance to Join Dogecoin20 Presale: $10M Hard Cap Nears As DOGE20 Goes Viral &#8211; Don&#8217;t Miss Final Day</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-188492 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million.jpg" alt="In latest Solana meme coin skyrocket, new SOLGraph (GRAPH token) has exploded overnight - and this other new dogecoin could be next." width="1792" height="1024" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million.jpg 1792w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million-300x171.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million-1024x585.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million-1536x878.jpg 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122325/1711369404-doge20-5million-150x86.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1792px) 100vw, 1792px" /></p>
<p>In an outstanding move, investors are racing back to ERC-20 from Solana meme coin markets, to participate in the new DOGECOIN20 presale, which has accelerated to a near sell-out in just 4-days.</p>
<p>As the snowball grows, markets anticipate the birth of the next skyrocket, with a current $8,827,266 raised at the time of writing &#8211;<span> </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener sponsored">Dogecoin20</a><span> </span>appears poised as a breakout meme coin for the year ahead.</p>
<p>Dogecoin20 developers have revealed in their latest announcement, that DOGE20 coins will be claimable on 4/20 &#8211; following a 3-week marketing campaign in a move aimed at targeting the Bitcoin halving event.</p>
<p>With a carefully planned launch underway, viral success forms the focus here, and as aeplica play on the biggest meme coin, Dogecoin (DOGE), retail investors are rushing to buy the next DOGE at just 0.0001% of Dogecoin’s market cap.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Think <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$DOGE</a> might be getting a bit jealous! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f914.png" alt="🤔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f436.png" alt="🐶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Dogecoin20?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Dogecoin20</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Memecoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Memecoins</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Altcoins</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cryptomemes?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Cryptomemes</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE</a> <a href="https://t.co/Q3QMhqsh6f">pic.twitter.com/Q3QMhqsh6f</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dogecoin20 (@DOGE_COIN20) <a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20/status/1772186719292387636?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Indeed, if DOGECOIN20 replicates just 1% of Dogecoin’s success, and hits a $192M market cap – investors could be sat atop a 50x return.</p>
<p><strong>Revolutionizing Meme Coins:</strong><span> </span>Dogecoin20, is already making headlines across the crypto industry. With the presale skyrocketing towards $10m  raised in its first week of presale, this innovative token pays homage to the original meme coin while laying the foundation for the next generation of moon-boys.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-188498 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig.jpeg" alt="In latest Solana meme coin skyrocket, new SOLGraph (GRAPH token) has exploded overnight - and this other new dogecoin could be next." width="800" height="388" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig.jpeg 800w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig-300x146.jpeg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig-768x372.jpeg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig-130x63.jpeg 130w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig-104x50.jpeg 104w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig-83x40.jpeg 83w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122745/1711369665-1711020552-1710866567-d0camefwv_pcvtgzkb8si3xqxiwvv65hik386c4kgvcmw8e02r_1710512890nac9jgtlig-150x73.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<p><strong>Innovative Tokenomics:</strong><span> </span>Dogecoin20 isn’t just another meme coin; it’s a powerhouse of innovation. Featuring a capped supply and an ingenious high-yielding staking mechanism, this token rewards active participation and shields against inflation, setting a new standard for meme coins everywhere.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-188499 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122800/1711369680-1711020567-1710866580-czaq-kdbqu-m5cvhvqeai3btzoosuyalzrr3xwpchzqwdx2w7_1710512890kvhmcrotre.jpeg" alt="In latest Solana meme coin skyrocket, new SOLGraph (GRAPH token) has exploded overnight - and this other new dogecoin could be next." width="800" height="408" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122800/1711369680-1711020567-1710866580-czaq-kdbqu-m5cvhvqeai3btzoosuyalzrr3xwpchzqwdx2w7_1710512890kvhmcrotre.jpeg 800w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122800/1711369680-1711020567-1710866580-czaq-kdbqu-m5cvhvqeai3btzoosuyalzrr3xwpchzqwdx2w7_1710512890kvhmcrotre-300x153.jpeg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122800/1711369680-1711020567-1710866580-czaq-kdbqu-m5cvhvqeai3btzoosuyalzrr3xwpchzqwdx2w7_1710512890kvhmcrotre-768x392.jpeg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122800/1711369680-1711020567-1710866580-czaq-kdbqu-m5cvhvqeai3btzoosuyalzrr3xwpchzqwdx2w7_1710512890kvhmcrotre-150x77.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<p><strong>Mission &amp; Roadmap:</strong><span> </span>More than just a token, Dogecoin20 embodies the ethos of “Do Only Good Everyday.” With a roadmap focused on charity, community support, and real-world impact, this project aims to redefine the crypto landscape and pave the way for a brighter, more inclusive future.</p>
<p><strong>Join the Revolution:</strong><span> </span>Be part of something special. Follow<span> </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" rel="sponsored nofollow">Dogecoin20’s</a><span> </span>journey<span> </span><a href="https://twitter.com/DOGE_COIN20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">on X</a><span> </span>or<span> </span><a href="https://t.me/DOGE_COIN20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">join their Telegram</a><span> </span>for the latest updates. Ready to dive in? Visit their<span> </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" rel="sponsored nofollow">website</a><span> </span>to acquire and stake tokens today!</p>
<p>Don’t miss out on the next big thing in crypto as capital flights Solana meme coins —join the Dogecoin20 revolution on ERC-20 now!</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/dogecoin20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener sponsored">Buy DOGE20 Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/graph-token-goes-viral-on-solana-and-this-new-dogecoin-ico-is-poised-for-takeoff.htm">GRAPH Token Goes Viral on Solana and This New Dogecoin ICO is Poised for Takeoff</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25124451/1711370689-gjyr_faxuaa54dh-scaled.jpg" length="99188" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indonesian College Student Behind NFT Selfies Success Returns with $1.8 Million Meme Coin Presale</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/indonesian-college-student-behind-nft-selfies-success-returns-with-1-8-million-meme-coin-presale.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188490</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sultan Gustaf Al Ghozali, the Indonesian college student who became an internet sensation in 2022 for selling millions of dollars worth of NFTs featuring his daily selfies, is back in the spotlight with a meme coin project.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/indonesian-college-student-behind-nft-selfies-success-returns-with-1-8-million-meme-coin-presale.htm">Indonesian College Student Behind NFT Selfies Success Returns with $1.8 Million Meme Coin Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sultan Gustaf Al Ghozali, the Indonesian college student who became an internet sensation in 2022 for selling millions of dollars worth of NFTs featuring his daily selfies, is back in the spotlight with a meme coin presale.</p>
<p>Ghozali <a href="https://x.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771717570586095647?s=20">announced</a> the second edition of &#8220;Ghozali Everyday&#8221; on March 224th. This project uniquely blends meme coins with NFTs on the Base blockchain. The project&#8217;s presale surpassed its initial target of 400 Ether (ETH), reaching 527 ETH.</p>
<h2>Ghozali Returns to X with Meme Coin and NFT Hybrid Project: Announces Second Iteration of &#8216;Ghozali Everyday&#8217;</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Uploading my photo into nft lol<a href="https://t.co/E3Q4sBmN26">https://t.co/E3Q4sBmN26</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NFT?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NFT</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/opensea?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#opensea</a> <a href="https://t.co/rD51rdcpzp">pic.twitter.com/rD51rdcpzp</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1480524562609573892?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 10, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In January 2022, Sultan Gustaf Al Ghozali, a 22-year-old computer science student from Semarang, Indonesia, made waves in the crypto world by minting nonfungible tokens (NFTs) featuring daily selfies he took over five years. He captured nearly 1,000 self-portraits that chronicled his journey from 18 to 22.</p>
<p>These selfies, taken as a personal reflection on his academic journey, depicted him sitting or standing in front of his computer in various poses. This collection, named &#8220;Ghozali Everyday,&#8221; quickly gained traction within the crypto community, earning Ghozali, a student at the time, more than $1 million.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Just took the last selfie when I graduated from college and finally i can stop this doing this shit almost every day </p>
<p>6 years taking selfies every day is the stupidest idea I ever came up with, but luckily I can make money from it <a href="https://t.co/qftRH6WRua">pic.twitter.com/qftRH6WRua</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1694679286182293848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Reflecting on his success, Ghozali expressed gratitude for the support and opportunity to turn a personal project into a profitable venture. He announced on X that with his graduation, he would no longer continue the daily selfie tradition, marking the end of an era that unexpectedly brought him financial success and recognition in the NFT space.</p>
<p>On March 22, after being absent from X for several months, Ghozali returned amidst the rising interest in meme coins. He made a significant announcement about the second iteration of his project, &#8220;Ghozali Everyday,&#8221; which now combined meme coins and NFTs in an ERC-404 format on the Base blockchain. To kick things off, he <a href="https://x.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771178492442312969?s=20">initiated an airdrop for the holders</a> of the first Ghozali Everyday NFTs.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">TuRn On NOtIfIcaTioN, Drop sOmE NeWs SoOn <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6ce.png" alt="🛎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/7zJ7BIrA2j">pic.twitter.com/7zJ7BIrA2j</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771178492442312969?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 22, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Following this, on March 24, Ghozali unveiled the launch of the second part of &#8220;Ghozali Everyday.&#8221; He disclosed the presale address with an intended cap set at 400 ETH. However, the presale quickly exceeded this limit, <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x4553555f6a451EC415f698A524B5e02E38acFB6C">reaching 527 ETH</a>, equivalent to around $1.8 million at the time of writing.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">launching the second part of Ghozali Everyday: a memecoin and nft hybrid on Base 🛜</p>
<p>PRESALE is open, send eth to 0x4553555f6a451EC415f698A524B5e02E38acFB6C (eth mainnet/base only) <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64f-1f3fb.png" alt="🙏🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>min 0.05 ETH <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f448-1f3fb.png" alt="👈🏻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />max 2 ETH <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2705.png" alt="✅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />cap 400 ETH <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6ce.png" alt="🛎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />100% of ETH raised goes to LP 🛜</p>
<p>Ghozali 404    <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f646-1f3fb-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="🙆🏻‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />… <a href="https://t.co/HYAfHkh1z3">pic.twitter.com/HYAfHkh1z3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ghozali (@Ghozali_Ghozalu) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771717570586095647?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Despite the overwhelming response, Ghozali took to X to <a href="https://twitter.com/Ghozali_Ghozalu/status/1771724578005340402">announce</a> that he would refund those who sent more than 2 ETH after the cap was reached. He also clarified that the cap would not increase, ensuring fairness and transparency in the project&#8217;s execution.</p>
<h2>Solana&#8217;s Meme Coin Craze: Traders Flock Amid Bitcoin&#8217;s Bullish Surge</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Amidst the recent bullish run of Bitcoin (BTC) prices, there has been a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-solana-meme-coins/">resurgence of interest in meme coins</a>, mainly driven by traders on the Solana blockchain. Notably, data indicates that presale projects on Solana raised an astounding $100 million within just three days, from March 15 to 18.</p>
<p>This surge in funding reflects a trend where meme coin founders are leveraging t<a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-memecoin-sector-surges-by-45-as-traders-pour-100-million-in-72-hours.htm">oken presales to raise significant amounts</a> for unreleased coins. The presale mechanism typically involves investors sending cryptocurrency to a specified wallet address in exchange for the distribution of tokens once the coin is officially launched. Nevertheless, there&#8217;s no guarantee of receiving tokens in return, making <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-presale-scams-take-a-toll-as-meme-coin-season-continues.htm">presales susceptible to fraud and scams.</a></p>
<p>The recent frenzy surrounding meme coin presales peaked with the launch of Book of Meme on March 14. Created by the pseudonymous artist Darkfarms1, the coin initially held a valuation of approximately $4 million but skyrocketed by an astonishing 36,000% within just 56 hours, reaching a peak market capitalization of $1.45 billion.</p>
<p>While the profitability of meme coins has captivated the crypto space, concerns about the presale model and its associated risks surfaced.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/indonesian-college-student-behind-nft-selfies-success-returns-with-1-8-million-meme-coin-presale.htm">Indonesian College Student Behind NFT Selfies Success Returns with $1.8 Million Meme Coin Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25123548/1711370147-1711370134479_processed.jpg" length="82747" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dead or Alive: Number of Cryptocurrencies Worldwide from 2013 to January 2024</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-globally-2013-2024.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sead Fadilpašić]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exclusives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2024 crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=188486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2024 began with over 9,000 cryptocurrencies available globally, 13% fewer projects ‘alive’ compared to the all-time high reached in 2022, accordign to Statista data.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-globally-2013-2024.htm">Dead or Alive: Number of Cryptocurrencies Worldwide from 2013 to January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span>2024 began with over 9,000 cryptocurrencies created and still available globally, </span><a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/863917/number-crypto-coins-tokens/"><span>according</span></a><span> to </span><b>Statista</b><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>This is 13% fewer projects ‘alive’ compared to the all-time high reached in February 2022.</span></p>
<p><span>That said, between February 2023 and January 2024, there was a 4% increase in the number of available projects. </span></p>
<p><span>The road to the current volume was turbulent, yet it witnessed only four significant drops.</span></p>
<p><span>This is impressive, given that that that road started at 66 coins in 2013. </span></p>
<p><span>Therefore, the crypto world has seen a 13,573% jump in the number of cryptocurrencies between 2013 and 2024.</span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="2cb9d6fa-78aa-40de-9377-dcddeb7cb085" data-type="interactive" data-title="Dead Coins PR"></div>
<p><span>Individuals, groups, or companies can create a coin on an existing blockchain or create a new chain entirely. </span></p>
<p><span>Reasons for creating cryptocurrencies vary, but generally speaking, they may serve as a solution to specific real-world payment issues, or the creators seek to make a profit at the detriment of the users and the sector.</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, when we talk about cryptocurrencies, we actually talk about several different kinds of coins. Besides the most popular </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/"><b>Bitcoin (BTC)</b></a><span> and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/ethereum/"><b>Ethereum (ETH)</b></a><span>, there are thousands of altcoins, including the (in)famous meme coins, as well as stablecoins, governance and utility tokens, and many more.</span></p>
<p><span><div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"> </span></p>
<h3><b><i>How is cryptocurrency created?</i></b></h3>
<p><em>It is worth noting that creating a cryptocurrency is a relatively easy process, and anybody can do it.</em></p>
<p><em>Whether that project achieves any significance – or survives at all – is a different story. Most do not.</em></p>
<p><em>There are several different<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/how-to-make-a-cryptocurrency-5215343"> options</a> for making a cryptocurrency. Creating a blockchain and a native token or modifying the existing blockchain are the more difficult options and require more technical knowledge and training.</em></p>
<p><em>Meanwhile, making a coin on an existing chain, or paying a developer to make it, is a lot easier.</em></p>
<p><em>Many will opt to create a cryptocurrency on an existing chain, and there are even<a href="https://www.walletbuilders.com/"> online tools</a> that allow the creation of tokens and blockchains without programming knowledge.</em></p>
<p><em>The more one wishes to customize the coin, the more knowledge is needed.</em></p>
<p><em>Once the crypto is created, the coins are minted for issuance.</em></p>
<p><em>This is the simplest, most basic explanation. Serious projects will invest a lot of time and money into their crypto, they will have a highly skilled team of developers constantly working on it, and the project will be thoroughly audited.</em></p>
</div></div>
<p><span>Meanwhile, there are other estimates out there per which there may be some 20,000 cryptocurrencies in existence. “Most of these are either inactive or discontinued,” said Statista.</span></p>
<p><span>These coins are typically referred to as ‘dead.’ They cease to exist due to a number of reasons, including halted development, lack of users or traders, fraud exposure, and more.</span></p>
<p><span>Per </span><b>99bitcoins</b><span>, as of February 2023, </span><a href="https://99bitcoins.com/deadcoins/"><span>there are at least 1,774 dead coins</span></a><span>. And these are the reported projects.</span></p>
<p><span>A 2024 report </span><a href="https://alphaquest.io/blog/dead-coins-report-2024/"><span>conducted by </span><b>AlphaQuest</b><span> and </span><b>Storible</b></a><span>, which analyzed 12,343 cryptos, found that nearly two-thirds of cryptocurrencies created over the past several years “have met their demise.”</span></p>
<h2><b>2013-2020: From 66 Coins to 4,000</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>The crypto industry has seen significant growth in the seven years up to early 2021, as per Statista data. </span></p>
<p><span>While it may be difficult to fathom today, there was no </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/"><span>top 100 coins per market capitalization</span></a><span> to talk about in 2013. At the time, there were only 66 available cryptos.</span></p>
<p><span>However, within a single year, the 66 jumped 666.6 % to 506 in 2014.</span></p>
<p><span>Over the following two years, the market saw a more modest increase: there were 562 coins recorded in 2015 and 644 in 2016.</span></p>
<p><span>This is where we notice another sharp increase in the number of cryptocurrencies, surpassing the 1,000 mark. In 2017, it increased 107% compared to 2016, hitting 1,335 coins.</span></p>
<p><span>Two years later, in 2019, the 2,000 mark was surpassed, with the number of coins reaching 2,817. </span></p>
<p><span>Between November 2019 and February 2021, another 1,694 coins were added to the available lot – nearly doubling the amount and totaling 4,501.</span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="dd37dae5-fd09-452b-953b-bcd2f250289b" data-type="interactive" data-title="Copy: Dead Coins PR- 2013-20"></div>
<p><span>This 2020-2021 period and the bull run that marked it were very significant for the industry. </span></p>
<p><b>CoinGecko</b> <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/how-many-cryptocurrencies-failed"><span>found</span></a><span> that most dead cryptocurrencies came from projects launched during this bull run.</span></p>
<p><span>The data aggregator stated in a January 2024 report that, </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“7,530 cryptocurrencies from that period have died, accounting for 53.6% of all dead cryptocurrencies on CoinGecko. Over 11,000 cryptocurrencies were listed on CoinGecko during the previous bull run, with ~70% having shut down since.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>However, when the researchers looked at the results of the 2017-2018 bull run, they discovered that 1,450 projects shut down. “This is on the back of over 3,000 cryptocurrencies listed, resulting in a similar fail rate of ~70%.”</span></p>
<p><span>As for the reasons behind the high rates of dead coins, CoinGeko identified the ease of deploying tokens and the rise in popularity of meme coins as contributing factors.</span></p>
<p><span>Many <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-ecosystem-boasts-over-2500-monthly-active-developers-reports-solana-foundation.htm">meme coin projects</a> launched but without a product to offer and were soon abandoned entirely.</span></p>
<h2><b>2021-2022: Hitting the All-Time-High</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>2021 saw major increases in the number of available cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span>While there were 4,501 coins in February, by July that same year, the number was up to 6,044.</span></p>
<p><span>Soon after, we notice the first drop in this ten-year time frame. In August 2021, the number fell to 5,840. </span></p>
<p><span>That said, just two months after that, it surpassed the July level, climbing to 6,826, and ended the year with 7,557.</span></p>
<p><span>This ‘rally’ resulted in a new all-time high (ATH) at the beginning of 2022. </span></p>
<p><span>Between November 2021 and January 2022, the number was up 31.4% to 9,929.</span></p>
<p><span>Then in February 2022, it hit its final ATH to date: 10,397 different coins existing in the nascent ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span>Therefore, between February 2021 and February 2022, the number of coins increased by 131%. </span></p>
<p><span>Following the ATH, the space recorded a 10.5% fall in November 2022 to 9,310. </span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="f3950e6a-7ef0-46b1-94d2-a082d5057bd6" data-type="interactive" data-title="Copy: Copy: Dead Coins PR- 2021-22"></div>
<p><span>According to CoinGecko, nearly 6,000 cryptocurrencies from 2021 failed. The report stated that,</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“Cryptocurrencies created in 2021 have suffered the worst, with 5,724 having died as of January 2024. Over 70% of cryptocurrencies listed on CoinGecko in 2021 have died, making it the worst year for project launches.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>2022 follows it as another bad year: 3,520 listed coins died (~60%) by January 2024.</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, the AlphaQuest and Storible report also found that most cryptocurrencies born during the 2020-2021 bull run failed, saying:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“In particular, out of the 4,834 crypto projects introduced during the bullish trend, 72% failed to survive.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><b>2023-2024: 13% Drop from ATH</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>A notable development in 2023 is that the year saw two more drops in the number of cryptocurrencies. This is as many drops as recorded over the previous nine years combined.</span></p>
<p><span>All in all, the numbers haven’t moved much since the November 2022 level of 9,310.</span></p>
<p><span>February 2023 saw a decrease to 8,685, followed by a slight increase to 9,321, then dropping again to 8,866 by the end of the year. </span></p>
<p><span>January 2024 began with 9,024 cryptocurrencies. Compared to February 2023, this is a 3.9% increase.</span></p>
<p><span>However, compared to the February 2022 ATH, January 2024 saw a 13.2% fall in the number of cryptocurrencies available.</span></p>
<div class="infogram-embed" data-id="a87432b1-597a-476e-af69-ad74b085f516" data-type="interactive" data-title="Copy: Copy: Copy: Dead Coins PR- 2021-22"></div>
<p><span>That said, between 2013 and 2024, the crypto space witnessed a 13,572.7% rise in the number of cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span>CoinGecko found that 289 cryptocurrencies listed on the platform in 2023 subsequently died, stating:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“This represents a failure rate of &lt;10%, with over 4,000 cryptocurrencies listed, a sharp decline from previous years.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>The AlphaQuest and Storible report stated that, among 12,343 crypto projects investigated, 8,854 have become defunct in the past year.</span></p>
<p><span>Leading up to 2023, it said, there has been a decrease in the cryptocurrency market, leading to the death of 65% of projects.</span></p>
<p><span>Per this report, “2023 is the toughest year in the 2020-2023 cycle, with nearly 60% of dead coins disappearing during that period.”</span></p>
<p><span>That said, 2023 was indeed a difficult year for crypto projects, bearing the brunt of the 2022 crypto industry crisis. </span></p>
<p><span>The entire space suffered due to the bear market fallout and the domino effect that began in 2022 with the collapse of the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-appeals-extradition-decision-amid-claims-of-political-pressure.htm"><b>Terra/Luna</b></a><span> ecosystem, followed by the infamous fall of the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-ceo-slams-attempt-to-reduce-sbf-sentence.htm"><b>FTX</b></a><span> exchange and its sister company </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/alameda-research-drops-lawsuit-against-grayscale-amid-gbtc-outflows.htm"><b>Alameda Research</b></a><span>. </span></p>
<p><span>These events were so monumental that their effects are still felt, and the companies’ executives are facing prison time.</span></p>
<p><span>Then, after months of struggling, crypto lending and trading firm </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-agrees-to-pay-21m-fine-to-settle-sec-crypto-lending-charges.htm"><b>Genesis</b></a><span>, a unit of the </span><b>Digital Currency Group</b><span> (DCG), </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-files-for-bankruptcy-as-it-seeks-protection-from-its-creditors-which-dcg-unit-next-fail.htm"><span>filed for bankruptcy</span></a><span> following a significant loan loss to the now also defunct </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis-seeks-court-help-to-reduce-settlement-payout-to-3ac.htm"><b>Three Arrows Capital</b></a><span>.</span></p>
<p><span>The aftershocks impacted numerous projects and coins. Companies like </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-network-announces-unstaking-of-ethereum-holdings-to-facilitate-distribution-to-creditors.htm"><b>Celsius</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-digital-announces-liquidation-shutdown-following-failed-ftx-binanceus-deals.htm"><b>Voyager</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-clients-can-now-submit-withdrawal-requests-as-bankruptcy-plan-takes-effect.htm"><b>BlockFi</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-platform-recur-to-shut-down-after-raising-50m-two-years-ago/"><b>RECUR</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-firm-lbry-ceases-operations-cites-insurmountable-debt.htm"><b>LBRY</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-niftys-shuts-down-tel-aviv-stock-exchange-signs-ground-breaking-deal-with-fireblocks-aventus-partners-with-vodafone-htm.htm"><b>Nifty’s</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bittrex-global-to-halt-all-trading-in-december.htm"><b>Bittrex Global</b></a><span>, and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billion-dollar-crypto-payments-firm-wyre-shut-down-amid-market-conditions.htm"><b>Wyre</b></a><span> all announced they’d wind down their operations in 2022 and 2023, citing hostile market conditions and/or debts.</span></p>
<p><span>Therefore, </span><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/659195da8efdab762672810b/"><span>according</span></a><span> to </span><b>CoinMarketCap</b><span>, these project’s coins are just some of those that died over 2023.</span></p>
<p><span>Losses from these various collapses numbered in the billions. FTX alone had an $8 billion hole in its accounts.</span></p>
<p><span>The collapses also showcased how interconnected the crypto ecosystem was at the time. </span></p>
<p><span>Poor management, mismanagement of funds, lack of liquidity, and cyberattacks contributed to the fallout, fueling the bear market, which in turn increased the pressure on the market participants until many buckled under it and went bankrupt.</span></p>
<h2><b>2025: Could This Be The Year of the Most Crypto Projects Launched?</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>After the Terra crash, 35% of crypto projects were deemed defunct, the AlphaQuest and Storible report said. And after the FTX fall, 32% of crypto projects closed shop. </span></p>
<p><span>Half of the cryptocurrencies backed by Three Arrows Capital subsequently failed.</span></p>
<p><span>“Other top-tier VCs with over half of their projects in their portfolio having died include </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-supports-coinbases-case-against-the-sec-files-amicus-curiae-brief.htm"><b>Paradigm</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-blockchain-cryptogpt-secures-10-million-in-funding-valued-at-250-million-bull-market-back.htm"><b>DWF Labs</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/polychain-warns-users-against-engaging-with-ceos-x-account-following-hack.htm"><b>Polychain Capital</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/a16z-backed-projects-sold-tokens-and-nfts-contrary-to-claims-by-general-partner-chris-dixon.htm"><b>a16z</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/animoca-brands-and-hashkey-sign-strategic-partnership-deal-more-crypto-news.htm"><b>Animoca Brands</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-investor-binance-splits-from-venture-capital-arm.htm"><b>Binance Labs</b></a><span>, and </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/investor-letter-shocker-multicoin-capitals-hedge-fund-reports-914-loss-2022-heres-what-happened.htm"><b>Multicoin Capital</b></a><span>,” it said.</span></p>
<p><span>No ecosystem was safe. </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/cardano/"><b>Cardano</b></a><span> witnessed 74% of the projects in its ecosystem go defunct. For Terra, it was 74% of the projects. Furthermore, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/celo/"><b>Celo</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/harmony-one/"><b>Harmony</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/near-near-protocol/"><b>Near</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/zilliqa/"><b>Zilliqa</b></a><span>, </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/moonriver/"><b>Moonriver</b></a><span>, and others all experienced “notable losses.”</span></p>
<p><span>Meanwhile, the report found that a whopping 93% of the dead projects suffered from low liquidity or trading volume. </span></p>
<p><span>58% of them had </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/over-65-of-crypto-related-tweets-and-84-of-conversations-on-reddit-were-positive-in-2023.htm"><b>Twitter</b></a><span> accounts or websites that were either inactive or deleted, and 48% were removed from major tracking platforms such as </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinmarketcap-launches-chatgpt-plugin-simplify-crypto-analysis.htm"><b>CoinMarketCap</b></a><span>.</span></p>
<p><span>Moreover, the average lifespan of a crypto project is three years, “which means an average project can barely survive through a market cycle of 4 years,” the report said.</span></p>
<p><span>Commenting on the decrease in the number of cryptocurrencies, Ramy Bekhiet, Senior Advisor and Commercial Partnerships Coordinator at </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/castle-fund-just-because-bitcoin-etfs-are-allowed-doesnt-mean-theyll-succeed.htm"><b>PDX</b></a><span>, told </span><i><span>Cryptonews</span></i><span> that projects are realizing that they need to offer real-world utility.</span></p>
<p><span>“Also, with regulations looming around, projects are becoming more careful in how they operate and launch new coins/tokens,&#8221; he said.</span></p>
<p><span>Aaron Rafferty, co-founder and CEO of technology incubation hub </span><a href="https://www.standarddao.finance/"><b>Standard</b></a><span>, said that,</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“The drop is clearly the tail end of the last bull market and aftermath of overspeculation, hype cycles that failed, and fraudsters that ran pump-and-dump schemes. Many of these individuals are still in the market under alternative personas, and the creation of new tokens and projects is far from over.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>In fact, with Large Language Models, the gap to launch a crypto project is lower than ever, said Rafferty, and requires zero coding experience. </span></p>
<p><span>Platforms like </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-presale-scams-take-a-toll-as-meme-coin-season-continues.htm"><b>Solana</b></a><span> are attracting hundreds of millions of consumer investor dollars, speculating on the next pump-and-dump scheme. This week alone, we saw $149.2 million in funding go directly to 33 project presales where personalities on Twitter effectively shared a wallet address to which people sent their </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-bounces-11-from-recent-bottom-is-the-sell-off-over.htm"><b>SOL</b></a><span> tokens. </span></p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/propykeys-launches-base-dapp-rwa-ai-nft-features-for-minting-addresses-and-deeds-onchain.htm"><b>Base</b></a><span> chain will have a similar moment as it is even easier and cheaper to launch a project there, with fees costing less than $1 for the entire process, Rafferty argued, adding:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“Couple these two factors together along with the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-spot-etfs-see-net-outflow-on-third-consecutive-day.htm"><span>ETF</span></a><span> [exchange-traded fund] approvals and lack of regulatory clarity from the </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-reportedly-probing-key-crypto-companies-in-push-to-make-eth-a-security-fortune.htm"><b>SEC</b></a><span> [US Securities and Exchange Commission], and 2025 will be the year of the most crypto projects launched that we have ever seen. The gap now seems to be the size of one&#8217;s audience and ability to draw a crowd.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/etfs-are-inevitable-but-not-imminent-crypto-expert-argues.htm"><span>Peter Eberle</span></a><span>, President and Chief Investment Officer of </span><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/castle-fund-just-because-bitcoin-etfs-are-allowed-doesnt-mean-theyll-succeed.htm"><b>Castle Funds</b></a><span>, commented that the reason we are excited about some cryptocurrencies is the underlying technology that some of these have developed. </span></p>
<p><span>This includes Bitcoin as a means of transferring large amounts of money across borders without middlemen and on a public distributed ledger. Also, there’s Ethereum and its smart contracts that can be executed based on predetermined rules. </span></p>
<p><span>However, said Eberle,</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span>“Unfortunately, many others provide nothing of value. Meme coins are cheap to issue and extract money from people chasing quick riches, enriching the issuers. New coins will continue to be released, and others will collapse. Investors must do their own research and due diligence. Don&#8217;t be someone else’s exit liquidity.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span>Meanwhile, the AlphaQuest and Storible report noted that, despite the downfall of numerous coins, many new projects and narratives emerge each month. </span></p>
<p><span>It stated that “the cryptocurrency field still holds promise for the future” and “the enduring relevance of cryptocurrencies cannot be underestimated.”</span></p>
<h2><b>Conclusion</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span>Between 2013 and 2024, there was a 13,572.7% rise in the number of cryptocurrencies, from 66 to 9,024, according to Statista.</span></p>
<p><span>Compared to the February 2022 ATH of 10,397, there was a 13% drop by January 2024 in the number of cryptocurrencies available.</span></p>
<p><span>Year-on-year, from February 2023 until January 2024, the space saw a 3.9% increase in the number of available coins worldwide.</span></p>
<p><span>There were four recorded drops over the past decade: August 2021, November 2022, February 2023, and December 2023.</span></p>
<p><span><div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"></span></p>
<h3><em>Why do cryptocurrencies fail?</em></h3>
<p><span>Some of the key reasons why the cryptocurrencies fail and end up dying include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span> crypto volatility</span></li>
<li><span>unpredictability</span></li>
<li><span>lack of investment and trading volume</span></li>
<li><span>abandonment by developers</span></li>
<li><span>lack of regulations</span></li>
<li><span>over-speculation</span></li>
<li><span>hype cycle fails</span></li>
<li><span>hacks</span></li>
<li><span>fraud (such as rug pulls).</span></li>
</ul>
</div></div>
<p><span>Most projects created during the 2020-2021 bull run have died by now. Most new coins don’t even last one four-year cycle. </span></p>
<p><span>Per various reports, 2021 and 2023 were particularly bad years for crypto projects. Bear markets, as well as a string of bankruptcies that began in 2022, led to the fall of numerous projects.</span></p>
<p><span>All that said, more cryptocurrencies are being created every day. Following the improvements in the crypto space and approval of ETFs, 2025 may see the most cryptocurrencies created yet.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-globally-2013-2024.htm">Dead or Alive: Number of Cryptocurrencies Worldwide from 2013 to January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/25122728/1711369648-dead-or-alive-number-of-cryptocurrencies-worldwide-from-2013-to-january-2024.jpg" length="124541" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
