<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoSlate</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptoslate.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptoslate.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News and Real-time Coin Data</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:50:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cropped-cryptoslate-transparent-icon-256x256-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CryptoSlate</title>
	<link>https://cryptoslate.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ark&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF witnesses record-breaking inflow day</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/insights/arks-bitcoin-etf-witnesses-record-breaking-inflow-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James Van Straten]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?post_type=crypto_insight&#038;p=407865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Quick Take Bitcoin (BTC) ETFs witnessed net inflows on March 27, totaling a solid $243.4 million, equivalent to 3,534.7 BTC. Leading the charge was BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT, which recorded a net inflow of $323.8 million, or 4,701.5 BTC, bringing its total net inflow to an impressive $13,862.7 billion, equivalent to 250,787 BTC. This is the largest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/arks-bitcoin-etf-witnesses-record-breaking-inflow-day/">Ark&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF witnesses record-breaking inflow day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Quick Take</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/four-bitcoin-etfs-secure-top-spots-in-bloombergs-global-etf-asset-race-balchunas/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> ETFs witnessed net inflows on March 27, totaling a solid $243.4 million, equivalent to 3,534.7 BTC. Leading the charge was <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/larry-fink-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-after-ibits-record-breaking-performance/">BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT</a>, which recorded a net inflow of $323.8 million, or 4,701.5 BTC, bringing its total net inflow to an impressive $13,862.7 billion, equivalent to 250,787 BTC. This is the largest inflow BlackRock has seen in 7 days and over ten times more than its lowest inflow just last week.</p>
<figure style="width: 566px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GJv28XlWMAAsaHM?format=jpg&amp;name=large" alt="ETF Data in dollars: (Source: BitMEX)" width="566" height="704" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">ETF Data in dollars: (Source: BitMEX)</figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">BitMEX data shows that Ark Investment Management&#8217;s ArkB had a record day, raking in $200.7 million in net inflows, equivalent to 2,915.2 BTC, pushing its total net inflows to $2,276.7 billion or equivalent to 44,086 BTC. However, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) continued to experience outflows, with $299.8 million, or 4,354.2 BTC, leaving the fund, bringing its total net outflows to a staggering $14,662.8 billion, equivalent to 282,454 BTC.</p>
<p>Fidelity&#8217;s FBTC experienced a notably record low inflow of just $1.5 million, equating to 21.8 BTC. This addition brought their total net inflows to an impressive $7,494.0 billion, equivalent to 140,905 BTC, according to BitMEX.</p>
<figure style="width: 578px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GJv3UkiWsAAlwZx?format=jpg&amp;name=large" alt="ETF Data in Bitcoin: (Source: BitMEX)" width="578" height="719" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">ETF Data in Bitcoin: (Source: BitMEX)</figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Despite the outflows from GBTC, the overall net inflows into Bitcoin ETFs reached $11,942.6 billion, equivalent to 210,264 BTC, according to BitMEX.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/arks-bitcoin-etf-witnesses-record-breaking-inflow-day/">Ark&#8217;s Bitcoin ETF witnesses record-breaking inflow day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ark-invest-bitcoin-etf.-jpg.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ark-invest-bitcoin-etf.-jpg.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DePIN protocol peaq gears up for mainnet launch as token offering &#8216;closing in by the day&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/depin-protocol-peaq-gears-up-for-mainnet-launch-as-token-offering-closing-in-by-the-day/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/depin-protocol-peaq-gears-up-for-mainnet-launch-as-token-offering-closing-in-by-the-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Liam 'Akiba' Wright]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DePIN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Dorlochter, the co-founder of peaq, revealed that the layer-1 blockchain focused on decentralized physical infrastructure networks (DePINs) and Machine RWAs is gearing up for its mainnet launch and token offering in an exclusive statement to CryptoSlate. &#8220;The mainnet launch will be a historic milestone for the project, the culmination of years&#8217; worth of research [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/depin-protocol-peaq-gears-up-for-mainnet-launch-as-token-offering-closing-in-by-the-day/">DePIN protocol peaq gears up for mainnet launch as token offering &#8216;closing in by the day&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Dorlochter, the co-founder of peaq, revealed that the layer-1 blockchain focused on decentralized physical infrastructure networks (<a href="/cryptos/iot">DePINs</a>) and Machine <a href="/cryptos/real-world-assets/">RWAs</a> is gearing up for its mainnet launch and token offering in an exclusive statement to <em>CryptoSlate</em>.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The mainnet launch will be a historic milestone for the project, the culmination of years&#8217; worth of research and development, of collaborations with industry giants like Bosch.</p>
<p>Equally exciting is the fact that soon, we will begin to open peaq to the community through the upcoming token offering[&#8230;] these exciting events will take place over the next few weeks, they are closing in by the day.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The announcement comes on the heels of peaq&#8217;s successful $15 million pre-launch funding round, led by Generative Ventures and Borderless Capital, with participation from a host of prominent Web3 investors. The substantial investment in peaq highlights the growing interest in the DePIN space, which Messari estimates could reach a market potential of $3.5 trillion by 2028.</p>
<p>While details about the token offering remain under wraps due to ongoing processes, Dorlochter confirmed that these events are set to unfold over the next few weeks. He also shared plans for a major campaign to support DePINs building on peaq, stating, &#8220;We are planning a major campaign to support the DePINs building on peaq and foster their adoption through a wide variety of gamified challenges with rewards to earn.&#8221;</p>
<p>peaq&#8217;s layer-1 blockchain is specifically designed to cater to the unique requirements of DePINs, offering crucial backend functions, a machine-centric economic model, and a supportive ecosystem. These features differentiate peaq from other networks, with the aim of positioning it as a leading player in the DePIN space.</p>
<p>The funding round follows a year of significant growth for peaq, which saw the onboarding of over 20 DePINs spanning various use cases, such as Silencio, ELOOP, and Wingbits. In 2023, peaq showcased its real-world applications through collaborations with industry leaders like <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/bosch-showcases-depin-sensor-kit-using-ai-agents-to-reward-users-for-local-environmental-data-streams/">Bosch</a> and <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/fetch-ocean-singularitynet-tokens-merge-into-single-asi-token-with-7-6-billion-market-cap/">Fetch</a>.ai, demonstrating the potential for DePINs to bridge the gap between Web3 and the physical world.</p>
<p>As the DePIN sector continues to gain traction, peaq&#8217;s upcoming mainnet launch and token offering hope to play a crucial role in driving the adoption and growth of decentralized physical infrastructure networks. The project&#8217;s focus on providing a robust, scalable, and interoperable platform for DePINs, coupled with its growing ecosystem and industry partnerships, positions it in the middle of a key <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/bosch-showcases-depin-sensor-kit-using-ai-agents-to-reward-users-for-local-environmental-data-streams/">narrative for this cycle</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/depin-protocol-peaq-gears-up-for-mainnet-launch-as-token-offering-closing-in-by-the-day/">DePIN protocol peaq gears up for mainnet launch as token offering &#8216;closing in by the day&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/depin-protocol-peaq-gears-up-for-mainnet-launch-as-token-offering-closing-in-by-the-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/depin-peaq.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/depin-peaq.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum nears 1 million active validators as network surge strengthens security</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/ethereum-nears-1-million-active-validators-as-network-surge-strengthens-security/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/ethereum-nears-1-million-active-validators-as-network-surge-strengthens-security/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oluwapelumi Adejumo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[validators]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407866</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum network has witnessed a surge in validator numbers, with the count nearing one million. On-chain data from Beacon Chain and Ethereum&#8217;s Validator Queue show an active validator count of 979,686. However, a Dune Analytics dashboard curated by Dragonfly analyst Hildobby places the total number on the network above the one million mark. These [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ethereum-nears-1-million-active-validators-as-network-surge-strengthens-security/">Ethereum nears 1 million active validators as network surge strengthens security</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> network has witnessed a surge in validator numbers, with the count nearing one million.</p>
<p>On-chain data from <a href="https://beaconcha.in/charts">Beacon Chain</a> and Ethereum&#8217;s <a href="https://www.validatorqueue.com/">Validator Queue</a> show an active validator count of 979,686. However, a Dune Analytics <a href="https://dune.com/hildobby/eth2-staking">dashboard</a> curated by Dragonfly analyst Hildobby places the total number on the network above the one million mark.</p>
<figure id="attachment_407892" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-407892" style="width: 781px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-407892" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-28-112707.jpg" alt="Ethereum Validators" width="781" height="592" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-28-112707.jpg 781w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-28-112707-300x227.jpg 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Screenshot-2024-03-28-112707-768x582.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 781px) 100vw, 781px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-407892" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Active Validators. (Source: Beaconcha.in)</figcaption></figure>
<p>These validators have collectively staked 31.36 million ETH, constituting approximately 26% of the digital asset&#8217;s total supply.</p>
<p>Notably, according to Nansen <a href="https://pro.nansen.ai/eth2-deposit-contract">data</a>, most of these validators staked their assets through the liquid staking platform <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/lido/">Lido</a>, which accounts for around 30% of the staked ETH.</p>
<p>Ethereum validators play a critical role in maintaining the network&#8217;s security through its proof-of-stake mechanism. To participate, they stake a minimum of 32 ETH and, in return, are rewarded with a portion of ETH.</p>
<p>Consequently, an increasing number of validators signifies a bolstered network and reflects the blockchain&#8217;s enhanced security.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, this milestone is particularly significant amid a <a href="https://www.validatorqueue.com/">surge in validator interest</a>, evidenced by a growing queue of over 10,000 validators awaiting network entry—the highest seen this year. This waitlist represents over 320,000 ETH, equivalent to $1.1 billion, and is anticipated to clear within the next seven days.</p>
<h2>Decentralized staking</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/vitalik-buterin/">Vitalik Buterin</a>, the co-founder of Ethereum, recently put forth a proposal aimed at improving the network&#8217;s<a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sp-global-warns-of-spot-ethereum-etfs-impact-on-staking-concentration/"> staking mechanism.</a></p>
<p>In his blog <a href="https://ethresear.ch/t/supporting-decentralized-staking-through-more-anti-correlation-incentives/19116">post</a>, Buterin outlined a plan to impose penalties on validators in proportion to their average failure rates. This move addresses the inherent advantage larger ETH stakes possess over smaller ones.</p>
<p>Additionally, Buterin recommended stricter penalties for failures occurring simultaneously among several validators controlled by one entity.</p>
<p>According to him:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;One tactic for incentivizing better decentralization in a protocol is to <em>penalize correlations</em>. That is, if one actor misbehaves (including accidentally), the penalty that they receive would be greater the more other actors (as measured by total ETH) misbehave at the same time as them.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Buterin argued that these measures would encourage larger entities to diversify their operations, thus lowering the likelihood of widespread network failures.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ethereum-nears-1-million-active-validators-as-network-surge-strengthens-security/">Ethereum nears 1 million active validators as network surge strengthens security</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/ethereum-nears-1-million-active-validators-as-network-surge-strengthens-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ethereum-validators-.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ethereum-validators-.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Bitcoin set to overshadow Ethereum in the next bull market?</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/insights/is-bitcoin-set-to-overshadow-ethereum-in-the-next-bull-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James Van Straten]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 10:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?post_type=crypto_insight&#038;p=407864</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Quick Take The Ethereum (ETH) to Bitcoin (BTC) exchange rate, currently trading slightly above 0.05, has utilized this support level for the past six months. This enduring stability at the support level may indicate an impending alteration in market dynamics. Historically, Ethereum has closely tracked Bitcoin&#8217;s market movements. However, this correlation has weakened in recent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/is-bitcoin-set-to-overshadow-ethereum-in-the-next-bull-market/">Is Bitcoin set to overshadow Ethereum in the next bull market?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Quick Take</h2>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Ethereum (ETH) to Bitcoin (BTC) exchange rate, currently trading slightly above 0.05, has utilized this support level for the past six months. This enduring stability at the support level may indicate an impending alteration in market dynamics.</p>
<figure id="attachment_407867" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-407867" style="width: 1514px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-407867 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHBTC.png" alt="BTCUSD vs ETHUSD: (Source: TradingView)" width="1514" height="853" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHBTC.png 1514w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHBTC-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHBTC-1024x577.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ETHBTC-768x433.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1514px) 100vw, 1514px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-407867" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD vs ETHUSD: (Source: TradingView)</figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Historically, Ethereum has closely tracked Bitcoin&#8217;s market movements. However, this correlation has weakened in recent weeks, now standing at 0.85. Since April 2023, the ETH/BTC ratio has declined by 25%, highlighting Ethereum&#8217;s relative underperformance. This shift is mainly due to the success of <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/four-bitcoin-etfs-secure-top-spots-in-bloombergs-global-etf-asset-race-balchunas/">Bitcoin ETFs</a>.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A chart from <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/workbench/mrkt-btceth-dominance?zoom=all">Glassnode</a> illustrates the BTC-ETH Dominance metric, which monitors overarching trends in market performance. The metric is at -0.002, indicating a marginal period of Ethereum&#8217;s dominance. Nonetheless, the prevailing trend hints at a forthcoming shift favoring Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance. Should this occur, it would mark the first bull market since Ethereum&#8217;s creation in which Bitcoin surpasses its nearest competitor in performance.</p>
<figure id="attachment_407868" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-407868" style="width: 1800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-407868 size-full" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3.png" alt="BTC-ETH Market Cap Dominance: (Source: Glassnode)" width="1800" height="1013" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1800px) 100vw, 1800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-407868" class="wp-caption-text">BTC-ETH Market Cap Dominance: (Source: Glassnode)</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/is-bitcoin-set-to-overshadow-ethereum-in-the-next-bull-market/">Is Bitcoin set to overshadow Ethereum in the next bull market?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3.png" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/btc-3.png" length="1800" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sell-side risk ratio hit 3-year high as Bitcoin broke above $73k</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/sell-side-risk-ratio-hit-3-year-high-as-bitcoin-broke-above-73k/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/sell-side-risk-ratio-hit-3-year-high-as-bitcoin-broke-above-73k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andjela Radmilac]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Alpha]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[profit realization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sell-side risk ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volatility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin sell-side risk ratio is calculated by dividing the sum of all profits and losses realized on-chain by the realized capitalization, offering a comparative view of daily investor activity against the total market capitalization adjusted for real-time inflows and outflows. A rise in this metric indicates a higher likelihood of sell-side pressure, potentially leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sell-side-risk-ratio-hit-3-year-high-as-bitcoin-broke-above-73k/">Sell-side risk ratio hit 3-year high as Bitcoin broke above $73k</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">The <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/"><span class="s1">Bitcoin</span></a> sell-side risk ratio is calculated by dividing the sum of all profits and losses realized on-chain by the realized capitalization, offering a comparative view of daily investor activity against the total market capitalization adjusted for real-time inflows and outflows.</p>
<p class="p1">A rise in this metric indicates a higher likelihood of sell-side pressure, potentially leading to increased market volatility.</p>
<p class="p1">Between Feb. 8 and March 13, the Bitcoin sell-side risk ratio saw a significant surge, climbing from 0.12% to 0.777%. This increase followed a significant rise in Bitcoin&#8217;s price from $45,330 to $73,104. This period marked the highest sell-side risk ratio and the first instance of the ratio surpassing the 0.75% threshold since March 9, 2021.</p>
<p class="p1">Following this peak, BTC dropped to $61,860 by Mar. 19 before <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoin-market-absorbs-mining-output-and-more-sparking-price-spike/"><span class="s1">recovering</span></a> to $70,000 on Mar. 26. The sell-side risk ratio adjusted to 0.556%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_407588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-407588" style="width: 1800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-407588" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sell-side-risk-ratio-ytd.png" alt="sell side risk ratio ytd" width="1800" height="1013" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sell-side-risk-ratio-ytd.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sell-side-risk-ratio-ytd-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sell-side-risk-ratio-ytd-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sell-side-risk-ratio-ytd-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/sell-side-risk-ratio-ytd-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1800px) 100vw, 1800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-407588" class="wp-caption-text">Graph showing Bitcoin&#8217;s sell-side risk ratio from Jan. 1 to Mar. 26, 2024 (Source: <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/workbench/btc-sellside-risk-ratio?s=1704063600&amp;u=1711543428&amp;zoom=ytd">Glassnode</a>)</figcaption></figure>
<p class="p1">The increase of the sell-side risk ratio above its upper bound shows a period of <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/bitcoin-experiences-near-historic-levels-of-net-profit-realization/"><span class="s1">high value realization</span></a> among investors, often observed during the late stages of bull markets or bear market capitulation events. However, spikes like these can also occur at the beginning of bull cycles, particularly when the market undergoes initial corrections.</p>
<p class="p1">The subsequent correction in Bitcoin&#8217;s price and the sell-side risk ratio indicates volatility. However, this volatility is not without precedent. Since 2011, the trend has been toward diminishing returns with each market cycle, leading to lower highs in the sell-side risk ratio. This is consistent with the observed pattern where, with each cycle, investors are realizing less profit, hinting at a maturing market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_407590" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-407590" style="width: 1800px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-407590" src="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-sell-side-risk-ratio-14y.png" alt="bitcoin sell side risk ratio 14y" width="1800" height="1013" srcset="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-sell-side-risk-ratio-14y.png 1800w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-sell-side-risk-ratio-14y-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-sell-side-risk-ratio-14y-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-sell-side-risk-ratio-14y-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-sell-side-risk-ratio-14y-1536x864.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1800px) 100vw, 1800px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-407590" class="wp-caption-text">Graph showing Bitcoin&#8217;s sell-side risk ratio from Jul. 19, 2010, to Mar. 26, 2024 (Source: <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/workbench/btc-sellside-risk-ratio?s=1277998138&amp;u=1711411200&amp;zoom=">Glassnode</a>)</figcaption></figure>
<p class="p1">The continuous stay of the ratio above the 0.1% mark since Nov. 29, 2023, further emphasizes a shift from the <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sth-sell-side-risk-ratio-drops-to-decade-low/"><span class="s1">very low value realization</span></a> observed on Sept. 18, 2023, at 0.039%. This transition suggests a move away from market bottoms and accumulation phases towards more active and possibly speculative trading phases.</p>
<p class="p1">The break above the upper bound signals a significant turning point, likely driven by investor optimism and profit-taking. However, the historical trend towards lower highs in this ratio may indicate a gradual stabilization of the market, with less pronounced peaks in value realization as the market matures.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sell-side-risk-ratio-hit-3-year-high-as-bitcoin-broke-above-73k/">Sell-side risk ratio hit 3-year high as Bitcoin broke above $73k</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/sell-side-risk-ratio-hit-3-year-high-as-bitcoin-broke-above-73k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-neon.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-neon.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US sanctions Palestinian media group Gaza Now, including its crypto wallets</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/us-sanctions-palestinian-media-group-gaza-now-including-its-crypto-wallets/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/us-sanctions-palestinian-media-group-gaza-now-including-its-crypto-wallets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407798</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US Department of the Treasury and its Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) sanctioned the Palestinian news network Gaza Now on March 27 over allegations of supporting Hamas. The Treasury sanctions also designate several crypto addresses linked to Gaza Now and its related parties. The Treasury designated an empty Bitcoin address and two Ethereum [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/us-sanctions-palestinian-media-group-gaza-now-including-its-crypto-wallets/">US sanctions Palestinian media group Gaza Now, including its crypto wallets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Department of the Treasury and its Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) sanctioned the Palestinian news network Gaza Now on March 27 over allegations of supporting Hamas.</p>
<p>The Treasury sanctions also designate several crypto addresses linked to Gaza Now and its related parties.</p>
<p>The Treasury designated an empty <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> address and two Ethereum addresses holding more than $2,690 in <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/ethereum/">ETH</a> and other tokens. It also designated five <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/tether/">USDT</a> addresses holding more than $10,350, though only two addresses appeared to contain funds.</p>
<p>One of the USDT addresses was linked to Gaza Now founder Mustafa Ayash.</p>
<p>The Treasury also sanctioned Qureshi Executives, Aakhirah Limited, and their director, Aozma Sultana. It did not designate crypto addresses related to Sultana or either company.</p>
<h2>Gaza Now aided Hamas fundraising</h2>
<p>The Treasury said that it imposed the sanctions because Gaza Now allegedly supported Hamas&#8217; fundraising efforts following the Oct. 7, 2023 attacks against Israel. Al-Qureshi Executives and Aakhirah Limited, in turn, supported Gaza Now financially and through advertising.</p>
<p>Brian E. Nelson, Under Secretary of the Treasury for Terrorism and Financial Intelligence, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Treasury remains committed to degrading Hamas’ ability to finance its terrorist activities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Treasury imposed those sanctions in a joint effort with the UK, which <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/new-sanctions-on-persons-linked-to-hamas-supporting-media-network">separately stated</a> that it had performed a full asset freeze. In both countries, individuals and entities cannot do business with the sanctioned parties, and transactions involving their assets are generally prohibited.</p>
<p>Blockchain analytics firm Elliptic publicly reported in <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/blog/setting-the-record-straight-on-crypto-crowdfunding-by-hamas">October 2023</a> that Gaza Now received $21,000 in crypto following the attacks, including $2,000 frozen by exchanges and $9,000 in USDT frozen by Tether.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/us-sanctions-palestinian-media-group-gaza-now-including-its-crypto-wallets/">US sanctions Palestinian media group Gaza Now, including its crypto wallets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/us-sanctions-palestinian-media-group-gaza-now-including-its-crypto-wallets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/us-treasury-sanction.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/us-treasury-sanction.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ondo Finance adds $95 million to BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL, bringing total AUM to $240 million</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/ondo-finance-adds-95-million-to-blackrocks-buidl-as-it-brings-in-240-million-overall/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/ondo-finance-adds-95-million-to-blackrocks-buidl-as-it-brings-in-240-million-overall/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tokens]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ondo Finance, a tokenized real-world asset company, announced plans to add $95 million of its own assets to a tokenized fund from BlackRock. In a blog post on March 27, the company said it would move a &#8220;substantial portion&#8221; of the assets behind its OUSG token to the BlackRock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund (BUIDL). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ondo-finance-adds-95-million-to-blackrocks-buidl-as-it-brings-in-240-million-overall/">Ondo Finance adds $95 million to BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL, bringing total AUM to $240 million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ondo Finance, a tokenized real-world asset company, announced plans to add $95 million of its own assets to a tokenized fund from <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/blackrock/">BlackRock</a>.</p>
<p>In a blog post on <a href="https://blog.ondo.finance/introducing-instant-24-7-365-subscriptions-and-redemptions-shifting-ousg-funds-into-blackrocks-buidl/">March 27</a>, the company said it would move a &#8220;substantial portion&#8221; of the assets behind its OUSG token to the BlackRock USD Institutional Digital Liquidity Fund (BUIDL).</p>
<p>That amount represents OUSG&#8217;s entire total value locked (TVL), according to the asset&#8217;s <a href="https://ondo.finance/ousg">official overview</a>. The same page suggests that some of the funds may also be held in BlackRock&#8217;s FedFund (TFDXX), the USDC stablecoin, and other investments.</p>
<p>The OUSG token provides liquid exposure to short-term US Treasuries. The company said that the latest developments &#8220;[validate its] original concept of a tokenized US Treasury fund&#8221; and demonstrate that the tokenization of traditional securities is a significant step forward for financial markets.</p>
<p>Reliance on BUILD is part of Ondo&#8217;s broader strategy to provide instant, 24/7 settlement and redemptions.</p>
<h2>BUIDL has attracted $240 million</h2>
<p>The latest news comes alongside a <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/blackrock-tokenized-fund-draws-160-million-in-week-since-debut-1.2052365">Bloomberg report</a> indicating that BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL attracted $240 million in its first week of operations.</p>
<p>Real-time data from <a href="https://platform.arkhamintelligence.com/explorer/address/0x13e003a57432062e4EdA204F687bE80139AD622f">Arkham Intel</a> suggests that BUIDL&#8217;s Ethereum address has a balance above $100 million, primarily consisting of USDC that seeded the fund. Some of the balance — more than <span class="Header_portfolioValue__4KQk0">$141,000</span> — appears to come from crypto donations from the community rather than assets related to the fund.</p>
<p>BlackRock launched its BUIDL fund on the Ethereum blockchain on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-launches-100-million-tokenized-asset-fund-using-ethereum/">March 19</a>, as indicated in a regulatory filing. A later public announcement on <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240320771318/en/BlackRock-Launches-Its-First-Tokenized-Fund-BUIDL-on-the-Ethereum-Network">March 20</a> stated that the fund tokenizes assets in the form of the BUIDL token, which allows qualified investors to earn US dollar yields via a subscription with Securitize Markets.</p>
<p>The fund invests 100% of its assets in cash, US Treasury bills, and repurchase agreements. BlackRock called the fund the &#8220;first tokenized fund issued on a public blockchain.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ondo-finance-adds-95-million-to-blackrocks-buidl-as-it-brings-in-240-million-overall/">Ondo Finance adds $95 million to BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL, bringing total AUM to $240 million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/ondo-finance-adds-95-million-to-blackrocks-buidl-as-it-brings-in-240-million-overall/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/blackrock-bitcoin-holdings-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/blackrock-bitcoin-holdings-1.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Larry Fink &#8216;very bullish&#8217; on Bitcoin after IBIT&#8217;s record-breaking performance</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/larry-fink-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-after-ibits-record-breaking-performance/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/larry-fink-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-after-ibits-record-breaking-performance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Assad Jafri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407744</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink said the record-breaking performance of IBIT has made him more bullish about the future of Bitcoin. Fink made the statement during an interview on Fox Business on March 27, where he called the company&#8217;s spot Bitcoin ETF the most rapidly expanding fund in history. He also stated: &#8220;I’m very bullish on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/larry-fink-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-after-ibits-record-breaking-performance/">Larry Fink &#8216;very bullish&#8217; on Bitcoin after IBIT&#8217;s record-breaking performance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/blackrock/">BlackRock</a> CEO <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/people/larry-fink/">Larry Fink</a> said the record-breaking performance of <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/products/ishares-bitcoin-trust/">IBIT</a> has made him more bullish about the future of <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>Fink made the statement during an <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/shows/the-claman-countdown">interview</a> on Fox Business on March 27, where he called the company&#8217;s spot Bitcoin ETF the most rapidly expanding fund in history.</p>
<p>He also stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I’m very bullish on the long-term viability of Bitcoin.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>He also said that the SEC classifying <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> as a security would not be that detrimental to its future and would not hamper the company from issuing a spot ETH ETF. However, Fink did not disclose further details about the status of the current application process.</p>
<h2>Explosive success</h2>
<p>The BlackRock CEO said he was particularly struck by the performance of IBIT, which has <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/insights/blackrocks-ibit-emerges-as-us-etf-with-second-largest-inflows-for-2024/">shattered expectations</a>, drawing significant retail investor interest beyond initial predictions.</p>
<p>Fink said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I was pleasantly surprised and would never have predicted before we filed it that we would see this kind of retail demand.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The explosive success of the IBIT ETF is rooted in various investor concerns and market conditions, including fears of inflation, prevailing economic uncertainties, and a burgeoning recognition of the importance of portfolio diversification through alternative assets.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s appeal is further magnified by its intrinsic properties, such as a capped supply and decentralized framework, positioning it as both a strategic store of value and a prudent hedge against the vulnerabilities of conventional financial systems.</p>
<p>Fink&#8217;s commentary highlights a notable pivot in investor sentiment towards Bitcoin, spotlighting the flagship crypto&#8217;s burgeoning appeal in the traditional financial sector.</p>
<h2>Shifting tides</h2>
<p>The enthusiasm surrounding the spot Bitcoin ETFs indicates a more <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/blackrock-sees-bitcoin-as-integral-part-of-financial-system-little-interest-in-other-crypto/">significant trend</a> of institutional engagement with Bitcoin on the horizon. This shift suggests a reevaluation of digital assets, transitioning from speculative novelty to a recognized investment avenue.</p>
<p>Based on his leadership at the helm of the globe&#8217;s preeminent asset management firm, Fink&#8217;s optimism wields considerable influence, potentially shaping financial sector attitudes towards Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The trajectory of IBIT&#8217;s growth illustrates a burgeoning confidence in Bitcoin&#8217;s lasting value and its emerging role within the broader financial ecosystem.</p>
<p>Fink&#8217;s comments lend significant support to Bitcoin&#8217;s credibility and its potential role in the global financial landscape. Additionally, the endorsement may encourage further institutional exploration of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, marking a shift towards more inclusive investment strategies that recognize the benefits of digital assets.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/larry-fink-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-after-ibits-record-breaking-performance/">Larry Fink &#8216;very bullish&#8217; on Bitcoin after IBIT&#8217;s record-breaking performance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/larry-fink-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-after-ibits-record-breaking-performance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-larry-fink.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/bitcoin-larry-fink.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon completes $4 billion deal with Anthropic, deepening strategic AI partnership</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/amazon-completes-4-billion-deal-with-anthropic-deepening-strategic-ai-partnership/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/amazon-completes-4-billion-deal-with-anthropic-deepening-strategic-ai-partnership/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Dalton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 19:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407691</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amazon completed an investment deal with AI firm Anthropic after injecting another $2.75 billion into the company on March 27. The latest investment follows $1.25 billion given to the company in September 2023 as part of a $4 billion deal. The deal provides Amazon with minority ownership in Anthropic. Under the deal, the two companies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/amazon-completes-4-billion-deal-with-anthropic-deepening-strategic-ai-partnership/">Amazon completes $4 billion deal with Anthropic, deepening strategic AI partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/amazon/">Amazon</a> completed an investment deal with AI firm <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/anthropic/">Anthropic</a> after injecting another $2.75 billion into the company on <a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/company-news/amazon-anthropic-ai-investment">March 27</a>.</p>
<p>The latest investment follows $1.25 billion given to the company in <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/amazon-invests-4b-in-openai-alumni-anthropic-launching-ai-cloud-war-with-microsoft-and-google/">September 2023</a> as part of a $4 billion deal. The deal provides Amazon with minority ownership in Anthropic.</p>
<p>Under the deal, the two companies have entered a strategic collaboration, including making Anthropic&#8217;s AI models accessible via Amazon Bedrock. Additionally, Anthropic will use AWS for some of its operations and the AWS Trainium and Inferentia microchips to power some of its activities.</p>
<p>Dr. Swami Sivasubramanian, vice president of Data and AI at AWS, said that Amazon has a &#8220;notable history with Anthropic&#8221; and that the two firms have helped organizations worldwide use AI.</p>
<p>Sivasubramanian called Anthropic&#8217;s work with generative AI &#8220;visionary&#8221; and the &#8220;most transformative technology of our time,&#8221; promising that the collaboration will improve customer experiences.</p>
<p>Anthropic itself acknowledged its ongoing partnership with Amazon on <a href="https://www.anthropic.com/news/accenture-aws-anthropic">March 20</a>, emphasizing a role for the professional services company Accenture. It said that more than 1,400 Accenture engineers will be trained as specialists using Anthropic models on AWS.</p>
<h2>Anthropic valued above $18 billion</h2>
<p>The investment will significantly increase Anthropic&#8217;s finances. In <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/12/21/openai-rival-anthropic-in-talks-to-raise-750-million-funding-round.html">December 2023,</a> the company had a valuation of $18 billion following a funding round led by Menlo Ventures.</p>
<p>Anthropic has recently attracted attention for its previous ties to the failed crypto exchange FTX. FTX reached a deal in bankruptcy court to sell its stake in Anthropic for $884 million on <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/25/ftx-estate-sells-majority-stake-in-startup-anthropic-for-884-million.html">March 22</a>, with most of the sale going toward the UAE sovereign wealth fund Mubadala, as <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-founders-block-saudi-arabia-from-buying-ftx-owned-stake/">previously expected</a>.</p>
<p>Anthropic is best known for its AI chatbot, Claude. The company <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/anthropic-releases-next-generation-of-claude-claims-it-is-superior-to-gpt-4/">released version 3</a> of Claude in early March and claimed superior performance over some competitors.</p>
<p>The firm is also known for being founded by former OpenAI employees and for its more transparent approach to AI safety.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/amazon-completes-4-billion-deal-with-anthropic-deepening-strategic-ai-partnership/">Amazon completes $4 billion deal with Anthropic, deepening strategic AI partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/amazon-completes-4-billion-deal-with-anthropic-deepening-strategic-ai-partnership/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/amazon-ai-anthropic.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/amazon-ai-anthropic.jpg" length="1200" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity files registration statement for Ethereum ETF despite regulatory uncertainty</title>
		<link>https://cryptoslate.com/fidelity-files-registration-statement-for-ethereum-etf-despite-regulatory-uncertainty/</link>
					<comments>https://cryptoslate.com/fidelity-files-registration-statement-for-ethereum-etf-despite-regulatory-uncertainty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Assad Jafri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 19:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptoslate.com/?p=407683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity Investments has taken another step in its effort to launch a spot Ethereum ETF, filing a registration statement on March 27 despite the uncertain regulatory landscape. The move follows a previous filing by Cboe, the exchange planned for this ETF, which submitted a form 19b-4 to the SEC on Fidelity&#8217;s behalf in November 2023. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/fidelity-files-registration-statement-for-ethereum-etf-despite-regulatory-uncertainty/">Fidelity files registration statement for Ethereum ETF despite regulatory uncertainty</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/fidelity-investments/">Fidelity Investments</a> has taken another step in its effort to launch a spot <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> ETF, filing a registration statement on March 27 despite the uncertain regulatory landscape.</p>
<p>The move follows a previous filing by Cboe, the exchange planned for this ETF, which submitted a form 19b-4 to the SEC on Fidelity&#8217;s behalf in November 2023.</p>
<p>Fidelity&#8217;s actions, alongside those of other firms aiming to introduce spot ether ETFs, illustrate the growing interest in integrating digital assets into traditional financial products. Yet, obtaining regulatory approval presents a notable challenge, highlighting the evolving and uncertain nature of crypto regulation.</p>
<h2>S-1 filing</h2>
<p>The company&#8217;s recent <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/2000046/000119312524077886/d759655ds1.htm">Form S-1 filing</a> marks an essential step in seeking SEC approval for the Fidelity Ethereum Fund to begin trading. The regulator must approve both the 19b-4 and S-1 forms before the fund can trade,</p>
<p>Fidelity&#8217;s latest submission did not disclose the fund&#8217;s details, such as the ticker and fees.  However, it detailed the fund&#8217;s intention to stake a portion of its assets with one or more staking infrastructure providers, anticipating that staking rewards of ether could count as income for federal income tax purposes.</p>
<p>Fidelity Digital Asset Services, serving as the fund custodian, will exclusively maintain the private keys associated with any staked ETH, ensuring security for the fund&#8217;s operations.</p>
<p>The regulator is expected to decide on ETFs that directly hold ETH by late May. However, industry experts predict the SEC <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/sec-delays-lower-expectations-of-ethereum-etf-approval-by-may-despite-staking-amendments/">may not be as open</a> to Ethereum as <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>Uncertain landscape</h2>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s approval of <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/spot-bitcoin-etfs-record-10-billion-in-daily-volume-breaking-previous-record/">spot Bitcoin ETFs</a> in January led to expectations of a potential opening for other cryptocurrency-based investment products. However, the regulator said at the time that the approval did not mean the regulator had softened its stance toward the digital asset industry.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/companies/ethereum-foundation/">Ethereum Foundation</a> recently revealed it was <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/ethereum-foundation-facing-inquiry-by-unknown-state-authority/">under scrutiny</a> by an unnamed &#8220;state authority,&#8221; triggering concerns about the impact on Ethereum&#8217;s future and the approval of related ETFs.</p>
<p>The inquiry has led to speculation about its implications for Ethereum&#8217;s market performance and regulatory status.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Republican lawmakers are pressing the SEC for <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/us-lawmakers-demand-sec-clarity-on-ethereums-asset-classification/">clarity on Ethereum&#8217;s regulatory classification</a>, highlighting the need for definitive guidance to mitigate market uncertainties.</p>
<p>Despite this, the industry <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/grayscale-executive-sees-path-to-ethereum-etf-approval-despite-sec-silence/">remains optimistic</a> about the approval of Ethereum ETFs, citing previous engagements with the SEC over Bitcoin ETFs as a positive precedent.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/fidelity-files-registration-statement-for-ethereum-etf-despite-regulatory-uncertainty/">Fidelity files registration statement for Ethereum ETF despite regulatory uncertainty</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptoslate.com">CryptoSlate</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cryptoslate.com/fidelity-files-registration-statement-for-ethereum-etf-despite-regulatory-uncertainty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ethereum-lighthouse.jpg" medium="image"/>
<enclosure url="https://cryptoslate.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/ethereum-lighthouse.jpg" length="1456" type="image/jpg"/>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
