<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>The Coin Republic</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/</link>
	<description>By the Coins, From the Coins, For the Coins</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/thecoinrepublic-logo_4dfefd11e401f10473b04f3db4d145f2-75x75.png</url>
	<title>The Coin Republic</title>
	<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>8 Best Meme Coins To Buy Now!</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Serena James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Best Meme Coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme Coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme Coins A]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="BOME" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p>The crypto space is enjoying one of its best-ever bullish phases despite a recent pullback, which analysts say is normal for the market to grow. This explosive growth can be seen when Bitcoin (BTC) hit an all-time high. Interestingly, it is more relevant to the meme coin market than most users might notice. In most cases, what is good for Bitcoin proves to be great for altcoins, especially meme coins.</p>



<p>The reason for this market dynamics is profit-taking. The trend happens when Bitcoin pumps. Investors take some of their profits and invest it elsewhere in the market. This time, it &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="BOME" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/A-racing-track-with-all-leading-memecoins-and-place-BOME-and-Dogecoin-equal-on-the-track-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p>The crypto space is enjoying one of its best-ever bullish phases despite a recent pullback, which analysts say is normal for the market to grow. This explosive growth can be seen when Bitcoin (BTC) hit an all-time high. Interestingly, it is more relevant to the meme coin market than most users might notice. In most cases, what is good for Bitcoin proves to be great for altcoins, especially meme coins.</p>



<p>The reason for this market dynamics is profit-taking. The trend happens when Bitcoin pumps. Investors take some of their profits and invest it elsewhere in the market. This time, it seems like the meme coin space will be where most of that money is going.</p>



<p>2024 could be the year of these meme coins. The meme market exploded in March, notably gaining 30% in a day only at the start of the month. The market fundamentals show lots of potential, mostly now that most investors are rushing to trade and invest in the sector.</p>



<p>If you want to invest in the meme market, here is a list of 8 best meme coins to buy now.</p>



<p><strong>1. Dogecoin20 (DOGE20)<br>2. Sponge V2 ($SPONGEV2) <br>3. PEEN ($PEEN) <br>4. DogWifCat (DWIFC)  <br>5. Frog Wif Hat ($FWIF<br>6. Shiba Inu (SHIB)<br>7. Pepe Coin (PEPE)<br>8. Floki Inu (FLOKI)</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://coinrepublic.care/b_btcmtx_43675?referrer=8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now!" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt;Buy The Best Coin Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Dogecoin20 (DOGE20): The Eco-Friendly DOGE Successor with High Staking Rewards</strong></h2>



<p>Dogecoin20 (DOGE20) is not another DOGE successor. Despite belonging to the same lineage, Dogecoin20 focuses on offering investors utility. The project is eco-friendly and highly adaptable compared to the original DOGE. Dogecoin20 is supported on the Ethereum blockchain and works on a Proof-of-Stake network.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full is-resized"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="812" height="628" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-347.png" alt="Meme Coins" class="wp-image-198411" style="width:1009px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-347.png 812w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-347-300x232.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-347-768x594.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-347-750x580.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 812px) 100vw, 812px" /></figure></div>


<p>Additionally, this project is designed with a fixed supply, which enables unlimited upward pressure on the token’s price. Hence, there is no fear of inflation when users invest in DOGE20. Additionally, the staking mechanism allows the holders to participate actively in the network as they earn various rewards. The holders contribute significantly to the project’s security, stability, and growth via on-chain staking. The current rewards through staking are 226%.</p>



<p>Dogecoin20 is on presale and has raised over $3.9 million in funding. This project is near the next presale stage and has a significant price increase. If you want to invest, now is a great time to buy the meme coin before its price explodes and becomes excessively expensive.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Sponge V2: Staking Success and Potential 100X Growth with Play-to-Earn Game and CEX Listings</strong></h3>



<p>Since it was introduced to the market, Sponge V2 has already staked<a href="https://x.com/spongeoneth/status/1767120226502463798?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> over 9,138,851,394 tokens</a>. The total value of staked tokens is more than $27.8 million. In case you lock your <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/20/top-5-altcoins-with-1000-upside-potential/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SPONGEV2 coins</a>, you earn up to 172% rewards rate on Ethereum and 409% on Polygon.</p>



<p>Analysts say Sponge V2 can follow BONK’s success path and gain over 100% once it features on multiple CEX listings. Another factor that will impact SPONGEV2’s price is the release of its play-to-earn (P2E) game. Its blockchain-based game will enable gamers to purchase credits and access the paid gameplay models.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="441" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346-1024x441.png" alt="Meme Coins" class="wp-image-198410" style="width:1010px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346-1024x441.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346-300x129.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346-768x331.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346-750x323.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346-1140x491.png 1140w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-346.png 1428w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure></div>


<p>Sponge V2 price forecasts say the meme coin is poised for 100X growth and might hit $0.0075 by 2025 and $0.011 by 2030. If you missed gains from SpongeBob Token, Sponge V2 could be your chance for massive ROI. For those who missed the gains offered by SpongeBob Token, Sponge V2 might provide an opportunity for massive ROI.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://bs_64bbc77e.coinrepublic.care/?referrer=8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now!" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; Buy $SPONGEV2 Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Peen Token (PEEN): The Adult-Themed Meme Coin Surging with Explosive Potential</strong></h3>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/all-about-fronk-crypto-a-meme-coin-to-develop-fair-ecosystem/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Meme coin</a> investors always prefer a crude joke regarding their projects. In that context, Peen Token (PEEN) is a meme coin powered by such fundamentals. Whenever users visit the Peen Token website, they say it resembles most high school students’ copybooks.</p>



<p>According to developers, the project will not need any pumping to thrive. The core mission of this project is to hit a $100 million market cap and offer its investors a massive return on their investment. Each investor is reminded of their inner teenager, which means this coin is destined to explode.</p>



<p>PEEN, a new meme coin, made headlines by surging by at least 300% within minutes of its launch on March 5, 2024, helping attract increased investor attention. Famous for its adult-themed humor, Peen coin can be purchased on Uniswap DEX. With a supply of 919 million PEEN, the project offers a high-reward investment opportunity in the coming months. PEEN tokens are available at $0.0001137, and users can purchase them now to enjoy massive gains in the coming weeks.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://bs_0b34fc1e.coinrepublic.care?referrer=8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now!" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>>>> Buy Peen Coin Now &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DogWifCat (DWIFC): The Explosive New Meme Coin on Solana with Over $13.5 Million Market Cap</strong></h3>



<p>As the Solana network becomes a host for many meme coins, we have seen the massive success of many animal-themed projects. A new highly explosive meme coin, DogWifCat (DWIFC), entered the scene and enjoyed a great start less than 24 hours after launch. Unlike the other Solana meme coins, it swapped the “Wif-hat” riff for a rhyming word, “Wif-cat,” which includes a unique allure to its appeal.</p>



<p>This token has a market cap of over $13.5 million and boasts a trading volume of over $7 million since its launch. Furthermore, the project has at least 1,650 DWIFC token holders, attracting investors and whales on DEX (Decentralized Exchange) platforms like Raydium and Jupiter.</p>



<p>This Solana-based meme project launched on DEXs and is already thriving. Since the launch of DogWifCat, it has grown by at least 2900%, reaching $0.0135. This project has a supply of 1 billion, and the fun and memorable branding appears promising.</p>



<p>Its early performance suggests this project has great potential and is one of the best meme coins to buy now. Ensure that you invest early to enjoy DogWifCat’s massive success.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://bs_0bb7b1ff.coinrepublic.care?referrer=8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now!" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>>>>Buy DogWifCat Now &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>FrogWifHat (FWIF): A Meme Coin with Pepe-Inspired Twist and Potential for Massive Gains</strong></h3>



<p>FrogWifHat (FWIF) is the purest form of meme coin because no fancy attachments are involved in this project. A meme coin exists primarily for gains. Interestingly, it is a throwback coin similar to Pepe (PEPE). It makes sense since there are rumors that the people who made Pepe successful are involved with FrogWifHat.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-1024x576.jpeg" alt="Meme Coins" class="wp-image-198409" style="width:1013px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-1536x864.jpeg 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-750x422.jpeg 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36-1140x641.jpeg 1140w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-36.jpeg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure></div>


<p>That is not where the similarities with Pepe stop. FrogWifHat also features a frog meme coin but is designed with a big twist. Accompanied by a beret, a glass of wine, and a baguette, the frog is as French as they can be. On that note, investors will love the meme coin as much as the frog dislikes American tourists.</p>



<p>In that context, the project is following DogWifHat’s lead, another highly successful meme coin from Solana’s network. FrogWifHat might also enjoy massive gains as its guarantee to surge is unmatchable.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://bs_f0ddeeb4.coinrepublic.care?referrer=8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now!" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; Buy FrogWifHat Now &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Shows Bullish Sentiment Despite Price Drop: Meme Count Set to Explode in 2024</strong></h3>



<p>Despite the recent drop in its price, Shiba Inu’s (SHIB) sentiment is still bullish. The meme count is set to explode to 100X in 2024, showing considerable activity with 73% green days in the past 30 days. Technical market indicators are high, reaching 96.35 and showing some bullish outlook. The analytics indicate that it might be a great time for users to invest in SHIB, considering its massive growth potential.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pepe Coin (PEPE) is a Top Meme Project: Can Gain 62% by March End</strong></h3>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/02/23/pepe-coin-analysis-heroic-entry-of-bulls-broke-the-downtrend/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Pepe Coin </a>(PEPE) is the top meme project on the Ethereum blockchain. This project resulted in the recent meme coin rush, rising 15% in the past 24 hours. In the first week of March 2024, Pepe Coin gained nearly 350%, giving millions to investors who invested $3000 in the project several weeks before.</p>



<p>Analysts predict that PEPE will rise by up to 62% by the end of March 2024. If that happens, Pepe might surge to $0.00001077.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Floki Inu (FLOKI) Surges with Bullish Sentiment: Fear &amp; Greed Index Hits 80+</strong></h3>



<p>Floki Inu’s (FLOKI) market statistics indicate a bullish sentiment, with the Fear &amp; Greed Index above 80. This project gained over 530% in March, reaching an all-time high of $0.31. It means that investors are currently buying this meme coin extensively. Interestingly, the project’s price increased by 32.79% to $0.0002439. Experts say that FLOKI will reach $0.00026 by March 25.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><a href="https://coinrepublic.care/b_btcmtx_43675?referrer=8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now!" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt;Buy Best Meme Coins Now&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Takeaway</strong></h3>



<p>The eight meme coins listed are great buys now, with guaranteed massive gains in the coming bull cycle. Their active trading and positive sentiments make them great investments in 2024. In case you want to select the best projects, this list is the perfect starting point. These projects offer utility and huge rewards while trading at lower prices.</p>



<p><strong>Disclaimer:</strong> Any information written in this press release or sponsored post does not constitute investment advice. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not, and will not endorse any information on any company or individual on this page. Readers are encouraged to do their research and take any actions based on their findings and not from any content written in this press release or sponsored post. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not and will not be responsible for any damage or loss caused directly or indirectly by the use of any content, product, or service mentioned in this press release or sponsored post.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/8-best-meme-coins-to-buy-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>RSR An Utility Token Of Reserve; Is It Heading for a Dip?</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/rsr-an-utility-token-of-reserve-is-it-heading-for-a-dip/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/rsr-an-utility-token-of-reserve-is-it-heading-for-a-dip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amanda Shinoy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSV]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="RSR" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>The RSR Operates as a utility token and plays a pivotal role in RSV crypto and confirmed a sign of weakness as the price spiked downward.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>Its price is trading at $0.007755 and shows an intraday loss of -1.84% with an average volume of 30 days is 574.46 Million.</a>
    </li>
 
</ul>






<p>Reserve(RSV) is a crypto, and its utility token’s ticker is known as RSR; it aims to establish a robust, decentralized currency system that assets will anchor. These are specifically designed to expand or contract its supply in response to market demands while ensuring a collateral surplus.</p>



<p>In particular, the &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="RSR" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/rsv-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<ul class="list-ic vertical">
    <li>
        <span>1</span>
        <a>The RSR Operates as a utility token and plays a pivotal role in RSV crypto and confirmed a sign of weakness as the price spiked downward.</a>
    </li>
    <li>
        <span>2</span>
        <a>Its price is trading at $0.007755 and shows an intraday loss of -1.84% with an average volume of 30 days is 574.46 Million.</a>
    </li>
 
</ul>






<p>Reserve(RSV) is a crypto, and its utility token’s ticker is known as RSR; it aims to establish a robust, decentralized currency system that assets will anchor. These are specifically designed to expand or contract its supply in response to market demands while ensuring a collateral surplus.</p>



<p>In particular, the initiative presents an unwavering and reliable value repository for areas that are swarmed by unstable financial systems or rampant inflation. The Reserve framework incorporates a trio of distinct tokens like RSV, RSR, and Collateral tokens.</p>



<p>Mainly, RSV functions as a stable digital currency, enabling its users to transact and save as they would with traditional money. Likewise, RSR Operates as a utility token and plays a pivotal role in preserving RSV&#8217;s equilibrium. Moreover, these collateral tokens are a diverse and distinct collection of asset-representative tokens, which include various stablecoins that the Reserve protocol employs to support the value of RSV.</p>



<p>In essence, Reserve Crypto seeks to forge a universally accessible monetary store that remains consistently stable and fully collateralized.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Volume Analysis Of Reserve (RSV) In Aspects Of RSR</strong></h2>



<p>The price and volume correlation showed that the price gained good volume from last week, February, and the price surged significantly, from a low of $0.002100 to $0.009100, where volume spiked from $25 Million to $300 million, respectively. Furthermore, the same phenomenon took the price on the daily chart and showed exponential growth.</p>



<p>However, the price met the resistance level, and the price declined. With respect to that, volume stumbled massively and declined to $40.52 million (at press time).</p>



<iframe loading="lazy" title="Santiment Chart: Price (RSR), Volume (RSR)" width="1170" height="425" src="https://embed.santiment.net/chart?ps=volt-inu-v2&#038;pt=VOLT&#038;df=2023-09-24T18%3A29%3A59.558Z&#038;dt=2024-03-24T18%3A29%3A59.558Z&#038;emcg=1&#038;wm=%5B1%3Bprice_usd%3Breserve-rights%3BRSR%5D%3B%5B1%3Bvolume_usd%3Breserve-rights%3BRSR%5D&#038;wax=0%3B1&#038;wc=%23FF5B5B%3B%23FFCB47&#038;ws=%3B" scrolling="no"></iframe>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>RSV Token In Aspects Of RSR Token</strong></h2>



<p>RSV token market cap is $50,351,486, ranked 659 in terms of market cap. The RSR token is essential for Reserve (RSV).</p>



<p>The Reserve Rights token showed a fruitful performance in 2024 and exponential growth over the daily chart. It has shown good performance in the past week, month, and three months by 28.37%, 154.74%, and 142.64%, respectively, indicating a consistent upward trend.</p>



<p>However, the RSR Operates as a utility token and plays a pivotal role in RSV crypto; the RSR crypto confirmed a sign of weakness as the price spiked downward from a key level of around $0.009500 on the chart. The asset is displaying bearish characteristics and can reduce its price more as more buyers are losing their ground, and sellers seem to be in the driving seat now.</p>



<p>Therefore, RSV utility<a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/a-comprehensive-guide-to-erc-404-a-hybrid-token-standard/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> token</a> RSR crypto appears close to a considerable drop, as it reached the resistance level at the supply region and has set its path towards new depths from the current zone.</p>



<p>The RSR asset working for Reserve asset is demonstrating bearishness and downward momentum as it sinks below the supply and approaches major trend 20-day and 50-day EMA bands from above, subject to the sellers&#8217; surge, which could lead to a giant plunge on the chart.</p>



<p>On observing indicators of the Reserve asset, it is showing bearish signs as the RSI has taken rejection from 14-SMA and is approaching the 50 level from above, indicating that the RSR asset (utility token of RSV asset) is approaching a bearish zone and can go lower.</p>



<p>At press time, its price is trading at $0.007755 and shows an intraday loss of -1.84% with an average volume of 30 days is 574.46 Million.</p>



<p>Therefore, if the price slips past the $0.007000 price level, it could deteriorate and reach a lower level. However, if the asset price turns around and surpasses the supply level at $0.009500, it could open the door to new heights.</p>



<!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN -->

<script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"></script>

<script type="text/javascript">

var tradingview_embed_options = {};

tradingview_embed_options.width = '980';

tradingview_embed_options.height = '425';

tradingview_embed_options.chart = 'oTooGyHg';

new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);

</script>

<p><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/chart/RSRUSDT/oTooGyHg-Reserve-asset-is-demonstrating-bearishness/"></a><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/u/Sam_TCR/"></a><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/"></a></p>

<!-- TradingView Chart END -->



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Reserve had a strong performance in 2024, with significant growth over various time spans. Despite this, recent trends suggest a bearish outlook as the price has declined from a key level of $0.009500.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The RSR token, which is crucial for the functioning of the Reserve (RSV) stablecoin, is showing signs of weakness, with technical indicators like the RSI and EMA bands indicating potential further declines.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The current trading price is $0.007755, with a recent intraday loss of 1.84%. If the price falls below $0.007000, it could signal a continued downtrend, whereas a rebound above $0.009500 could lead to a recovery and new highs.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Technical Levels</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Support Levels</strong>: $0.007000</p>



<p><strong>Resistance Levels</strong>: $0.009500</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>In this article, the views, and opinions stated by the author, or any people named are for informational purposes only, and they don’t establish the investment, financial, or any other advice. Trading or investing in cryptocurrency assets comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/rsr-an-utility-token-of-reserve-is-it-heading-for-a-dip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Staking Made Simple with DeFi Altcoins Polygon, Litecoin &#038; Scorpion Casino </title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/crypto-staking-made-simple-with-defi-altcoins-polygon-litecoin-scorpion-casino/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/crypto-staking-made-simple-with-defi-altcoins-polygon-litecoin-scorpion-casino/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Chess]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi  Ecosystem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi Altcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1.png 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-300x169.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-768x432.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-1536x864.png 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-750x422.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-1140x641.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p>The decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape is undergoing a dynamic transformation, with crypto staking emerging as a prominent investment strategy. This method allows investors to earn passive income on their holdings by locking them up in a smart contract to support the operations of a blockchain network. Staking rewards have become a major draw for investors, particularly in the current bull run, where established projects and innovative newcomers are vying for attention.</p>



<p>This article will dissect three DeFi altcoins generating significant buzz &#8211; Polygon (MATIC), Litecoin (LTC), and <a href="https://presale.scorpion.casino/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Scorpion Casino (SCORP)</a> &#8211; to help readers navigate the intricacies of crypto staking &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1.png 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-300x169.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-768x432.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-1536x864.png 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-750x422.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-345-1-1140x641.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p>The decentralized finance (DeFi) landscape is undergoing a dynamic transformation, with crypto staking emerging as a prominent investment strategy. This method allows investors to earn passive income on their holdings by locking them up in a smart contract to support the operations of a blockchain network. Staking rewards have become a major draw for investors, particularly in the current bull run, where established projects and innovative newcomers are vying for attention.</p>



<p>This article will dissect three DeFi altcoins generating significant buzz &#8211; Polygon (MATIC), Litecoin (LTC), and <a href="https://presale.scorpion.casino/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Scorpion Casino (SCORP)</a> &#8211; to help readers navigate the intricacies of crypto staking and identify the project best aligned with their investment goals. By examining the unique value propositions and staking mechanisms offered by each, this article aims to equip investors with the necessary insights to make informed decisions within the rapidly evolving DeFi ecosystem.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Scorpion Casino Mixing up the Status Quo&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/24/can-you-make-money-with-crypto-how-trending-coins-like-mania-bitbot-scorpion-casino-are-redefining-earnings/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Scorpion Casino</a> may have been getting plaudits for its record-breaking presale, which has raised over $8.5 million. Still, its ecosystem, with over 30,000 betting options, 210 casino games, and 160 live dealer tables, caters to a wide range of gaming preferences. However, the true game-changer lies in SCORP&#8217;s unique tokenomics.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The increasing Scorpion Casino feature list offers daily passive income for token holders directly tied to the casino&#8217;s performance. This groundbreaking feature, powered by an automatic staking mechanism, allows users to earn up to 10,000 USDT in daily passive income, regardless of market conditions.</p>



<p>Purchased SCORP tokens are also automatically staked, eliminating the complexities often associated with traditional staking methods. The excitement surrounding SCORP is palpable, with a rapidly closing presale already surpassing $8.5 million and a significant exchange listing scheduled for March 25th. What’s more, the project&#8217;s commitment to user engagement is further solidified by its ongoing $250,000 giveaway.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344-1024x576.png" alt="DeFi" class="wp-image-198398" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344-300x169.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344-768x432.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344-750x422.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344-1140x641.png 1140w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-344.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure></div>


<p class="has-text-align-center"><strong><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3b0.png" alt="🎰" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Do You Want To Own Part Of A Casino?<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3b0.png" alt="🎰" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polygon (MATIC) The Staking Powerhouse, But Lacks Direct User Rewards</strong></h2>



<p>2017 Polygon emerged as a leading layer-2 scaling solution for the Ethereum network. This innovative platform offers faster transaction speeds and lower fees than the congested Ethereum blockchain. Polygon also boasts a robust staking ecosystem, allowing users to earn rewards for contributing to network security by staking<a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2020/04/07/matic-network-unlocks-100-of-team-foundation-tokens/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> MATIC tokens</a>.</p>



<p>While Polygon offers a compelling staking solution, it needs the direct user rewards and engagement features that set Scorpion Casino apart. Investors seeking a more interactive and potentially lucrative crypto experience might find SCORP&#8217;s model more appealing.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Litecoin (LTC) Has Recent Upgrades But Limited Scope</strong></h2>



<p>Launched in 2011, Litecoin is a well-established cryptocurrency often called &#8220;silver to Bitcoin&#8217;s gold.&#8221;&nbsp; Like Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/20/litecoin-price-prediction-ltc-goes-bearish-what-next/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Litecoin</a> utilizes a Proof-of-Work (PoW) consensus mechanism, allowing users to earn rewards for mining new LTC blocks. The recent Litecoin Core v0.21.3rc3 upgrade focused on improving network security and functionality, showcasing the project&#8217;s commitment to staying relevant.</p>



<p>Despite its veteran status, Litecoin&#8217;s staking capabilities are limited compared to the other contenders. Furthermore, it needs Scorpion Casino&#8217;s comprehensive ecosystem and user engagement features.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Staking Made Easy</strong></h2>



<p>The current bull run presents many investment opportunities within the DeFi staking landscape. Polygon offers a robust staking infrastructure, while Litecoin boasts a long-standing reputation. However, Scorpion Casino stands out with its unique blend of gaming, a groundbreaking passive income model, and a commitment to user rewards.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This multifaceted approach positions SCORP as a strong contender for investors seeking a well-rounded DeFi project with the potential for substantial growth. With the presale rapidly closing and a significant exchange listing on the horizon, Scorpion Casino might be the project to propel investors toward a windfall of USDT rewards.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Like to know more about the new Scorpion Casino project? Take a look at the links below</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Presale</strong>:<a href="https://presale.scorpion.casino/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> https://presale.scorpion.casino/</a> </p>



<p><strong>Twitter</strong>:<a href="https://twitter.com/ScorpionCasino" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> https://twitter.com/ScorpionCasino</a></p>



<p><strong>Telegram</strong>:<a href="https://t.me/scorpioncasino_official" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> https://t.me/scorpioncasino_official</a></p>



<p><strong>Disclaimer:</strong> Any information written in this press release or sponsored post does not constitute investment advice. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not, and will not endorse any information on any company or individual on this page. Readers are encouraged to do their research and take any actions based on their findings and not from any content written in this press release or sponsored post. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not and will not be responsible for any damage or loss caused directly or indirectly by the use of any content, product, or service mentioned in this press release or sponsored post.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/crypto-staking-made-simple-with-defi-altcoins-polygon-litecoin-scorpion-casino/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Clients’ Growing Interest in Crypto, Reports Shows</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/goldman-sachs-clients-growing-interest-in-crypto-reports-shows/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/goldman-sachs-clients-growing-interest-in-crypto-reports-shows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Adarsh ​​Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Group Inc (GS)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs Group Inc. (NYSE: GS)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Goldman Sachs" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>Goldman Sachs’ Asia Pacific division is observing a revived inclination towards crypto assets. Specifically Institutional clients.  </strong></em></p>



<p>Goldman Sachs has noticed an increasing interest in cryptocurrency among its clients this year. The approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) has been a factor in reigniting their enthusiasm for assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Max Minton Shared The Reports</strong></h2>



<p>According to Max Minton, Head of Assets for Goldman Asia Pacific, many of the firm&#8217;s clients have either started getting involved in the crypto industry or are considering entering it. The approval of ten Bitcoin ETFs in the United States in January sparked renewed interest among their clients.&#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Goldman Sachs" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Goldman-Sachs-hedge-fund-clients-are-piling-back-into-crypto-this-year-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>Goldman Sachs’ Asia Pacific division is observing a revived inclination towards crypto assets. Specifically Institutional clients.  </strong></em></p>



<p>Goldman Sachs has noticed an increasing interest in cryptocurrency among its clients this year. The approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) has been a factor in reigniting their enthusiasm for assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Max Minton Shared The Reports</strong></h2>



<p>According to Max Minton, Head of Assets for Goldman Asia Pacific, many of the firm&#8217;s clients have either started getting involved in the crypto industry or are considering entering it. The approval of ten Bitcoin ETFs in the United States in January sparked renewed interest among their clients.</p>



<p>While <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/02/24/goldman-sachs-delays-fed-rate-cut-amid-solid-growth-of-sp-500/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> currently doesn&#8217;t provide products, its clients have been interacting with the bank through options and future offerings related to cryptocurrencies. Hedge funds have especially shown interest in this field. As of the end of 2023, Goldman Sachs reported a record-breaking $2.8 trillion in assets under management.</p>



<p>Minton highlighted that clients use derivatives to capitalize on crypto volatility and make informed predictions about price movements. Despite introducing a trading desk in 2021, Goldman Sachs services are limited to derivatives, like Bitcoin and Ether options and futures.</p>



<p>Crypto enthusiasm might have dipped a bit in the year. Minton observed an apparent uptick in new participants, market activity, and trade volume since the start of this year. This trend indicates a rising trust in the potential of cryptocurrencies among sectors.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Not Now, But Soon&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Goldman Sachs does not offer any immediate cryptocurrency products to its clients, although it launched their first cryptocurrency trading desk in 2021. Currently, the trading desk only gives exposure to cryptocurrency derivatives, such as Bitcoin and Ethereum.&nbsp;</p>



<p>According to the head of digital assets at Goldman Sachs, Mathew McDermott, client interest in onboarding, pipeline, and volume has increased since the start of the year. McDermott stated that clients primarily use derivatives to gain exposure to the volatility of cryptocurrency and make predictions on where prices are headed in the mid-term.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Clients Show Interest in Bitcoin-related products</strong></h2>



<p>Active clients have shown a preference for Bitcoin-related products as the most popular investment vehicle, McDermott added. Furthermore, McDermott mentioned the possibility of an Ether ETF approval in the US, potentially shifting institutional clients towards Ether.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, according to Bloomberg ETF analysts, the chances of an Ether ETF approval by May are only 35%. The extended lack of response from the Securities and Exchange Commission towards potential fund issuers is viewed as more negative. Regardless of the approval of an ETF, Goldman Sachs plans to widen its client base to include banks, asset management funds, and more specialized firms dealing with crypto assets in the future.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Goldman Sachs has seen increased client interest in cryptocurrency this year. Many clients are using derivatives to capitalize on crypto&#8217;s volatility. Although they introduced a trading desk in 2021, their services are limited to Bitcoin and Ether options and futures.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any people named in this article are for informational purposes only. They do not establish financial, investment, or other advice. Investing in or trading in stocks, cryptos, or other related indexes comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/goldman-sachs-clients-growing-interest-in-crypto-reports-shows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LTC and APT Communities Rally to Fezoo (FEZ) Presale, Attracted by 40X Forecast</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/ltc-and-apt-communities-rally-to-fezoo-fez-presale-attracted-by-40x-forecast/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/ltc-and-apt-communities-rally-to-fezoo-fez-presale-attracted-by-40x-forecast/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Chadhokar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fezoo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="LTC" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1.png 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-300x169.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-768x432.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-1536x864.png 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-750x422.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-1140x641.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p>It took a long while before industry players and enthusiasts knew the endless possibilities in the blockchain ecosystem. Since then, developers have exploited various use cases and launched several protocols with exciting features.&#160;</p>



<p>One such blockchain protocol with multiple use cases and exciting features is <a href="https://fezoo.tech" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Fezoo (FEZ)</a>, which explores new possibilities by introducing a more decentralized exchange platform. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Fezoo (FEZ) Gathers Community Attention With 40X Forecast</strong></h2>



<p>Crypto investors and traders have been seeking a viable and reliable alternative to centralized exchanges for a while now. No wonder there has been increased community attention around<a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/21/ethereum-classic-dai-holders-see-opportunity-in-fezoo-fez-for-a-25x-uplift/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> Fezoo</a>, as it presents &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="LTC" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1.png 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-300x169.png 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-768x432.png 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-1536x864.png 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-750x422.png 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234826.147-1-1140x641.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p>It took a long while before industry players and enthusiasts knew the endless possibilities in the blockchain ecosystem. Since then, developers have exploited various use cases and launched several protocols with exciting features.&nbsp;</p>



<p>One such blockchain protocol with multiple use cases and exciting features is <a href="https://fezoo.tech" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Fezoo (FEZ)</a>, which explores new possibilities by introducing a more decentralized exchange platform. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Fezoo (FEZ) Gathers Community Attention With 40X Forecast</strong></h2>



<p>Crypto investors and traders have been seeking a viable and reliable alternative to centralized exchanges for a while now. No wonder there has been increased community attention around<a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/21/ethereum-classic-dai-holders-see-opportunity-in-fezoo-fez-for-a-25x-uplift/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> Fezoo</a>, as it presents a decentralized exchange platform where traders can connect and transact for just $0.013 and potentially surge 40X.&nbsp;</p>



<p>During and after the presale, FEZ holders will completely control their funds when they set up their wallets by entering their email addresses and usernames. When you invest in this crypto at its presale, you enjoy lower trading fees and can use trading bots to make copy trades. This trading bot helps you prompt your trade orders instead of manually putting them.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It offers a sophisticated VIP program that rewards users for their trading activity. Unlike other exchange platforms that charge for every trade, Fezoo encourages more trading by offering rewards and kickbacks. The more you trade using Fezoo FEZ, the higher your rewards and the more you can move up the ranks. Besides, the cherry on top? More trading on Fezoo can attract up to a 70% kickback.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bumpy Roads Ahead of Litecoin (LTC) Rally To $100</strong></h3>



<p>Litecoin recently recorded a surge to about $87.79, with expectations that it will cross the $90 support level and coast toward $100. However, LTC has recorded a price decline to $86.69. Analysts considered this setback a bumpy ride for this coin and attributed it to price correction across the crypto market.&nbsp;</p>



<p>On the brighter side, Litecoin has other metrics that make the $100 rally inevitable. They include the continuous surge in average transaction size on LTC in the last 60 days. As of March 24, the average transaction size on Litecoin (LTC) has reached $17,594, representing a 768% growth within the last 60 trading days. Litecoin (LTC) enthusiasts rally to <a href="https://fezoo.tech" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Fezoo (FEZ)</a>, confident that such a decentralized exchange would push up transactions and guarantee a 40X return.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Aptos (APT) Holders Remain Confident Amidst The Bull Run</strong></h3>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2023/09/25/crypto-exchange-upbits-confusing-act-around-aptos-apt-token/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Aptos (APT)</a> remains an unpopular token performing well in the market. According to CoinMarketCap, APT, with a price value above $16, recorded a 22.5% increase in the last week, while other popular assets were nosediving at the same percentage.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Similarly, this token’s trading volume continues to spike with increased investor movement and a market cap of $6.5B. With APT&#8217;s latest partnership with Movement Labs towards enhancing interoperability, we expect increased movement and a significant upsurge in the crypto price value.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Find out more about the Fezoo (FEZ) presale by visiting the website </strong><a href="https://fezoo.tech/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>.</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong>: Any information written in this press release or sponsored post does not constitute investment advice. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not, and will not endorse any information on any company or individual on this page. Readers are encouraged to do their research and take any actions based on their findings and not from any content written in this press release or sponsored post. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not and will not be responsible for any damage or loss caused directly or indirectly by the use of any content, product, or service mentioned in this press release or sponsored post.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/ltc-and-apt-communities-rally-to-fezoo-fez-presale-attracted-by-40x-forecast/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NoOnes CEO Ray Youssef is Bullish On the Nigerian Crypto Economy </title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/noones-ceo-ray-youssef-is-bullish-on-the-nigerian-crypto-economy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/noones-ceo-ray-youssef-is-bullish-on-the-nigerian-crypto-economy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Anderrson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigerian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NoOnes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198447</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="NoOnes" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>Ray Youssef is hopeful Nigeria&#8217;s crypto industry will grow despite recent regulatory hurdles. Data shows that Nigeria is experiencing a surge in the crypto market.</strong></em></p>



<p>Despite the proposed increase in crypto registration fees, venture capitalists still see potential in Nigeria. However, the services they provide may struggle to gain momentum due to government restrictions on P2P platforms aimed at curbing free market promotion, according to Ray Youssef, the CEO of NoOnes, a financial communication and P2P app.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ray Youssef’s NoOnes</strong></h2>



<p>NoOnes is an app that connects people to the global financial system, empowering them in the process. Its &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="NoOnes" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Nigerian-crypto-fee-hike-invitation-for-crypto-‘big-boys-—-NoOnes-CEO-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>Ray Youssef is hopeful Nigeria&#8217;s crypto industry will grow despite recent regulatory hurdles. Data shows that Nigeria is experiencing a surge in the crypto market.</strong></em></p>



<p>Despite the proposed increase in crypto registration fees, venture capitalists still see potential in Nigeria. However, the services they provide may struggle to gain momentum due to government restrictions on P2P platforms aimed at curbing free market promotion, according to Ray Youssef, the CEO of NoOnes, a financial communication and P2P app.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ray Youssef’s NoOnes</strong></h2>



<p>NoOnes is an app that connects people to the global financial system, empowering them in the process. Its marketplace allows users from the Global South to trade with a variety of payment methods while also facilitating peer-to-peer payments through a Bitcoin wallet that stores value.&nbsp;</p>



<p>NoOnes offers more than 450 payment methods, which include banks, Momo, and online wallets. The app&#8217;s fees are as follows: there is no fee for selling cryptocurrency, no fee for credit/debit cards, digital currencies, online wallets, and cash, which is set at 1%, no fee for gift cards, which is set at 5%, and 0% trading fees for the USDT and Nigerian Naira pair.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Regulations in Nigeria&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>A recent report by Nigeria&#8217;s Securities and <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/03/23/heres-why-thailand-securities-and-exchange-commission-banned-crypto-transactions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) suggested amendments to the rules guiding platforms offering crypto services. The proposed report recommends increasing the registration fee for crypto exchanges from 30 million naira ($18,620) to 150 million naira ($93,000).</p>



<p>Youssef believes that the increase will attract crypto &#8220;big boys&#8221; like Coinbase and other major companies to operate in the Nigerian market. He emphasized that the government aims to restrict P2P services to address foreign exchange challenges, and exchanges willing to forgo P2P support can operate smoothly in Nigeria.</p>



<p>However, this approach contradicts the Nigerian crypto market&#8217;s strong preference for P2P trading, a major challenge for exchanges. Nonetheless, despite the recent regulatory challenges, Youssef is still hopeful regarding Nigeria&#8217;s ability to maintain its position in the ecosystem.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Youssef Shares His Views</strong></h2>



<p>Youssef said the government could use the abundance of P2P traders in Nigeria. They can be used as an asset and treat crypto stakeholders as allies to understand how to use crypto to the advantage of the nation&#8217;s economy.</p>



<p>Nigeria is currently the world&#8217;s largest P2P crypto market, which came about after the Central Bank of Nigeria banned institutions from buying and selling crypto in 2021. As of December 2023, Nigerian crypto exchanges can apply for licenses in Nigeria following the government&#8217;s lifting of the 2021 crypto ban.</p>



<p>Regarding the recent partnership between Gluwa and the Nigerian government to improve the adoption of the nation&#8217;s central bank digital currency (CBDC), the eNaira, Youssef said the government could have taken a different approach when introducing the CBDC.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This could be done by leveraging it to stimulate local economic growth, providing credit to aspiring entrepreneurs, and encouraging the younger generation to embrace it. In February, the Nigerian government&#8217;s criticism of crypto exchanges singled out Binance.&nbsp; This ceased operations using the naira on March 8.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Nigeria&#8217;s SEC proposed higher crypto registration fees. Despite government criticism of exchanges, venture capitalists still see potential in Nigeria&#8217;s crypto market. P2P trading is preferred, posing an obstacle for exchanges. In February, Binance was criticized by the Nigerian government.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any people named in this article are for informational purposes only. They do not establish financial, investment, or other advice. Investing in or trading in stocks, cryptos, or other related indexes comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/noones-ceo-ray-youssef-is-bullish-on-the-nigerian-crypto-economy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon and Chainlink Advocates Discover the Advantages of Lending with Kelexo</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/polygon-and-chainlink-advocates-discover-the-advantages-of-lending-with-kelexo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/polygon-and-chainlink-advocates-discover-the-advantages-of-lending-with-kelexo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Serena James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Polygon" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p>New opportunities are constantly rising in the cryptocurrency market. Its diversity can be a blessing and a curse, especially for newbies in the industry. For those who do not know which projects have potential, it is easy for them to fall for scam projects and incur severe financial losses. However, for expert traders, identifying potentially successful coins is the first step to massive gains.</p>



<p>Polygon (MATIC) and Chainlink (LINK) traders are beginning to realize the advantages of the new lending platform, Kelexo (KLXO). These traders are making moves to join the <a href="http://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kelexo</a> (KLXO) train before the end of its presale.&#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Polygon" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234554.167-1-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p>New opportunities are constantly rising in the cryptocurrency market. Its diversity can be a blessing and a curse, especially for newbies in the industry. For those who do not know which projects have potential, it is easy for them to fall for scam projects and incur severe financial losses. However, for expert traders, identifying potentially successful coins is the first step to massive gains.</p>



<p>Polygon (MATIC) and Chainlink (LINK) traders are beginning to realize the advantages of the new lending platform, Kelexo (KLXO). These traders are making moves to join the <a href="http://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kelexo</a> (KLXO) train before the end of its presale.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How does the launch of RIP affect Polygon (MATIC) price?</strong></h2>



<p>The <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2022/03/16/dr-disrespect-disallowed-by-twitch-releases-gaming-nfts-on-polygon-network/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polygon network</a> recently put out an announcement stating the successful implementation of RIP on its chain, which is expected to drive down transaction fees for roll-ups.</p>



<p>However, the price of MATIC has not yet benefited from this significant improvement to the network. It is currently trading under $1 af $0.986. It had dropped by 9.95% in only 7 days. This token has a market cap of $9.86 billion and a 7 days trading volume of about $2.36 billion.&nbsp;</p>



<p>There seems to be a bearish momentum building that could see Polygon (MATIC) drop to the $0.5000 zone.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Chainlink (LINK) is on its way to a significant price breakout</strong></h3>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/23/chainlink-surpassed-cardano-secured-top-rank-as-dev-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Chainlink</a> is currently trading at $18.05, and from all indications, it looks like the coin is set for a substantial rise in value. Though trading at 5.24% less than 7 days ago and about 2.32% below last month, analysts believe LINK could enter a bull run soon.</p>



<p>The immediate resistance level for the coin is around $18.5 and should Chainlink surpass this resistance level, it could be headed toward $30</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Kelexo (KLXO) way of lending and borrowing</strong></h3>



<p>Kelexo might be the most profitable opportunity available in the cryptocurrency market. It has drawn the attention of investors and expert traders with its exciting opportunities and mouth-watering returns on every investment.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is a golden opportunity for investors to make massive profits before the end of the year. Its unique prospects have analysts predicting as much as 25x gains from the coin.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It) is a golden opportunity for investors to make massive profits before the end of the year. Its unique prospects have analysts predicting as much as 25x gains from the coin. These predictions are backed by the exciting features of the <a href="http://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kelexo</a> (KLXO) platform.</p>



<p>KLXO removes the need for an intermediary in loan transactions. Borrowers and lenders can come together in one marketplace and decide to favor both parties. It increases the speed of transactions and eases the entire process.</p>



<p>A token of Kelexo (KLXO) is available for only $0.05, which is the cheapest it will ever be. Investors have an early opportunity to buy into an excellent project at a low price point. You do not want to miss out on this.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Find out more about the Kelexo (KLXO) presale by visiting the website </strong><a href="https://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>.</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Disclaimer:</strong> Any information written in this press release or sponsored post does not constitute investment advice. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not, and will not endorse any information on any company or individual on this page. Readers are encouraged to do their research and take any actions based on their findings and not from any content written in this press release or sponsored post. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not and will not be responsible for any damage or loss caused directly or indirectly by the use of any content, product, or service mentioned in this press release or sponsored post.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/polygon-and-chainlink-advocates-discover-the-advantages-of-lending-with-kelexo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin News: Spot ETFs Outflow, JP Morgan Analysts on BTC Price</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/bitcoin-news-spot-etfs-outflow-jp-morgan-analysts-on-btc-price/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/bitcoin-news-spot-etfs-outflow-jp-morgan-analysts-on-btc-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steefan George]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price chart]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>After the Current Ups &#38; Downs in BTC Price, Bitcoin ETFs Saw Huge Outflows. The Analysts at J.P Morgan Believe That Bitcoin is OverValued.</strong></em></p>



<p>Despite Bitcoin’s price facing pressure and currently trading at $64,051 with a market cap of $1.259 trillion, analyst Michael van de Poppe sees BlackRock’s consistent inflows into Spot Bitcoin ETFs as a positive sign of ongoing institutional buying activity, which suggests that the market cycle is far from over.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>OutFlows in Bitcoin ETFs&#160;</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/01/15/spot-bitcoin-etfs-would-push-btc-price-to-500k-crypto-trader/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin ETFs</a> saw a total outflow of over $888 million this week, with Spot Bitcoin ETFs experiencing a net outflow of $51.6 million &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-ETF-Weekly-Outflows-Reach-900M-JP-Morgan-Analysts-Labeled-Bitcoin-Overvalued-News-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>After the Current Ups &amp; Downs in BTC Price, Bitcoin ETFs Saw Huge Outflows. The Analysts at J.P Morgan Believe That Bitcoin is OverValued.</strong></em></p>



<p>Despite Bitcoin’s price facing pressure and currently trading at $64,051 with a market cap of $1.259 trillion, analyst Michael van de Poppe sees BlackRock’s consistent inflows into Spot Bitcoin ETFs as a positive sign of ongoing institutional buying activity, which suggests that the market cycle is far from over.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>OutFlows in Bitcoin ETFs&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/01/15/spot-bitcoin-etfs-would-push-btc-price-to-500k-crypto-trader/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin ETFs</a> saw a total outflow of over $888 million this week, with Spot Bitcoin ETFs experiencing a net outflow of $51.6 million on Friday, March 22. GBTC alone recorded a single-day outflow of $169 million. However, BlackRock’s ETF (IBIT) observed minimal net inflows, helping mitigate some negative impacts.</p>



<p>The persistent outflows from GBTC continue to impact the Bitcoin ETF market, with Thursday, March 21, seeing another substantial outflow of $359 million, summing up to $1.8 billion for the week. Additionally, Bitcoin ETF outflows accelerated, reaching $95 million on the same day.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>GBTC&#8217;s Single-Day Outflow</strong></h2>



<p>GBTC faced a significant single-day outflow of $386 million on Wednesday, March 20, while IBIT saw a considerable inflow of $49.28 million, bringing its total historical net inflow to $13.09 billion. However, concerns over central bank actions have led to a drying up of ETF inflows this week.</p>



<p>On Tuesday, March 19, Bitcoin ETFs saw outflows for multiple days, amounting to $326 million. It has caused a shift in the market sentiment. Institutional investors appeared to be cautious with the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) decision scheduled for March 20.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As a result, there have been subdued inflows across most ETFs.GBTC’s losses were increased by a massive $444 million outflow on Tuesday, while BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF regained momentum on Monday, March 18, with $451.5 million inflows, contrasting with minimal inflows for other ETFs.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>JP Morgan Analysts Share Their Views on Bitcoin</strong></h2>



<p>JP Morgan has warned that the recent slowdowns in spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) inflows cast doubt on the market’s optimistic prediction of year-end price hikes.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Expectations were optimistic for steady demand driven by bitcoin ETFs and the approaching Bitcoin halving event. However, these latest statistics indicate that the influx of funds into spot ETFs may not be as consistent as previously anticipated.</p>



<p>10 spot bitcoin ETFs that began trading in early January saw money flow out last week as Grayscale’s bitcoin trust (GBTC) continued to see significant outflows.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>A Drop Coming in BTC Price- JP Morgan Analysts</strong></h2>



<p>JPMorgan analysts have predicted a drop in Bitcoin’s price to $42,000 after the April halving. JPMorgan believes that the halving and Ethereum upgrade will not significantly impact the market as it has already factored them in. The bank&#8217;s CEO, Jamie Dimon, remains skeptical of cryptocurrencies and has no plans to invest in Bitcoin.</p>



<p>In an interview with CNBC, Jamie Dimon expressed his belief that cryptocurrency is a minor aspect of finance and requires too much attention. He compared crypto tokens to pet rocks and criticized the excessive hype around them. However, as always, Jamie has acknowledged the legitimacy of blockchain technology and Web 3.0.</p>



<p>He questioned why such illegal activities are allowed to take place and why banks are blamed while crypto remains unchecked. He also discussed the possibility of a wage-price spiral, which could be a concern.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>Bitcoin ETFs saw a net outflow of over $888m this week. JP Morgan has warned that the recent slowdowns in spot Bitcoin ETF inflows cast doubt on the market’s optimistic prediction of year-end price hikes. Jamie Dimon expressed his belief that cryptocurrency is a minor aspect of finance and requires too much attention.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any people named in this article are for informational purposes only. They do not establish financial, investment, or other advice. Investing in or trading in stocks, cryptos, or other related indexes comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/bitcoin-news-spot-etfs-outflow-jp-morgan-analysts-on-btc-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts Tip Kelexo for Huge Gains, Sparking Interest Among DOGE and SHIB Holders</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/analysts-tip-kelexo-for-huge-gains-sparking-interest-among-doge-and-shib-holders/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/analysts-tip-kelexo-for-huge-gains-sparking-interest-among-doge-and-shib-holders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sam Chess]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kelexo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198380</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Kelexo" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p>A major driving force for the prices of some cryptocurrencies is the hype around the coins. This hype creates a buying frenzy that leads to an increase in the prices of these coins. Many, if not all, meme coins usually benefit from this strategy to see an uptick in the market charts. However, many investors know that massive profits come from projects with real utility.</p>



<p>Investors are buying into the new Kelexo (KLXO) for its potential for massive gains as the new lending platform plans to dominate its industry. Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) enthusiasts have identified <a href="http://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kelexo</a> as &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Kelexo" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image1-2024-03-25T234056.270-1-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p>A major driving force for the prices of some cryptocurrencies is the hype around the coins. This hype creates a buying frenzy that leads to an increase in the prices of these coins. Many, if not all, meme coins usually benefit from this strategy to see an uptick in the market charts. However, many investors know that massive profits come from projects with real utility.</p>



<p>Investors are buying into the new Kelexo (KLXO) for its potential for massive gains as the new lending platform plans to dominate its industry. Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) enthusiasts have identified <a href="http://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kelexo</a> as a great project to reinvest the profits made this month.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Whale activity lifts Dogecoin (DOGE) price</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/21/coinbase-to-launch-dogecoin-futures-trading-cftcs-letter/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dogecoin</a> is counting monthly gains of about 75.45%. The ninth-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization is currently trading at $0.1484. The whales seem to be active in the DOGE market, as the number of transactions worth $1 million and more has increased by about 600% in the last month alone.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This increased activity of large investors in the market is expected to grow the price of Dogecoin, with analysts predicting the popular meme coin could reach $0.600 in a few months.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Increasing Shiba Inu (SHIB) activity</strong></h3>



<p>There has been so much activity within the <a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2023/06/26/shiba-inu-another-notable-token-on-ethereum-network-to-invest/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Shiba Inu network</a>. It is reported that more than two trillion SHIB tokens have changed hands in only a few days. The network has recorded several large transactions and analysts are predicting that this whale activity might be good for the price of thsee token.</p>



<p>SHIB is selling at $0.00002622, recording gains of up to 170% in the last month. It has a 7-day trading volume of $10.05 billion.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Kelexo (KLXO): the innovative solution to lending problems</strong></h3>



<p>Kelexo is an innovative lending platform that seeks to transform the borrowing experience into a seamless and stress-free process.</p>



<p>Unlike traditional methods that require longer processing times due to bureaucracy and third-party interference, it is introducing a fully decentralized model that will help provide loans faster and at lower costs.</p>



<p>This project is a success story waiting to happen and analysts predict that its rise will not only be astronomical but will also rival that of top cryptocurrencies in the industry.</p>



<p>Kelexo (KLXO) investors are in luck as they can purchase a token of Kelexo at a giveaway price of only $0.05 while the coin is in its second stage of <a href="https://presale.kelexo.com/login" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">presale</a>. Aside from the enormous profits that are sure to come from these tokens, the holders will also be able to determine the future of the platform through their votes and suggestions. </p>



<p>The price of KLXO could rise soon, so hurry up and get a token while it is still available for a cheap price.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Find out more about the Kelexo (KLXO) presale by visiting the website </strong><a href="https://kelexo.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>.</strong></h4>



<p><strong>Disclaimer: </strong>Any information written in this press release or sponsored post does not constitute investment advice. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not, and will not endorse any information on any company or individual on this page. Readers are encouraged to do their research and take any actions based on their findings and not from any content written in this press release or sponsored post. Thecoinrepublic.com and all its authors do not and will not be responsible for any damage or loss caused directly or indirectly by the use of any content, product, or service mentioned in this press release or sponsored post.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/analysts-tip-kelexo-for-huge-gains-sparking-interest-among-doge-and-shib-holders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SLERF’s $10M Disaster, While GFOX Presale Soared to $6 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/slerfs-10m-disaster-while-gfox-presale-soared-to-6-million/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/slerfs-10m-disaster-while-gfox-presale-soared-to-6-million/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ritika Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GFOX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GFOX  Presale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/?p=198445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="GFOX " style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><p><em><strong>SLERF,  Solana&#8217;s newest blockchain, is in the news for a $10M disaster. Moreover, the presale for the P2E GFOX aims to reach $6 million this week.   </strong></em></p>



<p>The cryptocurrency market is experiencing a surge in investment as more players explore the play-to-earn option, and new blockchains continue to emerge on Solana.&#160;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>GFOX Presale is Catering Spotlight</strong></h2>



<p>The GFOX crypto, an ERC-20 meme token, has been gaining popularity with its meteoric rise. This hybrid meme coin has already achieved an impressive $6 million in sales, setting a new benchmark for the potential of meme coins in 2024.&#160;</p>



<p>GFOX is a hybrid token &#8230;</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1920" height="1080" src="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News.webp" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="GFOX " style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" srcset="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News.webp 1920w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-750x422.webp 750w, https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GFOX-presale-aims-at-6m-as-SLERFs-10m-disaster-draws-reactions-News-1140x641.webp 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" />
<p><em><strong>SLERF,  Solana&#8217;s newest blockchain, is in the news for a $10M disaster. Moreover, the presale for the P2E GFOX aims to reach $6 million this week.   </strong></em></p>



<p>The cryptocurrency market is experiencing a surge in investment as more players explore the play-to-earn option, and new blockchains continue to emerge on Solana.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>GFOX Presale is Catering Spotlight</strong></h2>



<p>The GFOX crypto, an ERC-20 meme token, has been gaining popularity with its meteoric rise. This hybrid meme coin has already achieved an impressive $6 million in sales, setting a new benchmark for the potential of meme coins in 2024.&nbsp;</p>



<p>GFOX is a hybrid token with multiple utilities on the Galaxy Fox network and premium potential for passive income. Galaxy Fox generates financial rewards and offers premium entertainment value for investors by incorporating play-to-earn (P2E) and memecoin features.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Huge Marketplace of Galaxy Fox ecosystem</strong></h2>



<p>The Galaxy Fox ecosystem also has a marketplace and a proposal for about 3,000 exclusive<a href="https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/17/the-top-10-nft-dapps-on-optimism-exceeding-nfts-limitations/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> NFTs</a> for GFOX holders. The network also dedicates 2% of transaction fees to its community&#8217;s growth and sustainability across social media platforms. </p>



<p>With GFOX, staking rewards are available to early investors from the presale. The protocol burn of the network has made GFOX an asset that experiences deflation. It is expected to increase the asset&#8217;s demand, value, and price in the coming months.</p>



<p>Over the past five months, GFOX has raised over $5.2 million through 10 presale stages and is currently worth $0.00364. The token is expected to reach $6 million in a few weeks at this rate. The token has been listed by analysts as 2024&#8217;s one of the most promising meme coins, with multiple utilities and potential for passive income generation for holders.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana’s New Blockchain SLERF Caused Disaster</strong></h2>



<p>SLERF&#8217;s $10 million disaster occurred when the anonymous developer claimed to have accidentally sent the presale funds to a burn address. It resulted in the loss of nearly 50% of the token&#8217;s supply and the $10 million allocated to presale participants.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Another situation occurred as some clever investors took advantage of the problem. That created a great demand, and the price of SLERF increased drastically after the burn.</p>



<p>However, it is important to note that some crypto exchanges have pledged their support for SLERF. HTX, Bitget, and BingX have declared their intention to offer traders who participated in the non-public sale of SLERF on their platforms the option of donating their trading fees.</p>



<p>The accidental burn has sparked a debate in the crypto community, with some investors believing that the &#8220;accidental burn&#8221; is a marketing scheme to gain the attention of investors and increase the token&#8217;s price. Some people argue that the developer&#8217;s expression of regret and recognition suggests that the burn was not intentional. Despite investors&#8217; lingering questions about the reason behind the &#8220;accidental burn,&#8221; GFOX has maintained its stable price increase and is nearing the $6 million mark.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Summary</strong></h3>



<p>GFOX is a popular ERC-20 meme token with impressive sales of $6 million. The Galaxy Fox ecosystem includes a marketplace and 3,000 exclusive NFTs for GFOX holders. SLERF suffered a $10 million disaster due to the accidental loss of nearly 50% of its supply. Nonetheless, some crypto exchanges have pledged support for SLERF.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h4>



<p>The views and opinions stated by the author or any people named in this article are for informational purposes only. They do not establish financial, investment, or other advice. Investing in or trading in stocks, cryptos, or other related indexes comes with a risk of financial loss.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thecoinrepublic.com/2024/03/25/slerfs-10m-disaster-while-gfox-presale-soared-to-6-million/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
