<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"

	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.newsbtc.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<description>Bitcoin &#38; Cryptocurrency News Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:38:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-cropped-favicon.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>NewsBTC</title>
	<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">221170450</site>	<item>
		<title>Is Jupiter’s Next Leg Up Coming? Crypto Analyst Weighs In As JUP Surges 13%</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/is-jupiters-next-leg-up-coming-crypto-analyst-weighs-in-as-jup-surges-13/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubmar Garcia]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto analyst]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JUP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jupiter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JUPUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jupiter (JUP) has had a remarkable month, with its price skyrocketing over 150% in the last 30 days. Amid the crypto market slowdown and some controversies, JUP’s performance has maintained momentum. Related Reading: Solana Tokens Among Top Gainers: JUP and WEN Soar Over 12%, WIF Hits New ATH Crypto Analyst Sees &#8220;Decent&#8221; Entry Spot For JUP Jupiter’s JUP started the month trading around $0.63 and has seen the price jump 106% in 25 days. The token’s performance this month showed sideways price action before climbing to a new support level twice, which could suggest that another price surge is possible despite the turbulent week. In an X post, renowned crypto analyst Altcoin Sherpa commented on JUP’s most recent performance as he wondered about the possibility of a leg up. $JUP: Wondering if next leg is coming for JUPITER&#8230;consolidation and looks ok + btc looks somewhat stable (for now). Might be a decent spot entry here. pic.twitter.com/uE8IHblbFY &#8212; Altcoin Sherpa (@AltcoinSherpa) March 25, 2024 The analyst shared JUP’s price chart, which displayed the token’s sideways movement inside the $1.12-$1.47 price range for the past few days. The chart shows that the consolidation phase started after the token’s price jumped and unsuccessfully tested the $1.50 resistance level on March 16. After a pullback to the $1.20 mark, JUP retested the resistance zone again on March 18, briefly reaching $1.60, but ultimately failed to maintain it. Following the unsuccessful attempts to climb, the price dipped even lower to the $1.10 support zone in the following days. Since then, JUP has bounced back, hovering between the $1.15-$1.25 zone. The recent price consolidation looks “ok,” according to the analyst. He further highlights Bitcoin’s current stability, seemingly suggesting to Sherpa that JUP could repeat its March trajectory. As a result, the analyst deems this moment as a “decent entry spot” for Jupiter’s token. Additionally, he has shown a positive sentiment towards JUP before, calling the token a “winner” that’s “gonna keep on winning.” winners gonna keep on winning. $PYTH and $JUP are some of the great ones. pic.twitter.com/nL4BmzxFJo &#8212; Altcoin Sherpa (@AltcoinSherpa) March 16, 2024 JUP’s Price Action Recently, JUP’s Community showed some concerns after its co-founder Meow announced a controversial decision. Meow revealed on X that Jupiter would donate the SLERF limit order and DCA fees to the token’s presale participants. This decision was taken without consulting the community, a crucial part of the project. After the criticism, Meow explained that &#8220;no JUP tokens were involved in the donation and, despite the turbulence in the community, JUP’s price didn’t seem to be affected.&#8221; It’s worth noting that Bitcoin’s price showed stabilization signs over the weekend, as highlighted by Sherpa. This matters as JUP followed BTC’s trajectory closely over the last week. As the chart below shows, the Solana-based token mimicked the moves of the flagship cryptocurrency. JUP and BTC's price performance over the last 7 days. Source: CoinGecko In the last 24 hours, Jupiter’s trading volume has surged 64.1%, with $214.7 million being traded. According to CoinMarketCap data, JUP’s market capitalization increased 8.5% in the past day, placing the token as the 65th largest cryptocurrency by this metric, with $1.77 billion. Despite the negative 3.5% performance in the past week, the token exhibits a significant 71.8% price jump in the biweekly timeframe. At the time of writing, JUP is trading at $1.33, a 13.2% surge in the last day. Related Reading: Social Media Storm Gives Dogecoin 14% Price Boost – Details Jupiter's performance in the 3-day chart. Source: JUPUSDT on Trading.view.com  Featured Image from Unsplash.com, Chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400">Jupiter (JUP) has had a remarkable month, with its price skyrocketing over 150% in the last 30 days. Amid the crypto market slowdown and some controversies, JUP’s performance has maintained momentum.</p>

<h2 style="font-weight: 400">Crypto Analyst Sees &#8220;Decent&#8221; Entry Spot For JUP</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana-jupiter-jup-price-tumbles-controversy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Jupiter’s</a> JUP started the month trading around $0.63 and has seen the price jump 106% in 25 days. The token’s performance this month showed sideways price action before climbing to a new support level twice, which could suggest that another price surge is possible despite the turbulent week.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">In an X post, renowned crypto analyst Altcoin Sherpa commented on JUP’s most recent performance as he wondered about the possibility of a leg up.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24JUP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$JUP</a>: Wondering if next leg is coming for JUPITER&#8230;consolidation and looks ok + btc looks somewhat stable (for now). Might be a decent spot entry here. <a href="https://t.co/uE8IHblbFY" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/uE8IHblbFY</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Altcoin Sherpa (@AltcoinSherpa) <a href="https://twitter.com/AltcoinSherpa/status/1772079659984802211?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 25, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">The analyst shared JUP’s price chart, which displayed the token’s sideways movement inside the $1.12-$1.47 price range for the past few days. The chart shows that the consolidation phase started after the token’s price jumped and unsuccessfully tested the $1.50 resistance level on March 16.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">After a pullback to the $1.20 mark, JUP retested the resistance zone again on March 18, briefly reaching $1.60, but ultimately failed to maintain it. Following the unsuccessful attempts to climb, the price dipped even lower to the $1.10 support zone in the following days.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Since then, JUP has bounced back, hovering between the $1.15-$1.25 zone. The recent price consolidation looks “ok,” according to the analyst. He further highlights <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retests-resistance-level-break-lead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin’s</a> current stability, seemingly suggesting to Sherpa that JUP could repeat its March trajectory.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">As a result, the analyst deems this moment as a “decent entry spot” for Jupiter’s token. Additionally, he has shown a positive sentiment towards JUP before, calling the token a “winner” that’s “gonna keep on winning.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">winners gonna keep on winning. <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PYTH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$PYTH</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24JUP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$JUP</a> are some of the great ones. <a href="https://t.co/nL4BmzxFJo" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/nL4BmzxFJo</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Altcoin Sherpa (@AltcoinSherpa) <a href="https://twitter.com/AltcoinSherpa/status/1768842957140963801?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 16, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h2 style="font-weight: 400">JUP’s Price Action</h2>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Recently, JUP’s Community showed some <a href="https://x.com/DeNomics_/status/1770061164829122893?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">concerns</a> after its co-founder Meow announced a controversial decision. Meow revealed on X that Jupiter would donate the SLERF limit order and DCA fees to the token’s presale participants.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">This decision was taken without consulting the community, a crucial part of the project. After the criticism, Meow explained that &#8220;no JUP tokens were involved in the donation and, despite the turbulence in the community, JUP’s price didn’t seem to be affected.&#8221;</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">It’s worth noting that Bitcoin’s price showed stabilization signs over the weekend, as highlighted by Sherpa. This matters as JUP followed BTC’s trajectory closely over the last week. As the chart below shows, the Solana-based token mimicked the moves of the flagship cryptocurrency.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-599594 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-25-a-las-8.01.33-a.-m.png?w=741&#038;resize=741%2C514" alt="crypto, BTC, JUP" width="741" height="514" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-25-a-las-8.01.33-a.-m.png?w=741&#038;resize=741%2C514 741w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Captura-de-Pantalla-2024-03-25-a-las-8.01.33-a.-m.png?w=460 460w" sizes="(max-width: 741px) 100vw, 741px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>

<p style="font-weight: 400">In the last 24 hours, Jupiter’s trading volume has surged 64.1%, with $214.7 million being traded. According to CoinMarketCap data, JUP’s market capitalization increased 8.5% in the past day, placing the token as the 65th largest cryptocurrency by this metric, with $1.77 billion.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Despite the negative 3.5% <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/altcoin-season-bitcoin-performance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">performance</a> in the past week, the token exhibits a significant 71.8% price jump in the biweekly timeframe. At the time of writing, JUP is trading at $1.33, a 13.2% surge in the last day.</p>

<p><img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-599591 aligncenter" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C433" alt="JUP, JUPUSDT; Jupiter, Crypto" width="860" height="433" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=1022 1022w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=860&#038;resize=860%2C433 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=360 360w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/JUPUSDT_2024-03-25_07-50-05.png?w=750 750w" sizes="(max-width: 860px) 100vw, 860px" loading="lazy" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/andy-hermawan-bVBvv5xlX3g-unsplash.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599590</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin To $50,000 Or $80,000? Crypto Expert Predicts Where Price Is Headed Next</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-to-50000-or-80000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599547</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Crypto expert popularly known as KSI has shared his thoughts on how the Bitcoin price could progress until the peak of this bull cycle. Based on his prediction, the flagship crypto could experience significant dips on its way to a new all-time high of $100,000.  $80,000 Could Be Next For Bitcoin KSI mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that Bitcoin could rise to between $73,000 and $80,000 from here. However, a correction could quickly follow, as the crypto analyst remarked that Bitcoin would drop to between $50,000 and $60,000 afterwards. KSI added that it would be a “boring red summer,” suggesting that BTC&#8217;s price won’t be encouraging during that period.  Related Reading: Ethereum Sees Notable Rise In Daily Activity, But Why Is Price Down? KSI claimed that things would then pick up again in the winter. He also stated that Bitcoin could hit $100,000 by the beginning of 2025 or even before the end of this year. With his prediction, KSI joins a list of analysts who have predicted that Bitcoin could hit the $100,000 mark before the year runs out.  Tom Dunleavy, Partner and Chief Investment Officer (CIO) at MV Capital, previously stated that BTC would rise to that price level this year. Meanwhile, Standard Chartered initially predicted that Bitcoin would hit $100,000 by year-end before taking a more bullish stance and predicting that the flagship crypto would hit $150,000 by the end of 2024.  What To Expect From BTC&#8217;s Price KSI’s prediction also echoes the sentiments of crypto analyst Rekt Capital. In a recent analysis, Rekt Capital mentioned that Bitcoin would enter a “multi-month re-accumulation” after the Bitcoin Halving, which could last up to five months. The crypto analyst noted that this period is usually characterized by Bitcoin’s tepid price movement.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Whales Go On Massive Buying Spree, Here’s How Much They’ve Bought Once that phase was over, Rekt Capital revealed that Bitcoin would break out from the re-accumulation area and make a parabolic move. This is said to be when BTC experiences “accelerated growth into a parabolic uptrend.” This phase lasts over a year, but Rekt Capital believes it may be cut in half in this market cycle with a “potential accelerated cycle occurring right now.” The accelerated cycle he refers to includes the fact that BTC hit a new all-time high (ATH) before the Bitcoin Halving. That has never happened in previous market cycles, raising the possibility of this bull market being largely different from past ones.  At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $67,400, up over 4% in the last 24 hours according to data from CoinMarketCap.  BTC bulls struggle to hold price above $67,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from Forkast News, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto expert popularly known as KSI has shared his thoughts on how the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-breaks-through-69000-setting-new-record/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin price</a> could progress until the peak of this bull cycle. Based on his prediction, the flagship crypto could experience <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-crash-10-69000/">significant dips</a> on its way to a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-100000-cardano-dead/#:~:text=Why%20Cardano%20Is%20Dead,non%2Dexistent%E2%80%9D%20on%20it.">new all-time high of $100,000</a>. </p>
<h2>$80,000 Could Be Next For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>KSI mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://x.com/ksicrypto/status/1771933873565282424?s=20" rel="nofollow">post</a> that Bitcoin could rise to between $73,000 and $80,000 from here. However, a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-new-ath-by-year-end/">correction could quickly follow</a>, as the crypto analyst remarked that Bitcoin would drop to between $50,000 and $60,000 afterwards. KSI added that it would be a “boring red summer,” suggesting that BTC&#8217;s price won’t be encouraging during that period. </p>

<p>KSI claimed that things would then pick up again in the winter. He also stated that Bitcoin could hit $100,000 by the beginning of 2025 or even before the end of this year. With his prediction, KSI joins a list of analysts who have predicted that Bitcoin could <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-analyst-sees-100k-before-halving/" rel="nofollow">hit the $100,000 mark</a> before the year runs out. </p>
<p>Tom Dunleavy, Partner and Chief Investment Officer (CIO) at MV Capital, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-100000-cardano-dead/#:~:text=Why%20Cardano%20Is%20Dead,non%2Dexistent%E2%80%9D%20on%20it.">previously stated</a> that BTC would rise to that price level this year. Meanwhile, Standard Chartered <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/mark-your-calendars-bitcoin-to-hit-100000-by-end-of-2024-standard-chartered-says/">initially predicted </a>that Bitcoin would hit $100,000 by year-end before taking a more bullish stance and predicting that the flagship crypto would hit $150,000 by the end of 2024. </p>
<h2>What To Expect From BTC&#8217;s Price</h2>
<p>KSI’s prediction also echoes the sentiments of crypto analyst Rekt Capital. In a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-crash-10-69000/">recent analysis</a>, Rekt Capital mentioned that Bitcoin would enter a “multi-month re-accumulation” after the Bitcoin Halving, which could last up to five months. The crypto analyst noted that this period is usually characterized by Bitcoin’s tepid price movement. </p>

<p>Once that phase was over, Rekt Capital revealed that Bitcoin would break out from the re-accumulation area and make a parabolic move. This is said to be when BTC experiences “accelerated growth into a parabolic uptrend.” This phase lasts over a year, but Rekt Capital believes it may be cut in half in this <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bull-market-glassnode/" rel="nofollow">market cycle</a> with a “potential accelerated cycle occurring right now.”</p>
<p>The accelerated cycle he refers to includes the fact that BTC hit a <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-breaks-through-69000-setting-new-record/" rel="nofollow">new all-time high (ATH)</a> before the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-halving-could-bring-uncertainty-to-mining-industry/#:~:text=The%20halving%2C%20which%20occurs%20approximately,reward%20for%20each%20validated%20block." rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Halving</a>. That has never happened in previous market cycles, raising the possibility of this bull market being largely different from past ones. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $67,400, up over 4% in the last 24 hours according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">data</a> from CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jgGyFuMI/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530" loading="lazy"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin_e05fb8.jpeg?fit=460%2C307" width="460" height="307" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599547</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Top In Yet? What The Legendary MVRV Ratio Says</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-top-yet-legendary-mvrv-ratio-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin bull run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin MVRV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin MVRV Ratio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599563</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s what the latest trend in the Bitcoin Market Value to Realized Value (MVRV) ratio suggests about where the market is currently in terms of a top. Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Has Seen A Decline To The 2.34 Level According to data from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, the BTC MVRV ratio surged high earlier this year as the cryptocurrency rally took place. The &#8220;MVRV ratio&#8221; is a popular indicator that tracks the ratio between the Bitcoin market cap and the realized cap. The former is simply the total valuation of the asset&#8217;s supply at the current spot price, while the latter is an on-chain capitalization model. Related Reading: Bitcoin Long-Term Holders &#38; Price Top: Glassnode Reveals Pattern The realized cap measures the total sum of the value of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s supply, assuming that each coin in circulation has its true value at the price at which it was last transferred on the blockchain rather than the current spot value. One way to interpret the realized cap is that since it takes into account the buying price of every token in circulation (assuming that the last transaction of every token was indeed the point at which it last changed hands), it essentially sums up the total capital the investors have invested in the asset. As such, the MVRV ratio tells us how the total value that Bitcoin investors are carrying right now (that is, the market cap) compares against the value they put in (the realized cap). Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin MVRV ratio over the past few years: Looks like the value of the metric has been turning down in recent days &#124; Source: IntoTheBlock on X As is visible in the graph, the Bitcoin MVRV ratio has had a value greater than 1 for a while now. When the indicator has such values, the market cap is greater than the realized cap, and hence, the investors carry net profits. With the latest rally in the asset, this indicator has surged to relatively high levels, a natural consequence of the holders&#8217; profits ballooning up with the price surge. After the recent drawdown in the price, though, the MVRV ratio has also turned itself around, as it&#8217;s now heading down. At present, the ratio has a value of around 2.34. &#8220;Traditionally, an MVRV ratio above 3 has been a reliable marker for predicting price peaks,&#8221; notes IntoTheBlock. So far, in the current rally, the metric hasn&#8217;t crossed this mark. It did come close recently, but the latest decline has meant it has gained a bit more distance to the level. Related Reading: This Bitcoin Halving May Not Result In Supply Squeeze: Glassnode Why have tops historically occurred at high values of the Bitcoin MVRV ratio? The answer is that investors in profits are more likely to participate in selling, and this temptation to take profits only increases as their gains grow larger. Because of this, selloffs are most probable when the market is holding extreme levels of profits, which is exactly what high MVRV ratio values reflect. BTC Price At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $67,200, up 3% over the past 24 hours. The price of the asset appears to have rebounded over the last few days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Yiğit Ali Atasoy on Unsplash.com, IntoTheBlock.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here&#8217;s what the latest trend in the Bitcoin Market Value to Realized Value (MVRV) ratio suggests about where the market is currently in terms of a top.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin MVRV Ratio Has Seen A Decline To The 2.34 Level</h2>
<p>According to data from the market intelligence platform <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1772191939544150204" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">IntoTheBlock</a>, the BTC MVRV ratio surged high earlier this year as the cryptocurrency rally took place.</p>
<p>The &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-mvrv-ratio-approaches-1-5-break-happen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">MVRV ratio</a>&#8221; is a popular indicator that tracks the ratio between the Bitcoin market cap and the realized cap. The former is simply the total valuation of the asset&#8217;s supply at the current spot price, while the latter is an on-chain capitalization model.</p>

<p>The realized cap measures the total sum of the value of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s supply, assuming that each coin in circulation has its true value at the price at which it was last transferred on the blockchain rather than the current spot value.</p>
<p>One way to interpret the realized cap is that since it takes into account the buying price of every token in circulation (assuming that the last transaction of every token was indeed the point at which it last changed hands), it essentially sums up the total capital the investors have invested in the asset.</p>
<p>As such, the MVRV ratio tells us how the total value that Bitcoin investors are carrying right now (that is, the market cap) compares against the value they put in (the realized cap).</p>
<p>Now, here is a chart that shows the trend in the Bitcoin MVRV ratio over the past few years:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GJgWV_XWsAEgwv-?format=jpg&amp;name=large" alt="Bitcoin MVRV ratio" width="1696" height="430"/></p>

<p>As is visible in the graph, the Bitcoin MVRV ratio has had a value greater than 1 for a while now. When the indicator has such values, the market cap is greater than the realized cap, and hence, the investors carry net profits.</p>
<p>With the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/crypto-alameda-gap-bitcoin-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">latest rally</a> in the asset, this indicator has surged to relatively high levels, a natural consequence of the holders&#8217; profits ballooning up with the price surge.</p>
<p>After the recent drawdown in the price, though, the MVRV ratio has also turned itself around, as it&#8217;s now heading down. At present, the ratio has a value of around 2.34.</p>
<p>&#8220;Traditionally, an MVRV ratio above 3 has been a reliable marker for predicting price peaks,&#8221; notes IntoTheBlock. So far, in the current rally, the metric hasn&#8217;t crossed this mark. It did come close recently, but the latest decline has meant it has gained a bit more distance to the level.</p>

<p>Why have tops historically occurred at high values of the Bitcoin MVRV ratio? The answer is that investors in profits are more likely to participate in selling, and this temptation to take profits only increases as their gains grow larger.</p>
<p>Because of this, selloffs are most probable when the market is holding extreme levels of profits, which is exactly what high MVRV ratio values reflect.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $67,200, up 3% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/N7V9R1NL/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/yigit-ali-atasoy-z1jggXh29_Q-unsplash_c6aff6.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599563</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin is &#8220;Overheating&#8221; For The First Time Ever Before Halving</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-overheating-first-time-ever-before-halving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dalmas Ngetich]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s most valuable coin, is once again deviating from historical norms. According to an analysis by one crypto analyst, the coin is in the &#8220;overbought&#8221; territory of the Relative Strength Index (RSI) for the first time in the lead-up to halving. The RSI is a popular technical indicator analysts use to gauge the price momentum of traded instruments.  Bitcoin Overheating? RSI Stands Above 70 The analyst points out that the Bitcoin RSI on the monthly chart is currently above 70, indicating an overbought condition and overheating. This is a significant development as it&#8217;s the first time in Bitcoin&#8217;s history that this has happened before a halving.  The Bitcoin network is set to halve miner rewards in mid-April. This event, which occurs roughly every 200,000 blocks, will cut rewards distributed to miners by 50% from the current level of 6.125 BTC. Miners play a vital role in confirming transactions and maintaining network security.  Related Reading: Bitcoin ‘Real Pump’ Nears New All-Time Highs, Analyst Says The fact that Bitcoin prices appear to be &#8220;overheating&#8221; just before halving is net bullish for the coin. It suggests that prices are not only breaking from historical trends but also building strong momentum. Besides the strong upside momentum, the analyst notes that Bitcoin now trades above a critical dynamic level on the monthly chart. The confluence of these positive developments could explain why traders are upbeat. Most analysts agree that the coin will likely break higher in the weeks ahead, clearing the recent all-time high of around $73,800. BTC Pinned Below $73,000 And Consolidating  Thus far, Bitcoin prices are firm, increasing as evident in the daily chart. After sharp contractions in the past few trading sessions, the welcomed reversal over the weekend lifted the coin towards the elusive $70,000 level and a previous all-time high. However, judging from the candlestick arrangement in the daily chart, a break above $73,800 would likely catalyze more demand. So far, prices are moving sideways within a broad range despite signals of strength relayed from other indicators. Related Reading: Why Is The Price Of LUNC And USTC Up Today? While some investors are bullish, expecting prices to rise, caution should prevail. A close above $74,000 would thrust Bitcoin into unchartered territory. Beyond this, the analyst uses technical indicators to make projections. These tools use historical parameters and lag. As such, they may not be as accurate and, thus, misleading in some instances. Feature image from DALLE, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, the world&#8217;s most valuable coin, is once again deviating from historical norms. According to an <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/el_crypto_prof/status/1772198663504179682" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">analysis</a> by one crypto analyst, the coin is in the &#8220;overbought&#8221; territory of the Relative Strength Index (RSI) for the first time in the lead-up to halving. The RSI is a popular technical indicator analysts use to gauge the price momentum of traded instruments. </p>
<h2>Bitcoin Overheating? RSI Stands Above 70</h2>
<p>The analyst points out that the Bitcoin RSI on the monthly chart is currently above 70, indicating an overbought condition and overheating. This is a significant development as it&#8217;s the first time in Bitcoin&#8217;s history that this has happened before a halving. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-599584" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526" alt="BTC overheating | Source: Analyst on X" width="1024" height="526" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=2560 2560w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJgdOS1WsAAqilC.jpg?resize=1024%2C526?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>The Bitcoin network is set to halve miner rewards in mid-April. This event, which occurs roughly every 200,000 blocks, will <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-halving-result-supply-squeeze-glassnode/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">cut rewards</a> distributed to miners by 50% from the current level of 6.125 BTC. Miners play a vital role in confirming transactions and maintaining network security. </p>

<p>The fact that Bitcoin prices appear to be &#8220;overheating&#8221; just before halving is net bullish for the coin. It suggests that prices are not only breaking from historical trends but also building strong momentum. </p>
<p>Besides the strong upside momentum, the analyst notes that Bitcoin now trades above a critical dynamic level on the monthly chart.</p>
<p>The confluence of these positive developments could explain why traders are upbeat. Most analysts agree that the coin will likely break higher in the weeks ahead, clearing the recent all-time high of around $73,800.</p>
<h2>BTC Pinned Below $73,000 And Consolidating </h2>
<p>Thus far, Bitcoin prices are firm, increasing as evident in the daily chart. After sharp contractions in the past few trading sessions, the welcomed reversal over the weekend lifted the coin towards the elusive $70,000 level and a previous all-time high.</p>
<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2LgfhZs9/" rel="nofollow"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/2LgfhZs9/" alt="Bitcoin price trending upward on the daily chart | Source: BTCUSDT on Binance, TradingView" width="1787" height="904"/></a>
<p>However, judging from the candlestick arrangement in the daily chart, a break above $73,800 would likely catalyze more demand. So far, prices are moving sideways within a broad range despite signals of strength relayed from other indicators.</p>

<p>While some investors are bullish, expecting prices to rise, caution should prevail. A close above $74,000 would thrust Bitcoin into unchartered territory. Beyond this, the analyst uses technical indicators to make projections. These tools use historical parameters and lag. As such, they may not be as accurate and, thus, misleading in some instances.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-20-08.54.10-A-wide-dramatic-digital-illustration-depicting-a-stylized-Bitcoin-coin-partially-shattered-on-the-ground-with-digital-fragments-and-sparks-flying-ar.jpg?fit=460%2C263" width="460" height="263" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599583</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Days Of Crypto: Key Events That You Should Keep An Eye On This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/crypto/7-days-crypto-key-events/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto events]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are a couple of events to watch out for this week, as they could prove pivotal in determining the future trajectory of the crypto market. These events could provide some certainty to the market or cause investors to wait on the sidelines for more favorable market conditions.  Events That Could Affect The Market This Week Some Federal Reserve officials are scheduled to speak at different events this week. One of them is Governor Lisa Cook, who will give a lecture on March 25. Fed Chair Jerome Powell will also participate in a discussion at the Monetary Policy Conference on March 29.  Related Reading: Bitcoin ETFs Bleed For One Week Straight – Can Price Recover To $73,000? Their speeches are significant as they could provide valuable insights into the current state of the economy and what to expect from the Federal Reserve regarding interest rates in its fight against inflation. Macroeconomic factors like interest rates usually impact the crypto market and partly determine the sentiments among crypto traders. The crypto market is usually bullish whenever the Federal Reserve adopts a dovish stance on whether or not to hike interest rates. Therefore, these officials sounding positive in their speeches could help boost investors’ confidence in the crypto market since they would be less worried about things on the macro side.  Meanwhile, several economic data will be released this week, including the Consumer Confidence and Consumer Sentiment data and the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) index. These releases offer insights into the economy’s strength and guide the Fed in deciding on future interest rate decisions.  Crypto Needs A Big Win This Week Stakeholders and investors in the industry will no doubt hope that the events lined up for this week will provide a momentum boost for the crypto market. Last week was one to forget as things cooled after weeks of seeing the flagship crypto, Bitcoin, and altcoins make significant runs. This downward trend is believed to have been due to some external factors. Related Reading: Bernstein Analysts Says Bitcoin Will Reach A New ATH By Year End, Here’s The Target One of them is the net outflows that the Spot Bitcoin ETFs recorded throughout last week, with many investors taking profits from the various funds. These Bitcoin ETFs had previously seen an impressive amount of inflows into them, which positively affected Bitcoin’s price. As such, a trend of outflows was also expected to influence Bitcoin’s price, although negatively.  These Spot Bitcoin ETFs will again be in the spotlight this week, with the crypto community waiting to see if the sentiments among the ETF investors will change. A sustained trend of profit-taking this week could spark another decline in the crypto market.  Total market cap chart at $2.47 trillion &#124; Source: Crypto Total Market Cap on Tradingview.com Featured image from CNBC, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are a <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-price-major-events/">couple of events</a> to watch out for this week, as they could prove pivotal in determining the future trajectory of the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/gary-gensler-says-crypto-needs-disinfectant/" rel="nofollow">crypto market</a>. These events could provide some certainty to the market or cause <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coin-mania-breaks-records/" rel="nofollow">investors</a> to wait on the sidelines for more favorable market conditions. </p>
<h2>Events That Could Affect The Market This Week</h2>
<p>Some Federal Reserve officials <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/calendar.htm" rel="nofollow">are scheduled</a> to speak at different events this week. One of them is Governor Lisa Cook, who will give a lecture on March 25. Fed Chair Jerome Powell will also participate in a discussion at the Monetary Policy Conference on March 29. </p>

<p>Their speeches are significant as they could provide valuable insights into the current state of the economy and what to expect from the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-crypto-in-trouble/" rel="nofollow">Federal Reserve</a> regarding interest rates in its fight against inflation. <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-recovers-on-fed-hike/" rel="nofollow">Macroeconomic factors like interest rates</a> usually impact the crypto market and partly determine the sentiments among crypto traders.</p>
<p>The crypto market is usually bullish whenever the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/fed-decision-bitcoin-price/" rel="nofollow">Federal Reserve</a> adopts a dovish stance on whether or not to hike interest rates. Therefore, these officials sounding positive in their speeches could help boost investors’ confidence in the crypto market since they would be less worried about things on the macro side. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, several economic data will be released this week, including the Consumer Confidence and Consumer Sentiment data and the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) index. These releases offer insights into the economy’s strength and guide the Fed in deciding on future interest rate decisions. </p>
<h2>Crypto Needs A Big Win This Week</h2>
<p>Stakeholders and investors in the industry will no doubt hope that the events lined up for this week will provide a momentum boost for the crypto market. Last week was one to forget as things cooled after weeks of seeing the flagship crypto, Bitcoin, and altcoins <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-breaks-through-69000-setting-new-record/" rel="nofollow">make significant runs</a>. This downward trend is believed to have been due to some external factors.</p>

<p>One of them is the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/back-to-back-negative-bitcoin-etf-flows/" rel="nofollow">net outflows</a> that the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-100-volume/" rel="nofollow">Spot Bitcoin ETFs</a> recorded throughout last week, with many investors taking profits from the various funds. These Bitcoin ETFs had previously seen an impressive <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etfs-record-2-2-billion-inflow-in-past-week/" rel="nofollow">amount of inflows</a> into them, which positively affected Bitcoin’s price. As such, a trend of outflows was also expected to influence Bitcoin’s price, although negatively. </p>
<p>These Spot Bitcoin ETFs will again be in the spotlight this week, with the crypto community waiting to see if the sentiments among the <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sheds-nearly-1-billion-in-grayscale-bitcoin-etf/" rel="nofollow">ETF investors</a> will change. A sustained trend of profit-taking this week could spark another decline in the crypto market. </p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/hZJIFsap/" alt="Crypto total market cap chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Crypto_447459.jpeg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599549</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Presents Top 10 Cryptos To Turn $5,000 Into $500,000 By 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/analyst-top-10-crypto-turn-5000-into-500000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jake Simmons]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top Altcoins 2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top Crypto Coins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599544</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a thread on X (formerly Twitter), the popular crypto analyst known as cyclop (@nobrainflip) delivered a bold forecast to his substantial following of 394,000. He proclaimed, &#8220;We are close to the biggest altseason in history. Everyone will make x50-x100 on their entire portfolio. $5k portfolio will be around $250k-$500k in 2025. All you need is to buy the right lowcaps.&#8221; This assertion hinges on a strategic selection of low market capitalization cryptocurrencies, which, according to Cyclop, are poised for an exponential surge in value. Cyclop elucidates his strategy by detailing the liquidity flow typically observed during a bull market phase, a sequential process starting with Bitcoin (BTC) and cascading down to meme coins. He explains, &#8220;Here is a typical bull run liquidity flow: 1: BTC pump 2: ETH pump 3: High cap alts pump 4: Low caps pump 5: Memecoin pump.&#8221; Importantly, he highlights that high cap memecoins have already experienced their growth phase, suggesting that &#8220;lowcap/lowcap memecoins &#8211; next&#8221; are primed for significant value appreciation. Related Reading: What is Macro/Crypto Summer? Don’t Miss Out, Says Expert Within this framework, Cyclop underscores the potential for staggering returns without the necessity for professional day trading expertise. &#8220;It&#8217;s cause each coin has its maximum, and if its MC is already high, it&#8217;s not so far away. But when the market cap is almost at zero, the potential is enormous,&#8221; he advises, promoting a hands-off investment strategy focused on the &#8216;right&#8217; coins. Crypto Watchlist: Top-10 Lowcap Coins Cyclop&#8217;s watchlist is a selection of ten recently launched projects with low market caps and, in his view, substantial growth potential: #1 Wolf Wif (BALLZ): A meme coin that took the Solana blockchain by storm, achieving a $75 million market cap within a day of its launch. Despite a subsequent correction, Cyclop views this as an optimal entry point, confidently stating, &#8220;I&#8217;m holding my BALLZ tight.&#8221; #2 Entangle (NGL): Positioned as a potential leading messaging infrastructure for the Web3 space, Entangle aims to enhance liquidity within the ecosystem. It offers secure, flexible, and interoperable solutions for blockchain data communication, positioning itself as a critical infrastructure for dApps and builders. #3 StarHeroes (STAR): This esports-centric, multiplayer third-person space shooter game is making waves with its dynamic and competitive gameplay. Cyclop sees this as a revolutionary blend of gaming and blockchain technology, offering intense gaming emotions and a new avenue for esports within the crypto realm. #4 Heroes of Mavia (MAVIA): A blockchain strategy game that allows players to build bases, engage in battles for cryptocurrency rewards, and form partnerships with landowners. Cyclop highlights its potential in the play-to-earn space, marking it as a standout project. #5 VoluMint (VMINT): This project introduces a decentralized, AI-driven market-making service, aiming to redefine market-making in the era of blockchain. Cyclop is bullish on its ability to unlock the potential of crypto projects, emphasizing its innovative approach. #6 SatoshiVM (SAVM): As a decentralized Bitcoin ZK Rollup Layer 2 solution, SatoshiVM bridges the gap between Bitcoin and Ethereum&#8217;s EVM, using BTC as gas. This project aims to combine the value and security of Bitcoin with the programmability of Ethereum, creating a powerful ecosystem for decentralized applications. Cyclop notes, &#8220;SAVM&#8217;s unique positioning as a bridge between BTC and EVM ecosystems presents a groundbreaking opportunity for growth.&#8221; Related Reading: STX Brushes Off Sluggish Crypto Market As It Shoots Up By 30% #7 Graphlinq Chain (GLQ): Offering a no-code interface for automating blockchain tasks, Graphlinq Chain simplifies the creation and deployment of blockchain automations. Its suite of tools, including an IDE, App, Engine, and Marketplace, is designed to make blockchain automation accessible to a wider audience. &#8220;GraphLinq Protocol demystifies blockchain automation, paving the way for innovative applications and efficiencies,&#8221; Cyclop remarks. #8 zKML (ZKML): This project addresses the pressing need for privacy in digital transactions and communications. By combining zero-knowledge proofs, homomorphic encryption, and multi-party computation (MPC), zKML offers a secure and private framework for blockchain interactions. &#8220;ZKML&#8217;s focus on privacy-enhancing technologies is timely and critical, offering a secure haven for digital transactions,&#8221; observes Cyclop. #9 Monai (MONAI): Monai stands out for its development of uncensored generative AI tools, integrated with its blockchain, Monad. It features an advanced, unrestricted Large Language Model as its flagship product, aiming to revolutionize the way we interact with AI. &#8220;Monai&#8217;s pioneering approach to generative AI within the blockchain space is a game-changer, offering unparalleled possibilities,&#8221; Cyclop asserts. #10 EMC Protocol (EMC): Dedicated to AI applications, EMC Protocol is a blockchain network that includes a computing power consensus mechanism. It aims to facilitate the execution of AI tasks within a decentralized framework, including validator, smart router, and computing power nodes. &#8220;EMC&#8217;s innovative approach to integrating AI and blockchain could redefine the landscape of decentralized applications,&#8221; Cyclop concludes. At press time, cyclop&#8217;s top pick &#8211; BALLZ &#8211; traded at $0.04231, down almost 50% from its alltime-high. Featured image from Shutterstock, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/nobrainflip/status/1772020031276167221" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">thread</a> on X (formerly Twitter), the popular crypto analyst known as cyclop (@nobrainflip) delivered a bold forecast to his substantial following of 394,000. He proclaimed, &#8220;We are close to the biggest altseason in history. Everyone will make x50-x100 on their entire portfolio. $5k portfolio will be around $250k-$500k in 2025. All you need is to buy the right lowcaps.&#8221;</p>
<p>This assertion hinges on a strategic selection of low market capitalization cryptocurrencies, which, according to Cyclop, are poised for an exponential surge in value. Cyclop elucidates his strategy by detailing the liquidity flow typically observed during a bull market phase, a sequential process starting with Bitcoin (BTC) and cascading down to meme coins.</p>
<p>He explains, &#8220;Here is a typical bull run liquidity flow: 1: BTC pump 2: ETH pump 3: High cap alts pump 4: Low caps pump 5: Memecoin pump.&#8221; Importantly, he highlights that high cap memecoins have already experienced their growth phase, suggesting that &#8220;lowcap/lowcap memecoins &#8211; next&#8221; are primed for significant value appreciation.</p>

<p>Within this framework, Cyclop underscores the potential for staggering returns without the necessity for professional day trading expertise. &#8220;It&#8217;s cause each coin has its maximum, and if its MC is already high, it&#8217;s not so far away. But when the market cap is almost at zero, the potential is enormous,&#8221; he advises, promoting a hands-off investment strategy focused on the &#8216;right&#8217; coins.</p>
<h2>Crypto Watchlist: Top-10 Lowcap Coins</h2>
<p>Cyclop&#8217;s watchlist is a selection of ten recently launched projects with low market caps and, in his view, substantial growth potential:</p>
<p><strong>#1 Wolf Wif (BALLZ):</strong> A meme coin that took the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/solana/solanas-memecoin-bonk-reaches-1-6-billion-market-cap-witnesses-explosive-100-price-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Solana blockchain</a> by storm, achieving a $75 million market cap within a day of its launch. Despite a subsequent correction, Cyclop views this as an optimal entry point, confidently stating, &#8220;I&#8217;m holding my BALLZ tight.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>#2 Entangle (NGL):</strong> Positioned as a potential leading messaging infrastructure for the Web3 space, Entangle aims to enhance liquidity within the ecosystem. It offers secure, flexible, and interoperable solutions for blockchain data communication, positioning itself as a critical infrastructure for dApps and builders.</p>
<p><strong>#3 StarHeroes (STAR):</strong> This esports-centric, multiplayer third-person space shooter game is making waves with its dynamic and competitive gameplay. Cyclop sees this as a revolutionary blend of gaming and blockchain technology, offering intense gaming emotions and a new avenue for esports within the crypto realm.</p>
<p><strong>#4 Heroes of Mavia (MAVIA):</strong> A blockchain strategy game that allows players to build bases, engage in battles for cryptocurrency rewards, and form partnerships with landowners. Cyclop highlights its potential in the play-to-earn space, marking it as a standout project.</p>
<p><strong>#5 VoluMint (VMINT):</strong> This project introduces a decentralized, AI-driven market-making service, aiming to redefine market-making in the era of blockchain. Cyclop is bullish on its ability to unlock the potential of crypto projects, emphasizing its innovative approach.</p>
<p><strong>#6 SatoshiVM (SAVM):</strong> As a decentralized Bitcoin <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/matic-analysis/polygon-zkevm-successfully-completes-first-major-upgrade-introduces-dragonfruit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">ZK Rollup</a> Layer 2 solution, SatoshiVM bridges the gap between Bitcoin and Ethereum&#8217;s EVM, using BTC as gas. This project aims to combine the value and security of Bitcoin with the programmability of Ethereum, creating a powerful ecosystem for decentralized applications. Cyclop notes, &#8220;SAVM&#8217;s unique positioning as a bridge between BTC and EVM ecosystems presents a groundbreaking opportunity for growth.&#8221;</p>

<p><strong>#7 Graphlinq Chain (GLQ):</strong> Offering a no-code interface for automating blockchain tasks, Graphlinq Chain simplifies the creation and deployment of blockchain automations. Its suite of tools, including an IDE, App, Engine, and Marketplace, is designed to make blockchain automation accessible to a wider audience. &#8220;GraphLinq Protocol demystifies blockchain automation, paving the way for innovative applications and efficiencies,&#8221; Cyclop remarks.</p>
<p><strong>#8 zKML (ZKML):</strong> This project addresses the pressing need for privacy in digital transactions and communications. By combining zero-knowledge proofs, homomorphic encryption, and multi-party computation (MPC), zKML offers a secure and private framework for blockchain interactions. &#8220;ZKML&#8217;s focus on privacy-enhancing technologies is timely and critical, offering a secure haven for digital transactions,&#8221; observes Cyclop.</p>
<p><strong>#9 Monai (MONAI):</strong> Monai stands out for its development of uncensored generative AI tools, integrated with its blockchain, Monad. It features an advanced, unrestricted Large Language Model as its flagship product, aiming to revolutionize the way we interact with AI. &#8220;Monai&#8217;s pioneering approach to generative <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/top-ai-trend-coins-this-bull-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">AI within the blockchain space</a> is a game-changer, offering unparalleled possibilities,&#8221; Cyclop asserts.</p>
<p><strong>#10 EMC Protocol (EMC):</strong> Dedicated to AI applications, EMC Protocol is a blockchain network that includes a computing power consensus mechanism. It aims to facilitate the execution of AI tasks within a decentralized framework, including validator, smart router, and computing power nodes. &#8220;EMC&#8217;s innovative approach to integrating AI and blockchain could redefine the landscape of decentralized applications,&#8221; Cyclop concludes.</p>
<p>At press time, cyclop&#8217;s top pick &#8211; BALLZ &#8211; traded at $0.04231, down almost 50% from its alltime-high.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-599551 size-full" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673" alt="BALLZ price" width="3628" height="1673" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3628 3628w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1536 1536w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=2048 2048w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=1140 1140w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/BALLZUSDT_2024-03-25_13-06-26.png?resize=3628%2C1673?w=3000 3000w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/space-shuttle-in-sky-with-stars-and-clouds-rocket-in-deep-space-scifi-picture-id1360144430.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599544</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Infinity And Beyond: Analyst Forecasts Bitcoin To Hit $100,000 In High-Speed</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/to-infinity-and-beyond-analyst-forecasts-bitcoin-to-hit-100000-in-high-speed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godspower Owie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor Profit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599552</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency expert and analyst Doctor Profit has identified regions that are vital for Bitcoin (BTC) presently, which could possibly propel the crypto asset&#8217;s price to unprecedented heights at a very fast pace. For the most part, the cryptocurrency community is concerned about the way that Bitcoin&#8217;s price has performed during the last week. Nonetheless, Doctor Profit&#8217;s latest weekly update on the crypto market and Bitcoin has provided optimism for investors within the crypto space. Bitcoin For A Massive Leg Up To $100,000 In his analysis, Doctor Profit explores the Life Cycle Assessment (LCA), psychological analysis, and technical analysis (TA) of Bitcoin&#8217;s recent performance.  Drawing attention to the previous Sunday report, the analyst predicted a sideways movement for Bitcoin in the longer term. However, the largest cryptocurrency asset is currently moving in the indicated sideways region, as he points out. Related Reading: Bitcoin ‘Real Pump’ Nears New All-Time Highs, Analyst Says The expert claims that some people are unable to see the wider picture playing out within the sideways movement. Due to this, they fail to understand that price fluctuations in the 20% range are normal and even beneficial for moves in big market caps.  Thus, Bitcoin is preparing for its next big move, which will push prices over $80,000 and hit $100,000 at high speed. He noted that this bullish sideways movement is referred to as an accumulation area in trading terminology.  During this stage, a convergence of profit-taking, incoming investment, and undecided money, practically leads to a mid-term consolidation. Consequently, he is bullish about the sideways trend and anticipates a looming upward surge.  Furthermore, Doctor Profit underscored the significance of Bitcoin&#8217;s recent breakout above its previous all-time high (ATH) of $69,000, and the necessity of exercising patience as the coin consolidates close to its peak level. He stated: What many fail to understand is that Bitcoin just broke through its all-time high (ATH) in the last few weeks and is now slowly building support near the ATH region. People don&#8217;t realize that this is a process that takes weeks. Doctor Profit asserts that before continuing to rise and entering the super cycle, the market would spend weeks in the area of the Golden Bull. &#8220;After confirmation at $72,500, it won&#8217;t be long until BTC rises beyond $70,000 and enters the super cycle,&#8221; he added. Recent Retest Pattern Aligns With Past Trends Doctor Profit seems to be pleased with Bitcoin retesting its previous ATH level in the $60,000 range. He highlights the potential of Bitcoin and the slow transformation of the $60,000 resistance level into a solid support point, paving the way for the upcoming super cycle similar to other ATH breakouts. Related Reading: Bitcoin Pre-Halving Dip Expected: Will BTC Rally Before US Fed Decision? &#8220;Bitcoin now appears mature enough to withstand this pressure at $60,000 and maintain its above-average price without any difficulty,&#8221; he stated. Despite ongoing corrections, the analyst has urged investors to be confident, citing the Bitcoin Halving as a catalyst for an impending upward surge. Featured image from iStock, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency expert and analyst Doctor Profit has identified regions that are vital for <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/press-releases/bitcoin-recovery-will-ignite-massive-crypto-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> presently, which could possibly propel the crypto asset&#8217;s price to unprecedented heights at a very fast pace.</p>
<p>For the most part, the cryptocurrency community is concerned about the way that Bitcoin&#8217;s price has performed during the last week. Nonetheless, Doctor Profit&#8217;s <a href="https://x.com/DrProfitCrypto/status/1771938758209794501?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">latest weekly update</a> on the crypto market and Bitcoin has provided optimism for investors within the crypto space.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin For A Massive Leg Up To $100,000</h2>
<p>In his analysis, Doctor Profit explores the Life Cycle Assessment (LCA), psychological analysis, and technical analysis (TA) of Bitcoin&#8217;s recent performance. </p>
<p>Drawing attention to the previous Sunday report, the analyst predicted a sideways movement for Bitcoin in the longer term. However, the largest cryptocurrency asset is currently moving in the indicated sideways region, as he points out.</p>

<p>The expert claims that some people are unable to see the wider picture playing out within the sideways movement. Due to this, they fail to understand that price fluctuations in the 20% range are normal and even beneficial for moves in big market caps. </p>
<p>Thus, Bitcoin is preparing for its next big move, which will push prices over $80,000 and hit $100,000 at high speed. He noted that this bullish sideways movement is referred to as an accumulation area in trading terminology. </p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-599562" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C234" alt="Bitcoin" width="460" height="234" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=1200 1200w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=460&#038;resize=460%2C234 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Doctor-Profits-Bitcoin-Chart.jpg?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 460px) 100vw, 460px" data-recalc-dims="1"/>
<p>During this stage, a convergence of profit-taking, incoming investment, and undecided money, practically leads to a mid-term consolidation. Consequently, he is bullish about the sideways trend and anticipates a looming upward surge. </p>
<p>Furthermore, Doctor Profit underscored the significance of Bitcoin&#8217;s recent breakout above its previous <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin-blasts-past-70000-in-wild-week-to-register-new-all-time-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">all-time high (ATH)</a> of $69,000, and the necessity of exercising patience as the coin consolidates close to its peak level.</p>
<p>He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>What many fail to understand is that Bitcoin just broke through its all-time high (ATH) in the last few weeks and is now slowly building support near the ATH region. People don&#8217;t realize that this is a process that takes weeks.</p></blockquote>
<p>Doctor Profit asserts that before continuing to rise and entering the super cycle, the market would spend weeks in the area of the Golden Bull. &#8220;After confirmation at $72,500, it won&#8217;t be long until BTC rises <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-jumps-68k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">beyond $70,000</a> and enters the super cycle,&#8221; he added.</p>
<h2>Recent Retest Pattern Aligns With Past Trends</h2>
<p>Doctor Profit seems to be pleased with Bitcoin retesting its previous ATH level in the $60,000 range. He highlights the potential of Bitcoin and the slow transformation of the $60,000 resistance level into a solid support point, paving the way for the upcoming super cycle similar to other ATH breakouts.</p>

<p>&#8220;Bitcoin now appears mature enough to withstand this pressure at $60,000 and maintain its above-average price without any difficulty,&#8221; he stated. Despite ongoing corrections, the analyst has urged investors to be confident, citing the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-halving-retrace-investors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">Bitcoin Halving</a> as a catalyst for an impending upward surge.</p>
<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/eWQqV1zH/" alt="Bitcoin" width="2273" height="1351"/>

]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/iStock-1296910866.jpg?fit=460%2C283" width="460" height="283" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599552</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whales Remove A Staggering $2.3 Billion From Exchanges, Is It Time To Buy?</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-whales-2-3-billion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Scott Matherson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599548</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales have been very active in the past few days as the crypto continues to trade below $68,000. Notably, on-chain data has shown a trend of accumulation among Bitcoin whales, with large bouts of the cryptocurrency leaving crypto exchanges into private wallets.  These massive transfers appear to have piqued the interest of a few investors who are keeping a watchful eye, as this accumulation pattern points to a price increase up ahead.  According to various posts by whale transaction tracker Whale Alerts, Bitcoin whales have recently transferred $2.3 billion worth of BTC in a span of 24 hours, indicating their bullish sentiment. Similarly, crypto analyst Ali Martinez recently revealed that over 25,000 BTC worth approximately $1.60 billion had been transferred into accumulation addresses. Bitcoin Whale Accumulation Signal Price Surge Ahead Bitcoin has largely traded below $69,000 since March 15, struggling to regain the momentum that saw it shooting past $70,000 earlier in the month. Interestingly, Bitcoin fell to as low as $61,766 last week, representing a 16% decline from its all-time high.  Related Reading: Dogecoin Whales Go On Massive Buying Spree, Here’s How Much They’ve Bought Meanwhile, Spot Bitcoin ETFs saw consistent outflows throughout the week which was spearheaded by Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC and weak inflows into BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT and Fidelity&#8217;s FBTC. This decline became much of a concern for investors as it signaled the bullish sentiment surrounding BTC might finally be coming to an end. However, on-chain data is now telling a different tale of a strong bullish sentiment from Bitcoin whales. Data from Whale Alerts show large amounts of BTC leaving crypto exchanges, one of which was a transfer of 8,136 BTC worth $517 million from Coinbase into a new private wallet. Shortly after, 8,172 BTC worth $519 million were transferred from Coinbase into another new private wallet. Interestingly, the different alerts from the whale tracker added up to $2.3 billion worth of BTC to and from crypto exchanges on March 22.  Analyst Ali Martinez noted that these transfers added up to $1.6 billion being added into accumulation addresses, the largest inflow so far this year.  Yesterday, over 25,000 #Bitcoin, valued at approximately $1.60 billion, were transferred to accumulation addresses, marking the highest inflow to these $BTC wallets so far this year! pic.twitter.com/mAIHkG9ROC — Ali (@ali_charts) March 23, 2024 According to CryptoQuant data, this accumulation trend has seen the Bitcoin reserves on exchanges on a downtrend since March 21. At the time of writing, the Bitcoin exchange reserve is at 1.98 million BTC.  Related Reading: Ethereum Sees Notable Rise In Daily Activity, But Why Is Price Down? Basically, whale accumulation tends to swing the balance into bullish among other traders. Fundamentals surrounding Bitcoin like the upcoming halving point to price growth in the near future, making it an ideal time for investors to position themselves in the market.  At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $67,478. A key price level to watch is $69,000. If Bitcoin breaks above this resistance level, it could continue surging higher with the accumulation trend. BTC price at $67,000 &#124; Source: BTCUSD on Tradingview.com Featured image from GoBankingRates, chart from Tradingview.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin whales <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-long-term-holders-price-top-glassnode/">have been very active</a> in the past few days as the crypto continues to trade below $68,000. Notably, on-chain data has shown a trend of accumulation among Bitcoin whales, with large bouts of the cryptocurrency leaving crypto exchanges into private wallets.  These massive transfers appear to have piqued the interest of a few investors who are keeping a watchful eye, as this accumulation pattern points to a price increase up ahead. </p>
<p>According to various posts by whale transaction tracker Whale Alerts, Bitcoin whales have recently transferred $2.3 billion worth of BTC in a span of 24 hours, indicating their bullish sentiment. Similarly, crypto analyst Ali Martinez recently revealed that over 25,000 BTC worth approximately $1.60 billion had been transferred into accumulation addresses.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whale Accumulation Signal Price Surge Ahead</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has largely <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-rejects-68k/">traded below $69,000</a> since March 15, struggling to regain the momentum that saw it <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/breaking-news-ticker/breaking-bitcoin-hits-new-all-time-high-surging-past-70000-for-the-first-time-in-history/">shooting past $70,000</a> earlier in the month. Interestingly, Bitcoin fell to as low as $61,766 last week, representing a 16% decline from its all-time high. </p>

<p>Meanwhile, Spot Bitcoin ETFs <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etfs-bleed-for-one-week-straight-can-price-recover-to-73000/">saw consistent outflows</a> throughout the week which was spearheaded by Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC and weak inflows into BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT and Fidelity&#8217;s FBTC. This decline became much of a concern for investors as it signaled the bullish sentiment surrounding BTC <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-etf-netflows-may-experience-rebound-if-this-price-is-attained-analyst-explains/">might finally be coming to an end.</a></p>
<p>However, on-chain data is now telling a different tale of a strong bullish sentiment from Bitcoin whales. Data from Whale Alerts show large amounts of BTC leaving crypto exchanges, one of which was a transfer of 8,136 BTC worth $517 million <a href="https://x.com/whale_alert/status/1771242694016192637?s=20" rel="nofollow">from Coinbase</a> into a new private wallet. Shortly after, 8,172 BTC worth $519 million <a href="https://x.com/whale_alert/status/1771242697359073284?s=20" rel="nofollow">were transferred from Coinbase</a> into another new private wallet. Interestingly, the different alerts from the whale tracker added up to $2.3 billion worth of BTC to and from crypto exchanges on March 22. </p>
<p>Analyst Ali Martinez noted that these transfers added up to $1.6 billion being added into accumulation addresses, the largest inflow so far this year. </p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Yesterday, over 25,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">#Bitcoin</a>, valued at approximately $1.60 billion, were transferred to accumulation addresses, marking the highest inflow to these <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">$BTC</a> wallets so far this year! <a href="https://t.co/mAIHkG9ROC" rel="nofollow">pic.twitter.com/mAIHkG9ROC</a></p>
<p>— Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1771477802707034192?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow">March 23, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p>According to <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/asset/btc/chart/exchange-flows/exchange-reserve?exchange=all_exchange&amp;window=DAY&amp;sma=0&amp;ema=0&amp;priceScale=log&amp;metricScale=linear&amp;chartStyle=line" rel="nofollow">CryptoQuant data</a>, this accumulation trend has seen the Bitcoin reserves on exchanges on a downtrend since March 21. At the time of writing, the Bitcoin exchange reserve is at 1.98 million BTC. </p>

<p>Basically, whale accumulation tends to swing the balance into bullish among other traders. Fundamentals surrounding Bitcoin like the upcoming halving point to price growth in the near future, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/bitcoin/bitcoin-new-ath-by-year-end/">making it an ideal time</a> for investors to <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/buy-much-bitcoin-as-you-can/" rel="nofollow">position themselves</a> in the market. </p>
<p>At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $67,478. A key price level to watch is $69,000. If Bitcoin breaks above this resistance level, it <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-upside-break-68k/">could continue surging higher</a> with the accumulation trend.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/jgGyFuMI/" alt="Bitcoin price chart from Tradingview.com" width="3286" height="1530"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bitcoin-price-1.jpeg?fit=299%2C168" width="299" height="168" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599548</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Retests Resistance: Here&#8217;s The Level A Break Could Lead To</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-retests-resistance-level-break-lead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keshav Verma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Break]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin On-Chain Resistance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin resistance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data shows Bitcoin is currently retesting a major on-chain resistance level, and a break above which can potentially lead to a surge in its price. Bitcoin Has Major On-Chain Resistance Around $67,000 As pointed out by analyst Ali in a post on X, BTC may be able to see a rise towards the $72,900 level if the asset can break the current on-chain resistance barrier. Related Reading: Bitcoin Long-Term Holders &#38; Price Top: Glassnode Reveals Pattern In on-chain analysis, any level&#8217;s potential to act as support or resistance is measured using the amount of Bitcoin that was acquired/bought by the investors around said level. The analyst has shared the chart for the &#8220;UTXO Realized Price Distribution&#8221; (URPD) indicator from Glassnode, that reveals how the various levels around the current spot value of BTC are looking like right now based on the density of supply that was last bought at them. Looks like there is significant resistance coming up ahead at the $72,900 mark &#124; Source: @ali_charts on X The URPD here is &#8220;ATH partitioned,&#8221; which means that the price ranges here are defined by dividing the levels between zero and the current all-time high (ATH) into 100 equal partitions. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the partition around the $66,990 level carries the cost basis of a notable amount of the supply right now (1.3%). This also happens to be the range BTC is retesting at the moment. Generally, the cost basis is a special level for investors, and thus, they tend to be more likely to show some reaction when a retest takes place. If a large number of holders share their cost basis inside the same narrow range, then this reaction may result in a scale that could be relevant for the market. As for what direction this reaction from the holders would be probable to happen depends on the side the retest is happening from. A retest from under (meaning that these holders had been in loss prior to the retest) could lead to a selling reaction in the market. This is because these investors may not want to risk the cryptocurrency declining again in the future, so exiting while they have the opportunity to at their break-even might be tempting. Related Reading: This Bitcoin Halving May Not Result In Supply Squeeze: Glassnode As such, retests like these can lead to the asset feeling some degree of resistance. In the current case, the range is notably filled up with coins, so it&#8217;s possible that the strength of this resistance would be just as powerful. From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that after this range, the asset potentially faces no strong on-chain resistance barriers until the $72,879 level, which hosts the cost basis of about 1.61% of the supply. &#8220;If Bitcoin can break past $66,990, it will likely rise toward $72,880!&#8221; says Ali. BTC Price Bitcoin has been climbing up in the past day, with its price now reaching the $67,200 level. Should this surge be sustained, the asset would be through the current resistance block. The price of the coin appears to have been going up over the past couple of days &#124; Source: BTCUSD on TradingView Featured image from Kanchanara on Unsplash.com, Glassnode.com, chart from TradingView.com]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data shows Bitcoin is currently retesting a major on-chain resistance level, and a break above which can potentially lead to a surge in its price.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Has Major On-Chain Resistance Around $67,000</h2>
<p>As pointed out by analyst Ali in a <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1771966295744893213" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">post</a> on X, BTC may be able to see a rise towards the $72,900 level if the asset can break the current <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/all-clear-40000-bitcoin-little-on-chain-resistance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">on-chain resistance</a> barrier.</p>

<p>In on-chain analysis, any level&#8217;s potential to act as support or resistance is measured using the amount of Bitcoin that was acquired/bought by the investors around said level.</p>
<p>The analyst has shared the chart for the &#8220;<a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitcoin-plunges-64000-on-chain-support/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">UTXO Realized Price Distribution</a>&#8221; (URPD) indicator from Glassnode, that reveals how the various levels around the current spot value of BTC are looking like right now based on the density of supply that was last bought at them.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/GJdJwuOW0AAi7P-?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Bitcoin URPD" width="2416" height="1298"/></p>

<p>The URPD here is &#8220;ATH partitioned,&#8221; which means that the price ranges here are defined by dividing the levels between zero and the current all-time high (ATH) into 100 equal partitions.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that the partition around the $66,990 level carries the cost basis of a notable amount of the supply right now (1.3%). This also happens to be the range BTC is retesting at the moment.</p>
<p>Generally, the cost basis is a special level for investors, and thus, they tend to be more likely to show some reaction when a retest takes place. If a large number of holders share their cost basis inside the same narrow range, then this reaction may result in a scale that could be relevant for the market.</p>
<p>As for what direction this reaction from the holders would be probable to happen depends on the side the retest is happening from. A retest from under (meaning that these holders had been in loss prior to the retest) could lead to a selling reaction in the market.</p>
<p>This is because these investors may not want to risk the cryptocurrency declining again in the future, so exiting while they have the opportunity to at their break-even might be tempting.</p>

<p>As such, retests like these can lead to the asset feeling some degree of resistance. In the current case, the range is notably filled up with coins, so it&#8217;s possible that the strength of this resistance would be just as powerful.</p>
<p>From the chart, it&#8217;s visible that after this range, the asset potentially faces no strong on-chain resistance barriers until the $72,879 level, which hosts the cost basis of about 1.61% of the supply. &#8220;If Bitcoin can break past $66,990, it will likely rise toward $72,880!&#8221; says Ali.</p>
<h2>BTC Price</h2>
<p>Bitcoin has been <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-upside-break-68k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener ">climbing up</a> in the past day, with its price now reaching the $67,200 level. Should this surge be sustained, the asset would be through the current resistance block.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-medium aligncenter" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/iuVOItYA/" alt="Bitcoin Price Chart" width="1534" height="854"/></p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/kanchanara-rhm7H8X5J98-unsplash.jpg?fit=460%2C306" width="460" height="306" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599510</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social Media Storm Gives Dogecoin 14% Price Boost &#8211; Details</title>
		<link>https://www.newsbtc.com/dogecoin-2/social-media-storm-gives-dogecoin-14-price-boost-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Christian Encila]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social media]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsbtc.com/?p=599508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE), the meme-inspired cryptocurrency, has experienced a rollercoaster ride in recent days. A surge in social media activity surrounding the coin coincided with a price increase of over 14% within the last week. However, technical indicators hint at a potential pullback, leaving investors to grapple with mixed signals. Related Reading: Analyst Bullish On Polkadot (DOT), Predicts $17 Price Target Before April Social Media Frenzy Fuels Optimism Data from LunarCrush, a crypto analytics platform, revealed a significant uptick in social media interactions related to DOGE. Likes, comments, retweets, and upvotes on various platforms reached a staggering 30 million within a 24-hour period. This surge in social volume not only placed DOGE at the forefront of meme coin discussions but also suggests renewed investor interest. Regulatory Integration Paves The Way For Institutional Adoption Adding fuel to the fire, Coinbase Derivatives recently filed with the CFTC to introduce US-regulated futures contracts for DOGE, alongside Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash. This regulatory move signifies a growing acceptance of established cryptocurrencies beyond the realm of traditional financial institutions. Integration with established players could lead to greater market stability and wider adoption for DOGE. April: Historically A Bullish Month For Dogecoin? The report also highlights a historical trend – April has proven to be a particularly strong month for DOGE in previous years. This historical data injects a dose of optimism into the current scenario, hinting at a potential price upswing in the coming weeks. However, past performance doesn&#8217;t guarantee future results, and investors should be cautious about relying solely on historical trends. Total crypto market cap is currently at $2.472 trillion. Chart: TradingView Technical Indicators Flash Caution Despite the positive social media sentiment and historical precedent, technical indicators paint a somewhat contrasting picture. The Aroon Up Line, an indicator that gauges trend strength, suggests a weakening uptrend for DOGE. Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) – a measure of money flow – currently displays a negative value, indicating potential selling pressure. DOGE seven-day price action. Source: Coingecko Dogecoin Bearish Signals  The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, often used to identify trend changes, further reinforces the bearish sentiment. Readings show the MACD line crossing below the signal line in mid-March, potentially marking the beginning of a short-term downtrend. Related Reading: Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: Can FTM Hit $2 After 20% Price Spike? Lastly, the Parabolic SAR indicator, which identifies potential trend reversals, positions its dotted lines above the current DOGE price, suggesting increased selling activity. Navigating The Uncertain Waters The current situation surrounding DOGE presents a complex scenario with both positive and negative factors at play. While social media buzz and regulatory progress offer reasons for optimism, technical indicators warn of a potential short-term price correction. Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:332">Dogecoin (DOGE), the meme-inspired cryptocurrency, has experienced a rollercoaster ride in recent days. A surge in social media activity surrounding the coin coincided with a price increase of over 14% within the last week. However, technical indicators hint at a potential pullback, leaving investors to grapple with mixed signals.</p>

<h2 data-sourcepos="5:1-5:38"><strong>Social Media Frenzy Fuels Optimism</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:379"><a href="https://lunarcrush.com/categories/cryptocurrencies?metric=alt_rank&amp;filter=meme&amp;cols=alt_rank%2Cinteractions_24h%2Cclose%2Cpercent_change_24h%2Caverage_sentiment%2Ctop_influencers%2Cmarket_cap%2Cvolume_24h%2Clast_7_days&amp;rpp=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">Data from LunarCrush,</a> a crypto analytics platform, revealed a significant uptick in social media interactions related to<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow"> DOGE</a>. Likes, comments, retweets, and upvotes on various platforms reached a staggering 30 million within a 24-hour period. This surge in social volume not only placed DOGE at the forefront of meme coin discussions but also suggests renewed investor interest.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:379"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-599519" src="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283" alt="" width="1024" height="283" srcset="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283?w=1452 1452w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283?w=460 460w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283?w=768 768w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283?w=860 860w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283?w=750 750w, https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_1d8be2.png?resize=1024%2C283?w=1140 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-recalc-dims="1"/></p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="9:1-9:67"><strong>Regulatory Integration Paves The Way For Institutional Adoption</strong></h2>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:410">Adding fuel to the fire, Coinbase Derivatives recently filed with the CFTC to introduce US-regulated futures contracts for <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow">DOGE,</a> alongside Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash. This regulatory move signifies a growing acceptance of established cryptocurrencies beyond the realm of traditional financial institutions. Integration with established players could lead to greater market stability and wider adoption for DOGE.</p>
<strong>April: Historically A Bullish Month For Dogecoin?</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:395">The report also highlights a historical trend – April has proven to be a particularly strong month for DOGE in previous years. This historical data injects a dose of optimism into the current scenario, hinting at a potential price upswing in the coming weeks. However, past performance doesn&#8217;t guarantee future results, and investors should be cautious about relying solely on historical trends.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:395"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full" src="https://www.tradingview.com/x/D2u5R3fD/" width="1835" height="883"/></p>

<strong>Technical Indicators Flash Caution</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="19:1-19:374">Despite the positive social media sentiment and historical precedent, technical indicators paint a somewhat contrasting picture. The Aroon Up Line, an indicator that gauges trend strength, suggests a weakening uptrend for DOGE. Additionally, the Chaikin Money Flow (CMF) – a measure of money flow – currently displays a negative value, indicating potential selling pressure.</p>

<strong>Dogecoin Bearish Signals </strong>
<p data-sourcepos="23:1-23:450">The Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) indicator, often used to identify trend changes, further reinforces the bearish sentiment. Readings show the MACD line crossing below the signal line in mid-March, potentially marking the beginning of a short-term downtrend.</p>

<p data-sourcepos="23:1-23:450">Lastly, the Parabolic SAR indicator, which identifies potential trend reversals, positions its dotted lines above the current DOGE price, suggesting increased selling activity.</p>
<strong>Navigating The Uncertain Waters</strong>
<p data-sourcepos="27:1-27:396">The current situation surrounding DOGE presents a complex scenario with both positive and negative factors at play. While social media buzz and regulatory progress offer reasons for optimism, technical indicators warn of a potential short-term price correction.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="35:1-35:373"><em>Featured image from Pexels, chart from TradingView</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.newsbtc.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/a_461236.jpg?fit=460%2C259" width="460" height="259" /><post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">599508</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
