<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:17:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Scammers Utilize AI Tools to Exploit Tax Season Anxiety</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/scammers-use-ai-tools-to-exploit-tax-season/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Kanana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Explained]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scammers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tax Season]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As tax season unfolds, anxiety surges among Americans, not only over the complexities of filing taxes but also due to the escalating threat of online tax scams. According to recent findings by McAfee, a leading cybersecurity firm, 25% of Americans have fallen victim to online tax scams. The prevalence of these scams underscores the pressing [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As tax season unfolds, anxiety surges among Americans, not only over the complexities of filing taxes but also due to the escalating threat of online tax scams. According to recent findings by McAfee, a leading cybersecurity firm, 25% of Americans have fallen victim to online tax scams. The prevalence of these scams underscores the pressing need for heightened vigilance and awareness among consumers.</p>



<p>In a disturbing trend, cybercriminals are increasingly turning to advanced artificial intelligence (AI) tools to orchestrate their fraudulent activities. McAfee&#8217;s research highlights the proliferation of deepfake technology, particularly in deceptive robocalls. These AI-generated calls, often embellished with regionally appropriate accents, pose a formidable challenge to unsuspecting recipients.</p>



<p>Despite the growing sophistication of these scams, a concerning number of Americans remain inadequately prepared to discern fraudulent content. Alarmingly, nearly half of respondents express confidence in their ability to identify deepfake videos or AI-generated audio, leaving a significant portion vulnerable to manipulation and exploitation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Consumer education and vigilance are crucial</h2>



<p>Against this backdrop of evolving cyber threats, McAfee emphasizes the paramount importance of consumer education and proactive measures to thwart online tax scams. With tax-related phishing emails emerging as a prevalent tactic, consumers are urged to exercise caution when encountering messages purporting to be from tax authorities, particularly those with PDF attachments.</p>



<p>Steve Grobman, Chief Technology Officer at McAfee, underscores the imperative for consumers to leverage AI-powered protection mechanisms to safeguard their personal information and privacy. He emphasizes the need for a balanced approach, advocating for adopting cyber hygiene practices alongside utilizing advanced security measures.</p>



<p>Despite widespread concerns surrounding online tax scams, a significant portion of Americans remain ill-equipped to combat this menace. McAfee&#8217;s findings reveal a striking lack of confidence among individuals in discerning the authenticity of tax-related communications, with over half expressing uncertainty in identifying potential scams.</p>



<p>Furthermore, some respondents admit to overlooking basic security measures during tax season, such as refraining from clicking on unfamiliar links or opening attachments from unknown sources. Alarmingly, only a third of individuals utilize two-factor authentication, leaving their accounts vulnerable to exploitation.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Pervasive nature of online tax scams</h2>



<p>The pervasive nature of online tax scams is underscored by the prevalence of deceptive messages impersonating tax authorities. McAfee&#8217;s research indicates that many Americans have encountered fraudulent messages purporting to be from the IRS or state tax authorities, often soliciting sensitive personal information.</p>



<p>In response to these escalating threats, McAfee urges consumers to remain vigilant and proactive in safeguarding their financial and personal information. By exercising caution and leveraging AI-powered security solutions, individuals can mitigate the risks posed by cybercriminals seeking to exploit the anxieties of tax season.</p>



<p>The convergence of tax season anxiety and the proliferation of AI-driven scams underscores the urgent need for heightened awareness and proactive measures among consumers. By staying informed and adopting robust security practices, individuals can navigate the intricacies of tax season while safeguarding themselves against online threats.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_online_scammers_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_online_scammers_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron Price Prediction 2024-2033: Is it a Good Time to buy TRX?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tron-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=45257</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tron Price Prediction 2024-2033 TRX, or rather Tronix, is the native&#160;crypto asset of the TRON Network. TRON is a Blockchain-based decentralized network targeting an unchained, worldwide digital content entertainment structure using distributed ledger technology and enabling straightforward and cheap data sharing. How is Tron Price Prediction making out in this turbulent crypto weather as major [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Tron Price Prediction 2024-2033</h3>



<ul>
<li><a href="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2024" data-type="internal" data-id="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2024">Tron Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; up to <strong>$0.22</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2027" data-type="internal" data-id="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2027">Tron Price Prediction 2027 &#8211; up to <strong>$0.58</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2029" data-type="internal" data-id="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2029">Tron Price Prediction 2</a><a href="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2030" data-type="internal" data-id="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2030">0</a><a href="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2030" data-type="internal" data-id="#TRON-Price-Prediction-2029">30 &#8211; up to <strong>$1.74</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#TRON-(TRX)-Price-Prediction-2033" data-type="internal" data-id="#TRON-(TRX)-Price-Prediction-2033">Tron Price Prediction 2033 &#8211; up to <strong>$4.97</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<p>TRX, or rather Tronix, is the native<strong>&nbsp;crypto asset of the TRON Network</strong>. TRON is a Blockchain-based decentralized network targeting an unchained, worldwide digital content entertainment structure using distributed ledger technology and enabling straightforward and cheap data sharing. How is Tron Price Prediction making out in this turbulent crypto weather as major crypto exchanges unravel?</p>



<p>One of the several cryptocurrencies that experienced an all-time high during the late 2017 and early 2018 cryptocurrency craze is TRX. It may be realistic to wonder whether and when it can return there, if at all, given that it hasn&#8217;t even come close to the heights it attained back then. As with other cryptos, it is always advised to do your own research and seek investment advice whenever investing.</p>



<p>Like many&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/web-stories/top-5-proof-of-stake-coins-in-2022/" data-type="web-story" data-id="224303">cryptocurrencies</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tron-price-analysis-2022-06-03-2/" data-type="post" data-id="167115">blockchain</a>&nbsp;assets, Tron enjoys a great deal of interest not only in its immediate utility in empowering the next form of the internet – but also in its potential to bring profit to those holding it. Rest assured that a lot of development is taking place to improve the <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TronScript/comments/ybzhbi/tron_v1204_20221023_add_additional_win10/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Tron ecosystem</a>. If you encounter any issue with the system, here is a good place to <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TronScript/wiki/index/#wiki_cq_.28common_questions.29" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">look</a>.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is TRX worth?</h4>



<p>Today’s TRON price is $0.1211 with a 24-hour trading volume of $363,462,492 USD. TRON is up 1.50% in the last 24 hours. The current CoinMarketCap ranking is #10, with a live market cap of $10,628,918,132 USD. It has a circulating supply of 87,775,562,934 TRX coins and the max. supply is not available.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Tron price analysis: Bullish wave surpasses $0.1216 target rapidly</h2>



<p>TL; DR Breakdown</p>



<ul>
<li>Tron price analysis confirms an uptrend.</li>



<li>Coin value has climbed up to $0.1216.</li>



<li>Support is being provided at $0.1121.</li>
</ul>



<p>The latest one-day and four-hour Tron price analysis for 26 March 2024 predicts signs of a growing bullish trend. The bulls have been ruling the market since the past week as the buying activity remained on the intense side. As the upswing seems to be aggravating once again, the coin value has been able to achieve $0.1216 target today.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">TRX price analysis 1-day chart: Upswing aggravates surge beyond $0.1216 high</h3>



<p>The latest one-day and four-hour Tron price analysis depict a highly bullish scenario for the cryptocurrency today. The price has been following an ascending path since the past few days as the buying pressure remained considerably high. Because of the bullish rush observed during the last 24-hours, TRX/USD value has climbed up to $0.1216 hill. On the opposite side, its Moving Average (MA) value has deteriorated to $0.1197 because of the previous downside.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1015" height="579" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-47.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501726" style="aspect-ratio:1.822262118491921;width:1015px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-47.png 1015w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-47-300x171.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-47-768x438.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1015px) 100vw, 1015px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">TRX/USD 1-day price chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>The volatility is declining which is a bullish signal for the future. As the volatility is on the decreasing side, the upper end of the Bollinger bands indicator has moved to $0.1404. Whereby, the lower end of the Bollinger bands indicator is currently situated at $0.1121. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator confirms the bullish spike as its overall value has improved up to 41.81.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">TRX/USD 4-hour price chart: Upturn aids coin value achieve $0.1216 target</h3>



<p>The latest four-hour Tron price analysis confirms a strong bullish swing for now. The increasing trend has remained quite intense since the earlier hours of the day. In the past four hours, a further aggravation in the uptrend was observed as TRX/USD value climbed up to $0.1216 high. Side by side, its Moving Average value has stepped up to $0.1202 because of the increasing momentum. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" width="1015" height="579" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-50.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501727" style="width:840px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-50.png 1015w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-50-300x171.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-50-768x438.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1015px) 100vw, 1015px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">TRX/USD 4-hour price chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/TRXUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>The volatility seems to be on the increasing side which is a bearish signal for the future. Because of the rising volatility, the upper end of the Bollinger bands indicator has moved to $0.1221. Whereby, the lower end of the Bollinger bands indicator is now situated at $0.1168. The RSI graph confirms the bullish revival as its overall value has moved up to index 56.52.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from TRX price analysis?</h3>



<p>The one-day and four-hour Tron price analysis confirms an increasing trend for the cryptocurrency today. The circumstances remained highly favorable for the buyers as the coin value achieved a massive recovery above $0.1216 peak. Similarly, the four-hour price analysis confirms an upward swing as the buying pressure intensified in the past few hours of the day.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">is Tron a good investment?</h2>



<p>Tron (TRX) presents an intriguing investment prospect with notable advantages despite facing criticisms and challenges. Its enduring presence in the cryptocurrency market, consistently maintaining a top 50 position, underscores its resilience. Tron&#8217;s bold ambition to decentralize the web, exemplified by strategic acquisitions like BitTorrent, has drawn attention. The integration of the USDD stablecoin has bolstered Tron&#8217;s liquidity, appealing to investors seeking stability amidst market volatility. The recent introduction of an algorithmic stablecoin has catalyzed TRX&#8217;s price surge, showcasing its innovative potential.</p>



<p>However, detractors highlight concerns over founder Justin Sun&#8217;s controversial reputation, potential risks associated with the USDD stablecoin, and issues within Tron&#8217;s ecosystem, particularly concerning low-quality decentralized applications. Consequently, while some investors view Tron as a promising asset for portfolio diversification, others advise caution due to uncertainties surrounding its leadership and ecosystem. Ultimately, investing in Tron demands careful evaluation, thorough research, and an understanding of one&#8217;s risk tolerance to navigate its opportunities and challenges effectively. Our Tron price forecast section provides analysis on the profitability of the coin in the coming years.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News on TRON</h2>



<p><strong>Crypto Market Outlook: TRON, and Optimism Gain Momentum. </strong>The cryptocurrency market is witnessing notable upticks in TRON (TRX) and Optimism (OP) driven by various factors. TRON&#8217;s resilience amidst market volatility, and Optimism&#8217;s rebound fueled by ecosystem growth and partnerships. TRX is expected to surpass $0.130, while OP expected to exceed $3.50 to generate substantial returns, these coins represent promising opportunities amid ongoing market fluctuations.</p>



<p><strong>Tron Founder Justin Sun Counters UN Report on USDT Misuse. </strong>Tron founder Justin Sun has disputed a United Nations (UN) report that raised concerns about the misuse of Tether&#8217;s USDT in illicit activities, particularly in Southeast Asia. The report highlighted potential issues with online gambling and money laundering. Sun refuted specific details related to USDT transactions on the TRC-20 protocol within the Tron network, emphasizing the network&#8217;s commitment to transparency and legal compliance. Tether, the company behind USDT, responded by emphasizing its role in developing economies, commitment to transparency, and proactive efforts against misuse. The UN report acknowledged successful law enforcement operations against money laundering networks using Tether. Justin Sun advocated for increased blockchain education and proposed collaborations between Tron, HTX DAO, and the United Nations to expand global understanding of blockchain technology and foster legitimate financial transactions.</p>



<p><strong>Solana Overtakes Tron in Stablecoin Volume.</strong> Tron, once a leader in stablecoin volumes, has lost its top spot to Solana, raising concerns about its market position and user confidence. Solana recorded a stablecoin transfer volume of $24.58 billion in December, surpassing Tron and Ethereum. Tron faces additional challenges with legal issues, as the SEC charges founder Justin Sun and affiliated entities. The legal uncertainties could impact Tron&#8217;s credibility and market sentiment. Despite these challenges, Tron is exploring partnerships, such as the one with ChainGPT for an AI-powered chatbot, and has implemented Stake 2.0 to enhance its staking model. TRX&#8217;s current price stands at $0.109931, showing resilience despite the stablecoin volume setback.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Tron Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Predictions By Cryptopolitan&nbsp;</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/F9Ke41CGj2BDkmGzxAmsHPfJIO7WGF5awrZF64nMMpdT3XIDPcWSdjlYp_SEceF4rr-gafPS6oDsqfTpIlp0UVhJARPWHtcSkSRKhwFOSCjG5dBqjp4LJcfVwSYtS4Ixw7b45DDeOufH_vEbQSm92KU" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum ($)</td><td>Average ($)</td><td>Maximum ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>0.11</td><td>0.15</td><td>0.22</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>0.22</td><td>0.23</td><td>0.27</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>0.32</td><td>0.34</td><td>0.38</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>0.48</td><td>0.50</td><td>0.58</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>0.71</td><td>0.73</td><td>0.83</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>1.01</td><td>1.04</td><td>1.24</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>1.43</td><td>1.47</td><td>1.74</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>2.00</td><td>2.07</td><td>2.47</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>2.93</td><td>3.01</td><td>3.50</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>4.05</td><td>4.17</td><td>4.97</td></tr></tbody></table><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">TRON Price Predictions 2024-2033</figcaption></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>Our deep technical analysis of past TRX price data suggests that in 2024, TRON&#8217;s price is expected to hit a minimum of $0.1578. The TRX price may peak at $0.1935, with an average trading price of $0.1624.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>Based on forecasted prices and technical analysis, TRON&#8217;s price in 2025 is anticipated to reach a minimum of $0.2233. The TRX price might rise to a maximum of $0.2727, averaging around $0.2314.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRX Price Forecast for 2026</h4>



<p>The forecast for 2026 indicates that TRON&#8217;s price could drop to as low as $0.3247. However, the TRX price might climb to a peak of $0.3797, with an expected average of $0.3362.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON (TRX) Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>In 2027, TRON&#8217;s price is projected to reach a minimum of $0.4813. The price may surge to a maximum of $0.5844, maintaining an average of about $0.4981 throughout the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>The 2028 forecast suggests that TRON&#8217;s price could reach a minimum of $0.7059. The TRX price might escalate to a high of $0.8332, with an average trading value of $0.7308.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our in-depth technical analysis indicates that in 2029, TRON&#8217;s price is expected to hover around a minimum of $1.01. The maximum price value could be $1.24, with an average value of $1.04.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON (TRX) Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>TRON&#8217;s price in 2030 is predicted to reach at least $1.43. The price may peak at $1.74, with an average value of $1.47 throughout the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Forecast 2031</h4>



<p>The 2031 forecast for TRON suggests a minimum price of $2.00. The TRX price might achieve a maximum of $2.47, averaging around $2.07.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON (TRX) Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>For 2032, TRON&#8217;s price is predicted to reach a minimum of $2.93. The price might climb to a high of $3.50, with an average price of $3.01.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>In 2033, the price of 1 TRON is expected to reach at least $4.05. The TRX price may escalate to a maximum of $4.97, averaging around $4.17 throughout the year.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction By Coincodex&nbsp;</h3>



<p>According to the current TRON price prediction provided by Coincodex, the value of TRON is anticipated to decline by -8.69%, reaching $0.127464 by March 10, 2024. Coincodex&#8217;s technical indicators suggest a Bullish current sentiment, with the Fear &amp; Greed Index indicating 90 (Extreme Greed). TRON has experienced 18/30 (60%) green days, with a price volatility of 5.97% over the past 30 days.</p>



<p>The forecast from Coincodex suggests that it is now an opportune time to purchase TRON. Considering the historical price trends of TRON and the BTC halving cycles, the lowest predicted price for TRON in 2025 stands at $0.121087. Meanwhile, TRON&#8217;s price is expected to climb to a high of $0.431121 in the following year.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Coin Price Prediction By DigitalCoinPrice</h3>



<p>Digital Coin Price suggests that there is potential for TRON to surpass the $0.36 mark and sustain its market position by the end of 2025. The lowest price for TRON is projected to be between $0.30 and $0.36, with the most probable price expected to stabilize at around $0.34 by the conclusion of 2025.</p>



<p>Despite the significant fluctuations in TRON&#8217;s value and the debates over its environmentally unfriendly energy consumption, billionaire venture capitalist Tim Draper remains firm in his forecast, anticipating that TRON will achieve $0.36 by the end of 2025 or early in the year.</p>



<p>In 2033, TRON is expected to aim for a minimum value of $2.62. It is projected to strive for a maximum and subsequent top-tier price of $2.72, with an average forecast price pegged at $2.71. TRON may surpass its previous highs and advance to new levels. Should conditions evolve favorably, it is anticipated that TRON will ascend to its next stage. However, there is also the possibility of a decline in its value.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price Prediction By CryptoPredictions.com</h3>



<p>According to Cryptopredictions.com, TRON&#8217;s price is expected to begin at $0.15 in April 2024 and conclude the month at $0.17. Throughout April, the highest projected TRX price is $0.217, with the lowest price forecasted to be $0.147.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="908" height="253" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_2945.png" alt="Screenshot 2945" class="wp-image-306774" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_2945.png 908w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_2945-300x84.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot_2945-768x214.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 908px) 100vw, 908px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Tron Market Statistics</figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Price History</h2>



<p>As seen on the Tron chart, the price of Tron cryptocurrency has seen a good amount of volatility over the past years.</p>



<p>After spending the second half of 2019 retracing from $0.04, TRX eventually found support around the exchange rate of $0.11.</p>



<p>This resulted in a push higher at the beginning of 2020 as the price set a new higher high, indicating that a new bull cycle has potentially begun.</p>



<p>However, after peaking at $0.026 in the middle of February 2020, the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tron-trx-price-28-august-2019/">Tron price</a> got heavily rejected to the downside, destroying any bullish price prediction at the time. What followed for the price of crypto was another dump lower.</p>



<p>The Tron price pushed through previous support and set a new several-year low at $0.07.</p>



<p>The price started to slowly recover from there on, creating a bullish Tron (TRX) price action structure by the end of the year.</p>



<p>In September, the Tron price moved and saw a very sharp spike to the upside, resulting in a brief breakout from the significant resistance of $0.04 as it hit a new several-year high of $0.05.</p>



<p>During the following weeks, the crypto retraced toward the previous resistance of $0.22-$0.025 and retested it as support.</p>



<p>As expected by analysis of several well-known traders at the time, Tron&#8217;s price reversed from thereon. After spending the end of 2020 in a consolidation, Tron pushed higher at the beginning of February in a solid bull run, resulting in a $0.065 level being reached, beating several predictions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/6_IaP_KjuZ6FOWNI21AFB_zEz_Pp0ElLOYsoMu1zIqWDA_m8II1Wo64-z90iZK1v4KWCDWiOUlAnyJb1eq5ub6uU6yvynsdvmTj_K_KGCKXMevQOm60raYPuUcdZj2QXCrc9vhr9" alt="" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Source: Tradingview</figcaption></figure>



<p>It is in a bearish momentum and has an RSI index of 39. In the 4-hour chart, we can make a short-term Tron price prediction using the above technical analysis. With the reversal in the trend, the coin price has changed its bearish outlook as it is trading above the 50-day and 100-day MA, breaking out of the upper end of the Bollinger Band.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Developments affecting the TRX Price</h3>



<p>The price took a sudden hit of 7% when,&nbsp;on&nbsp;December 17,&nbsp; Justin Sun&nbsp;announced&nbsp;that he had been appointed as&nbsp;Ambassador, Permanent Representative of Grenada to the World Trade Organization, and would be stepping back from TRON. As a result, the TRON Foundation has&nbsp;said&nbsp;it&nbsp;has <strong>&#8220;settled to dissolve itself on July 25, 2022&#8221;</strong>.</p>



<p>Despite this, the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tron-price-analysis-2022-01-11/" data-type="post" data-id="143851"> Tron (TRX) price</a> still keeps going up. Could it be that the strategic investment of an undisclosed amount in the DeFine social NFT platform is finally bearing fruits? The funding will be used to develop the first NFT marketplace in the TRON ecosystem and launch auctions soon.&nbsp;Or could it be that the network&#8217;s BTFS file storage system (was integrated with DeFine in September? Or TRON&#8217;s expansion into the NFT ecosystem with APENFT is operating successfully? Or was some other strategy hatched by Justin Sun?</p>



<p>Now, let’s look at the long-term Tron price prediction for the upcoming years and remember that these Tron price predictions are not investment advice.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on the Tron Network</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Is Tron (TRX)?</h3>



<p>Tron (TRX) was created by tech entrepreneur Justin Sun in 2017. The TRON project funds were raised through an&nbsp;Initial Coin Offering (ICO), with a subscription of funds reaching 70 million. This was one of the largest ICOs and increased cryptocurrency popularity even further.</p>



<p>Today, Tron has grown into one of the largest cryptocurrencies with over $5.4 billion in capitalization, while the 24-hour trading volume exceeds $250 million.</p>



<p>At first, TRX ran on Ethereum&#8217;s ERC-20 blockchain as it offered a quick and easy solution for running the peer-to-peer network. Later on, the developers of Tron switched the blockchain to their custom-made solution.</p>



<p>The blockchain used proof of stake mining and validation consensus algorithm and was one of the first cryptocurrency projects to implement this solution.</p>



<p>One of the primary use cases and benefits of the TRX platform is the support for content creators and artists by providing ownership over the content they create.</p>



<p>This is done by storing and tracking the information about created content and its use on the blockchain.</p>



<p>Therefore, content creators can directly track how their creations are used and their reward for producing them. The middleman is eliminated, and content creators get paid instantly.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">TRON Ecosystem Applications</h3>



<p>Some of the core applications that the TRON ecosystem aims to provide include:</p>



<ul>
<li><strong>Wallet-Cli:</strong> Wallet-Cli is the official&nbsp;<a href="https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/getting-started/crypto-education/glossary/wallet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><u>wallet</u></a>&nbsp;client provided by the TRON foundation. Further, Wallet-Cli is a command-line version of the wallet that provides essential tools to communicate with the TRON public chain by RPC protocol.&nbsp;<a href="https://www.techopedia.com/definition/24022/remote-procedure-call-rpc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><u>RPC</u></a>&nbsp;protocol stands for remote procedure call, an inter-process communication technique used for point-to-point communication between software applications. Wallet-Cli supports all functions of the TRON public chain in real-time.</li>



<li><strong>TronLink: </strong>TronLink is a TRON wallet that provides users with a convenient experience, complete functions, and secure funding options.</li>



<li><strong>Blockchain Explorer: </strong>The first blockchain explorer based on TRON is tronscan.org, which offers essential functions like searching transactions, accounts,&nbsp;blocks,&nbsp;nodes, smart contracts, token creation, and more.</li>



<li><strong>DApp: </strong>TRON public chain aims to attract a vast community of developers to join in the development, deployment, and running of DApps on the blockchain because of their high performance, low cost, and safety.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Tron Foundation</h3>



<p>The Tron foundation is the governing body of the Tron blockchain. They aim to popularise and further develop the blockchain. Based in Singapore, they ensure that the TRX blockchain is regulated and complies with laws. Tron, Justin Sun, is still the Tron foundation leader and is listed in the Forbes list of 30 under 30 in Asia.</p>



<p>In 2018, a popular peer-to-peer torrent-sharing network – BitTorrent, announced that the TRON Foundation had acquired them to use TRX tokens to incentivize and reward network users. This created massive interest for the token, and it soon exceeded a $1 billion cap.</p>



<p>Several other projects and development phases have since been launched, with the most notable ones being the Odyssey, which created a system for incentivizing content creators. Further development phases – Great Voyage and Apollo-enable content creators to build their brands and issue personalized initial coin offerings to raise funds for their projects.</p>



<p>Plans to develop the ecosystem align with Star-Trek and Eternity phases. Star-Trek is set to launch in mid-2023, and Eternity in late 2025.</p>



<p>Therefore, we will probably see interest in Tron and blockchain itself grow even further in the upcoming years and increase the price.</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s look at Tron&#8217;s previous price history to understand what the future price could look like. It is a good investment if you rapidly lose money in all others.</p>



<p>Tron has been compared with Ethereum due to its lower fees and fast payment. When ETH was at its all-time high, a considerable amount of fees was applicable for transfer, and for this reason, people started shifting to TRON.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What other factors affect the TRX price?</h3>



<p>Tron celebrated the most significant milestones in its existence, surpassing a million active user accounts. But since then, a lot has changed because the total number of active user accounts surpassed 4 million, and it is flourishing.</p>



<p>Moving forward, in the first week of June 2021, there have been more than 10 million transactions recorded on the Tron blockchain. On June 14, it recorded a total of 1,049,206 transactions. That is almost triple the number of transactions recorded daily on the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>



<p>Factors affecting Tron&#8217;s price are the same as any other cryptocurrency – mainly, the supply and demand on cryptocurrency exchanges. More significant deals are often done off the exchanges, creating a negligible impact on the Tron price.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Supply and Demand</h4>



<p>The coin supply naturally comes from the number of tokens released into the market every day. In the case of Tron, you can earn a mining reward by staking the coin.</p>



<p>As of now, staking TRX offers around a 7 percent annual yield. However, this yield will vary over time and based on market conditions.</p>



<p>On the other hand, the demand for Tron comes from investors who want to buy it with the expectation that its long-term value will grow. Another motivation for purchasing Tron is the ability to stake your coins, giving you an annual yield.</p>



<p>Staking TRX tokens also gives the power to vote on various issues that the network developers want to solve or features that they want to add. Therefore, by purchasing and staking TRX, you help ensure the TRX blockchain&#8217;s consensus mechanism.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Regulatory Compliance</h4>



<p>Recently rumors of the United States and China investigating the TRON Foundation and the blockchain itself. In his Twitter account, the founder of Tron Network, Justin Sun, ensured no reasons to doubt the accusations of malpractice as the network is run as a decentralized network. Therefore, claims of centralized manipulation are of no sense since the TRON Foundation is only one of several thousands of participants.</p>



<p>Overall, TRX is compliant with various global regulations as any other major blockchain. This ensures the demand for TRX continues growing. Therefore, over time, the crypto market price should continue to rise over the next five years.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">The Rise of DApps</h4>



<p>Over the last months, the TRX network experienced an increased interest in decentralized applications (DApps). As of now, more than 100 DApps are running on the blockchain, offering various categories of functionality ranging from exchanges to gaming and gambling.</p>



<p>Websites such as DappRadar offer a quick overview of the most popular ones and how many users have each decentralized application attracted over time. User count ranges from several hundred to several thousand, and this number is expected to grow further over the next 5-year period.</p>



<p>This raised interest in the TRX blockchain functionality, which created an additional appeal to invest in Tron. Therefore, creating extra trading volume and market growth for the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Where to buy Tron?</h3>



<p>Tron is available for trading on practically every major exchange, just like Bitcoin or Ethereum. It is one of the best-known cryptocurrencies, with a high average trading volume of more than $2 billion per day. As seen during previous bull markets of cryptocurrencies, this number is likely to grow over the next five years. Therefore purchasing crypto shouldn&#8217;t be an issue for anyone interested in trading or investing.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How to store Tron?</h3>



<p>Tron offers several options for storing crypto. The basic one is the so-called TRON paper wallet, which involves a primary method of printing out your private keys and keeping them on a piece of paper in a place to which only you have access. This basic solution comes from earlier cryptocurrencies such as Ethereum.</p>



<p>Other options include Tron Android wallet, Tron IOS wallet, Chrome wallet, Exodus desktop wallet, and the commonly used hardware wallets of<a href="https://www.ledger.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">&nbsp;Ledger</a>&nbsp;Nano and<a href="https://trezor.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">&nbsp;Trezor</a>. This means that the Tron coin can be stored in as many different wallet options as other well-established cryptos, such as Ethereum.</p>



<p>TRON DAO introduced a development fund to support blockchain projects focused on AI. With AI technology gaining increased attention and experiencing growth, especially within the cryptocurrency sector, TRON DAO seeks to expedite this trend through its latest $100 million fund.</p>



<p>It is anticipated that TRON will soon position itself at the top list of dominating the payment sector, significantly pushing TRX&#8217;s price to the North.</p>



<p>Not long ago, TRON&#8217;s stablecoin USDD depegged from $1 and traded at $0.97, which built up a strong negative sentiment in the TRON community with an extended bearish consolidation ahead in the TRX price graph. However, the development team seems promising as it looks for several ways to revive the ecosystem with great enhancements to the network. It is advised to do your own research and conduct good investment advice before investing in the highly volatile market.&nbsp;</p>



<p>TRON has evolved the blockchain space to a new era as it focuses on developing the foundation of a decentralized global ecosystem, which is a crucial sector of the crypto space. TRON coin is a <strong>highly-rated</strong> cryptocurrency with massive potential for widespread adoption in the future. Much of these expectations are due to the strategic partnerships continuously secured by the TRON ecosystem in a bid to promote awareness of the platform.</p>



<p>An example of such partnerships is the recent collaboration with the Republic of Dominica, in which the TRON platform will be used to create fan tokens known as Dominica Coins (DMC), which serve to promote the country&#8217;s national and cultural heritage.</p>



<p>The Tron ecosystem is rapidly growing with new users and dApps. This results from the robustness, scalability, and low cost of the blockchain. As we transition into WEB 3, we anticipate new industry players to <strong>plug into the Tron blockchain</strong>, like Samsung.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the TRON network continues to attract numerous developers and users with its high throughput and low transaction fees. On the first of September, Tron&#8217;s founder, Justin Sun, <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1565247306475024384?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1565247306475024384%7Ctwgr%5E54addde0e9823b5dd23a710d1ce8cf4ba8841018%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2022%2F09%2F01%2Ftron-surpasses-5-trillion-in-total-transfer-value%2F" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">announced</a> the network had hit a new milestone, recording a total transfer value of over $5 trillion since its launch in 2018.</p>



<p>Tron has weathered its investors from this year&#8217;s crypto winter, and due to its<strong> high utility</strong>, it will be highly profitable in the following market bull run. The shaky performance of Tron USDD stablecoin will adversely affect Tron’s performance in the case of a crash.</p>



<p>Many Tron opponents and Ethereum proponents have long believed that Tron is not legitimate crypto. They have speculated on the legitimacy of Tron as a company in general after Tron openly admitted that it is going after Ethereum. ETH is the second-largest crypto by market capitalization.</p>



<p>However, crypto enthusiasts think that the two projects cannot be compared. They are different since the ETH developers wrote their code from scratch, while Tron might have copied and improved the code. Nonetheless, Sun said that the Tron blockchain code was written from scratch and <strong>originally in Chinese</strong>, the main thing going for TRX.</p>



<p>TRON may soon make a bullish reversal as the developing team is actively looking for valuable opportunities to bring to the TRX platform. If the demand for TRX stays stable or increases, and supply remains constant, TRON crypto may see a<strong> price increase</strong> in the future. With the Tron Foundation out of the way, TRX will be one of the most decentralized cryptos and can shoot up to a high of<strong> $3.05</strong> with an average forecast price of $2.56 by 2032. You have to trade and hold TRX for a long time before<strong> getting rich</strong> due to its volatility.</p>



<p>Most TRON price predictions consider TRX a favorable asset for long-term investment, capable of delivering steady profits over the years. The future prices of TRON will majorly depend on the crypto <strong>market&#8217;s favorability</strong> to make it a good investment option. That said, these price predictions are not guaranteed, as various factors can influence cryptocurrency market prices. Thus, investors are advised to consult with financial market experts before <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/is-cryptocurrency-a-good-investment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">making investment decisions</a>.</p>



<p>By reading your favorite coins&#8217; <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/tron-price-analysis-2022-01-11/" data-type="post" data-id="143851">price analysis</a> and <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bitcoin-ethereum-solana-tron-daily-price-analysis-15-december-roundup/" data-type="post" data-id="138120">daily roundups</a>, you may keep yourself updated and better able to make a decision.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/tron-price-prediction.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/tron-price-prediction.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enugu State Partners with ALX Nigeria to Offer Free AI Course to 5,000 Youths</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/enugu-state-partners-with-alx-nigeria/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Kanana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Trending News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI Course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ALX Nigeria]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501720</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enugu State has announced a groundbreaking partnership with ALX Nigeria aimed at providing essential Artificial Intelligence (AI) skills to 5,000 youths. This initiative, known as the Free Artificial Intelligence Career Essentials (AICE) course, signifies a pivotal step towards empowering Enugu&#8217;s youth and preparing them for the fast-evolving tech-driven job market. The collaboration between ALX Nigeria [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Enugu State has announced a groundbreaking partnership with ALX Nigeria aimed at providing essential Artificial Intelligence (AI) skills to 5,000 youths. This initiative, known as the Free Artificial Intelligence Career Essentials (AICE) course, signifies a pivotal step towards empowering Enugu&#8217;s youth and preparing them for the fast-evolving tech-driven job market.</p>



<p>The collaboration between ALX Nigeria and the Enugu State Government is strategically designed to equip young individuals with the fundamental skills required in Artificial Intelligence. Recognizing the importance of staying abreast of technological advancements, this initiative ensures that Enugu&#8217;s youth are well-prepared to thrive in the digital age.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Fostering economic empowerment</h2>



<p>ALX and the Enugu State Government share the goal of democratizing access to high-quality tech education. By offering the AICE course free of charge, they aim to foster economic empowerment among youths, providing them with the necessary tools to pursue promising career paths in AI and related fields.</p>



<p>Speaking at a press briefing in Enugu, the Commissioner for Youth and Sports, Lloyd Ekweremadu, highlighted the significance of the collaboration in driving socio-economic development and youth empowerment within the state. Ekweremadu underscored Enugu State&#8217;s commitment to equipping its youth with relevant skills to excel in today&#8217;s tech-driven world and compete globally in technology and ICT.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Tackling youth unemployment</h2>



<p>With youth unemployment being a pressing issue in Nigeria, initiatives like the AICE course play a crucial role in addressing this challenge. By building capacity among the youth in tech, the partnership between ALX and the Enugu State Government aims to create opportunities for young people, enabling them to harness the power of AI and embark on fulfilling career paths.</p>



<p>Through collaboration with ALX Nigeria, Enugu State is opening doors to opportunity for 5,000 young individuals. By providing them with access to quality tech education, the state aims to empower its youth to leverage AI effectively, thereby contributing to their personal development and the overall growth of the region&#8217;s technology sector.</p>



<p>The partnership between ALX Nigeria and the Enugu State Government marks a significant milestone in efforts to empower youths and drive socio-economic development through tech education. By offering the AICE course, Enugu State is preparing its youth for the future and positioning itself as a hub for innovation and technological advancement. With this initiative, Enugu&#8217;s youth are poised to embrace the opportunities of the digital era and contribute meaningfully to the advancement of society.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_A_university_course_in_Nigeria_0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_A_university_course_in_Nigeria_0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin Price Prediction 2024-2033: Is BNB Ready for the Bull Run?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/binance-coin-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=119696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance Coin Price Prediction 2024-2033 After notable changes in its executive team, Binance has shown notable resilience and prospects for recovery. The departure of Changpeng Zhao, Binance&#8217;s CEO, who was also embroiled in legal challenges, initially caused a decline in the value of Binance Coin (BNB). Despite this initial setback, the cryptocurrency has shown a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Binance Coin Price Prediction 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2024" data-type="internal" data-id="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2024">BNB Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; up to <strong>$511.62</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2027" data-type="internal" data-id="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2027">BNB Price Prediction 2027 &#8211; up to <strong><strong>$</strong>1,593.00</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2030" data-type="internal" data-id="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2030">BNB Price Prediction 2030 &#8211; up to <strong><strong>$</strong>4,915.00</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2033" data-type="internal" data-id="#Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2033">BNB Price Prediction 2033 &#8211; up to <strong>$15,903.00</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<p>After notable changes in its executive team, Binance has shown notable resilience and prospects for recovery. The departure of Changpeng Zhao, Binance&#8217;s CEO, who was also embroiled in legal challenges, initially caused a decline in the value of Binance Coin (BNB). Despite this initial setback, the cryptocurrency has shown a positive trend. Presently, BNB is trading at $317.6, reflecting a modest rise of 7.01% in the past month.<strong> What next for BNB in 2024? </strong>Let’s get into the details.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is BNB worth?</h4>



<p>The current<strong> Binance coin price is $593.25 </strong>with a 24-hour trading volume of $2,353,178,190. <strong>BNB is up 1.14%</strong> in the last 24 hours. The current CoinMarketCap ranking is #4, with a live market cap of $88,797,061,389. It has a circulating supply of 149,536,886 BNB coins and the max. supply is not available.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Binance Coin Price Analysis: BNB upgrades to $594.2 following ascent</h2>



<p>TL;DR Breakdown</p>



<ul>
<li>Binance Coin price analysis confirms an uptrend.</li>



<li>Coin value has recovered up to $592.8.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Strong support is available at $467.7.</li>
</ul>



<p>The latest one-day and four-hour Binance Coin price analysis for 26th March 2024 indicates signs of a growing bullish wave. The price has been following an ascending movement since the past few days. As the buying activity is going through revival, the coin value has achieved a considerable recovery above $594.2 high.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BNB price analysis on a daily timeframe: Bullish wave transcends $594 amidst upside</h3>



<p>The latest one-day Binance Coin price analysis depicts a bullish scenario for the ongoing market events. As the bullish pressure is on the rising end, a strong uptrend was observed in the past 24-hours. Because of the upward spike, the coin value has climbed up to $594.2 high and further recovery seems near. Moreover, the Moving Average (MA) value has spiked up to $558.7 because of the upswing.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" width="1015" height="579" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-46.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501716" style="aspect-ratio:1.7232597623089982;width:1015px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-46.png 1015w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-46-300x171.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/1-day-46-768x438.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1015px) 100vw, 1015px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BNB/USD 1-day price chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>The volatility is declining which is a bullish hint for the coming future. As a result of the decreasing volatility, the upper end of the Bollinger bands indicator has shifted to $640.4. Whereby, the lower end of the Bollinger bands indicator has moved to $467.8 end. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicator confirms the rapid bullish wave as its overall value has hit 64.85 marker.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BNB price analysis on the 4-hour chart: Upturn results in upsurge beyond $594 high</h3>



<p>The latest four-hour Binance Coin price analysis confirms a bullish scenario for the current price movements. As a result of the ongoing upswing, the cryptocurrency faced considerable boost. The bulls seem to be back on track as the buying momentum is rising and the overall coin value has climbed above $594. On the other side, the Moving Average value has improved up to $586.1 because of the earlier spike.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" width="1015" height="579" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-49.png" alt="" class="wp-image-501717" style="aspect-ratio:1.7953846153846154;width:1018px;height:auto" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-49.png 1015w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-49-300x171.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/4-hour-49-768x438.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1015px) 100vw, 1015px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BNB/USD 4-hour price chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TradingView</a></figcaption></figure>



<p>The volatility is rising which is a bearish signal for the coming hours. Because of the ongoing shift in volatility, the upper extreme of the Bollinger bands indicator has shifted to $602.1. Whereby, the lower extreme of the Bollinger bands indicator has moved to $537.1. The RSI graph displays an ascending curve as its overall value has upgraded beyond 64.51.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from Binance Coin price analysis</h3>



<p>The latest one-day and four-hour Binance Coin price analysis depicts a highly bullish scenario for the day. The bulls remained on the leading end today as BNB/USD value has elevated above $594.2 high. Side by side, the four-hour price analysis depicted similar price movements as the bullish swing experienced further growth in the past few hours of the day. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is BNB a Good Investment?</h2>



<p>The Binance Ecosystem has seen significant growth over the years, with the utility of its token extending beyond the exchange, finding use in the DeFi space, NFT marketplaces, and as a staking token on Binance Smart Chain (BSC). The future profitability of BNB hinges on the expansion of the Binance ecosystem, regulatory developments, and further widespread adoption. Binance&#8217;s strategy of regularly burning BNB tokens to reduce supply could potentially increase its value, provided demand remains strong. BNB&#8217;s role as a key asset in the cryptocurrency space is likely to grow as blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies continue to gain adoption. Our Binance Coin price forecast section provides analysis on the profitability of the coin in the coming years.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News/Opinion on BNB</h2>



<p><strong>Concerns Arise: BNB Chain&#8217;s Fee Surge Amidst User Decline</strong></p>



<p>The BNB Chain has witnessed a significant increase in daily transaction fees and revenue, reaching its highest levels so far in 2024. However, this spike comes alongside a notable drop in user activity on the network, raising concerns about economic sustainability, centralization risks, and potential market manipulation. While bullish sentiment surrounds BNB&#8217;s price, it&#8217;s essential to scrutinize the underlying factors driving these metrics to ensure the long-term health and resilience of the ecosystem.</p>



<p><strong>AltLayer Launch: Decentralized Rollup &amp; Staking on Binance. </strong></p>



<p>A decentralized protocol for rollups, AltLayer (ALT) supports native and restaked Rollups, including Optimistic and ZK Rollup Stacks. Users can farm ALT tokens by staking BNB and FDUSD in separate pools until January 24, 2024. ALT is set to be listed on Binance on January 25, 2024, with various trading pairs. The ALT token, with a maximum supply of 10 billion, serves as an economic bond, enables governance voting, and incentivizes protocol operators. AltLayer enhances security and decentralization through its innovative Restaked Rollups concept, offering unique opportunities for farming and staking on the Binance Launchpool platform.</p>



<p><strong>Binance Boosts BNB Presence with Expanded Margin Trading Options.</strong></p>



<p>In its recent update, Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, has rolled out new margin trading pairs for popular assets like Solana (SOL), NFPrompt (NFP), and Enzyme (MLN). Notably, the focus on Binance Coin (BNB) is evident with the introduction of BNB/USDC pairs on both cross and isolated margins. The move aims to enrich the trading experience, offering users greater portfolio diversification and increased flexibility in trading strategies. Alongside these developments, Binance has also launched USDC-margined perpetual contracts for various cryptocurrencies and updated its Coin-Margined Futures Liquidity Provider Program. As of the latest market update, SOL has seen a 6% decline, trading at $107.91, while BNB remains stable at $318, and SEI has experienced a 3% decrease to $0.731 after a recent 60% rally.</p>



<p><strong>Binance and CEO CZ Fined $2.7 Billion in CFTC Verdict for Money Laundering Charges.</strong></p>



<p>The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has imposed fines of $2.7 billion on Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, and $150 million on its former CEO, Changpeng Zhao (CZ). The penalties stem from allegations of violating US anti-money laundering and sanctions laws, with Binance accused of facilitating over 100,000 suspicious transactions, including those linked to terrorist groups and illegal content. CZ stepped down as CEO in November, pleading guilty to anti-money laundering law violations. The fines highlight regulators&#8217; efforts to enforce anti-money laundering regulations in the cryptocurrency sector, as Binance aims to rebuild trust under new leadership led by CEO Richard Teng.</p>



<p><strong>Judge Rules Binance Founder Must Stay in U.S. for Sentencing. </strong></p>



<p>A&nbsp;federal judge in Seattle has ruled that Changpeng Zhao, founder of Binance, must remain in the U.S. pending sentencing for money laundering charges. The decision overturned a previous ruling allowing Zhao to return to the UAE. The judge expressed concerns about Zhao being a flight risk despite a substantial bond, citing the belief that his vast wealth, mostly held overseas, might incentivize him to forfeit the bond for freedom. The case involves allegations of Binance ignoring criminal transactions, resulting in one of the largest corporate fines in U.S. history. Zhao faces a maximum of 18 months in prison, and both Binance and Zhao have agreed to substantial settlements.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Predictions by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<p>As the crypto landscape continues to evolve, it&#8217;s essential to stay informed about potential price trends and developments in one of the industry&#8217;s leading assets. Join us as we explore what the years 2024 to 2033 may hold for BNB and gain valuable insights into its potential price movements.</p>



<p><img decoding="async" width="1178" height="676" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/GSF_-oJe0naX8efZQyxFmPLKcgGUf50Y22cHc-BbibDMFZ8dYieJ4D7gLa4gRJU89rkvDFU7qmvYRLMzkKMV2Wn3QHqgvxGq_h8z1vgfnUZxDyrAvMgNn7yTwOqQUkkjBlLRfliGVCmbb9ejIEtB3pY"></p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td><strong>Year</strong></td><td><strong>Minimum Price ($)</strong></td><td><strong>Average Price ($)</strong></td><td><strong>Maximum Price ($)</strong></td></tr><tr><td><strong>2024</strong></td><td>443.23</td><td>459.36</td><td>511.62</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2025</strong></td><td>644.43</td><td>667.40</td><td>776.71</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2026</strong></td><td>899.36</td><td>932.73</td><td>1,107.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2027</strong></td><td>1,305.00</td><td>1,342.00</td><td>1,593.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2028</strong></td><td>1,980.00</td><td>2,047.00</td><td>2,268.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2029</strong></td><td>2,864.00</td><td>2,946.00</td><td>3,426.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2030</strong></td><td>4,134.00</td><td>4,281.00</td><td>4,915.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2031</strong></td><td>6,006.00</td><td>6,220.00</td><td>7,135.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2032</strong></td><td>9,055.00</td><td>9,304.00</td><td>10,547.00</td></tr><tr><td><strong>2033</strong></td><td>13,054.00</td><td>13,519.00</td><td>15,903.00</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2024">BNB Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>Our Binance Coin (BNB) price prediction for 2024 anticipates that the asset could reach a <strong>maximum price of $511.62</strong> by the end of December. We expect an average trading price of $459.36 and a floor price of $443.23.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>Looking ahead to 2025, our price forecast for Binance Coin suggests that the cryptocurrency could reach a <strong>maximum price of $776.71</strong>. Our estimations also propose an average value of $667.40 for BNB. In more conservative market conditions, the asset could still maintain a minimum price of about $644.43.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>With respect to our BNB price forecast for 2026, we posit that BNB could scale up to a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $1,107.00</strong>. Our model projects that the asset could still achieve a minimum price of $899.36, and an average price of $932.73.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2027">BNB Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>For the 2027 financial year, our Binance Coin price evaluation infers that BNB may reach a <strong>maximum valuation of $1,593.00</strong>. We expect an average trading price of approximately $1,342.00. The minimum price for the digital asset could be close to $1,305.00.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Our Binance Coin price prediction for 2028, suggests that the ongoing growth of the Binance ecosystem will contribute significantly to BNB&#8217;s future price action. Our projections foresee a <strong>maximum price of $2,268.00</strong>, an average price of $2,047.00, and a minimum trading value of $1,980.00.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>For the year 2029, our Binance Coin price analysis predicts a sustained upward trajectory for the asset, potentially reaching a <strong>maximum price of $3,426.00</strong>. We also forecast an average trading price of about $2,946.00, and a minimum price of $2,864.00.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2030">BNB Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our Binance Coin price prediction for 2030, BNB could attain a <strong>maximum market valuation of $4,915.00</strong>. In addition, our forecasts suggest an average market price of $4,281.00 and a minimum price of $4,134.00.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>Based on the Binance Coin price prediction for 2031, our analysis indicates that BNB could achieve a <strong>maximum market value of $7,135.00</strong>. The average projected price could be around $6,220.00, while the floor price might be approximately $6,006.00.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>Per our Binance Coin price prediction for 2032, we anticipate the possibility of BNB achieving a <strong>maximum price of $10,547.00</strong>. We predict a minimum price of $9,055.00 and an average price of $9,304.00.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="Binance-Coin-Price-Prediction-2033">BNB Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>According to our Binance Coin price projection for 2033, <strong>BNB may touch a peak value of $15,903.00</strong>. Our prediction suggests an average trading value of $13,519.00, with a potential minimum price of $13,054.00.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction by Wallet Investor</h3>



<p>Wallet Investor&#8217;s analysis presents a pessimistic outlook for Binance Coin (BNB), predicting a drop to $284.241 by 2025. Their price forecast for 2028 suggests a 30.88% reduction in BNB&#8217;s value.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Coincodex Binance Coin (BNB) Price Prediction&nbsp;</h3>



<p>Coincodex’s 5-day forecast shows a slight rise to $352.19, while a month later, it&#8217;s expected to rise to $488.89. In 3 and 6 months, projections are for BNB to hit $866.14 and $599.76, respectively. Their 1-year outlook suggests a peak value of $989.08 for BNB.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Prediction by Technewsleader</h3>



<p>Technewleader&#8217;s analysis projects significant growth for Binance Coin (BNB) in the coming years. They predict BNB will reach up to $512.45 in 2024, and in 2025, it&#8217;s expected to trade between $613.11 and $763.90. The forecast for 2027 shows a minimum price of $1,233 and a potential high of $1,537. For 2030, they suggest a dramatic increase, with BNB possibly hitting $4,344. By 2033, the price is anticipated to oscillate between $11,184 and $13,009.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price Predictions by Industry Influencers</h2>



<p><strong>World War Bitcoin,</strong>&nbsp;utilizing a data-driven approach to predict Binance&#8217;s future price, suggests a potential market cap of $255 billion, leading to a BNB price of around $1,822.74 by January 1, 2025. This analysis is based on a &#8216;normal&#8217; bull market scenario and a supply of 140 million coins. A second scenario provided by the analyst considers Binance&#8217;s market cap dominance reaching 4.18% of a $7 trillion total market, resulting in a BNB price of approximately $2,090.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe loading="lazy" title="Binance (BNB) Price Prediction for the 2024-25 Bull Run" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/i0ZTvvvHV10?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Popularity</td><td>#4</td><td>Market Cap</td><td>$47,470,827,649&nbsp;</td></tr><tr><td>Price Change (24 hours)&nbsp;</td><td>-1.51%</td><td>Trading Volume (24 hours)</td><td>$735,309,465</td></tr><tr><td>Price Change (7 days)&nbsp;</td><td>4.48%</td><td>Circulating Supply</td><td>149,545,260 BNB</td></tr><tr><td>All-time low (Aug, 2017)</td><td>$0.09611</td><td>All-time high (Oct, 2017)</td><td>$690.93</td></tr><tr><td>Price from ATL</td><td>+329954.81%</td><td>Price from ATH</td><td>-54.09%</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BNB Price History</h2>



<p>Binance Coin (BNB) was launched in July 2017 through an Initial Coin Offering (ICO), with an initial price of around $0.10. As a utility token for the Binance cryptocurrency exchange, it offered users reduced trading fees. In late 2017, BNB&#8217;s price saw a significant increase, aligning with the overall cryptocurrency market boom, and reached its first major peak in January 2018, hitting approximately $24. However, it experienced a decline following the broader market correction.</p>



<p>Throughout 2018 and 2019, BNB&#8217;s price experienced gradual growth. A key development during this period was the launch of Binance Chain in April 2019, which introduced Binance DEX, a decentralized exchange. This led to BNB reaching new highs, going above $30 in June 2019. Despite the global economic uncertainty due to the COVID-19 pandemic, BNB maintained relative stability and saw an upward trend in 2020. This was partly due to the growing popularity of Binance as an exchange and the expansion of its ecosystem.</p>



<p>BNB experienced a significant bull run in early 2021, reaching an all-time high above $600 in May 2021. This surge was attributed to the overall bullish cryptocurrency market, the growth of decentralized finance (DeFi), and Binance Smart Chain&#8217;s increasing popularity. Binance Coin&#8217;s price dynamics in 2022 were characterized by volatility and were influenced by a combination of macroeconomic factor and regulatory developments which led to a bearish scenario &#8211; that took BNB to less than $220 in June, and an average price of $250 in December.</p>



<p>BNB continued to be a significant player in the cryptocurrency market in 2023, recovering to about $350 in April, but soon lost momentum, reaching about $205 in October, mostly influenced by the prolonged crypto winter. The bulls got back into the market in late December and BNB climbed back to about $325. At the time of writing (February 12, 2024), Binance coin is trading at about $317.6.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on the BNB Network</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is Binance Coin?</h3>



<p>Binance Coin (BNB) is a digital currency issued by Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges. Initially launched as an ERC-20 token on the Ethereum blockchain, BNB was designed to offer reduced trading fees on the Binance platform. In 2019, BNB transitioned to Binance Chain, Binance&#8217;s own blockchain, enhancing transaction efficiency with faster speeds and lower costs. The Binance Chain operates using a Byzantine Fault Tolerance (BFT) consensus mechanism, facilitating high transaction throughput and low latency. BNB plays a central role in the Binance ecosystem, extending beyond fee reduction to include various applications in decentralized finance and other blockchain services.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Who are the founders of the Binance exchange?</h3>



<p>Changpeng Zhao and He Yi started the Binance coin in July 2017. They first began Binance as an Initial Coin Offering (ICO), but today, Binance has become one of the most significant crypto coins globally.</p>



<p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-26">The crypto token has garnered support from other partnerships, which has helped its usage spread. It includes a partnership with Asia&#8217;s premier high-end live video streaming platform, Uplive, which sells virtual gifts for BNB tokens to&nbsp;Uplive’s 20 million-strong user base. Binance coin is also supported by the platform, the mobile app, and the VISA debit card of Monaco, the pioneering payments and cryptocurrency platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The Binance Coin ecosystem has continued to draw investors who use the platform to explore opportunities its ecosystem presents, including Defi, the crypto market, and NFTs. The token has risen to glory within a short time as more applications are built on the smart chain. It has several use cases, making it engraved in the trading experience of several traders using the Binance crypto exchange platform. </p>



<p>With Binance Chain expertise, users can deploy smart contracts that fit their application needs or virtual machines that dictate exactly how the blockchain should operate. <strong>Binance has built one of the most secure trading platforms in the world</strong>&nbsp;where users can enjoy different security features, such as KYC, 2FA, and Anti-Phishing Code, to protect themselves against nefarious actors. Users can also rest assured that their funds are SAFU in Binance.</p>



<p>Currently, BNB is among the top five largest cryptocurrencies by market cap. Despite the current market downturn, the price predictions of BNB are relatively optimistic since the token demonstrates healthy growth behavior, and the trading platform continues to grow and amass new users. The overall development of the Binance exchange could directly translate to the <strong>positive growth of the BNB coin</strong>. </p>



<p>If the market stabilizes and further developments and collaborations continue in the Binance ecosystem, as we have had with the Binance chain, massive adoptions are imminent in the forthcoming years, which could result in BNB <strong>breaking through the $1000 mark</strong>. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zuDSzNiYK3g" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zuDSzNiYK3g" />
			<media:title type="plain">Binance Coin BNB Price News Today - BNB Technical Analysis Update Now and Price Prediction!</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[Trade on Bybit:Receive an up to $30,000 bonus (see terms on Bybit)https://partner.bybit.com/b/MCOBinance Coin BNB Price News Today - BNB Elliott Wave Technic...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/binance-coin-bnb-price-news-toda.jpg" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/binance-price.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/binance-price.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Impact of Automation: 25 Jobs Facing Machine Takeover</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/automation-25-jobs-facing-machine-takeover/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenda Kanana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Trending News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automation and AI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501710</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The relentless march of automation continues to reshape the job landscape across various industries. As technology advances, robots and artificial intelligence (AI) systems increasingly perform tasks once exclusively handled by humans. From manufacturing to healthcare, no sector is immune to the transformative power of automation. Here&#8217;s an overview of 25 jobs teetering on the brink [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The relentless march of automation continues to reshape the job landscape across various industries. As technology advances, robots and artificial intelligence (AI) systems increasingly perform tasks once exclusively handled by humans. From manufacturing to healthcare, no sector is immune to the transformative power of automation. Here&#8217;s an overview of 25 jobs teetering on the brink of machine takeover.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Transportation and logistics</h2>



<p>Drivers: The rise of self-driving technology signals a seismic shift in the transportation sector. Autonomous vehicles are poised to render professional driving roles obsolete, revolutionizing how people and goods are transported.</p>



<p>Delivery Workers: With the advent of robots and drones, the role of human mail and delivery carriers is diminishing. Automation is enhancing delivery speed and efficiency, reshaping the logistics landscape.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Manufacturing and retail</h2>



<p>Factory Operators: Automation is rapidly transforming manufacturing processes, reducing the demand for human operators. Robots take over tasks once performed by factory workers, from production line operations to inventory management.</p>



<p>Stock Clerks: Robots like Tally streamline inventory management in retail environments, improving accuracy and efficiency. Automation is reshaping stock management practices, minimizing the need for human intervention.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Service and hospitality</h2>



<p>Waiters: Self-service technology in restaurants is enabling customers to order and pay for their meals without the assistance of waitstaff. Automated ordering systems are gradually replacing human servers in many establishments.</p>



<p>Travel Agents: The advent of online platforms has revolutionized travel planning, eliminating the need for traditional travel agencies. Digital solutions enable users to book flights and accommodations independently, bypassing human intermediaries.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Healthcare and finance</h2>



<p>Doctors: While robots are assisting in medical procedures and diagnostics, human doctors remain indispensable. Automation augments healthcare processes but is unlikely to fully replace human expertise and empathy.</p>



<p>Financial Analysts: AI-powered algorithms are increasingly performing financial analysis and trading tasks, reshaping the finance sector. Automation is reducing the demand for human analysts as machines handle complex calculations efficiently.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Legal and creative industries</h2>



<p>Lawyers: AI-powered legal software streamlines document review and contract analysis, reducing the need for human lawyers for certain tasks. Automation is reshaping the legal profession, although human expertise remains critical in complex legal matters.</p>



<p>Journalists: Automated systems are generating news articles and reports, altering the media landscape. While automation streamlines certain journalistic tasks, human journalists remain essential for investigative reporting and storytelling.</p>



<p>The relentless march of automation is poised to reshape the labor market across various industries. While machines offer efficiency and productivity gains, they also raise concerns about job displacement and the future of work. As society navigates this transformative era, striking a balance between technological advancement and human welfare becomes paramount.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Adapting to this evolving landscape necessitates proactive measures, including reskilling initiatives and policy frameworks that prioritize the well-being of workers. Ultimately, harnessing the potential of automation while safeguarding human livelihoods remains a pressing challenge for stakeholders across sectors.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Engineers_waiters_and_drivers_at_one_place_1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Engineers_waiters_and_drivers_at_one_place_1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Best Casinos Not on GamStop UK &#8211; List of Reputable Non-GamStop Casinos</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/10-best-casinos-not-on-gamstop-uk-list-of-reputable-non-gamstop-casinos/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Guest User]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sponsored News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While GamStop has undoubtedly improved UK residents&#8217; lives and financial well-being, it isn&#8217;t for everyone. Not all players want their ability to win big restricted by a massive government program. That is why so many gambling enthusiasts prefer to seek out casinos not on GamStop, with all the bonuses, promotions, game diversity, and vibrant theming [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>While GamStop has undoubtedly improved UK residents&#8217; lives and financial well-being, it isn&#8217;t for everyone. Not all players want their ability to win big restricted by a massive government program. That is why so many gambling enthusiasts prefer to seek out <strong>casinos not on GamStop</strong>, with all the bonuses, promotions, game diversity, and vibrant theming they could ever want.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our List of Trusted Non GamStop Casinos (Weekly Updated List)</strong></h2>



<p>We&#8217;ll detail each of our casinos, but as a quick guide, here are our <strong>top 10 non-GamStop casinos</strong>. Read on the various details of what separates each one from another.</p>



<ul>
<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/mystake" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>MyStake</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Best Overall</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/donbet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Donbet</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Fastest Paying</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/goldenbet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Goldenbet</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Most Reputable</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/freshbet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Freshbet</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; No Verification</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/cosmobet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Cosmobet</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Highest Paying&nbsp;</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/velobet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Velobet</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Best Mobile</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/ninewin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>NineWin</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Same Day Payouts</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/jokabet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Jokabet</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; For High Rollers</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/seven7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Seven</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Best Live Casino</li>



<li><a href="https://suresbet.com/top10/rollino" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Rollino</strong></a><strong> </strong>&#8211; Best for Bonuses</li>



<li><a href="https://www.sure.bet/non-gamstop-casinos-uk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><strong>52 Other Non-GamStop Casinos</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<p>We&#8217;ll provide a list of the best casinos not on GamStop so you can enjoy online gambling whenever and wherever you go next. There is a lot of information to cover here, so be sure to read the crucial overviews of each casino. That will help you find the perfect fit for your particular betting needs.</p>



<p>If you have a suggestion for a casino not on GamStop that you don&#8217;t see on our fantastic list, leave a comment at the end or contact our team via our contact info. We always seek to provide the best information about casinos not on GamStop. Here we go!</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>MyStake Casino &#8211; Best Overall Casino Not On GamStop</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/CHWLPB4QALYDuuS35QsaqX1KoHmndT1iusMuTfG61SQFAUwyjh2mN014ynVm4HnQdZBqQBJqSIKC6HeQe8BbuSZAm9swQcrTSkZFUyC7m8Pv9KRbLBaO1DHaW3poFNlZS-QGmHgJz2JpvF7Pm2wudAs" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Let&#8217;s start our list of non-GamStop casinos in the UK with MyStake Casino. This is a beautiful collection of vibrant games with the full backing of an international gaming license. The darker theme of black with purple highlights makes it easy to navigate and better for your eyes if you prefer a little nighttime gambling.</p>



<p>MyStake Casino is among the new non-GamStop casinos. It hasn&#8217;t been around for decades but has worked hard to build a strong portfolio of well-known developers, games, and sports betting. You can do everything from spending a few hours with progressive slots to betting on an upcoming soccer game.</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>Highly engaging design that is easy to navigate.</li>



<li>Wide variety of deposit methods.</li>



<li>24/7 live agent support.</li>



<li>Good maximum monthly withdrawals.</li>



<li>A sound library of games to choose from.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Of course, none of the options on our list of non-GamStop casinos is worth exploring without paying close attention to the bonuses and promotions. You can leverage several different promotions, but we recommend starting with the Welcome Casino Bonus. Here you get 150% up to £300 in matching funds or 100% up to £1,000. Each is based on your deposits and only applies to the casino slot games.</p>



<p>Other bonuses include:</p>



<ul>
<li>70% exclusive casino reload bonus for a minimum £20 deposit.</li>



<li>Welcome sports bonus of up to £500 in matching funds.</li>



<li>Mini-games welcome bonuses with 100% matching funds.</li>



<li>170% crypto deposit bonus up to £600.</li>



<li>10% crypto cashback on specific deposits.</li>



<li>And much more.</li>
</ul>



<p>The money management side of this list of non GamStop casinos is just as diverse as the promotions. You can use major credit cards like Visa or MasterCard, Neteller, WebMoney, Bitcoin, Skrill, MiFinity, and much more. All of these have varying withdrawal limits and times – with crypto being the quickest turnaround.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>The game diversity at MyStake Casino is incredible. From the moment you land on the website, you&#8217;ll be treated to developers like Pragmatic Play, Play&#8217;n Go, Hacksaw Gaming, NoLimit City, and EGT. That introduces you to popular slots totaling well over <strong>3,100 individual titles</strong> from all themes.</p>



<p>Beyond slots is a vibrant sportsbook with live betting, parlays, and much more. You can also enjoy eSports, racing, and virtual casino games through live dealers or computer-based play. If you have time, the mini-games give you plenty of opportunities for big wins, and the tournaments are where you want to invest the most money.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Support:&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>MyStake Casino enjoys a full gaming license from the Cyprus Gaming Authority. It holds all the TLS/SSL certificates and encryption you could want to ensure your account, funds, and personal information are well protected. While MyStake is a member of casinos not on GamStop UK, it does have a self-exclusion policy if you wish to take a break.</p>



<p>As for customer service, you&#8217;ll enjoy all the answers to your questions through a vibrant 24/7 live chat and email support system. We found most of the answers we needed on the FAQ page before having to contact anyone. They also have Discord and Telegram channels for even faster insight into maximizing your winnings.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DonBet Casino &#8211; Fastest Paying Non GamStop Casino</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/BrLli_LlW_qFqjKcSrdLuJfQ4zDQFEb8ZsIoXn2A7MxZz8Ej3D3ZJg4h1u49MaKx0xq4jFVvV3lJ10jBafSYN4Vl3-fO2NYOPEvCfiu0F0ONAFx2IaUn8jbQyZcTIqvWKWHZWuy8K-wLq0Db6qER11c" alt=""/></figure>



<p>We have an American-inspired platform along with other casinos not on GamStop in the UK. Much like the &#8220;made men&#8221; in Sicily or the mainland, DonBet Casino follows a very &#8220;Godfather-like&#8221; structure that invites players to enjoy all the gambling they could want while rising the ranks of a mafioso.</p>



<p>Like <em>The Sopranos</em> or other mafia-themed shows, your job is to raise the ranks from starting out as a family member to being a boss in your own right (hence the name &#8220;Don&#8221;). You do this through a vibrant VIP program, plenty of bonuses, and continuing your gameplay as much as possible.</p>



<p><strong>Pros:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>It is one of the best casinos not on GamStop for various game offerings.</li>



<li>The specialized &#8220;Mafia&#8221; VIP program awards many bonuses and promotions.</li>



<li>Exceptional security measures through high-byte encryption and 24/7 live chat support.</li>



<li>Fully licensed and approved by the Curacao Gaming Commission.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>From the moment you see the gif of a hand rolling a gold coin on the loading page, you&#8217;ll want to see what bonuses are available from DonBet Casino. As one of the better British casinos not on GamStop, DonBet Casino offers a welcome bonus offering up to <strong>150% in matching funds</strong> for your initial deposits, with a cap of £750. That includes infusing your account with an additional 50 free spins for specific slots.</p>



<p>Other promotions include:</p>



<ul>
<li>Bet on the NHL, NFL, or soccer using 120% matching funds up to £600.</li>



<li>Enjoy Bitcoin and other crypto with a 170% matching funds bonus of up to £1,000 and 100 free spins for your first digital currency deposit.</li>



<li>Get 10% back on your deposit just for being a loyal mafioso.</li>



<li>Experience 100% in matching funds up to £600 for mini-games.</li>



<li>Get your 4th bet free after three successful bets in the sportsbook.</li>
</ul>



<p>As members of our English casinos not on GamStop, we were very happy to see the diversity of money management options. You can use everything from BitGo to Skrill, Visa, MasterCard, Neteller, Payop, AstroPay, and more. The only thing we caution you about is to pay close attention to the maximum withdrawal amounts so you don&#8217;t overlap requests.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>What keeps players engaged at DonBet Casino is the game variety. Plenty of incredible titles feature developers like Play&#8217;n Go, Hacksaw Gaming, Push Gaming, and Pragmatic Play. You&#8217;ll find little bonuses on the playing game cards telling you what else is available. For example, <em>Sweet Bonanza </em>has additional free spins.</p>



<p>Beyond slots, there are mini-games, virtual sports, racing, sports betting, live games, and a wealth of tools for you to leverage to get a great winning position. We highly recommend you engage with the slots&#8217; &#8220;demo&#8221; play options so you can better acquaint yourself with the mechanics before placing a bet.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>The security at DonBet Casino is top-notch, as you&#8217;d expect from a mafia-themed platform. This is one of the more reputable casinos not on GamStop, and it has a full gaming license from the government of Curacao. The platform also features transparent RTP (return to player) statistics as you explore.</p>



<p>Anytime you have a question about the VIP program or specific game titles, you can use the 24/7 live chat feature. We rank this high among the best casinos not on GamStop because of how quick, professional, and comprehensive the answers we receive while researching this article.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Goldenbet Casino &#8211; Most Reputable Casino Not On GamStop</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/lS7m_UH1aLvrhlsGYl5QdkEfqdIJNavlEytdpH2rRRWi05u02SEGp8q7NvmAqVJaWvMfK-wKQOVd1gTmSyXhX7NvfA5258jHNwRtK-KFTgyp8fWmnIIM9mUaWKjnv8ukIzAxK68UWgcV7PYToTA85e0" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Among our list of casinos not on GamStop, we tried to find a platform that is a little more refined in presentation than the others. Many UK residents want to play games and engage in promotions from a website that caters to the more luxurious side of online gambling, and we found our match with Goldenbet Casino.</p>



<p>Everything here is black and gold themed with incredible games, promotions, sports betting, and live dealers that are attractive and fun to interact with. We especially enjoyed the young lady handling the <em>Immersive Roulette Live </em>table. Her refinement and professionalism only elevated the overall feel of this platform.</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>Fully licensed by the Curacao Gaming Authority (CEG).</li>



<li>Established in 2021 with over $5 million in annual revenue by Santeda International BV.</li>



<li>Online solid reviews from users enjoy diverse payment methods, from Visa to Bitcoin.</li>



<li>Live chat customer support is available around the clock for any questions.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>For all online casinos not on GamStop, you first want to take advantage of the different promotions. That is how you&#8217;ll get the most winnings. Goldenbet Casino has a Casino Welcome Bonus spread out over three deposits. You get up to <strong>100% of £500</strong> for your first three deposits.</p>



<p>Other bonuses for Goldenbet Casino include:</p>



<ul>
<li>3 + 1 freebet, where every 4th ticket is a gift in sports.</li>



<li>Sports welcome bonuses of 100% of £500.</li>



<li>A separate eSports welcome bonus of the same value.</li>



<li>Free spins and free bets are based on the games you&#8217;re playing and the VIP program.</li>
</ul>



<p>Of course, all of these many promotions for new casinos not on GamStop come with withdrawal and time limits. You&#8217;ll want to use the cryptocurrency avenues the most if you need money quickly. Otherwise, bank transfers, physical checks, and major credit cards will be your other option.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Goldenbet Casino infuses its status as a winner because of the gameplay diversity. You can enjoy all the slot games you could want from major development houses like NoLimit City, Booongo, Play&#8217;n Go, and Pragmatic Play. We especially enjoyed <em>XWays Hoarder XSplit, Sun of Egypt, </em>and <em>Legacy of Dead</em>.</p>



<p>Outside of slots, they have one of the better live casinos, which is not on GamStop. The dealers are all incredibly professional and quite the treat as you set your various bets. If you are here for sports betting, you&#8217;ll enjoy instant wins in racing, major league play, eSports, and more. This is a comprehensive gambling platform.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Support:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Most people asking, &#8220;Are there any casinos not on GamStop?&#8221; are worried about security. The GamStop system comes with a sort of British Government seal of approval, so stepping outside of that can initially feel uncomfortable. Let us reassure you with the encryption and Curacao gaming license Goldenbet enjoys.</p>



<p>The customer support is incredible. All the people we spoke with quickly answered our questions and went out of their way to ensure our enjoyment of the platform. This was crucial because Goldenbet Casino&#8217;s sports betting side is so immersive that you may need help getting started.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Freshbet Casino &#8211; No Verification Casino Not On GamStop</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/eRWolibhFrMuOsJdJpNSEeGc16JRUqz8sSUg2HWpgFtpu54fd3l5nZ-AbDcgMub9IMyKl3UHxArj12iLGVoUGhtVd5i5TR2teySigVoSp32LatSA1jsev6j8C1S-He4MC03lAdAnn5KOQTX1YlfLeyQ" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Many of the best casinos not on GamStop fall into a unique category: Malta casinos not on GamStop with relevant licensing. For instance, Freshbet Casino enjoys a full license from the Curacao gaming authority, which gives most players, including those in the UK, peace of mind.</p>



<p>Freshbet Casino has a different theme than you&#8217;d expect. It is not a luxurious platform or something with quirky graphics to target a niche market. This is more of the darker-themed &#8220;middle of the road&#8221; options with exceptional promotions and plenty of gameplay but nothing that differentiates the platform from others.</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>It is owned by Ryker B.V. and was established in 2021 with $5 million in revenue.</li>



<li>License by the Curacao Gaming Authority for your playing security.</li>



<li>Uses a wealth of different money options, including leading cryptocurrencies.</li>



<li>Live chat is always available to answer your questions, and there are above-average withdrawal limits.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Similar to other casinos not registered on GamStop, Freshbet Casino offers a strong welcome bonus. Here, you can get up to <strong>£1,500 in additional funds</strong> spread out equally over your first three deposits, which must be at least £20 in value. Each level is different, with the first being 100%, the second being 50%, and the third being 100%.</p>



<p>Other bonuses for Freshbet Casino include:</p>



<ul>
<li>Joining the Freshbet Casino VIP club with exclusive promotions and benefits.</li>



<li>Crypto welcome bonus of up to £500 for 155% matching funds.</li>



<li>Sports welcome bonus for the sportsbook on your first deposit.</li>



<li>3 + 1 free bet options for a free fourth bet on applicable games.</li>



<li>10% loyalty bonus for returning users.</li>



<li>eSports welcome bonus of up to £500 on your first crypto deposit.</li>
</ul>



<p>From the casinos not on GamStop bonuses above, you can see you get plenty of money diversity. Everything from Visa to MasterCard to Bitcoin and more is covered under Freshbet Casino. We especially appreciated access to Ethereum and Litecoin under this platform as only some casinos signed on GamStop provide those options.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Landing on Freshbet Casino&#8217;s main page introduces you to leading slots titles from Wasdan, Play&#8217;n Go, NetEnt, Spinomenal, 1X2 Gaming, and Pragmatic Play. We liked <em>Raging Rex </em>and <em>9 Tigers </em>for our test run of the platform but found more than enough, from traditional 3-reel games to massive progressive jackpots.</p>



<p>The sportsbook on Freshbet Casino quickly answers what casinos are not on GamStop. This is a wealth of well-known games, tournaments, and leagues that you can bet on using various methods without sticking to restrictive limits from the GamStop system. You can also play live casino games, mini-games, and tabletop features if you&#8217;d like.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Support:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>As we&#8217;ve already mentioned, casinos not on GamStop tend to have some form of licensing. Freshbet Casino uses a license from the Curacao Gaming Authority. They feature leading encryption standards and a platform that looks incredible on any screen size you prefer to use for your gambling activities.</p>



<p>The customer support was easy to follow, and they featured professionals well-versed in both American and British English. That is an excellent differentiation, so you should indicate your preference when signing up for your Freshbet Casino account. The live chat will be your best bet for answers to any questions.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cosmobet &#8211; Highest Paying Slots Not On GamStop</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/6QpC9KlHXHxIEVoEZxX24rFGuA-lEfPZc0lZ6bzV1Pp3ua7S-Ymm_CtVQScra4FaYGt3_rz_R2-4T2YnaKu0j6aDeQAxdcUdi-z3E-koG-h1NPmWaiKlhc428vZaLyGNWPCNVvGA0ouId6MjEjaiLOA" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Most PayPal casinos not on GamStop prefer to embrace a singular theme or style on their platforms. This is how they can stand out from the competition and find a niche audience receptive to that style of play. At Cosmobet Casino, you get exactly what you expect in a high-quality gaming experience.</p>



<p>The entire platform has space-aged theming and intergalactic travel. The graphics, colors, and visuals support adventuring into the galaxy to uncover fantastic games, bonuses, and promotions that practically guarantee your ability to maximize your playing (and winning) strategy.</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>Evaluate your gaming skills on over 40 sports for betting, comprising 10,000 events.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Complete control over your cash-out choices to ensure you get your entire winnings.&nbsp;</li>



<li><strong>There are over 20 unique banking methods</strong> for you to choose from.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Great top casinos not on GamStop theme to experience with a fully mobile-friendly website.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Cosmobet Casino is one of the most trusted casinos not on GamStop. It has a strong reputation for quality gaming and reliable payouts whenever you win. The welcome bonus of up to £500 is a little lower than other slots not on GamStop, but still plenty to work with. We like the crypto bonuses a bit more as they have higher matching funds of up to £1,000.</p>



<p>Other bonuses include:</p>



<ul>
<li>A 3 + 1 system for bets where you get your fourth bet for free in the sportsbook.&nbsp;</li>



<li>There is plenty of cashback when you use crypto for your banking.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Progressive betting is not just jackpots that match your bet so you can win more.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Second and third matching bonuses on your first deposits.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>Cosmobet Casino includes all of the money management sides of casinos not on GamStop. You can use Paysafe, Visa, MasterCard, Skrill, and Neteller. Again, leaning into crypto will be your best bet, as this platform prefers digital currency for exchanges.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Even with the smaller welcome bonus features, you&#8217;ll never be unable to enjoy an individual title or game. Cosmobet Casino includes development houses like Booongo, Relax Gaming, Habanero Games, NoLimit City, Pragmatic Play, and Red Tiger. You&#8217;ll know which one you&#8217;re using because the various game cards have developer logos.</p>



<p>The sportsbook here is robust! Even though this isn&#8217;t among the Irish casinos not on GamStop, Cosmobet Casino features plenty of real-time, eSports, and tournament play from leading leagues and teams. Place a few bets in the sportsbook, and head to the live games while you wait.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Cosmobet Casino is protected using modern 256-bit encryption and SSL certificate security. The licensing comes from the internationally facing government of Cyprus, and they have a strong account verification system to ensure no one else ever gets access to your unique profile, funds, or information.</p>



<p>The professional customer support team at Cosmobet Casino is fantastic. This is part of why we rank this platform as one of the safest casinos not on GamStop. They seem to go out of their way to give you complete assurance that you are using a platform that desires long-term customer relationships.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Velobet Casino &#8211; Best Mobile Casino Not On GamStop</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/NJgNCcg_4M7Scbu7_v8CpRQKdiMK9_4qlvn1spxSEp286Zfr9eqPQQmVQjyaWCKajrkKcioslf6WXgskkd5kahdELY3pni3DFC9fZbUu3n4T5NwnIlYOZ11fBOT7el3x5JKZ5mB2By-2I2ivFIYqFlg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Good casinos not on GamStop are more accessible than you may imagine. At the sixth spot on our list of casinos not on GamStop, we land on the vibrant and Brazilian colors of Velobet Casino. With one of the lowest deposit requirements, you gain access to games from over 89 developers.</p>



<p>Another thing that sets Velobet Casino apart is that it features one of the highest RTP values in the industry. Whenever you&#8217;re trying to find which casinos are not on GamStop, you want to look at RTP to measure how much of your winnings you will get from active gameplay instead of losing to a scammer.</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>Solid bonuses beyond the welcome package.</li>



<li>Exceptional sports betting division for eSports and international events.</li>



<li>Low entry level for minimum deposits.</li>



<li>Licensed through Santeda International BV owners.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Velobet Casino likes the RNG (random number generator) side of things for your gameplay. If it is safe to play at casinos not on GamStop, that emphasis on RNG should help ease your fears. Regarding a welcome bonus, you get up to £500 for the first, second, and third deposits, with the first having 150% instead of 100% for the rest.</p>



<p>Other bonuses for Velobet Casino include:</p>



<ul>
<li>Strong 10% no wagering VIP cashback bonus.</li>



<li>Crypto deposit bonuses of up to 160% for £1,000 in funds.</li>



<li>Sports welcome bonus of 150% and £1,000 in matching funds.</li>



<li>10% cashback on your crypto deposits.</li>



<li>3 + 1 free bet system for various games with a qualifying minimum deposit.</li>
</ul>



<p>Another reason we know that it is safe to play at non GamStop casinos is the diversity of money management available to active players. Everything from MasterCard to Bitcoin to Ripple and more partners with this platform allows you to make a deposit or maximize your winnings strategy.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Most of the casinos not on GamStop would have you go to the slots first, but in the case of Velobet Casino, you&#8217;ll want to do the sports betting as your primary stop. This is because the heavy theming leans into futbal more than NHL or NBA tournaments. The entire platform prefers the soccer matches of international teams.</p>



<p>However, when you do explore the various non-GamStop casino slots, you get to check out developers like Pragmatic Play, Evolution Gaming, Relax Gaming, Red Tiger, and Habanero. There are also plenty of live-dealing games, table features, mini-games, and anything else that may tempt your gambling side.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Velobet Casino was only recently registered with a license from the Government of Curacao. They ran exclusively on the reputation of owner Santeda International BV for years before finally getting the approval needed. That means they are fresh from hitting the specific regulations you would want for added safety.</p>



<p>Beyond the high encryption standards and the easy-to-use player accounts, you get vital customer service doing everything possible to live up to the license agreement. They will go out of their way to ensure you are delighted with your time on this platform for non GamStop casinos.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>NineWin Casino &#8211; Same Day Payouts</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/DcJrBOcOs8xuBqMcTDtJjtv9-ZdRaslINi1NbbojYReiUT_Kt-UpyD7AuqHiur5Zx_SWd-TfkPQ3KH1mRsejOdh_XNwZw-R7iecy9iE30i99vWiTQVyln0katdFFTS3L-1xQ4n_Su1awpKxNOlXieHo" alt=""/></figure>



<p>How are you holding up? Still ready to learn more about the best non GamStop casinos in the world? Let&#8217;s head over to NineWin Casino for this next in-depth look. Here, you will find an incredible new platform that features over 6,000 unique game titles under the ownership of Pointissimo B.V.</p>



<p>Like most other UK casinos not on GamStop, you&#8217;ll find a similar darker background with vibrant graphics and themes to maintain your interest. This is one of the better casinos not on GamStop for your mobile device, as the HTML5 website is highly responsive to screens of different sizes.</p>



<p><strong>Pros:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>Numerous bonuses and loyalty rewards for return players.</li>



<li>A vast game selection from leading development houses for your entertainment.</li>



<li>In addition to slots, there are sports betting and live dealer sections.</li>



<li>Great for those interested in using crypto as a payment system.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Even though this is a newer option from our best casinos not on GamStop, we still feel it is worth checking out. NineWin Casino has worked hard to establish a strong presence in the online world with a three-tiered welcome bonus that gives you up to £450 as long as you meet the various minimum requirements.</p>



<p>Other bonuses at NineWin Casino include:</p>



<ul>
<li>Specific additional welcome bonus features for free spins if you are based in Canada (so use that VPN wisely).</li>



<li>Daily cashback of 25% as long as you&#8217;re part of the loyalty program.</li>



<li>Seasonal promotions that you&#8217;ll learn more about when you sign up as they arrive in your user account notices and email.</li>
</ul>



<p>The money management side of things is less vibrant than other <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/uk-casino-sites-not-on-gamstop/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">sites not on GamStop</a>. For example, you can use major credit and debit cards, MiFinity, and cryptocurrency, but they&#8217;re still determining what types of digital systems they are allowing. Again, this is a newer casino, not on GamStop so that they will evaluate the various customer needs over time.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>All the different money and bonus issues aside, NineWin Casino&#8217;s game diversity is impressive. They partner with all kinds of development houses, from Pragmatic Play to NetEnt and more. We enjoyed games like <em>Johnny Cash, Running Wins, </em>and <em>Fortune Five</em> but found so much more as we explored.</p>



<p>Whenever you&#8217;re done with the slots of this UK casino not on GamStop, you can hop over to the jackpot games, bonus buy games, live casino, or sportsbook. They also feature instant win scratchers and game shows. <em>Monopoly </em>and <em>Cash or Crash</em> were our favorites in this gaming section.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>We are thrilled to say NineWin Casino is fully licensed by the Curacao Gaming Authority. They have vital RTP transparency and partner with some of the most well-known development houses in the industry. You&#8217;ll find all the encryption you could want, but be sure to pay attention to the withdrawal limits so you balance your requests over time.</p>



<p>This non GamStop casino could only do better with a phone-based customer support system. Live chat and email are enough, but it is so new that people could also benefit from a phone. Other than that, this is a robust platform without any lag, regardless of the screen size you use to play.</p>



<p>The way you play each game is impressive concerning graphics. Many of the online slots, which are non-UK platforms we&#8217;ve tested, include HTML5 for mobile gaming, but there must be fast servers behind this casino because there was no lag at all.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Jokabet &#8211; Best for High Rollers</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/rp7LNjsYe7DVwAjgJpLf9kIajTY3AO9PW_9-K_4QLu3OfDXaNiwdcFwzuPwE8QeWeFs-LVpz5nEJiWcJRIinbIq9T99lT-XJWtNS0gBkKjnNp3-AWDaVxkXODmwVfapv0a1AoZQ7ovSgQzlTlUBEk1M" alt=""/></figure>



<p>We will move on to the next platform on our list of casino sites, not on GamStop, and discuss the finer points of Jokabet Casino. Of course, you get the Joker&#8217;s hat emblem on top of the logo and a little bit of Carnivale (yes, with an &#8220;e&#8221;) infusion of graphics, but Jokabet Casino is also very refined.</p>



<p>The beauty of UK sites not on GamStop on this is they cater to your needs. You get a complete mobile application to streamline your playing and jackpots that would rival most Las Vegas strip casinos. There is a sportsbook, but eSports is where you&#8217;ll find the most action at Jokabet.</p>



<p><strong>Features:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>There are plenty of optional bonuses from a wide array of available games.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The sportsbook is much more robust than other non-GamStop casinos.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Multiple currency options for the banking system.&nbsp;</li>



<li>A robust customer support system that is always ready to help.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>One of the few things that sets Jokabet Casino apart from other top non GamStop casinos is the structure. Everything is incredibly user-centric and intuitive. You don&#8217;t need a guide to walk you through the navigation. For example, the welcome bonus is easy to find with appropriate levels like:</p>



<ul>
<li>100% up to £150 plus 150 free spins on the first deposit.</li>



<li>55% off up to £150 plus 150 free spins on the second deposit.</li>



<li>100% up to £150 on the third deposit.</li>
</ul>



<p>The free spins are what make that bonus so magical, though. You get around 250 total over the three deposits to play on select titles. In addition, you get a unique chance to spin the Supernatural Spin Lottery. Every £10 you spend gives you one ticket.</p>



<p>As for money management, Jokabet Casino is similar to other trusted non GamStop casinos in that it uses cryptocurrencies, credit cards, eWallets, and other similar items. The VIP program is the only way to expand your chances at higher payouts and withdrawals.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>All the games on Jokabet Casino are aligned with current casinos not on GamStop winners. By that, you can access developers like Onlyplay, Spribe, Gamzix, and Felix Gaming for smaller titles and Pragmatic Play, BetSoft, and NoLimit City for traditional titles. That should give you all the diversity you could want.</p>



<p>From other games, you&#8217;re looking at over 322 table games from blackjack to roulette, live casino game shows like Mega Wheel and Funky Time!, and a vibrant online sportsbook with plenty of detailed prop systems to enjoy. You should have no difficulty finding a combination of gameplay that fits your unique playing strategy.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Jokabet Casino&#8217;s security is solid, even though it is a familiar non-GamStop casino option. The platform enjoys a full license from the Curacao Gaming Authority. The social media mentions we noticed discussed the reliable encryption and account verification systems players appreciate.</p>



<p>Customer service could be better. You only get access to the phone support system if you are already part of the VIP program (and must be at the upper levels). Otherwise, you&#8217;ll need to use what most non GamStop casinos UK use – 24/7 live chat and an email form for more extended questions.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Seven Casino &#8211; Best Live Casino Not On GamStop</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/SmNsov7RJkjsqKcnW2h1VyiubolGW--AyixjIpN9FfDGikDxYRCHkU6qKLgElDTz7tt_MKFLAfcDqx7c3EF9Il1cUTYGdu-YqvdI2EQyYKwyLllQ4qnsAOnAky-kzF7bvteJOL6MBHNKSaWpNCXyRa8" alt=""/></figure>



<p>We have Seven Casino in the second to last slot of our list of non GamStop casinos. You&#8217;ll follow the links we provide, as the spelling and domain extension for this one can send you to a different platform. Seeing this provider is well over ten years old and has a lucrative welcome bonus, you want to take advantage of it.</p>



<p>Seve Casino loves Las Vegas-style theming. Everything on this platform is designed to resemble the colors and feel of major casinos like the Bellagio or Caesar&#8217;s Palace. That means a dark black background with bright, engaging colors like pink and orange. However, don&#8217;t let that distract you from this platform&#8217;s authority and solid customer reviews.</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>The operating team has a lot of experience to ensure the casino runs flawlessly.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Good selection of games from leading and independent developers.&nbsp;</li>



<li>You get an additional 10% cashback bonus when you sign up as a new player.&nbsp;</li>



<li>It is the best UK casino, not on GamStop, and has total international licensing.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>It shouldn&#8217;t be surprising that most casinos not on GamStop UK use a tiered welcome bonus system. This ensures you are kept engaged for more than your initial deposit. With Seven Casino, that means access to 450% of matching funds that will deliver an additional £7,500 into your account.</p>



<p>Other fantastic bonuses and promotions include:</p>



<ul>
<li>Day-specific bonuses on Monday, Wednesday, and Friday, with some offering up to £500.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Leverage free spins from the easy-to-use no-deposit bonus.&nbsp;</li>



<li>10% cashback bonuses for any user who applies their first deposits to the platform.&nbsp;</li>



<li>You receive different seasonal and special occasion promotions through account services and email promotions.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>Seven Casino is among the casinos not on GamStop in the UK that prefer cryptocurrencies. Everything from Bitcoin to Ethereum is included in this system, so you have even more freedom and flexibility as you play. Combined with a VPN, you get more anonymity outside the British government.</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>A significant reason we&#8217;ve added Seven Casino to our list of casinos not on GamStop is for the developer relationships. Every house you can imagine is trying to get games on this platform. We found popular dev teams like Microgaming, NetEnt, and Playtech. Our favorite IP was <em>Gonzo&#8217;s Quest.</em></p>



<p>Every game on Seven Casino works on a smaller screen. The entire website is built using modern HTML5, which is fully mobile responsive and has lightning-fast response times for better user and graphical interfaces. Beyond slots, you&#8217;ll want to check out the sportsbook, like most of the other casinos not on GamStop from our list.</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>For British casinos not on GamStop, you should lean into some form of international licensing. Unless you&#8217;re using a sweepstakes casino, this ensures you get reassurance for betting and making withdrawals. Seven Casino enjoys a full gaming license from the government of Curacao.</p>



<p>The customer service at Seven Casino is standard. You don&#8217;t get the phone support we think is the best, but there is 24/7 live chat, email support, and a terms and conditions webpage on the site that outlines all the details you want to read before placing a bet.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Rollino &#8211; Best for Bonuses</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/qW8bM4J37xe0LK6t117PNbvKNdfKjqBnpb85Pr3VN1VLB3Zl0ukSgb0MtESgKn1d_gvz27sgTOERXcmgj3YmJ2qQoahF9L8Edg_YGq07eAdnsKpZXmdw0OECYtoe4UFK5LQJhmYLD3eDiiI8OXyo6HM" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Hey! You made it to the end of our list of English casinos not on GamStop. To finish this journey of gambling excellence, let&#8217;s add Rollino Casino to our repertoire. It may sound like a strange name, but that is only because it is supposed to inspire thoughts and graphics of theme parks where you ride a roller coaster.&nbsp;</p>



<p>All the nostalgia-related theming that takes you back to boardwalks and international parks isn&#8217;t a fleece over your eyes. The games, promotions, and customer service at Rollino Casino are still top-notch. You&#8217;ll get all the playing you could want from this option of a reputable casino not on GamStop.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Features:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>A solid online experience through an immersive and fun theme.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Easy-to-use deposit features and banking systems with remarkable turnaround.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Sign up for the VIP program if you want additional features or customer service.&nbsp;</li>



<li>The marketing and visuals shift depending on what region of the world you visit.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Bonuses &amp; Money Management:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>As one of the best casinos not on GamStop, you&#8217;ll enjoy up to £8,952 in bonuses from the welcome package. That is in addition to over 325 free spins on select titles so you can maximize your winnings.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Other bonuses for Rollino Casino include:&nbsp;</p>



<ul>
<li>Specific Fruit Zen bonus provides up to £100 in unrestricted funds.&nbsp;</li>



<li>Join the high roller bonus and get up to 100 free spins on your first deposit.&nbsp;</li>



<li>If you choose the sports book, you can get 100% matching funds up to £450.&nbsp;</li>



<li>An ongoing reload bonus of up to £450 and 50 free spins exists.&nbsp;</li>



<li>You can find seasonal-specific tournaments, weekend boosts, and some cashback opportunities if you want more.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>



<p>With your winnings, you&#8217;ll want to use major credit cards, MiFinity, Paysafe, Interact, and other cryptocurrencies. The daily limit is a little low at only £500 per day, so if you win big, you may need to contact customer service.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Types of Games:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>The gaming diversity at Rollino Casino is solid. Although they may have fewer options than other online casinos not on GamStop, there are plenty from Pragmatic Play, Evolution, and Play&#8217;n Go to keep you well entertained.&nbsp;</p>



<p>There is no sportsbook, but Rollino does feature live betting, table games, slots, and tournaments that can quickly lead to massive jackpots. You&#8217;ll want to pay close attention to the time limits so you can get all the rewards you can.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Security &amp; Customer Service:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Rollino Casino may be slightly younger, but it features new casinos not on GamStop security options, like a full license from Curacao Gaming Authority and accreditation from iGaming for third-party testing.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Most of the answers to our questions came from the FAQ section, but the 24/7 live chat was more than enough to cover the rest. We heard a rumor about a phone system in the VIP, but we were acceptable for our purposes.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Non-GamStop casinos don&#8217;t have strict parameters about how much you can bet when you gamble or if you have to shut down your account during specific hours. These casinos are well outside of regulation but still have the security, payment/withdrawal systems, and reliable customer service you could want for playing with peace of mind.</p>



<p>The only remaining challenge is uncovering which platforms are the best non-GamStop casinos to invest money in. That is where this article comes into play. We&#8217;ve done all the hard work for you by exploring the different UK casinos not on GamStop that you can rely on. These are the exceptional websites and online casinos where you can leverage free spins, cryptocurrencies, games outside of reel-based systems, and much more.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Why Look at Sites Not on GamStop?</h2>



<p>The GamStop system was created in April of 2018. Its intentions were well-meaning as a way to stop gamblers from overspending or getting stuck down a &#8220;rabbit hole&#8221; of too much time on any platform.</p>



<p>The way it works is simple. For a casino to be listed and open to UK players, it must pay a fee to join the GamStop scheme. Otherwise, it will be restricted and incredibly hard to access online.</p>



<p>There has been quite a bit of backlash. Not all players want something so restrictive. They prefer a UK casino, not GamStop, with the flexibility and diversity of games and bonuses that make them attractive.</p>



<p>Now, it is much more common to find UK players seeking out non-GamStop casino platforms. They are easy to register and sign up for, provide plenty of security and have the gaming diversity you want to stay engaged.</p>



<p>If you are looking for UK sites not on GamStop, but still a little on the fence about how safe they are to play with real money, we suggest using a VPN (Virtual Private Network). Plenty of VPNs you can sign up for that charge next to nothing per month. This creates an extra &#8220;tunnel&#8221; that all your website traffic goes through and protects you from scammers, fraudsters, and hackers while online.</p>



<p>Best of all, using a VPN with the top non-GamStop casinos also allows you to change your IP (Internet Protocol) address anywhere globally. So, if the platform restricts UK players, you can turn on your VPN and pretend you&#8217;re in Spain, the US, Japan, or wherever else you want to be.</p>



<p>Okay, that about covers the basics. Let&#8217;s understand why you&#8217;re reading through this article – the best casinos not on GamStop that you should be enjoying right now. Here is our list!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>And there you have it! Our list of casinos not on GamStop that are more than worth your time, deposits, and effort. Be sure to learn the various specifics of any game you play or deposit you make so you maximize every instance of play for the highest winnings.</p>



<p>If you know of other casinos not on GamStop you think we may still need to include, please comment below or send us a note. Happy gaming, and be sure to set a budget ahead of time so you can continue to enjoy all the online gambling you could want without using the GamStop UK system.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/mystake-casino-not-on-gamstop.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/mystake-casino-not-on-gamstop.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is AI Misinformation the New Norm in Democratic Processes? Insights from the University of Surrey Study</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-misinformation-democratic-process-surrey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hidden Gems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI misinformation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a pivotal year marked by electoral decisions shaping the course of nations, a clarion call resounds from the University of Surrey&#8217;s Institute for People-Centred AI, cautioning against the perils of AI misinformation. As millions of voters worldwide prepare to exercise their democratic rights, concerns mount over the proliferation of deepfakes and other deceptive digital [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In a pivotal year marked by electoral decisions shaping the course of nations, a clarion call resounds from the University of Surrey&#8217;s Institute for People-Centred AI, cautioning against the perils of AI misinformation. As millions of voters worldwide prepare to exercise their democratic rights, concerns mount over the proliferation of deepfakes and other deceptive digital content, casting shadows over the sanctity of electoral processes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Rising threats and calls for vigilance</h2>



<p>The University of Surrey&#8217;s Institute for People-Centred AI has released a groundbreaking report underscoring the imminent dangers posed by AI-generated misinformation, particularly in the realm of electoral politics. Led by Dr. Bahareh Heravi, a leading authority in AI and media dynamics, the report sheds light on the unprecedented ease with which artificial intelligence facilitates the dissemination of false narratives, a phenomenon exacerbating longstanding challenges of misinformation during electoral cycles.</p>



<p>Dr. Heravi emphasizes the imperative of equipping voters with robust media literacy tools to discern factual information from AI-generated fabrications. Against the backdrop of burgeoning technological advancements, heightened public awareness stands as a bulwark against the erosion of democratic principles, safeguarding the integrity of electoral processes against nefarious manipulations.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recommendations for safeguarding democracy</h2>



<p>Central to the Institute&#8217;s report are pragmatic recommendations aimed at fortifying democratic resilience in the face of AI-driven disinformation campaigns. Foremost among these proposals is the advocacy for comprehensive public education initiatives, empowering citizens to identify and combat the proliferation of deepfakes and other AI-generated falsehoods. Concurrently, the report advocates for increased funding allocations towards research and development endeavors focused on enhancing detection capabilities, a crucial step in the ongoing battle against digital deception.</p>



<p>Echoing these sentiments, Dr. Andrew Rogoyski, director of innovation and partnerships at the Institute for People-Centred AI, underscores the necessity of proactive measures to stem the tide of AI-enabled misinformation. With the stakes at an unprecedented high, Dr. Rogoyski admonishes political leaders to eschew complacency, urging them to assertively engage in shaping policies that mitigate the deleterious impact of AI on democratic processes. Against a backdrop of escalating technological sophistication, the imperative for decisive action resonates loudly, with the integrity of democratic institutions hanging in the balance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Safeguarding democracy amidst the AI misinformation era</h2>



<p>As the specter of <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-gen-misinformation-ahead-of-elections/" data-type="post" data-id="462725">AI misinformation</a> looms large over the democratic landscape, the urgency of concerted action becomes all too apparent. In a world increasingly shaped by digital narratives, the onus falls squarely on political leaders and policymakers to navigate the treacherous waters of technological innovation with vigilance and foresight. As nations stand on the precipice of pivotal electoral decisions, the question remains: Will our leaders rise to the challenge, or will democracy falter in the face of AI-driven disinformation? </p>



<p>With the fate of democratic principles hanging in the balance, the imperative for collaborative efforts across sectors cannot be overstated. Only through proactive measures and sustained vigilance can the integrity of democratic processes be preserved in an era dominated by AI influences.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/e8a4b9ed-aa4c-4a64-bb57-420c86cd38f0.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/e8a4b9ed-aa4c-4a64-bb57-420c86cd38f0.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock offers new advice on Bitcoin investment</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/blackrock-new-advice-on-bitcoin-investment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501691</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BlackRock just dropped some new wisdom on Bitcoin, and it&#8217;s not the usual you hear at every corner of the internet. When it comes to investing in Bitcoin, it seems like the playbook is getting a rewrite, with Robert Mitchnick, the digital assets lead at BlackRock, stepping up to the plate with some pretty impressive [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>BlackRock just dropped some new wisdom on Bitcoin, and it&#8217;s not the usual you hear at every corner of the internet. When it comes to investing in Bitcoin, it seems like the playbook is getting a rewrite, with Robert Mitchnick, the digital assets lead at BlackRock, stepping up to the plate with some pretty impressive insights.<a href="https://archive.is/XvNuS" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Digital Gold or Rollercoaster Ride?</h3>



<p>The moody diva Bitcoin has been puzzling folks left and right with its mood swings. One minute it&#8217;s soaring high like it&#8217;s got a rocket strapped to it, and the next, it&#8217;s plummeting faster than your dropped ice cream cone on a sunny day in London. Investors were betting on it as an inflation hedge, only to watch it take a nosedive along with stocks in 2022, amidst inflation drama and interest rate hikes. But then, just like that, it rallied back as soon as the economic temperature showed signs of chilling.</p>



<p>According to Mitchnick, while Bitcoin has had its moments of acting like that high-risk tech stock you&#8217;re scared to tell your partner you invested in, that&#8217;s not really its scene. &#8220;Think of it more like digital gold,&#8221; he suggests, noting its strikingly similar behavior to gold when you look at their correlation charts over time. This notion flips on its head the post-Covid era&#8217;s trend of painting Bitcoin as a risk-on asset, something Mitchnick is quick to clarify involves a whole different ball game. You know, given its lack of consistent correlation with equities and fixed income.</p>



<p>So, as the winds change, the narrative around Bitcoin being digital gold is becoming popular again. This comes as Bitcoin&#8217;s price actions start to look less and less like those of the S&amp;P 500, even going so far as to step on its partner&#8217;s toes with a brief negative correlation early this year. And guess what kicked off this latest rally? Wall Street, literally.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Navigating the Bitcoin Investment Maze</h3>



<p>Now, let&#8217;s go a bit deeper into the Bitcoin investment scene. To be honest, wrapping your head around Bitcoin&#8217;s Jekyll and Hyde act is no small task. Mitchnick sheds light on this, pointing out how important understanding Bitcoin&#8217;s correlation—or lack thereof—is for anyone looking to park their cash in it. Especially for the big investors, like those behind the curtains at BlackRock&#8217;s iShares Bitcoin Trust, which has been a magnet for nearly $8 billion of investor cash.</p>



<p>Mitchnick emphasizes that knowing whether Bitcoin is going to play nice with the rest of your investment portfolio or start a food fight is key. With many getting in with a modest 1% to 3% allocation, it&#8217;s all about balance. Too much, and you&#8217;re riding the volatility rollercoaster. Just enough, and you might have yourself a nifty diversifier or even a hedge against the storm.</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s not forget the fireworks happening over at Deribit, where nearly $9 billion in Bitcoin options are set to expire. The scene is packed with bullish vibes, as the put/call ratio leans heavily towards calls, signaling a hearty appetite for Bitcoin&#8217;s upward trajectory. This enthusiasm is echoed in the disparity between Bitcoin&#8217;s current high-flying price and the more conservative strike prices, hinting at a collective underestimation of its volatility potential.</p>



<p>But wait, there&#8217;s a twist. The recent script flip in crypto investment flows, as reported by CoinShares, has seen a dramatic exit stage left, with investors pulling out over $942 million in a single week. This pivot from a 7-week inflow spree throws a spotlight on the fickle nature of market sentiment, especially when it comes to Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Adding another layer to this complex narrative, the Age Consumed metric from Santiment signals a stirring among Bitcoin&#8217;s long-dormant holders. With a significant uptick in previously idle BTC hitting the market, it&#8217;s like waking a sleeping giant.</p>



<p>As always, we&#8217;re gonna be watching.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-22.29.38-Visualize-BlackRocks-new-advice-on-Bitcoin-investment-focusing-on-the-theme-of-guidance-and-strategy-without-using-explicit-text-or-labels.-Create-a.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-22.29.38-Visualize-BlackRocks-new-advice-on-Bitcoin-investment-focusing-on-the-theme-of-guidance-and-strategy-without-using-explicit-text-or-labels.-Create-a.webp"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How is Mark Zuckerberg Convincing DeepMind AI Researchers to Join Meta?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/mark-zuckerberg-convincing-to-join-meta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aamir Sheikh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Innovators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO of Meta, formerly Facebook, is leaving no stone unturned in his quest to bolster the company&#8217;s AI prowess. In a recent development reported by The Information, Zuckerberg has personally reached out to AI researchers at Google&#8217;s DeepMind, leveraging personal emails to entice them into joining Meta&#8217;s ranks. This aggressive recruitment tactic, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO of Meta, formerly Facebook, is leaving no stone unturned in his quest to bolster the company&#8217;s AI prowess. In a recent development reported by The Information, Zuckerberg has personally reached out to AI researchers at Google&#8217;s DeepMind, leveraging personal emails to entice them into joining Meta&#8217;s ranks. This aggressive recruitment tactic, coupled with offers made sans interviews, underscores Meta&#8217;s strategic push to solidify its standing in the evolving landscape of artificial intelligence.</p>



<p>In the fiercely competitive tech industry, the scarcity of competent AI talent poses a formidable challenge for companies vying to stay ahead of the curve. Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s proactive approach in directly engaging with DeepMind&#8217;s AI researchers underscores the urgency Meta places on securing top-tier talent. With the demand for AI expertise surpassing the available supply, Meta&#8217;s unorthodox recruitment methods reflect the company&#8217;s determination to maintain its edge in the dynamic realm of artificial intelligence.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s personal recruitment drive</h2>



<p>Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s outreach to AI researchers at Google&#8217;s DeepMind marks a significant shift in Meta&#8217;s recruitment strategy. According to sources familiar with the matter, Zuckerberg has been directly engaging with potential candidates, emphasizing the pivotal role AI plays in Meta&#8217;s future endeavors. These personalized emails, crafted to resonate with the expertise and aspirations of DeepMind researchers, highlight Meta&#8217;s concerted efforts to poach top talent from one of the industry&#8217;s leading AI research institutions.</p>



<p>At the same time, Meta&#8217;s recruitment strategies transcend conventional means of engagement. Allegedly, the corporation has taken to proffering employment opportunities to individuals sans the customary rigors of interviews. This unorthodox methodology not only accelerates the recruitment trajectory but also accentuates Meta&#8217;s assurance in discerning and captivating high-caliber professionals. Through the optimization of the hiring continuum, Meta endeavors to promptly integrate adept AI specialists poised to bolster the realization of the company&#8217;s ambitious AI endeavors and undertakings.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Meta&#8217;s AI dominance strategy</h2>



<p>Zuckerberg&#8217;s aggressive recruitment drive aligns with Meta&#8217;s broader strategy to assert its dominance in the AI landscape. The company&#8217;s recent investments in hardware underscore its commitment to building a robust AI infrastructure. In a recent interview with The Verge, Zuckerberg revealed Meta&#8217;s ambitious plan to acquire over 340,000 Nvidia H100 GPUs by the end of 2024. These high-performance chips are instrumental in training and deploying AI models, positioning Meta at the forefront of AI innovation.</p>



<p>Meta&#8217;s methodology in AI development distinguishes it from rival entities. Embracing an open-source philosophy, the corporation unveiled Llama 2, a largely open-source AI model, indicative of its dedication to collaborative and transparent AI exploration. Zuckerberg&#8217;s prioritization of AI as Meta&#8217;s principal investment domain also underscores the corporation&#8217;s far-reaching outlook and unwavering commitment to propelling AI advancements.</p>



<p>As Mark Zuckerberg continues to spearhead Meta&#8217;s aggressive AI recruitment efforts, the implications for the tech industry remain profound. Will Meta&#8217;s strategic maneuvers enable it to outpace rivals and emerge as a dominant force in AI innovation? As the battle for AI supremacy intensifies, only time will reveal the true impact of Zuckerberg&#8217;s personalized recruitment drive on Meta&#8217;s AI ambitions and the broader technological sphere. As stakeholders await the unfolding of events, one thing remains certain: the race for <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/china-surpasses-u-s-in-producing-ai-talent/" data-type="post" data-id="500493">AI supremacy</a> is far from over, and Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s strategic moves could shape its trajectory in unforeseen ways.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/5d1856bf-118c-436e-a77f-d49ae2c0d6a0-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/5d1856bf-118c-436e-a77f-d49ae2c0d6a0-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>European investors can still hop on the spot Bitcoin ETF wagon</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/europeans-can-still-hop-on-spot-bitcoin-etfs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Hamid]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For those of you in Europe eyeing the Bitcoin bonanza, rubbing your hands with glee at the thought of getting in on the action, here&#8217;s the deal:- Turns out you&#8217;re not late to the party. Not even by a long shot. This year, the U.S. approved the very first spot Bitcoin ETFs. That’s right. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For those of you in Europe eyeing the Bitcoin bonanza, rubbing your hands with glee at the thought of getting in on the action, here&#8217;s the deal:- Turns out you&#8217;re not late to the party. Not even by a long shot. This year, the U.S. approved the very first spot Bitcoin ETFs. That’s right. The real McCoy, holding actual Bitcoins rather than just betting on their future prices. <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/blackrock-expansion-of-crypto-products/" data-type="post" data-id="500804">BlackRock</a>, Fidelity, WisdomTree, and VanEck didn’t waste any time launching all eleven of these bad boys, getting a cool $48 billion in assets.<a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6543416e-27f2-455a-b42b-7ae87eb9231d" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> </a></p>



<p>Now, Europe might seem a step behind, with its single spot Bitcoin ETF sitting pretty in Guernsey, not mingling with the retail crowd because of those pesky regulatory hoops. But don’t let that fool you, boys! Europe’s got its own game with crypto-related products, to the tune of $12 billion in assets. These aren’t your garden-variety funds, but they’re making it work in their own way, through exchange traded commodities and notes. And they’re opening up to literally everyone, giving retail investors a slice of the pie.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Digging into the Details</h2>



<p>While the U.S. market for spot Bitcoin ETFs is blossoming, Europe’s approach has been more, let’s say, cautious. The Jacobi Asset Management’s ETF is the lone ranger riding through the continent, directly investing in Bitcoin. It’s an exclusive party, not for the general public, thanks to the regulatory labyrinth. Yet, this hasn’t stopped European asset managers from crafting their own versions of crypto investments. They’ve been at it for half a decade, putting together products that have now ballooned to $12 billion in assets. .</p>



<p>The whole shebang of trading these European products might sound a bit technical, but here’s the lowdown: they do it through in-kind transactions. This essentially means swapping assets for shares directly, a neat trick that keeps things efficient, especially with assets like Bitcoin. This can give investors a leg up in terms of costs and returns, which are not something you’d want to gloss over.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Challenges and Opportunities</h2>



<p>Now, don’t think for a second that selling these crypto products is a walk in the park. Every country has its own rulebook, throwing curveballs at asset managers trying to spread the crypto gospel. Places like the UK and Belgium can be tough nuts to crack. And don&#8217;t even get me started on the U.S. clientele or venturing into the untamed wilds of Asia and the Middle East markets. Yet, despite these problems, the interest in crypto-related ETPs in Europe has surged, with assets quadrupling since 2022.</p>



<p>But here’s a nugget of wisdom from the European Central Bank: Calm down a little, and step back. They’re not entirely sold on Bitcoin as the next best thing since deodorants for payments or investments. While the U.S. might be diving headfirst into the crypto pool, Europe’s regulators are still dipping their toes, deciding whether they actually want to get in.</p>



<p>So, what’s the takeaway for you eager investors on this side of the Atlantic? The crypto train hasn’t left the station, guys. Europe is simply just playing a different tune, but the opportunities to jump on the Bitcoin ETF wagon are out there, wrapped in different packages.</p>



<p>Go get em!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-22.26.51-Depict-the-concept-of-European-investors-having-the-opportunity-to-engage-with-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-focusing-on-the-theme-of-accessibility-and-potential.webp" medium="image"  type="image/webp" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DALL·E-2024-03-25-22.26.51-Depict-the-concept-of-European-investors-having-the-opportunity-to-engage-with-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-focusing-on-the-theme-of-accessibility-and-potential.webp"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
