<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:26:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Offshore Operations Has a New AI Solution Just for Asset Management</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/offshore-operations-new-ai-solution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Randa Moses]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Trending News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI Solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Offshore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Offshore Operations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501654</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Explore how Imrandd's AI-driven solution ALERT is changing offshore operations. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Imrandd, has just revealed an innovative breakthrough in asset management called ALERT. This new solution changes the way offshore operators manage and maintain the integrity of their assets. Backed by an investment of £1 million, the Aberdeen-based company, known for its expertise in data and engineering, is introducing an AI-powered tool. This cutting-edge technology makes monitoring of offshore assets not just easier, but smarter and more efficient than ever before.</p>



<p>ALERT offers real-time insights about the health of assets, using AI to identify risks of corrosion before they become a problem. This forward-thinking method allows operators to tackle potential issues early, safeguarding the safety and extending the life of essential infrastructure. By adopting this technology, the industry is moving away from the old way of doing periodic checks. Instead, it’s embracing a more vibrant, data-informed approach to asset management.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Innovation at the core</h2>



<p>The birth of ALERT stems from Imrandd&#8217;s passion for breaking new ground, especially when it comes to keeping assets in top shape. The team spotted a gap for a smarter, cheaper way to watch over things and tapped into AI to fill it. This isn&#8217;t just about guessing what might happen to our assets down the line; it&#8217;s about having the means to step in right away and stop trouble in its tracks.</p>



<p>This game-changing technology has caught the eye of some big players, securing a hefty chunk of support and funding from the likes of the Net Zero Technology Centre. This vote of confidence shines a spotlight on how ALERT could be a game-changer in making operations greener and more sustainable. Plus, its slick dashboard gives users a 24/7 snapshot of how their assets are doing, making it easier to make smart choices and keep things running safely and smoothly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Offshore operations efficiency</h2>



<p>Imrandd&#8217;s founder and CEO, Innes Auchterlonie, highlights the software&#8217;s ability to transform asset management through its predictive capabilities and system-agnostic design. ALERT enables operators to model asset conditions instantaneously, considering various factors such as ambient conditions and degradation hotspots. This holistic view not only reduces engineering time but also improves the quality and accuracy of asset monitoring.</p>



<p>Following a successful pilot program that demonstrated a 40% increase in efficiency, Imrandd is now engaging with UK operators to explore the software&#8217;s potential further. The firm&#8217;s commitment to research and development is evident in the growth of its team and the continuous expansion of its digital tool suite, aimed at meeting the expanding needs of the energy and industrial sectors.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Offshore.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Offshore.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance phases out Tron USDC amidst regulatory backlash</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/binance-out-tron-usdc-amidregulatory-hurdles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In response to escalating regulatory pressures and an impending blockade by the Philippines Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Binance, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has announced the cessation of support for Tron network-based USD Coin (USDC) stablecoins. This strategic move comes on the heels of Circle&#8217;s withdrawal from the Tron blockchain, as regulatory scrutiny intensifies across [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In response to escalating regulatory pressures and an impending blockade by the Philippines Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Binance, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has announced the cessation of support for Tron network-based USD Coin (<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/usdc-end-collaboration-with-tron-financially/">USDC</a>) stablecoins. This strategic move comes on the heels of Circle&#8217;s withdrawal from the Tron blockchain, as regulatory scrutiny intensifies across various jurisdictions</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Binance ends Tron USDC support</h2>



<p>Binance&#8217;s decision to terminate support for Tron-based USDC was communicated through a <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-cease-support-for-deposits-and-withdrawals-of-usdc-via-the-tron-network-trc20-33df0ff0e2e94259950b5c4b1f4952f7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">statement </a>indicating that the cessation of support would come into effect by April 5. Notably, transactions involving USDC via other supported networks, such as Ethereum, remain unaffected by this change.&nbsp;</p>



<p>With less than two weeks&#8217; notice, Binance users utilizing Tron-based USDC must swiftly withdraw their assets or convert them to USDC on alternative networks. The decision underscores the challenges faced by cryptocurrency exchanges amidst a rapidly evolving regulatory landscape, with the Philippines SEC&#8217;s move representing the latest in a series of regulatory setbacks for Binance.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As the cryptocurrency industry grapples with increased scrutiny and regulatory compliance demands, exchanges must navigate complex regulatory frameworks to maintain operational integrity and ensure compliance with evolving standards.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Reasons behind the decision</h2>



<p>The abrupt end to support for Tron-based USDC follows Circle&#8217;s announcement of its departure from the Tron blockchain, citing an &#8220;enterprise-wide approach&#8221; involving various departments, including business organization and compliance.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Justin Sun, the founder of the Tron network, acknowledged Circle&#8217;s decision, highlighting the decentralized nature of the blockchain akin to Bitcoin and Ethereum. Circle&#8217;s disassociation from Sun last year, prompted by concerns raised by international bodies like the United Nations regarding alleged involvement in illicit financial activities, likely contributed to this move.</p>



<p>Simultaneously, the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/philippines-plans-block-binance-exchange/"> Philippines</a>&#8216; Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has announced plans to block access to Binance for its citizens within the next three months. The SEC has raised concerns over Binance&#8217;s unregistered status in the country, emphasizing the need to safeguard the public from potential risks associated with unregulated investment products.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The financial regulator has also urged tech giants Google and Meta to cease Binance-related advertising targeting Filipino users on their platforms. Last year, the Philippines SEC issued a cautionary advisory against Binance, highlighting its unregistered operations in the Asian country.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Navigating global regulatory waters</h2>



<p>The move to block Binance in the Philippines marks the latest regulatory setbacks for the cryptocurrency exchange. Binance has faced heightened scrutiny across various jurisdictions, including the United States and<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/binance-faces-tax-evasion-lawsuit-in-nigeria/"> Nigeria</a>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>These regulatory challenges underscore the evolving landscape of cryptocurrency regulation globally, with authorities increasingly focusing on ensuring compliance and consumer protection within the burgeoning crypto industry.</p>



<p>Binance&#8217;s decision to cease support for Tron-based USDC and the impending regulatory blockade in the Philippines highlights the complex regulatory environment shaping the cryptocurrency landscape. As the industry matures, exchanges and blockchain projects must navigate regulatory requirements to maintain operational integrity and ensure compliance with evolving standards.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Binance_a_prominent_cryptocurrency_exchange_has_announ_0-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_Binance_a_prominent_cryptocurrency_exchange_has_announ_0-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unlocking Smarter Crypto Trading with AI Power</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/crypto-trading-with-ai-power/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Edward Hopelane]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[African News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI in Daily Life]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency, staying ahead of market trends is essential for maximizing profits in crypto trading with AI. Artificial intelligence (AI) tools offer a compelling solution, employing complex machine learning algorithms to analyze vast amounts of data with unprecedented speed and accuracy. By leveraging AI for trend analysis in crypto market, traders [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency, staying ahead of market trends is essential for maximizing profits in crypto trading with AI. <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-revolutionizing-revenue-cycle-management/" target="_blank" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-revolutionizing-revenue-cycle-management/" rel="noreferrer noopener">Artificial intelligence</a> (AI) tools offer a compelling solution, employing complex machine learning algorithms to analyze vast amounts of data with unprecedented speed and accuracy. By leveraging AI for trend analysis in crypto market, traders can gain valuable insights into market dynamics. This will enable them to make informed decisions and capitalize on lucrative opportunities. From detecting subtle price patterns to identifying emerging trends, AI-driven analysis empowers traders to navigate the volatile crypto landscape with confidence.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pioneering the Future of Crypto Trading with AI Insights</strong></h2>



<p>The intersection of artificial intelligence (AI) and cryptocurrency trading represents a paradigm shift in market analysis and decision-making. With the inherent volatility of cryptocurrencies, traditional trading strategies often fall short in capturing fleeting opportunities and mitigating risks effectively. Herein lies the allure of AI.  A technological marvel capable of processing vast datasets at lightning speed, uncovering nuanced trends, and predicting market movements with unparalleled accuracy. By leveraging advanced machine learning algorithms, AI tools empower traders to gain a competitive edge, navigating the tumultuous waters of crypto trading with confidence and precision.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Role of AI in Risk Management and Trade Execution</strong></h2>



<p>At the heart of effective crypto trading lies the art of risk management and swift trade execution. Here, AI-driven automation emerges as a game-changer, revolutionizing the way traders approach portfolio management and transactional processes. Through real-time data analysis and predictive modeling, AI algorithms dynamically adjust trading parameters, optimizing risk-reward ratios and maximizing profit potential.</p>



<p>Moreover, AI-powered trading bots execute transactions with unmatched efficiency, leveraging algorithmic strategies to capitalize on market inefficiencies and arbitrage opportunities. By seamlessly integrating AI automation into their trading arsenal, investors can streamline operational workflows, freeing up valuable time and resources to focus on strategic decision-making and market analysis.</p>



<p>Nevertheless, despite the undeniable benefits of AI in crypto trading, its widespread adoption is not without its fair share of controversies and challenges. One of the primary concerns revolves around the issue of market fairness and accessibility. As AI-equipped traders gain a competitive edge through algorithmic analysis and automated execution, traditional traders may find themselves marginalized in an increasingly digitized marketplace. </p>



<p>Moreover, questions about the reliability and transparency of AI algorithms persist. With skeptics raising concerns about potential biases and unforeseen consequences. The opacity of AI decision-making processes further compounds these anxieties, as traders grapple with the implications of entrusting critical decisions to black-box algorithms.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Striking a Balance Between Innovation and Ethical Considerations of AI in Crypto Trading</h2>



<p>As the crypto trading landscape continues to evolve, finding a harmonious balance between innovation and ethical considerations becomes paramount. While AI holds tremendous potential in enhancing profitability and efficiency, its adoption must be tempered with a commitment to transparency, fairness, and responsible use. Regulatory oversight and industry standards play a crucial role in safeguarding market integrity and protecting the interests of all participants. Moreover, efforts to democratize access to AI-driven insights and tools are essential in fostering a level playing field and promoting inclusivity within the crypto trading community.</p>



<p>Therefore, the integration of AI into cryptocurrency trading represents a transformative leap forward, offering unparalleled opportunities for profit generation and risk management. By harnessing the power of AI insights and automation, traders can unlock new dimensions of market analysis and execution efficiency. Positioning themselves for success in an ever-evolving landscape. </p>



<p>However, amidst the allure of technological innovation, it is imperative to remain vigilant and uphold ethical principles. Ensuring that <a href="https://mpost.io/%d1%81an-i-use-ai-to-trade-crypto/" data-type="link" data-id="https://mpost.io/%d1%81an-i-use-ai-to-trade-crypto/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">AI-driven</a> trading practices are conducted with integrity and accountability. Ultimately, by striking a delicate balance between innovation and ethical considerations, traders can chart a course towards sustainable trading success in the dynamic world of cryptocurrency markets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Unleasing-the-power-of-AI-12.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Unleasing-the-power-of-AI-12.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC proposes $2B fine against Ripple</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/sec-proposes-2b-fine-against-ripple/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501641</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is reportedly seeking a $2 billion penalty against blockchain firm Ripple Labs, according to statements from Ripple&#8217;s Chief Legal Officer Stuart Alderoty.&#160; The request to impose fines and penalties is part of a legal filing that remains under seal, with public disclosure expected imminently. This development escalates the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is reportedly seeking a $2 billion penalty against blockchain firm Ripple Labs, according to statements from Ripple&#8217;s Chief Legal Officer Stuart Alderoty.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">As you will see when the SEC’s brief is made public tomorrow, they ask the Judge for $2B in fines and penalties. 1/4 <a href="https://t.co/HM8dBbn7lp" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://t.co/HM8dBbn7lp</a></p>&mdash; Stuart Alderoty (@s_alderoty) <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1772339308151849153?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">March 25, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The request to impose fines and penalties is part of a legal filing that remains under seal, with public disclosure expected imminently. This development escalates the ongoing legal dispute initiated by the SEC in December 2020, alleging Ripple raised $1.3 billion through sales of XRP tokens, considered by the regulator as unregistered securities.</p>



<p>Ripple&#8217;s executives have publicly responded to the SEC&#8217;s latest action, challenging the regulator&#8217;s approach and intentions. Alderoty criticized the SEC for attempting to punish and intimidate Ripple, suggesting the regulator&#8217;s statements are misleading.</p>



<p>Similarly, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse expressed disbelief over the unprecedented size of the fine and committed <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1772340438671966496" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">to exposing</a> the SEC&#8217;s actions in their forthcoming response planned for April.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The case has been notable for its complexities, including a July 2023 ruling by Judge Analisa Torres that identified XRP not as a security in relation to programmatic sales on digital asset exchanges. This partial victory for Ripple shifted the momentum in the case, leading to the SEC moving to dismiss charges against individual executives Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen with prejudice in October 2023.</p>



<p>Last month, Ripple&#8217;s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, criticized the SEC for being &#8220;extremely antagonistic,&#8221; labeling SEC Chairman Gary Gensler as a &#8220;political burden&#8221; and critiquing his regulatory approach to the cryptocurrency sector as ineffective. Ripple represents just one of numerous firms that have come under the SEC&#8217;s scrutiny lately. The regulatory body has taken legal action against several prominent U.S. cryptocurrency exchanges and financial institutions, accusing them of consistently selling digital tokens that were not registered as securities.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_SEC_over_crypto_regulation_1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_SEC_over_crypto_regulation_1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC alleges multi-billion dollar crypto fraud by Terraform Labs and Co-Founder</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/sec-alleges-crypto-fraud-by-terraform-labs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Emman Omwanda]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Scam News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terraform Labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501634</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The civil trial against Terraform Labs commenced in the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York, with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launching scathing allegations against the blockchain firm.&#160; In the opening statements, SEC attorney Devon Staren characterized Terra as a deceptive enterprise, likening it to a &#8220;house of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The civil trial against<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/sec-sues-terraform-labs-and-founder/"> Terraform Labs </a>commenced in the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York, with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launching scathing allegations against the blockchain firm.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In the opening statements, SEC attorney Devon Staren characterized Terra as a deceptive enterprise, likening it to a &#8220;house of cards&#8221; that ultimately collapsed, leaving investors with substantial losses.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">SEC unveils multi-billion dollar scheme</h2>



<p>In a bold move, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has brought to light a staggering fraud allegedly orchestrated by Terraform Labs and its co-founder, Do Kwon. The SEC&#8217;s lawsuit, filed with significant gravity, accuses the firm and Kwon of engaging in a multi-billion dollar crypto asset securities fraud. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/terraform-labs-civil-fraud-trial-set-begin-new-york-2024-03-25/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">According </a>to the SEC&#8217;s assertions, investors bore the brunt of this fraudulent scheme, suffering substantial financial losses due to Terra and Kwon&#8217;s misleading representations. </p>



<p>At the heart of the allegations lies Terra&#8217;s stablecoin, TerraUSD (UST), which is purported to have depegged from the U.S. dollar, triggering instability in the market and resulting in detrimental outcomes for investors. </p>



<p>The repercussions of Terra&#8217;s purported actions reverberated throughout the cryptocurrency market, with several companies grappling with downturns and, in some cases, facing bankruptcy. This exposé by the SEC marks a significant turning point in the ongoing battle against cryptocurrency fraud, underscoring the need for heightened vigilance and regulatory oversight.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Kwon&#8217;s Absence and Legal Challenges</h2>



<p>While the trial unfolded in New York, co-founder<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/do-kwon-to-be-released-montenegro-prison/"> Do Kwon</a> remained in Montenegro, where he had been arrested for using falsified travel documents. Although reportedly released pending extradition, Kwon&#8217;s presence at the trial remained uncertain. Despite legal challenges and delays, the SEC it persisted in pursuing justice against Terra and its key figures.</p>



<p>The civil trial, initially slated for January, was postponed to March to accommodate potential in-person defense participation by Kwon. Judge Jed Rakoff ruled in favor of the SEC regarding Terra&#8217;s dealings with unregistered securities. </p>



<p>However, the judgment favored Kwon and the platform concerning offering and selling security-based swaps. Terraform Labs&#8217; legal battle is among many expected cases in the crypto space.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Cryptocurrency titans await verdicts amid Terra&#8217;s trial.</h2>



<p>While the spotlight shines on Terra&#8217;s legal battle, the cryptocurrency community awaits the impending sentences of industry heavyweights. Former FTX CEO Sam <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/former-ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-fried/">Bankman</a>-Fried faces the prospect of sentencing, having been convicted on seven felony charges. </p>



<p>Similarly, former Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, having pleaded guilty to a felony charge, anticipates his legal fate. As these prominent figures navigate their legal challenges, their cases underscore the heightened scrutiny and accountability within the cryptocurrency industry.</p>



<p>The SEC&#8217;s civil trial against Terraform Labs marks a pivotal moment in the ongoing scrutiny of cryptocurrency firms. With allegations of fraud and market manipulation, the outcome of this trial could significantly impact regulatory measures within the industry. The cryptocurrency community watches closely as legal proceedings unfold, recognizing the broader implications for investor protection and market integrity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_bitcoin_crypto_fraud_0-1.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Default_bitcoin_crypto_fraud_0-1.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BITO Price Prediction 2024-2033: Is BITO a Good Buy?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bito-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Micah Abiodun]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=122914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BITO ETF Price Predictions 2024-2033 In the constantly shifting domain of cryptocurrency investments, the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) emerges as a notable innovation, providing investors with an avenue to gain exposure to Bitcoin via the futures market. Launched as the first ETF of its kind, BITO has attracted attention from various quarters of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">BITO ETF Price Predictions 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="#1" data-type="internal" data-id="#1">BITO ETF Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; up to <strong>$42.25</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#2" data-type="internal" data-id="#2">BITO ETF Price Prediction 2027 &#8211; up to <strong>$56.24</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#3" data-type="internal" data-id="#3">BITO ETF Price Prediction 2030 &#8211; up to <strong>$7</strong></a><a href="#Proshares-Bitcoin-Strategy-ETF-Price-Prediction-2029" data-type="internal"><strong>4.86</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#4" data-type="internal" data-id="#4">BITO ETF Price Prediction 2033 &#8211; up to <strong>$99.64</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<p>In the constantly shifting domain of <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bybit-lists-notcoin-for-pre-market-trading-heres-everything-you-need-to-know/">cryptocurrency investments</a>, the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) emerges as a notable innovation, providing investors with an avenue to gain exposure to Bitcoin via the futures market. Launched as the first ETF of its kind, BITO has attracted attention from various quarters of the investment community, ranging from seasoned cryptocurrency enthusiasts to traditional investors seeking to diversify their portfolios with digital assets. This post delves into the BITO price predictions, navigating through its performance, the underlying factors influencing its market movements, and the broader economic indicators at play.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How much is the BITO ETF worth?</h2>



<p>Today&#8217;s <strong>Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF&#8217;s price is $32.42</strong> with a 24-hour trading volume of $15,398,805. The asset&#8217;s price is <strong>up 10.67% </strong>in the last 24 hours, and its market capitalization is N/A. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF price analysis: BITO ETF Eyes Key Resistance at $35 Amid Market Optimism</h2>



<p>TL;DR</p>



<ul>
<li>Crucial support levels at $27.10 and $30.58</li>



<li>BITO ETF to face resistance at $35</li>



<li>Current market shift indicates potential buying opportunities</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Strategy ETF&#8217;s&nbsp;price analysis on a 1-day chart: BITO ETF Pullback Opens Strategic Entry Points?</h3>



<p>Based on the 1-day price chart, the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF experienced a period of consolidation followed by a significant bullish trend. The upward movement broke through previous resistance levels with high volatility, as indicated by the Bollinger Bands.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/SnAYbP__QQAXPh0_QRqUt_Jps-RW1yMSla5ZU-LHkrDD9kBpSfvQ8kwpm-fjsh1x25G92OdAjmyfQQjrUedGJV79IG2uEulg88HDaYCTidDg0TnODsm6YACCeiLteurnB4Brrs7GhTT_FGwgOnpWnT0" alt="Bito price prediction" /></figure>



<p>Currently, the ETF price is in a pullback phase, which could represent a buying opportunity if the price holds above the support levels and the RSI remains above the oversold region. Investors and traders would watch the $27.10 and $30.58 levels for potential rebounds. Conversely, a breach below these support levels might indicate a deeper retracement or a trend reversal. The resistance level around $35 is key for the continuation of the bullish trend. If the price can break and hold above this level, it could indicate further upside potential.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">BITO ETF price action on a 4-hour price chart: Bulls Eye Resistance Amidst Positive Momentum</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/bBX8YnlsXASLrXQilA3dYbv6VEE-JIIE8zAWnxawYUC3duecaiC8mi7B6X3iN_cy8Js9UM1_tLEY2QVhB_3WZgpE7MJX4L0bZYPaEVOIw3IgEaZEasUpsjPXix-hT85y-Lj5HTYXK3ADiw1JDNW6jyk" alt="Bito price prediction " /></figure>



<p>Analyzing the four-hour chart for the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO), we observe a current trading price of $32.33, with the ETF navigating between established support at approximately $30.41 and resistance around $33.95. The MACD indicator suggests bullish momentum as it crosses above the signal line, hinting at a possible upcoming test of the resistance level. Whether BITO can breach and hold above $33.95 may dictate the short-term trend, signaling further bullish potential. Conversely, a retreat from this resistance could see prices revisiting the support level.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is Bito ETF a Good Investment?</h2>



<p>The ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) offers investors exposure to Bitcoin futures rather than the cryptocurrency itself, positioning it as a distinctive investment that hinges on the futures market&#8217;s dynamics. Its performance is influenced by market sentiment, the regulatory landscape, and the volatility of Bitcoin prices. As an investment, BITO suits those looking to include Bitcoin in their portfolio without direct exposure to the cryptocurrency, providing a regulated and potentially less risky avenue. However, it&#8217;s essential to note that investing in BITO involves risk, especially due to the volatility of the underlying assets and the complexity of the futures market. For believers in cryptocurrency&#8217;s growth and willing to tolerate high volatility, BITO could be a viable option.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Predictions by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/0pKloU_Xk8StqYGjuK_KGDwETvnxGW347lAskyVMdvfR_KBAWciIsWxXtq55ZqbrdA4vRc3Ns61VPcwj02iIlPx7eMeQVpWU2MEBzT7AvhmizsQs4_1LrW6kIPVpaJLfD_IfsxoVzKorG0RJLjs84tU" alt="" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum Price ($)</td><td>Average Price ($)</td><td>Maximum Price ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>35.63</td><td>36.74</td><td>42.25</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>39.2</td><td>40.41</td><td>46.47</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>43.12</td><td>44.45</td><td>51.12</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>47.43</td><td>48.9</td><td>56.24</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>52.17</td><td>53.79</td><td>61.86</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>57.39</td><td>59.17</td><td>68.05</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>63.13</td><td>65.09</td><td>74.86</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>69.45</td><td>71.6</td><td>82.34</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>76.39</td><td>78.76</td><td>90.58</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>84.03</td><td>86.63</td><td>99.64</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="1">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>Our BITO ETF price prediction for 2024 suggests a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $42.25</strong>, a minimum price of $35.63, and an average value of $36.74.</p>



<p>Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2025</p>



<p>According to our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF price prediction for 2025, we anticipate a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $46.47</strong>, a minimum price of $39.20, and an average trading price of $40.41.</p>



<p>Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2026</p>



<p>Our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction for 2026 indicates that BITO ETF will trade at an average price of $44.45, with a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $51.12</strong>, and a minimum market price of $43.12.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="2">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>Per our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF price predictions for 2027, BITO ETF will reach a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $56.24</strong>, a minimum price of $47.43, and a projected average price of $48.90.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Based on our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF price predictions for 2028, investors can expect the BITO ETF to attain a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $61.86</strong>, an average forecast price of $53.79, and a minimum price of $52.17.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction for 2029 indicates that BITO ETF will trade at an average price of $59.17, with a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $68.05</strong>, and a minimum price of $57.39.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="3">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our BITO ETF price prediction for 2030, the stock could reach a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $74.86</strong>, a predicted average trading price of $65.09, and a minimum price of $63.13.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>We estimate a&nbsp;<strong>maximum market price of $82.34</strong>&nbsp;for the Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF in 2031, along with a minimum price of $69.45 and an average market value of $71.60.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>Our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction for 2032 indicates that the BITO ETF will continue rising, reaching a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $90.58</strong>, an average value of $78.76, and a minimum price of $76.39.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="4">Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>Our Proshares Bitcoin Strategy ETF Price Prediction for 2033 indicates that the BITO ETF will continue rising, reaching a&nbsp;<strong>maximum price of $99.64</strong>, an average value of $86.63, and a minimum price of $84.03.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Wallet Investor BITO ETF Price Prediction</h3>



<p>According to Wallet Investor&#8217;s projections, the BITO ETF is expected to experience significant growth over both one-year and five-year periods. Within one year, the asset is forecasted to reach $47.99. Looking further ahead, the five-year forecast anticipates a substantial price increase to $122.22.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Coindataflow BITO Price Prediction</h3>



<p>Based on CoinDataFlow&#8217;s&nbsp;technical indicators, the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) is anticipated to exhibit considerable growth through the decade, with its value potentially climbing to $113.58 by 2025, $225.24 by 2029, and $385.76 by 2033. The forecast suggests a progressive increase in the ETF&#8217;s price, indicating promising prospects for long-term investment.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Gov.Capital BITO ETF Price Prediction</h3>



<p>According to Gov.Capital’s forecast, the ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) is expected to significantly grow, with predictions suggesting an increase to $42.65 by 2025, and reaching up to $65 by 2027. This indicates a strong potential for BITO ETF as a good investment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BITO ETF Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Popularity</td><td>&#8211;</td><td>Market Cap</td><td>&#8211;</td></tr><tr><td>Price Change (24 hours)&nbsp;</td><td>+10.67%</td><td>Trading Volume (24 hours)</td><td>$15,398,805</td></tr><tr><td>Price Change (30 days)&nbsp;</td><td>33.08%</td><td>Net Assets</td><td>$2.642B</td></tr><tr><td>52-week low</td><td>$12.79</td><td>52-week high</td><td>33.79</td></tr><tr><td>Price from ATL</td><td>&#8211;</td><td>Price from ATH</td><td>&#8211;</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BITO Price History</h2>



<p>The ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO), which arrived on the market scene in 2021, launched at a promising&nbsp;opening price of about&nbsp;$40. This initial valuation mirrored the market&#8217;s confidence in innovative Bitcoin-linked financial products. However, the&nbsp;market trends for the&nbsp;subsequent year, 2022, saw this confidence tested as BITO&#8217;s value dropped to as low as $10.15 amidst a broader market recalibration, reflecting the intrinsic volatility of cryptocurrency assets.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/b7lsQQdpXx2IDL04qjYlBRd3JVh0Exip4sRZym9mkQJxARaqjAe_XJrwsHEqAN102qtpl_xZ-boNkPDQZTNKdi_fD1LFqk6EPjFnTfgHvaMY_8090Q9zXYnpZDdeQ1TDDOXY3bl95VpMQJ-F_nGODhU" alt="" /></figure>



<p>Moving into 2023, BITO began to recover, tracing a path of gradual growth. This upward trend indicated a renewed investor confidence, backed by a deeper understanding and acceptance of the cryptocurrency market&#8217;s dynamics. By early 2024, BITO had recaptured much of its lost ground, with the current price trading at $32.28.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>More on BITO ETF</strong></h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ProShares Bitcoin-linked ETF</strong></h3>



<p>ProShares Fund will invest in Bitcoin while exposing the BTC futures trading on Chicago Mercantile Exchange or CME. The futures market is a volatile field in which investors can indirectly invest using the ProShares ETF, which provides exposure to Bitcoin.</p>



<p>After the approval of this ETF, Bitcoin soared to higher levels, and as a result, investors are bullish. ProShare celebrated this new development in the industry through a ceremony at a press conference wherein the prominent members rang their bell of success.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BITO vs. GBTC</strong></h3>



<p>Both BITO (ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF) and GBTC (Grayscale Bitcoin Trust) are investment vehicles that offer exposure to Bitcoin, but they function quite differently. Understanding these differences is crucial for investors, such as yourself, who are interested in incorporating cryptocurrency into their portfolios.</p>



<p>BITO is the first Bitcoin-linked Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) in the United States. It aims to track the performance of Bitcoin futures contracts rather than holding the underlying asset directly. An ETF structure allows for greater liquidity and accessibility, as it can be bought and sold on traditional stock exchanges. However, the fund’s dependence on futures contracts exposes investors to contango risk, where future prices may be higher than the current spot price, potentially eroding gains.</p>



<p>GBTC, on the other hand, is a grantor trust that holds actual Bitcoin. It operates in the over-the-counter (OTC) markets and often trades at a premium or discount to the net asset value (NAV) of its holdings. GBTC provides a more direct exposure to Bitcoin price movements but comes with higher management fees and less trading flexibility due to its OTC nature.</p>



<p>In summary, BITO offers accessibility and liquidity advantages but carries derivative risks, while GBTC provides direct exposure to Bitcoin at the cost of higher fees and potentially less optimal trading conditions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>



<p>Investing in Bitcoin ETF relies on your investment plan, per our BITO ETF price projection. The ProShares ETF should be your first choice if you are new to cryptocurrency and want to start off with minimal risk. One of the most popular assets on the Fidelity platform that received more than 7,500 buy orders from users was the BITO ETF.</p>



<p>Among registered financial advisors, there are doubters about a Bitcoin ETF tied to futures (RIAs). Investors are also wary of the complexity of a futures-oriented product compared to spot cryptocurrency trading. Even while economic actors may have different opinions about the possibilities for the new ETF, most agree that it constitutes a big legislative triumph for the bitcoin community. It is anticipated that the exchange-traded fund would provide new opportunities in this sector.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you are convinced that you can handle the volatility of BTC and have firm faith in blockchain-based projects, you can go ahead with direct investment in crypto. Although the BITO ETF sounds good, some crypto backers who want to&nbsp;trade bitcoin&nbsp;directly argue that this will create an extra cost for end-users. Something which you could avoid by using cash markets. Investors need to be particularly aware of what they’re buying and how it’s likely to perform.</p>



<p>Whether ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO ETF) is a good investment or not is entirely up to the investors. As always, it is highly advised to do your own research and never invest more money than you can afford to lose, and seek investment advice. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BITO.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BITO.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX estate plans to sell $884M stake in AI firm Anthropic</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ftx-estate-sell-884m-stake-anthropic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501621</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The estate of the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has announced plans to sell about two-thirds of its 8% stake in the artificial intelligence startup Anthropic in deals totaling $884 million.  According to a report by the Wall Street Journal on Monday, ATIC Third International Investment Company LLC, linked to the United Arab Emirates&#8217; sovereign wealth [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The estate of the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has announced plans to sell about two-thirds of its 8% stake in the artificial intelligence startup Anthropic in deals totaling $884 million. </p>



<p>According to<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/ftx-to-sell-two-thirds-of-anthropic-stake-for-884-million-2cb3ccd2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> a report</a> by the Wall Street Journal on Monday, ATIC Third International Investment Company LLC, linked to the United Arab Emirates&#8217; sovereign wealth fund Mubadala, is set to purchase approximately $500 million of FTX&#8217;s shares in Anthropic. The transaction also involves buyers like Jane Street, several funds managed by Fidelity Management and Research, venture capital firm HOF Capital, and 20 other investors, as per an agreement dated March 22.</p>



<p>FTX&#8217;s investment in Anthropic, amounting to $500 million in 2021, came a year before the exchange declared bankruptcy amidst fraud allegations.  Anthropic is considered one of FTX estate’s most valuable assets. Officials from the company have indicated that FTX creditors are likely to be fully compensated.</p>



<p>For several months, the bankruptcy estate has been attempting to sell its stake in Anthropic in an effort to <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/prosecutors-seek-court-approval-to-sell-jets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reimburse clients</a> affected by the downfall of FTX in late 2022. Over the recent years, Anthropic has secured $7 billion from major technology firms, including Amazon and Alphabet. At the same time, its competitor, OpenAI, saw its market value soar to $80 billion, tripling in less than a year.</p>



<p>Under the leadership of the new CEO, John Ray III, FTX has been actively recovering funds, high-end real estate, and cryptocurrency, in addition to seeking out assets that were previously unaccounted for. The team has successfully retrieved over $7 billion to date. This figure doesn&#8217;t include expensive gifts and real estate worth $26 million given to the parents of Bankman-Fried or the $700 million transferred to K5 Global and its founder, Michael Kives. Kives had invested FTX&#8217;s funds in several companies, including SpaceX, some of which have significantly increased in value.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTX-estate-plans-to-sell-884M-stake-in-AI-firm-Anthropic.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/FTX-estate-plans-to-sell-884M-stake-in-AI-firm-Anthropic.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bybit lists Notcoin for pre-market trading—here&#8217;s everything you need to know</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bybit-lists-notcoin-for-pre-market-trading-heres-everything-you-need-to-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Damilola Lawrence]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[$NOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Notcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501610</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bybit, a crypto exchange based in the United Arab Emirates, announced the listing of the Telegram-based meme coin Notcoin ($NOT) on its Pre-Market Trading platform, as of 10:00 am UTC on Monday.  Pre-Market Trading refers to an over-the-counter (OTC) trading platform that is tailored for the trading of new tokens prior to their official listing. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bybit, a crypto exchange based in the United Arab Emirates, announced the listing of the Telegram-based meme coin Notcoin ($NOT) on its Pre-Market Trading platform, as of 10:00 am UTC on Monday. </p>



<p>Pre-Market Trading refers to an over-the-counter (OTC) trading platform that is tailored for the trading of new tokens prior to their official listing. This platform facilitates buyers and sellers in establishing quotes and executing trades, guaranteeing that transactions occur at the preferred price in advance.</p>



<p>The recent development offers Bybit&#8217;s users, which number over 26 million worldwide, the chance to engage with $NOT tokens before their official introduction to spot trading. The exchange <a href="https://announcements.bybit.com/en/article/bybit-pre-market-unveils-notcoin-not-trade-not-ahead-of-the-crowd-blt8d71afe5a63c5d11/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">has advised</a> participants to stay updated on the delivery schedule to facilitate a seamless trading experience, warning of the potential risks of not adhering to the set timeline.</p>



<p>Notcoin has emerged as a prominent player within the Telegram ecosystem, leveraging its &#8220;tap-to-earn&#8221; gaming model to attract a substantial user base interested in Web 3.0 and GamiFi protocols. The project reports over 32 million players with more than 5.4 million active daily users. It has also seen significant engagement on social platforms, amassing 2.4 million followers on the X social platform since its inception in December of the previous year.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How do you play?</h2>



<p>The ecosystem has issued a total of 67.9 trillion NOT coins, with about 16 trillion tokens being permanently burned as part of its efforts to manage the coin&#8217;s supply. Moreover, players engage with the Notcoin game by tapping on their screens to earn tokens, with opportunities to gain additional tokens through in-game boosts, task completion, and an ongoing referral program. This setup not only encourages active participation but also fosters community growth through new user onboarding from different Telegram channels and groups. </p>



<p><br>Earlier this month, Notcoin introduced a feature allowing elite players to convert significant amounts of in-game currency into NFT vouchers, which can be traded prior to the official release of their tokens. Players have the option to trade either 10 million or 100 million in-game coins for a voucher. </p>



<p>This voucher can then be used to claim NOT tokens once they become available on the blockchain. This strategy enables cryptocurrency enthusiasts to speculate on Notcoin&#8217;s future value before its highly anticipated token generation event. As of now, vouchers that equate to 10 million in-game coins are being sold for approximately $25 in Toncoin (TON) on the <a href="https://getgems.io/notcoin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">GetGems marketplace.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bybit-lists-Notcoin-for-pre-market-trading—heres-everything-you-need-to-know.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Bybit-lists-Notcoin-for-pre-market-trading—heres-everything-you-need-to-know.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin and Ethereum see gains as halving event draws close</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/bitcoin-ethereum-gains-halving-event-close/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Owotunse Adebayo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market has been a rollercoaster ride in recent days, especially for Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) prices. Bitcoin, after dropping to $63,000 over the weekend, made a comeback with a 3% gain at the start of the week, reaching $66,964. Despite a slight 2.5% dip over the past week, Bitcoin has surged impressively [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The cryptocurrency market has been a rollercoaster ride in recent days, especially for Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) prices. Bitcoin, after dropping to $63,000 over the weekend, made a comeback with a 3% gain at the start of the week, reaching $66,964. Despite a slight 2.5% dip over the past week, Bitcoin has <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">surged</a> impressively by 31% over the last month, largely fueled by bullish sentiments among traders.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin and Ethereum see a 3% gain to start the week</h2>



<p>A significant event looming on the horizon is the upcoming Bitcoin halving. This event, expected to occur around April 19 according to estimates from NiceHash, will see mining rewards cut from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC. However, the exact date of the halving remains fluid as it depends on reaching the 210,000-block milestone rather than following a fixed calendar schedule.</p>



<p>This uncertainty surrounding the halving has contributed to the recent volatility in Bitcoin’s price, with investors carefully gauging its potential impact on the market. Andy Bromberg, CEO of Beam, highlighted the likelihood of continued volatility in Bitcoin’s price leading up to the halving. Investors are grappling with the challenge of accurate pricing in the halving’s effects, leading to fluctuations in the cryptocurrency’s value over the past week.</p>



<p>In contrast, Ethereum has been on a positive trajectory, registering a 2.6% gain in the last 24 hours and reaching $3,452 at the time of writing. While Ethereum came close to breaching the $3,000 mark last week, it has since demonstrated resilience and steady growth, posting a notable 17% increase in price over the past month.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Ethereum’s positive momentum amid regulatory uncertainties</h2>



<p>Amidst Ethereum’s upward momentum, regulatory developments have cast a shadow of uncertainty. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently announced yet another delay in its decision regarding the Grayscale Ethereum Trust (ETHE) conversion into a spot Ethereum ETF. The SEC’s decision has been postponed until May 30, prolonging the waiting period for market participants eagerly anticipating Ethereum ETF approvals.</p>



<p>Market observers and industry experts are closely monitoring these regulatory updates, particularly regarding spot Ethereum ETFs. Matt Hougan, Bitwise’s Chief Information Officer, pointed out on Twitter that the timing of spot <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/sec-delays-decision-on-grayscale-ethereum/" data-type="post" data-id="500997">Ethereum ETF</a> launches could influence their asset accumulation. He suggested that launching in December might attract more assets compared to a launch in May, as traditional finance (TradFi) players may require additional time to acclimate to Bitcoin ETFs.</p>



<p>The cryptocurrency market is navigating through a period of heightened volatility, driven by factors such as the upcoming Bitcoin halving and regulatory uncertainties surrounding Ethereum ETF approvals. Investors and stakeholders are treading cautiously, analyzing market movements and regulatory announcements to make informed decisions amidst the evolving landscape of digital assets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7454.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7454.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Philippines announce plans to block access to Binance exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/philippines-plans-block-binance-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Owotunse Adebayo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=501611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The financial regulator of the Philippines has announced plans to block local user access to Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange. This decision stems from concerns regarding Binance’s unlicensed operations in the country. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) of the Philippines disclosed that it sought assistance from the National Telecommunication Commission (NTC) to implement [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The financial regulator of the Philippines has announced plans to block local user access to Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange. This decision stems from concerns regarding Binance’s unlicensed operations in the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philippines" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">country</a>. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) of the Philippines disclosed that it sought assistance from the National Telecommunication Commission (NTC) to implement the ban on accessing Binance’s website and online trading platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Philippines set to block access to Binance</h2>



<p>This move, outlined in a document dated March 25, reflects the SEC’s apprehensions about the potential risks posed to Filipino investors due to Binance’s activities without the necessary licenses. Emilio B. Aquino, Chairperson of the SEC, emphasized the necessity of this action in a letter to the NTC. Aquino stated that the SEC had identified Binance’s platform and determined that continued access to its services could endanger the security of funds belonging to investing Filipinos.</p>



<p>The SEC’s primary concern revolves around Binance’s offerings of investment products such as leveraged trading services and crypto savings accounts, which are being provided without complying with the requirements outlined in the Securities Regulation Code. The ban on accessing Binance’s services in the Philippines is scheduled to come into effect within three months.</p>



<p>This grace period is intended to allow investors using Binance’s platform to exit their positions and transition to alternative platforms or investment strategies. Additionally, the SEC has reached out to major tech companies including Google and Meta (formerly Facebook) requesting them to block advertisements related to Binance from appearing on their platforms for Filipino users. This regulatory action in the Philippines adds to the ongoing challenges faced by Binance on a global scale.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">CZ faces legal settlements as US orders payments</h2>



<p>In December 2023, a U.S. court issued a significant ruling against Binance, ordering the exchange to pay $2.7 billion in penalties. Former CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao was also directed to pay $150 million as part of the settlement with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). This legal dispute stemmed from allegations of Binance evading federal laws and operating an illegal derivatives exchange, leading to a protracted legal battle that concluded with substantial financial penalties.</p>



<p>Furthermore, in November 2023, CZ agreed to step down from his role as CEO of Binance as part of a broader settlement with U.S. regulatory authorities including the Department of Justice, the Treasury Department, and the CFTC. This agreement also involved CZ pleading guilty to various civil charges and one criminal charge related to Anti-Money Laundering (AML) laws. Despite these developments, CZ’s sentencing for the money laundering charges has been postponed until April 30, with CZ currently on bail amounting to $175 million.</p>



<p>The combination of regulatory actions from different jurisdictions, including the Philippines and the United States, underscores the growing scrutiny and challenges faced by Binance. These developments highlight the importance of <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-regulation-debate-spurs-union-attention/" data-type="post" data-id="501320">regulatory</a> compliance and transparency in the cryptocurrency industry, as authorities worldwide seek to protect investors and maintain financial stability in the rapidly evolving digital asset landscape.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7455.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7455.jpeg"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
